<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:47:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-51075 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/user-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51075</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/user-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the searchdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51076 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/booking-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51076</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/booking-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System 1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchdata" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47640 | WordPress  WP ERP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in weDevs WP ERP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP ERP: from n/a through 1.13.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49632 | WordPress CWD 3D Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coral Web Design CWD 3D Image Gallery allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CWD 3D Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49634 | WordPress BP Member Type Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.01 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rimon Habib BP Member Type Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BP Member Type Manager: from n/a through 1.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49635 | WordPress Banner Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49635</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Manzurul Haque Banner Slider allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Banner Slider: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49636 | WordPress Agile Video Player Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prashant Mavinkurve Agile Video Player Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Agile Video Player Lite: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51180 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/index.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0, which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51180</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/index.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchifsccode" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51181 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/admin/profile.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51181</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/admin/profile.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via " searchifsccode" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6673 | CSRF Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6673</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the `install_comfyui` endpoint of the `lollms_comfyui.py` file in the parisneo/lollms-webui repository, versions v9.9 to the latest. The endpoint uses the GET method without requiring a client ID, allowing an attacker to trick a victim into installing ComfyUI. If the victim's device does not have sufficient capacity, this can result in a crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7042 | Prompt Injection in langchain-ai/langchainjs Leading to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7042</link><description>A vulnerability in the GraphCypherQAChain class of langchain-ai/langchainjs versions 0.2.5 and all versions with this class allows for prompt injection, leading to SQL injection. This vulnerability permits unauthorized data manipulation, data exfiltration, denial of service (DoS) by deleting all data, breaches in multi-tenant security environments, and data integrity issues. Attackers can create, update, or delete nodes and relationships without proper authorization, extract sensitive data, disrupt services, access data across different tenants, and compromise the integrity of the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7472 | Email Injection Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7472</link><description>lunary-ai/lunary v1.2.26 contains an email injection vulnerability in the Send email verification API (/v1/users/send-verification) and Sign up API (/auth/signup). An unauthenticated attacker can inject data into outgoing emails by bypassing the extractFirstName function using a different whitespace character (e.g., \xa0). This vulnerability can be exploited to conduct phishing attacks, damage the application's brand, cause legal and compliance issues, and result in financial impact due to unauthorized email usage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7774 | Path Traversal in langchain-ai/langchainjs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7774</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the `getFullPath` method of langchain-ai/langchainjs version 0.2.5. This vulnerability allows attackers to save files anywhere in the filesystem, overwrite existing text files, read `.txt` files, and delete files. The vulnerability is exploited through the `setFileContent`, `getParsedFile`, and `mdelete` methods, which do not properly sanitize user input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7783 | Improper Storage of Sensitive Information in Bearer Token in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7783</link><description>mintplex-labs/anything-llm version latest contains a vulnerability where sensitive information, specifically a password, is improperly stored within a JWT (JSON Web Token) used as a bearer token in single user mode. When decoded, the JWT reveals the password in plaintext. This improper storage of sensitive information poses significant security risks, as an attacker who gains access to the JWT can easily decode it and retrieve the password. The issue is fixed in version 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8309 | SQL Injection in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8309</link><description>A vulnerability in the GraphCypherQAChain class of langchain-ai/langchain version 0.2.5 allows for SQL injection through prompt injection. This vulnerability can lead to unauthorized data manipulation, data exfiltration, denial of service (DoS) by deleting all data, breaches in multi-tenant security environments, and data integrity issues. Attackers can create, update, or delete nodes and relationships without proper authorization, extract sensitive data, disrupt services, access data across different tenants, and compromise the integrity of the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41153 | Command injection vulnerability in the Edge Computing UI for the
TRO600 series radios that allows for the execution of arbitrary system comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41153</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in the Edge Computing UI for the
TRO600 series radios that allows for the execution of arbitrary system commands. If exploited, an attacker with write access to the
web UI can execute commands on the device with root privileges,
far more extensive than what the write privilege intends.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41156 | Profile files from TRO600 series radios are extracted in plain-text
and encrypted file formats. Profile files provide potential attackers
va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41156</link><description>Profile files from TRO600 series radios are extracted in plain-text
and encrypted file formats. Profile files provide potential attackers
valuable configuration information about the Tropos network. Profiles
can only be exported by authenticated users with write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49637 | WordPress Bet WC 2018 Russia plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49637</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Foxskav Bet WC 2018 Russia allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Bet WC 2018 Russia: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49638 | WordPress Risk Warning Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ali Azlan Risk Warning Bar allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Risk Warning Bar: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49639 | WordPress Monitor.chat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49639</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Edward Stoever Monitor.Chat allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Monitor.Chat: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49640 | WordPress ACL Floating Cart for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AmaderCode Lab ACL Floating Cart for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ACL Floating Cart for WooCommerce: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5823 | File Overwrite Vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5823</link><description>A file overwrite vulnerability exists in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt versions &lt;= 20240410. This vulnerability allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access to overwrite critical configuration files within the system. Exploiting this vulnerability can lead to unauthorized changes in system behavior or security settings. Additionally, tampering with these configuration files can result in a denial of service (DoS) condition, disrupting normal system operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5982 | Path Traversal in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5982</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the latest version of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt. The vulnerability arises from unsanitized input handling in multiple features, including user upload, directory creation, and template loading. Specifically, the load_chat_history function in modules/models/base_model.py allows arbitrary file uploads, potentially leading to remote code execution (RCE). The get_history_names function in utils.py permits arbitrary directory creation. Additionally, the load_template function in utils.py can be exploited to leak the first column of CSV files. These issues stem from improper sanitization of user inputs concatenated with directory paths using os.path.join.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6581 | Remote Code Execution due to Stored XSS in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6581</link><description>A vulnerability in the discussion image upload function of the Lollms application, version v9.9, allows for the uploading of SVG files. Due to incomplete filtering in the sanitize_svg function, this can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities, which in turn pose a risk of remote code execution. The sanitize_svg function only removes script elements and 'on*' event attributes, but does not account for other potential vectors for XSS within SVG files. This vulnerability can be exploited when authorized users access a malicious URL containing the crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6674 | Data Leak through CORS Misconfiguration in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6674</link><description>A CORS misconfiguration in parisneo/lollms-webui prior to version 10 allows attackers to steal sensitive information such as logs, browser sessions, and settings containing private API keys from other services. This vulnerability can also enable attackers to perform actions on behalf of a user, such as deleting a project or sending a message. The issue impacts the confidentiality and integrity of the information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6868 | Arbitrary File Write in mudler/LocalAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6868</link><description>mudler/LocalAI version 2.17.1 allows for arbitrary file write due to improper handling of automatic archive extraction. When model configurations specify additional files as archives (e.g., .tar), these archives are automatically extracted after downloading. This behavior can be exploited to perform a 'tarslip' attack, allowing files to be written to arbitrary locations on the server, bypassing checks that normally restrict files to the models directory. This vulnerability can lead to remote code execution (RCE) by overwriting backend assets used by the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7010 | Timing Attack in mudler/localai</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7010</link><description>mudler/localai version 2.17.1 is vulnerable to a Timing Attack. This type of side-channel attack allows an attacker to compromise the cryptosystem by analyzing the time taken to execute cryptographic algorithms. Specifically, in the context of password handling, an attacker can determine valid login credentials based on the server's response time, potentially leading to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7473 | IDOR Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7473</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability exists in the 'Evaluations' function of the 'umgws datasets' section in lunary-ai/lunary versions 1.3.2. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to update other users' prompts by manipulating the 'id' parameter in the request. The issue is fixed in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7474 | IDOR in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7474</link><description>In version 1.3.2 of lunary-ai/lunary, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists. A user can view or delete external users by manipulating the 'id' parameter in the request URL. The application does not perform adequate checks on the 'id' parameter, allowing unauthorized access to external user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7475 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7475</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary version 1.3.2 allows an attacker to update the SAML configuration without authorization. This vulnerability can lead to manipulation of authentication processes, fraudulent login requests, and theft of user information. Appropriate access controls should be implemented to ensure that the SAML configuration can only be updated by authorized users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7807 | Denial of Service (DOS) in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7807</link><description>A vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240628 allows for a Denial of Service (DOS) attack. When uploading a file, if an attacker appends a large number of characters to the end of a multipart boundary, the system will continuously process each character, rendering ChuanhuChatGPT inaccessible. This uncontrolled resource consumption can lead to prolonged unavailability of the service, disrupting operations and causing potential data inaccessibility and loss of productivity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7962 | Arbitrary File Read via Insufficient Validation in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7962</link><description>An arbitrary file read vulnerability exists in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240628 due to insufficient validation when loading prompt template files. An attacker can read any file that matches specific criteria using an absolute path. The file must not have a .json extension and, except for the first line, every other line must contain commas. This vulnerability allows reading parts of format-compliant files, including code and log files, which may contain highly sensitive information such as account credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8143 | Unauthorized Access to User Chat History in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8143</link><description>In the latest version (20240628) of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt, an issue exists in the /file endpoint that allows authenticated users to access the chat history of other users. When a user logs in, a directory is created in the history folder with the user's name. By manipulating the /file endpoint, an authenticated user can enumerate and access files in other users' directories, leading to unauthorized access to private chat histories. This vulnerability can be exploited to read any user's private chat history.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10458 | A permission leak could have occurred from a trusted site to an untrusted site via `embed` or `object` elements. This vulnerability affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10458</link><description>A permission leak could have occurred from a trusted site to an untrusted site via `embed` or `object` elements. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.17, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10459 | An attacker could have caused a use-after-free when accessibility was enabled, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10459</link><description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free when accessibility was enabled, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.17, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10460 | The origin of an external protocol handler prompt could have been obscured using a data: URL within an `iframe`. This vulnerability affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10460</link><description>The origin of an external protocol handler prompt could have been obscured using a data: URL within an `iframe`. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10461 | In multipart/x-mixed-replace responses, `Content-Disposition: attachment` in the response header was not respected and did not force a downl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10461</link><description>In multipart/x-mixed-replace responses, `Content-Disposition: attachment` in the response header was not respected and did not force a download, which could allow XSS attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10462 | Truncation of a long URL could have allowed origin spoofing in a permission prompt. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10462</link><description>Truncation of a long URL could have allowed origin spoofing in a permission prompt. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10463 | Video frames could have been leaked between origins in some situations. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10463</link><description>Video frames could have been leaked between origins in some situations. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.17, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10464 | Repeated writes to history interface attributes could have been used to cause a Denial of Service condition in the browser. This was address...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10464</link><description>Repeated writes to history interface attributes could have been used to cause a Denial of Service condition in the browser. This was addressed by introducing rate-limiting to this API. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10465 | A clipboard "paste" button could persist across tabs which allowed a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10465</link><description>A clipboard "paste" button could persist across tabs which allowed a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10466 | By sending a specially crafted push message, a remote server could have hung the parent process, causing the browser to become unresponsive....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10466</link><description>By sending a specially crafted push message, a remote server could have hung the parent process, causing the browser to become unresponsive. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10467 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 131, Firefox ESR 128.3, and Thunderbird 128.3. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10467</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 131, Firefox ESR 128.3, and Thunderbird 128.3. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10468 | Potential race conditions in IndexedDB could have caused memory corruption, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10468</link><description>Potential race conditions in IndexedDB could have caused memory corruption, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132 and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10474 | Focus was incorrectly allowing internal links to utilize the app scheme used for deeplinking, which could result in links potentially circum...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10474</link><description>Focus was incorrectly allowing internal links to utilize the app scheme used for deeplinking, which could result in links potentially circumventing some URL safety checks This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49641 | WordPress Tida URL Screenshot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tidaweb Tida URL Screenshot allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tida URL Screenshot: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49643 | WordPress Whitelist plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Abdullah Irfan Whitelist allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Whitelist: from n/a through 3.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49645 | WordPress Affiliate Platform plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ilias Gomatos Affiliate Platform allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Affiliate Platform: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20195 | LUNAD3v AreaLoad request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LUNAD3v AreaLoad up to 1a1103182ed63a06dde63d1712f3262eda19c3ec. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file request.php. The manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 264813c546dba03989ac0fc365f2022bf65e3be2. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49646 | WordPress Code Generate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ioannup Code Generate allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Code Generate: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49647 | WordPress Simple Custom Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Carl Alberto Simple Custom Admin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Custom Admin: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49648 | WordPress SVG Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rafasashi SVG Captcha allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SVG Captcha: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49650 | WordPress BuddyPress Greeting Message plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49650</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in xarbo BuddyPress Greeting Message allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BuddyPress Greeting Message: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49651 | WordPress WooCommerce Maintenance Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Royal WooCommerce Maintenance Mode allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Maintenance Mode: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49654 | WordPress Extra Privacy for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49654</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marian Heddesheimer Extra Privacy for Elementor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Extra Privacy for Elementor: from n/a through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49656 | WordPress DocumentPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Abdullah Irfan DocumentPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DocumentPress: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49659 | WordPress Coub plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49659</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rami Yushuvaev Coub allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Coub: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49660 | WordPress Campus Explorer Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49660</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Campus Explorer Campus Explorer Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Campus Explorer Widget: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49661 | WordPress leenk.me plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49661</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lew Ayotte leenk.Me allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects leenk.Me: from n/a through 2.16.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49662 | WordPress Simple Load More plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webgensis Simple Load More allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Load More: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49663 | WordPress uCAT – Next Story plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elena Zhyvohliad uCAT – Next Story allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects uCAT – Next Story: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10181 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via newsletters_video Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10181</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's newsletters_video shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49664 | WordPress chatplusjp plugin &amp;lt;= 1.02 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects chatplusjp: from n/a through 1.02.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49665 | WordPress  Web Bricks Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Web Bricks Web Bricks Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Web Bricks Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49667 | WordPress Local Business Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NervyThemes Local Business Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Local Business Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10184 | SW Kick Integration - Blocks and Shortcodes for Embedding Kick Streams &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sw-kick-embed Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10184</link><description>The StreamWeasels Kick Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sw-kick-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10185 | StreamWeasels YouTube Integration &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sw-youtube-embed Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10185</link><description>The StreamWeasels YouTube Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sw-youtube-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10233 | SMSAlert - WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sa_subscribe Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10233</link><description>The SMS Alert Order Notifications – WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sa_subscribe shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10266 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.60 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Box Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10266</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Video Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.60 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10360 | Move Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10360</link><description>The Move Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5 via the render function in includes/widgets/accordion/widget.php, includes/widgets/remote-template/widget.php, and other widget.php files. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49670 | WordPress Client Power Tools Portal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49670</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sam Glover Client Power Tools Portal allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Client Power Tools Portal: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49672 | WordPress Google Docs RSVP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49672</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Gifford Cheung, Brian Watanabe, Chongsun Ahn Google Docs RSVP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Google Docs RSVP: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49673 | WordPress LaTeX2HTML plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Van Abel LaTeX2HTML allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LaTeX2HTML: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49678 | WordPress js paper theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jinwen js allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects js paper: from n/a through 2.5.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49679 | WordPress WPKoi Templates for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPKoi WPKoi Templates for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPKoi Templates for Elementor: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49692 | WordPress AffiliateX plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49692</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AffiliateX allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AffiliateX: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50407 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50407</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50409 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50409</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50410 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50410</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50550 | WordPress LiteSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50550</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in LiteSpeed Technologies LiteSpeed Cache allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects LiteSpeed Cache: from n/a through 6.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10227 | affiliate-toolkit &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via atkp_product Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10227</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's atkp_product shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10436 | WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10436</link><description>The WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1 via the get_condition_value function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10437 | WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Message Activation/Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10437</link><description>The WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Smar Message activation/deactivation due to a missing capability check on the ajax_enable function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate or deactivate smart messages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9376 | Kata Plus – Addons for Elementor – Widgets, Extensions and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9376</link><description>The Kata Plus – Addons for Elementor – Widgets, Extensions and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22066 | There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in ZTE ZXR10 ZSR V2 intelligent multi service router . An authenticated attacker could use the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22066</link><description>There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in ZTE ZXR10 ZSR V2 intelligent multi service router . An authenticated attacker could use the vulnerability to obtain sensitive information about the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45477 | Apache NiFi: Improper Neutralization of Input in Parameter Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45477</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.27.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field for Parameters in a Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.28.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49642 | WordPress Todo Custom Field plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rafasashi Todo Custom Field allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Todo Custom Field: from n/a through 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50411 | WordPress WP Abstracts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50411</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kevon Adonis WP Abstracts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Abstracts: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50412 | WordPress Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50412</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jules Colle Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 2.4.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50413 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.27.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50413</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in codection Import and export users and customers allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.27.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50414 | WordPress Button contact VR plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50414</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VirusTran Button contact VR allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Button contact VR: from n/a through 4.7.9.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50415 | WordPress Ads.txt &amp;amp; App-ads.txt Manager for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50415</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pagup Ads.Txt &amp; App-ads.Txt Manager for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ads.Txt &amp; App-ads.Txt Manager for WordPress: from n/a through 1.1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50418 | WordPress Time Slot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50418</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Time Slot Booking Time Slot allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Time Slot: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50426 | WordPress Survey Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50426</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Survey Maker team Survey Maker allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Survey Maker: from n/a through 5.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50475 | WordPress Signup Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50475</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Scott Gamon Signup Page allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Signup Page: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50476 | WordPress GRÜN spendino Spendenformular plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50476</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GRÜN Software Group GmbH GRÜN spendino Spendenformular allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GRÜN spendino Spendenformular: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50481 | WordPress Bstone Demo Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50481</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Stack Themes Bstone Demo Importer allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Bstone Demo Importer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10048 | Post Status Notifier Lite and Premium &amp;lt;= 1.11.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10048</link><description>The Post Status Notifier Lite and Premium plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50420 | WordPress aDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50420</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in adirectory aDirectory allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects aDirectory: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50427 | WordPress SurveyJS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.136 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50427</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Devsoft Baltic OÜ SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder.This issue affects SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder: from n/a through 1.9.136.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50473 | WordPress Ajar in5 Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50473</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Ajar Productions Ajar in5 Embed allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Ajar in5 Embed: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50485 | WordPress Exam Matrix plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50485</link><description>: Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Udit Rawat Exam Matrix allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Exam Matrix: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50490 | WordPress PegaPoll plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50490</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Szabolcs Szecsenyi PegaPoll allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects PegaPoll: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9438 | SEUR Oficial &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9438</link><description>The SEUR Oficial plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'change_service' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46872 | Client-Side Path Traversal Leading to CSRF in Playbooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46872</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.10.x &lt;= 9.10.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.1, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to sanitize user inputs in the frontend that are used for redirection which allows for a one-click client-side path traversal that is leading to CSRF in Playbooks</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47401 | DoS via Amplified GraphQL Response in Playbooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47401</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.10.x &lt;= 9.10.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.1 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to prevent detailed error messages from being displayed in Playbooks which allows an attacker to generate a large response and cause an amplified GraphQL response which in turn could cause the application to crash by sending a specially crafted request to Playbooks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10241 | Private channel names leaked with Ctrl+K when ElasticSearch is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10241</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to properly filter the channel data when ElasticSearch is enabled which allows a user to get private channel names by using cmd+K/ctrl+K.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50052 | Arbitrary post deletion via Playbooks /ignore-thread endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50052</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.10.x &lt;= 9.10.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.1, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to check that the origin of the message in an integration action matches with the original post metadata which allows an authenticated user to delete an arbitrary post.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50480 | WordPress Marketing Automation by AZEXO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.27.80 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50480</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in azexo Marketing Automation by AZEXO allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Marketing Automation by AZEXO: from n/a through 1.27.80.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50482 | WordPress Woocommerce Product Design plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50482</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Chetan Khandla Woocommerce Product Design allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Woocommerce Product Design: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50484 | WordPress Multi Purpose Mail Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50484</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in mahlamusa Multi Purpose Mail Form allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Multi Purpose Mail Form: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50493 | WordPress Automatic Translation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50493</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in masterhomepage Automatic Translation allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Automatic Translation: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50494 | WordPress Sudan Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50494</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Amin Omer Sudan Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Sudan Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10312 | Exclusive Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10312</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 via the render function in elements/tabs/tabs.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 07:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10000 | Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.13.3 - Authenticated (Student+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Ask a Question Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10000</link><description>The Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the question's content parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with student-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 05:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10008 | Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.13.3 - Authenticated (Student+) Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10008</link><description>The Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user profile modification due to missing authorization checks on the /wp-json/masteriyo/v1/users/$id REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with student-level access and above, to modify the roles of arbitrary users. As a result, attackers can escalate their privileges to the Administrator and demote existing administrators to students.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 05:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22065 | ZTE MF258 Pro product has a OS Command injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22065</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in ZTE MF258 Pro product. Due to insufficient validation of Ping Diagnosis interface parameter, an authenticated attacker could use the vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10479 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Theme Management Module admin#themes cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10479</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms up to 2.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin#themes of the component Theme Management Module. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45656 | IBM Flexible Service Processor hard coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45656</link><description>IBM Flexible Service Processor (FSP) FW860.00 through FW860.B3, FW950.00 through FW950.C0, FW1030.00 through FW1030.61, FW1050.00 through FW1050.21, and FW1060.00 through FW1060.10 has static credentials which may allow network users to gain service privileges to the FSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50068 | mm/damon/tests/sysfs-kunit.h: fix memory leak in damon_sysfs_test_add_targets()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50068</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/damon/tests/sysfs-kunit.h: fix memory leak in damon_sysfs_test_add_targets()

The sysfs_target-&gt;regions allocated in damon_sysfs_regions_alloc() is not
freed in damon_sysfs_test_add_targets(), which cause the following memory
leak, free it to fix it.

	unreferenced object 0xffffff80c2a8db80 (size 96):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 187, jiffies 4294894363
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
	    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
	  backtrace (crc 0):
	    [&lt;0000000001e3714d&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;000000008e6835c1&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000001286d9f8&gt;] damon_sysfs_test_add_targets+0x1cc/0x738
	    [&lt;0000000032ef8f77&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;00000000f3edea23&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000adf936cf&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;0000000041bb1628&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50069 | pinctrl: apple: check devm_kasprintf() returned value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50069</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: apple: check devm_kasprintf() returned value

devm_kasprintf() can return a NULL pointer on failure but this returned
value is not checked. Fix this lack and check the returned value.

Found by code review.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50070 | pinctrl: stm32: check devm_kasprintf() returned value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50070</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: stm32: check devm_kasprintf() returned value

devm_kasprintf() can return a NULL pointer on failure but this returned
value is not checked. Fix this lack and check the returned value.

Found by code review.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50071 | pinctrl: nuvoton: fix a double free in ma35_pinctrl_dt_node_to_map_func()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50071</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: nuvoton: fix a double free in ma35_pinctrl_dt_node_to_map_func()

'new_map' is allocated using devm_* which takes care of freeing the
allocated data on device removal, call to

	.dt_free_map = pinconf_generic_dt_free_map

double frees the map as pinconf_generic_dt_free_map() calls
pinctrl_utils_free_map().

Fix this by using kcalloc() instead of auto-managed devm_kcalloc().</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50072 | x86/bugs: Use code segment selector for VERW operand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50072</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/bugs: Use code segment selector for VERW operand

Robert Gill reported below #GP in 32-bit mode when dosemu software was
executing vm86() system call:

  general protection fault: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
  CPU: 4 PID: 4610 Comm: dosemu.bin Not tainted 6.6.21-gentoo-x86 #1
  Hardware name: Dell Inc. PowerEdge 1950/0H723K, BIOS 2.7.0 10/30/2010
  EIP: restore_all_switch_stack+0xbe/0xcf
  EAX: 00000000 EBX: 00000000 ECX: 00000000 EDX: 00000000
  ESI: 00000000 EDI: 00000000 EBP: 00000000 ESP: ff8affdc
  DS: 0000 ES: 0000 FS: 0000 GS: 0033 SS: 0068 EFLAGS: 00010046
  CR0: 80050033 CR2: 00c2101c CR3: 04b6d000 CR4: 000406d0
  Call Trace:
   show_regs+0x70/0x78
   die_addr+0x29/0x70
   exc_general_protection+0x13c/0x348
   exc_bounds+0x98/0x98
   handle_exception+0x14d/0x14d
   exc_bounds+0x98/0x98
   restore_all_switch_stack+0xbe/0xcf
   exc_bounds+0x98/0x98
   restore_all_switch_stack+0xbe/0xcf

This only happens in 32-bit mode when VERW based mitigations like MDS/RFDS
are enabled. This is because segment registers with an arbitrary user value
can result in #GP when executing VERW. Intel SDM vol. 2C documents the
following behavior for VERW instruction:

  #GP(0) - If a memory operand effective address is outside the CS, DS, ES,
	   FS, or GS segment limit.

CLEAR_CPU_BUFFERS macro executes VERW instruction before returning to user
space. Use %cs selector to reference VERW operand. This ensures VERW will
not #GP for an arbitrary user %ds.

[ mingo: Fixed the SOB chain. ]</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50073 | tty: n_gsm: Fix use-after-free in gsm_cleanup_mux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50073</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tty: n_gsm: Fix use-after-free in gsm_cleanup_mux

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in gsm_cleanup_mux+0x77b/0x7b0
drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3160 [n_gsm]
Read of size 8 at addr ffff88815fe99c00 by task poc/3379
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 3379 Comm: poc Not tainted 6.11.0+ #56
Hardware name: VMware, Inc. VMware Virtual Platform/440BX
Desktop Reference Platform, BIOS 6.00 11/12/2020
Call Trace:
 
 gsm_cleanup_mux+0x77b/0x7b0 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3160 [n_gsm]
 __pfx_gsm_cleanup_mux+0x10/0x10 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3124 [n_gsm]
 __pfx_sched_clock_cpu+0x10/0x10 kernel/sched/clock.c:389
 update_load_avg+0x1c1/0x27b0 kernel/sched/fair.c:4500
 __pfx_min_vruntime_cb_rotate+0x10/0x10 kernel/sched/fair.c:846
 __rb_insert_augmented+0x492/0xbf0 lib/rbtree.c:161
 gsmld_ioctl+0x395/0x1450 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3408 [n_gsm]
 _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x92/0xf0 arch/x86/include/asm/atomic.h:107
 __pfx_gsmld_ioctl+0x10/0x10 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3822 [n_gsm]
 ktime_get+0x5e/0x140 kernel/time/timekeeping.c:195
 ldsem_down_read+0x94/0x4e0 arch/x86/include/asm/atomic64_64.h:79
 __pfx_ldsem_down_read+0x10/0x10 drivers/tty/tty_ldsem.c:338
 __pfx_do_vfs_ioctl+0x10/0x10 fs/ioctl.c:805
 tty_ioctl+0x643/0x1100 drivers/tty/tty_io.c:2818

Allocated by task 65:
 gsm_data_alloc.constprop.0+0x27/0x190 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:926 [n_gsm]
 gsm_send+0x2c/0x580 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:819 [n_gsm]
 gsm1_receive+0x547/0xad0 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3038 [n_gsm]
 gsmld_receive_buf+0x176/0x280 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3609 [n_gsm]
 tty_ldisc_receive_buf+0x101/0x1e0 drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:391
 tty_port_default_receive_buf+0x61/0xa0 drivers/tty/tty_port.c:39
 flush_to_ldisc+0x1b0/0x750 drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:445
 process_scheduled_works+0x2b0/0x10d0 kernel/workqueue.c:3229
 worker_thread+0x3dc/0x950 kernel/workqueue.c:3391
 kthread+0x2a3/0x370 kernel/kthread.c:389
 ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:257

Freed by task 3367:
 kfree+0x126/0x420 mm/slub.c:4580
 gsm_cleanup_mux+0x36c/0x7b0 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3160 [n_gsm]
 gsmld_ioctl+0x395/0x1450 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3408 [n_gsm]
 tty_ioctl+0x643/0x1100 drivers/tty/tty_io.c:2818

[Analysis]
gsm_msg on the tx_ctrl_list or tx_data_list of gsm_mux
can be freed by multi threads through ioctl,which leads
to the occurrence of uaf. Protect it by gsm tx lock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50074 | parport: Proper fix for array out-of-bounds access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50074</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

parport: Proper fix for array out-of-bounds access

The recent fix for array out-of-bounds accesses replaced sprintf()
calls blindly with snprintf().  However, since snprintf() returns the
would-be-printed size, not the actually output size, the length
calculation can still go over the given limit.

Use scnprintf() instead of snprintf(), which returns the actually
output letters, for addressing the potential out-of-bounds access
properly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50075 | xhci: tegra: fix checked USB2 port number</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50075</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xhci: tegra: fix checked USB2 port number

If USB virtualizatoin is enabled, USB2 ports are shared between all
Virtual Functions. The USB2 port number owned by an USB2 root hub in
a Virtual Function may be less than total USB2 phy number supported
by the Tegra XUSB controller.

Using total USB2 phy number as port number to check all PORTSC values
would cause invalid memory access.

[  116.923438] Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address 006c622f7665642f
...
[  117.213640] Call trace:
[  117.216783]  tegra_xusb_enter_elpg+0x23c/0x658
[  117.222021]  tegra_xusb_runtime_suspend+0x40/0x68
[  117.227260]  pm_generic_runtime_suspend+0x30/0x50
[  117.232847]  __rpm_callback+0x84/0x3c0
[  117.237038]  rpm_suspend+0x2dc/0x740
[  117.241229] pm_runtime_work+0xa0/0xb8
[  117.245769]  process_scheduled_works+0x24c/0x478
[  117.251007]  worker_thread+0x23c/0x328
[  117.255547]  kthread+0x104/0x1b0
[  117.259389]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[  117.263582] Code: 54000222 f9461ae8 f8747908 b4ffff48 (f9400100)</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50076 | vt: prevent kernel-infoleak in con_font_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50076</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vt: prevent kernel-infoleak in con_font_get()

font.data may not initialize all memory spaces depending on the implementation
of vc-&gt;vc_sw-&gt;con_font_get. This may cause info-leak, so to prevent this, it
is safest to modify it to initialize the allocated memory space to 0, and it
generally does not affect the overall performance of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50077 | Bluetooth: ISO: Fix multiple init when debugfs is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50077</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: ISO: Fix multiple init when debugfs is disabled

If bt_debugfs is not created successfully, which happens if either
CONFIG_DEBUG_FS or CONFIG_DEBUG_FS_ALLOW_ALL is unset, then iso_init()
returns early and does not set iso_inited to true. This means that a
subsequent call to iso_init() will result in duplicate calls to
proto_register(), bt_sock_register(), etc.

With CONFIG_LIST_HARDENED and CONFIG_BUG_ON_DATA_CORRUPTION enabled, the
duplicate call to proto_register() triggers this BUG():

  list_add double add: new=ffffffffc0b280d0, prev=ffffffffbab56250,
    next=ffffffffc0b280d0.
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:35!
  Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 2 PID: 887 Comm: bluetoothd Not tainted 6.10.11-1-ao-desktop #1
  RIP: 0010:__list_add_valid_or_report+0x9a/0xa0
  ...
    __list_add_valid_or_report+0x9a/0xa0
    proto_register+0x2b5/0x340
    iso_init+0x23/0x150 [bluetooth]
    set_iso_socket_func+0x68/0x1b0 [bluetooth]
    kmem_cache_free+0x308/0x330
    hci_sock_sendmsg+0x990/0x9e0 [bluetooth]
    __sock_sendmsg+0x7b/0x80
    sock_write_iter+0x9a/0x110
    do_iter_readv_writev+0x11d/0x220
    vfs_writev+0x180/0x3e0
    do_writev+0xca/0x100
  ...

This change removes the early return. The check for iso_debugfs being
NULL was unnecessary, it is always NULL when iso_inited is false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50078 | Bluetooth: Call iso_exit() on module unload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50078</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Call iso_exit() on module unload

If iso_init() has been called, iso_exit() must be called on module
unload. Without that, the struct proto that iso_init() registered with
proto_register() becomes invalid, which could cause unpredictable
problems later. In my case, with CONFIG_LIST_HARDENED and
CONFIG_BUG_ON_DATA_CORRUPTION enabled, loading the module again usually
triggers this BUG():

  list_add corruption. next-&gt;prev should be prev (ffffffffb5355fd0),
    but was 0000000000000068. (next=ffffffffc0a010d0).
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:29!
  Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 1 PID: 4159 Comm: modprobe Not tainted 6.10.11-4+bt2-ao-desktop #1
  RIP: 0010:__list_add_valid_or_report+0x61/0xa0
  ...
    __list_add_valid_or_report+0x61/0xa0
    proto_register+0x299/0x320
    hci_sock_init+0x16/0xc0 [bluetooth]
    bt_init+0x68/0xd0 [bluetooth]
    __pfx_bt_init+0x10/0x10 [bluetooth]
    do_one_initcall+0x80/0x2f0
    do_init_module+0x8b/0x230
    __do_sys_init_module+0x15f/0x190
    do_syscall_64+0x68/0x110
  ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50079 | io_uring/sqpoll: ensure task state is TASK_RUNNING when running task_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50079</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/sqpoll: ensure task state is TASK_RUNNING when running task_work

When the sqpoll is exiting and cancels pending work items, it may need
to run task_work. If this happens from within io_uring_cancel_generic(),
then it may be under waiting for the io_uring_task waitqueue. This
results in the below splat from the scheduler, as the ring mutex may be
attempted grabbed while in a TASK_INTERRUPTIBLE state.

Ensure that the task state is set appropriately for that, just like what
is done for the other cases in io_run_task_work().

do not call blocking ops when !TASK_RUNNING; state=1 set at [&lt;0000000029387fd2&gt;] prepare_to_wait+0x88/0x2fc
WARNING: CPU: 6 PID: 59939 at kernel/sched/core.c:8561 __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
Modules linked in:
CPU: 6 UID: 0 PID: 59939 Comm: iou-sqp-59938 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc3-00113-g8d020023b155 #7456
Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
pstate: 61400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO +DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
lr : __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
sp : ffff80008c5e7830
x29: ffff80008c5e7830 x28: ffff0000d93088c0 x27: ffff60001c2d7230
x26: dfff800000000000 x25: ffff0000e16b9180 x24: ffff80008c5e7a50
x23: 1ffff000118bcf4a x22: ffff0000e16b9180 x21: ffff0000e16b9180
x20: 000000000000011b x19: ffff80008310fac0 x18: 1ffff000118bcd90
x17: 30303c5b20746120 x16: 74657320313d6574 x15: 0720072007200720
x14: 0720072007200720 x13: 0720072007200720 x12: ffff600036c64f0b
x11: 1fffe00036c64f0a x10: ffff600036c64f0a x9 : dfff800000000000
x8 : 00009fffc939b0f6 x7 : ffff0001b6327853 x6 : 0000000000000001
x5 : ffff0001b6327850 x4 : ffff600036c64f0b x3 : ffff8000803c35bc
x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffff0000e16b9180
Call trace:
 __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
 mutex_lock+0x84/0x124
 io_handle_tw_list+0xf4/0x260
 tctx_task_work_run+0x94/0x340
 io_run_task_work+0x1ec/0x3c0
 io_uring_cancel_generic+0x364/0x524
 io_sq_thread+0x820/0x124c
 ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50080 | ublk: don&amp;#x27;t allow user copy for unprivileged device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50080</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ublk: don't allow user copy for unprivileged device

UBLK_F_USER_COPY requires userspace to call write() on ublk char
device for filling request buffer, and unprivileged device can't
be trusted.

So don't allow user copy for unprivileged device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50081 | blk-mq: setup queue -&amp;gt;tag_set before initializing hctx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50081</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-mq: setup queue -&gt;tag_set before initializing hctx

Commit 7b815817aa58 ("blk-mq: add helper for checking if one CPU is mapped to specified hctx")
needs to check queue mapping via tag set in hctx's cpuhp handler.

However, q-&gt;tag_set may not be setup yet when the cpuhp handler is
enabled, then kernel oops is triggered.

Fix the issue by setup queue tag_set before initializing hctx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50082 | blk-rq-qos: fix crash on rq_qos_wait vs. rq_qos_wake_function race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50082</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-rq-qos: fix crash on rq_qos_wait vs. rq_qos_wake_function race

We're seeing crashes from rq_qos_wake_function that look like this:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffafe180a40084
  #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
  PGD 100000067 P4D 100000067 PUD 10027c067 PMD 10115d067 PTE 0
  Oops: Oops: 0002 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 17 UID: 0 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/17 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc3-00013-geca631b8fe80 #11
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.0-0-gd239552ce722-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:_raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x1d/0x40
  Code: 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 f3 0f 1e fa 0f 1f 44 00 00 41 54 9c 41 5c fa 65 ff 05 62 97 30 4c 31 c0 ba 01 00 00 00  0f b1 17 75 0a 4c 89 e0 41 5c c3 cc cc cc cc 89 c6 e8 2c 0b 00
  RSP: 0018:ffffafe180580ca0 EFLAGS: 00010046
  RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffafe180a3f7a8 RCX: 0000000000000011
  RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: 0000000000000003 RDI: ffffafe180a40084
  RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 00000000001e7240 R09: 0000000000000011
  R10: 0000000000000028 R11: 0000000000000888 R12: 0000000000000002
  R13: ffffafe180a40084 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000003
  FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff9aaf1f280000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: ffffafe180a40084 CR3: 000000010e428002 CR4: 0000000000770ef0
  DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
  DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
  PKRU: 55555554
  Call Trace:
   
   try_to_wake_up+0x5a/0x6a0
   rq_qos_wake_function+0x71/0x80
   __wake_up_common+0x75/0xa0
   __wake_up+0x36/0x60
   scale_up.part.0+0x50/0x110
   wb_timer_fn+0x227/0x450
   ...

So rq_qos_wake_function() calls wake_up_process(data-&gt;task), which calls
try_to_wake_up(), which faults in raw_spin_lock_irqsave(&amp;amp;p-&gt;pi_lock).

p comes from data-&gt;task, and data comes from the waitqueue entry, which
is stored on the waiter's stack in rq_qos_wait(). Analyzing the core
dump with drgn, I found that the waiter had already woken up and moved
on to a completely unrelated code path, clobbering what was previously
data-&gt;task. Meanwhile, the waker was passing the clobbered garbage in
data-&gt;task to wake_up_process(), leading to the crash.

What's happening is that in between rq_qos_wake_function() deleting the
waitqueue entry and calling wake_up_process(), rq_qos_wait() is finding
that it already got a token and returning. The race looks like this:

rq_qos_wait()                           rq_qos_wake_function()
==============================================================
prepare_to_wait_exclusive()
                                        data-&gt;got_token = true;
                                        list_del_init(&amp;amp;curr-&gt;entry);
if (data.got_token)
        break;
finish_wait(&amp;amp;rqw-&gt;wait, &amp;amp;data.wq);
  ^- returns immediately because
     list_empty_careful(&amp;amp;wq_entry-&gt;entry)
     is true
... return, go do something else ...
                                        wake_up_process(data-&gt;task)
                                          (NO LONGER VALID!)-^

Normally, finish_wait() is supposed to synchronize against the waker.
But, as noted above, it is returning immediately because the waitqueue
entry has already been removed from the waitqueue.

The bug is that rq_qos_wake_function() is accessing the waitqueue entry
AFTER deleting it. Note that autoremove_wake_function() wakes the waiter
and THEN deletes the waitqueue entry, which is the proper order.

Fix it by swapping the order. We also need to use
list_del_init_careful() to match the list_empty_careful() in
finish_wait().</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50083 | tcp: fix mptcp DSS corruption due to large pmtu xmit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50083</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: fix mptcp DSS corruption due to large pmtu xmit

Syzkaller was able to trigger a DSS corruption:

  TCP: request_sock_subflow_v4: Possible SYN flooding on port [::]:20002. Sending cookies.
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 5227 at net/mptcp/protocol.c:695 __mptcp_move_skbs_from_subflow+0x20a9/0x21f0 net/mptcp/protocol.c:695
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 5227 Comm: syz-executor350 Not tainted 6.11.0-syzkaller-08829-gaf9c191ac2a0 #0
  Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 08/06/2024
  RIP: 0010:__mptcp_move_skbs_from_subflow+0x20a9/0x21f0 net/mptcp/protocol.c:695
  Code: 0f b6 dc 31 ff 89 de e8 b5 dd ea f5 89 d8 48 81 c4 50 01 00 00 5b 41 5c 41 5d 41 5e 41 5f 5d c3 cc cc cc cc e8 98 da ea f5 90 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 90 e9 47 ff ff ff e8 8a da ea f5 90 0f 0b 90 e9 99 e0 ff ff
  RSP: 0018:ffffc90000006db8 EFLAGS: 00010246
  RAX: ffffffff8ba9df18 RBX: 00000000000055f0 RCX: ffff888030023c00
  RDX: 0000000000000100 RSI: 00000000000081e5 RDI: 00000000000055f0
  RBP: 1ffff110062bf1ae R08: ffffffff8ba9cf12 R09: 1ffff110062bf1b8
  R10: dffffc0000000000 R11: ffffed10062bf1b9 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: dffffc0000000000 R14: 00000000700cec61 R15: 00000000000081e5
  FS:  000055556679c380(0000) GS:ffff8880b8600000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: 0000000020287000 CR3: 0000000077892000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
  DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
  DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
  Call Trace:
   
   move_skbs_to_msk net/mptcp/protocol.c:811 [inline]
   mptcp_data_ready+0x29c/0xa90 net/mptcp/protocol.c:854
   subflow_data_ready+0x34a/0x920 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1490
   tcp_data_queue+0x20fd/0x76c0 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:5283
   tcp_rcv_established+0xfba/0x2020 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:6237
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x96d/0xc70 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:1915
   tcp_v4_rcv+0x2dc0/0x37f0 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:2350
   ip_protocol_deliver_rcu+0x22e/0x440 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:205
   ip_local_deliver_finish+0x341/0x5f0 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:233
   NF_HOOK+0x3a4/0x450 include/linux/netfilter.h:314
   NF_HOOK+0x3a4/0x450 include/linux/netfilter.h:314
   __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5662 [inline]
   __netif_receive_skb+0x2bf/0x650 net/core/dev.c:5775
   process_backlog+0x662/0x15b0 net/core/dev.c:6107
   __napi_poll+0xcb/0x490 net/core/dev.c:6771
   napi_poll net/core/dev.c:6840 [inline]
   net_rx_action+0x89b/0x1240 net/core/dev.c:6962
   handle_softirqs+0x2c5/0x980 kernel/softirq.c:554
   do_softirq+0x11b/0x1e0 kernel/softirq.c:455
   
   
   __local_bh_enable_ip+0x1bb/0x200 kernel/softirq.c:382
   local_bh_enable include/linux/bottom_half.h:33 [inline]
   rcu_read_unlock_bh include/linux/rcupdate.h:919 [inline]
   __dev_queue_xmit+0x1764/0x3e80 net/core/dev.c:4451
   dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3094 [inline]
   neigh_hh_output include/net/neighbour.h:526 [inline]
   neigh_output include/net/neighbour.h:540 [inline]
   ip_finish_output2+0xd41/0x1390 net/ipv4/ip_output.c:236
   ip_local_out net/ipv4/ip_output.c:130 [inline]
   __ip_queue_xmit+0x118c/0x1b80 net/ipv4/ip_output.c:536
   __tcp_transmit_skb+0x2544/0x3b30 net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:1466
   tcp_transmit_skb net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:1484 [inline]
   tcp_mtu_probe net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:2547 [inline]
   tcp_write_xmit+0x641d/0x6bf0 net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:2752
   __tcp_push_pending_frames+0x9b/0x360 net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:3015
   tcp_push_pending_frames include/net/tcp.h:2107 [inline]
   tcp_data_snd_check net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:5714 [inline]
   tcp_rcv_established+0x1026/0x2020 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:6239
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x96d/0xc70 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:1915
   sk_backlog_rcv include/net/sock.h:1113 [inline]
   __release_sock+0x214/0x350 net/core/sock.c:3072
   release_sock+0x61/0x1f0 net/core/sock.c:3626
   mptcp_push_
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50084 | net: microchip: vcap api: Fix memory leaks in vcap_api_encode_rule_test()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50084</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: microchip: vcap api: Fix memory leaks in vcap_api_encode_rule_test()

Commit a3c1e45156ad ("net: microchip: vcap: Fix use-after-free error in
kunit test") fixed the use-after-free error, but introduced below
memory leaks by removing necessary vcap_free_rule(), add it to fix it.

	unreferenced object 0xffffff80ca58b700 (size 192):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898264
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    00 12 7a 00 05 00 00 00 0a 00 00 00 64 00 00 00  ..z.........d...
	    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 04 0b cc 80 ff ff ff  ................
	  backtrace (crc 9c09c3fe):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;0000000040a01b8d&gt;] vcap_alloc_rule+0x3cc/0x9c4
	    [&lt;000000003fe86110&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x1ac/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0400 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898265
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    80 04 0b cc 80 ff ff ff 18 b7 58 ca 80 ff ff ff  ..........X.....
	    39 00 00 00 02 00 00 00 06 05 04 03 02 01 ff ff  9...............
	  backtrace (crc daf014e9):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000000ff63fd4&gt;] vcap_rule_add_key+0x2cc/0x528
	    [&lt;00000000dfdb1e81&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x224/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0700 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898265
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    80 07 0b cc 80 ff ff ff 28 b7 58 ca 80 ff ff ff  ........(.X.....
	    3c 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 01 2f 03 b3 ec ff ff ff  &lt;......../......
	  backtrace (crc 8d877792):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000006eadfab7&gt;] vcap_rule_add_action+0x2d0/0x52c
	    [&lt;00000000323475d1&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x4d4/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0900 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898266
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    80 09 0b cc 80 ff ff ff 80 06 0b cc 80 ff ff ff  ................
	    7d 00 00 00 01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 ff 00 00 00  }...............
	  backtrace (crc 34181e56):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000000ff63fd4&gt;] vcap_rule_add_key+0x2cc/0x528
	    [&lt;00000000991e3564&gt;] vcap_val_rule+0xcf0/0x13e8
	    [&lt;00000000fc9868e5&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x678/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0980 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898266
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    18 b7 58 ca 80 ff ff ff 00 09 0b cc 80 ff ff ff  ..X.............
	    67 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 01 01 74 88 c0 ff ff ff  g.........t.....
	  backtrace (crc 275fd9be):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000000ff63fd4&gt;] vcap_rule_add_key+0x2cc/0x528
	    [&lt;000000001396a1a2&gt;] test_add_de
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50085 | mptcp: pm: fix UaF read in mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50085</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: fix UaF read in mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow

Syzkaller reported this splat:

  ==================================================================
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow+0xb44/0xcc0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:881
  Read of size 4 at addr ffff8880569ac858 by task syz.1.2799/14662

  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 14662 Comm: syz.1.2799 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc2-syzkaller-00307-g36c254515dc6 #0
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2~bpo12+1 04/01/2014
  Call Trace:
   
   __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
   dump_stack_lvl+0x116/0x1f0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
   print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:377 [inline]
   print_report+0xc3/0x620 mm/kasan/report.c:488
   kasan_report+0xd9/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:601
   mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow+0xb44/0xcc0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:881
   mptcp_pm_nl_rm_subflow_received net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:914 [inline]
   mptcp_nl_remove_id_zero_address+0x305/0x4a0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:1572
   mptcp_pm_nl_del_addr_doit+0x5c9/0x770 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:1603
   genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x202/0x2f0 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1115
   genl_family_rcv_msg net/netlink/genetlink.c:1195 [inline]
   genl_rcv_msg+0x565/0x800 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1210
   netlink_rcv_skb+0x165/0x410 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2551
   genl_rcv+0x28/0x40 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1219
   netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1331 [inline]
   netlink_unicast+0x53c/0x7f0 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1357
   netlink_sendmsg+0x8b8/0xd70 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1901
   sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:729 [inline]
   __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:744 [inline]
   ____sys_sendmsg+0x9ae/0xb40 net/socket.c:2607
   ___sys_sendmsg+0x135/0x1e0 net/socket.c:2661
   __sys_sendmsg+0x117/0x1f0 net/socket.c:2690
   do_syscall_32_irqs_on arch/x86/entry/common.c:165 [inline]
   __do_fast_syscall_32+0x73/0x120 arch/x86/entry/common.c:386
   do_fast_syscall_32+0x32/0x80 arch/x86/entry/common.c:411
   entry_SYSENTER_compat_after_hwframe+0x84/0x8e
  RIP: 0023:0xf7fe4579
  Code: b8 01 10 06 03 74 b4 01 10 07 03 74 b0 01 10 08 03 74 d8 01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 51 52 55 89 e5 0f 34 cd 80 &lt;5d&gt; 5a 59 c3 90 90 90 90 8d b4 26 00 00 00 00 8d b4 26 00 00 00 00
  RSP: 002b:00000000f574556c EFLAGS: 00000296 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000172
  RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 000000000000000b RCX: 0000000020000140
  RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: 0000000000000000
  RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000296 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000000
   

  Allocated by task 5387:
   kasan_save_stack+0x33/0x60 mm/kasan/common.c:47
   kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30 mm/kasan/common.c:68
   poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:377 [inline]
   __kasan_kmalloc+0xaa/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:394
   kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:878 [inline]
   kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1014 [inline]
   subflow_create_ctx+0x87/0x2a0 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1803
   subflow_ulp_init+0xc3/0x4d0 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1956
   __tcp_set_ulp net/ipv4/tcp_ulp.c:146 [inline]
   tcp_set_ulp+0x326/0x7f0 net/ipv4/tcp_ulp.c:167
   mptcp_subflow_create_socket+0x4ae/0x10a0 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1764
   __mptcp_subflow_connect+0x3cc/0x1490 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1592
   mptcp_pm_create_subflow_or_signal_addr+0xbda/0x23a0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:642
   mptcp_pm_nl_fully_established net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:650 [inline]
   mptcp_pm_nl_work+0x3a1/0x4f0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:943
   mptcp_worker+0x15a/0x1240 net/mptcp/protocol.c:2777
   process_one_work+0x958/0x1b30 kernel/workqueue.c:3229
   process_scheduled_works kernel/workqueue.c:3310 [inline]
   worker_thread+0x6c8/0xf00 kernel/workqueue.c:3391
   kthread+0x2c1/0x3a0 kernel/kthread.c:389
   ret_from_fork+0x45/0x80 arch/x86/ke
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50086 | ksmbd: fix user-after-free from session log off</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50086</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix user-after-free from session log off

There is racy issue between smb2 session log off and smb2 session setup.
It will cause user-after-free from session log off.
This add session_lock when setting SMB2_SESSION_EXPIRED and referece
count to session struct not to free session while it is being used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50087 | btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free on read_alloc_one_name() error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50087</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free on read_alloc_one_name() error

The function read_alloc_one_name() does not initialize the name field of
the passed fscrypt_str struct if kmalloc fails to allocate the
corresponding buffer.  Thus, it is not guaranteed that
fscrypt_str.name is initialized when freeing it.

This is a follow-up to the linked patch that fixes the remaining
instances of the bug introduced by commit e43eec81c516 ("btrfs: use
struct qstr instead of name and namelen pairs").</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50088 | btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free in add_inode_ref()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50088</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free in add_inode_ref()

The add_inode_ref() function does not initialize the "name" struct when
it is declared.  If any of the following calls to "read_one_inode()
returns NULL,

	dir = read_one_inode(root, parent_objectid);
	if (!dir) {
		ret = -ENOENT;
		goto out;
	}

	inode = read_one_inode(root, inode_objectid);
	if (!inode) {
		ret = -EIO;
		goto out;
	}

then "name.name" would be freed on "out" before being initialized.

out:
	...
	kfree(name.name);

This issue was reported by Coverity with CID 1526744.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10477 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Permission Management Page admin#permissions cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10477</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms up to 2.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin#permissions of the component Permission Management Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10478 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Edit Article edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10478</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms up to 2.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin#article/edit?id=2 of the component Edit Article Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51506 | Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Create a Wiki Pages" stored XSS payload in the description.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51506</link><description>Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Create a Wiki Pages" stored XSS payload in the description.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51507 | Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Create/Edit External Wiki" stored XSS payload in the Name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51507</link><description>Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Create/Edit External Wiki" stored XSS payload in the Name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51508 | Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Create/Edit External Wiki" stored XSS payload in the Index.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51508</link><description>Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Create/Edit External Wiki" stored XSS payload in the Index.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51509 | Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Modules" (aka tiki-admin_modules.php) stored XSS payload in the Nam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51509</link><description>Tiki through 27.0 allows users who have certain permissions to insert a "Modules" (aka tiki-admin_modules.php) stored XSS payload in the Name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30106 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30106</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability, due to an IBM WebSphere Application Server error, which could allow a user to obtain sensitive information they are not entitled to due to the improper handling of request data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44145 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44145</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access to a macOS device with Sidecar enabled may be able to bypass the Lock Screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44216 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44216</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44217 | A permissions issue was addressed by removing vulnerable code and adding additional checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44217</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed by removing vulnerable code and adding additional checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Password autofill may fill in passwords after failing authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44237 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44237</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44240 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44240</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. Processing a maliciously crafted font may result in the disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44256 | The issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44256</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44257 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44257</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44260 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44260</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious app with root privileges may be able to modify the contents of system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44283 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44283</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsing a maliciously crafted file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44295 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44295</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27849 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27849</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40792 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app may be able to chan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40792</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app may be able to change network settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40851 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40851</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to access contact photos from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40853 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40853</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker may be able to use Siri to enable Auto-Answer Calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40855 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A sandboxe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40855</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A sandboxed app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40867 | A custom URL scheme handling issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. A remote a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40867</link><description>A custom URL scheme handling issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. A remote attacker may be able to break out of Web Content sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44122 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44122</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An application may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44123 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44123</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A malicious app with root privileges may be able to access keyboard input and location information without user consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44126 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44126</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44137 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44137</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to share items from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44144 | A buffer overflow was addressed with improved size validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44144</link><description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved size validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44155 | A custom URL scheme handling issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44155</link><description>A custom URL scheme handling issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Sequoia 15, watchOS 11, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Maliciously crafted web content may violate iframe sandboxing policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44156 | A path deletion vulnerability was addressed by preventing vulnerable code from running with privileges. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44156</link><description>A path deletion vulnerability was addressed by preventing vulnerable code from running with privileges. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44159 | A path deletion vulnerability was addressed by preventing vulnerable code from running with privileges. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44159</link><description>A path deletion vulnerability was addressed by preventing vulnerable code from running with privileges. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44174 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An attacker may be able to view restricted content fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44174</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An attacker may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44175 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44175</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44194 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44194</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44196 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44196</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44197 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44197</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44203 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access a user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44203</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access a user's Photos Library.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44208 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to bypass certain Pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44208</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44213 | An issue existed in the parsing of URLs. This issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44213</link><description>An issue existed in the parsing of URLs. This issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44215 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44215</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. Processing an image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44218 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44218</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44222 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44222</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44228 | This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16. An app may be able to inherit Xcode permission...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44228</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16. An app may be able to inherit Xcode permissions and access user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44229 | An information leakage was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. Private brow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44229</link><description>An information leakage was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. Private browsing may leak some browsing history.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44235 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker may be able to view restricted co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44235</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44236 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44236</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44239 | An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44239</link><description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. An app may be able to leak sensitive kernel state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44244 | A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, watchOS 11.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44244</link><description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1, tvOS 18.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44247 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44247</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44251 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker may be able to view...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44251</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44252 | A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, visi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44252</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, visionOS 2.1, tvOS 18.1. Restoring a maliciously crafted backup file may lead to modification of protected system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44253 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to modify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44253</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44254 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44254</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44255 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44255</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, tvOS 18.1. A malicious app may be able to run arbitrary shortcuts without user consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44258 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44258</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, visionOS 2.1, tvOS 18.1. Restoring a maliciously crafted backup file may lead to modification of protected system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44259 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44259</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker may be able to misuse a trust relationship to download malicious content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44261 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, iOS 18.1 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44261</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44262 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1. A user may be able to view s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44262</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1. A user may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44263 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to access us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44263</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44264 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44264</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious app may be able to create symlinks to protected regions of the disk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44265 | The issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44265</link><description>The issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An attacker with physical access can input Game Controller events to apps running on a locked device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44267 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44267</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44269 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44269</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. A malicious app may use shortcuts to access restricted files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44270 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A sandboxed process ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44270</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44273 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, visionOS 2.1, macOS Sonoma 14....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44273</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, visionOS 2.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, tvOS 18.1. A malicious app may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44274 | The issue was addressed with improved authentication. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, watchOS 11.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44274</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved authentication. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, watchOS 11.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44275 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44275</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44277 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, visionOS 2.1, tvOS 18.1. An app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44277</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, visionOS 2.1, tvOS 18.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44278 | An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44278</link><description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. A sandboxed app may be able to access sensitive user data in system logs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44279 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44279</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsing a file may lead to disclosure of user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44280 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44280</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44281 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44281</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsing a file may lead to disclosure of user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44282 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44282</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. Parsing a file may lead to disclosure of user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44284 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44284</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. Parsing a maliciously crafted file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44285 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, watchOS 11.1, visionO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44285</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1, tvOS 18.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44287 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44287</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44289 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44289</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44294 | A path deletion vulnerability was addressed by preventing vulnerable code from running with privileges. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44294</link><description>A path deletion vulnerability was addressed by preventing vulnerable code from running with privileges. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. An attacker with root privileges may be able to delete protected system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44296 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44296</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may prevent Content Security Policy from being enforced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44297 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44297</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. Processing a maliciously crafted message may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44301 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44301</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1. A malicious application may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44302 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44302</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, visionOS 2.1. Processing a maliciously crafted font may result in the disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50495 | WordPress Plugin Propagator plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50495</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WidgiLabs Plugin Propagator allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Plugin Propagator: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50496 | WordPress AR For WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50496</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Web and Print Design AR For WordPress allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects AR For WordPress: from n/a through 6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48107 | SparkShop &lt;=1.1.7 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This vulnerability allows attacks to scan ports on the Intranet or lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48107</link><description>SparkShop &lt;=1.1.7 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This vulnerability allows attacks to scan ports on the Intranet or local network where the server resides, attack applications running on the Intranet or local network, or read metadata on the cloud server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48594 | File Upload vulnerability in Prison Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file upload component...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48594</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Prison Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file upload component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42011 | The Spotify app 8.9.58 for iOS has a buffer overflow in its use of strcat.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42011</link><description>The Spotify app 8.9.58 for iOS has a buffer overflow in its use of strcat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48177 | MRCMS 3.1.2 contains a SQL injection vulnerability via the RID parameter in /admin/article/delete.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48177</link><description>MRCMS 3.1.2 contains a SQL injection vulnerability via the RID parameter in /admin/article/delete.do.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48356 | LyLme Spage &lt;=1.6.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/group.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48356</link><description>LyLme Spage &lt;=1.6.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/group.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48178 | newbee-mall v1.0.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the goodsCoverImg parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48178</link><description>newbee-mall v1.0.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the goodsCoverImg parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48357 | LyLme Spage 1.2.0 through 1.6.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/apply.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48357</link><description>LyLme Spage 1.2.0 through 1.6.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/apply.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48465 | The MRBS version 1.5.0 has an SQL injection vulnerability in the edit_entry_handler.php file, specifically in the rooms%5B%5D parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48465</link><description>The MRBS version 1.5.0 has an SQL injection vulnerability in the edit_entry_handler.php file, specifically in the rooms%5B%5D parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50434 | WordPress NewsCard theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50434</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Theme Horse NewsCard.This issue affects NewsCard: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50435 | WordPress Meta News theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50435</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Theme Horse Meta News.This issue affects Meta News: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48195 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in eyouCMS v.1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48195</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in eyouCMS v.1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the post parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48196 | An issue in eyouCMS v.1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the post parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48196</link><description>An issue in eyouCMS v.1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the post parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50436 | WordPress Clean Retina theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50436</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Theme Horse Clean Retina.This issue affects Clean Retina: from n/a through 3.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50453 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50453</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor addons allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50457 | WordPress Qode Essential Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50457</link><description>: Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Qode Interactive Qode Essential Addons.This issue affects Qode Essential Addons: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42930 | PbootCMS 3.2.8 is vulnerable to URL Redirect.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42930</link><description>PbootCMS 3.2.8 is vulnerable to URL Redirect.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49755 | Duende IdentityServer has insufficient validation of DPoP cnf claim in Local APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49755</link><description>Duende IdentityServer is an OpenID Connect and OAuth 2.x framework for ASP.NET Core. IdentityServer's local API authentication handler performs insufficient validation of the cnf claim in DPoP access tokens. This allows an attacker to use leaked DPoP access tokens at local api endpoints even without possessing the private key for signing proof tokens. Note that this only impacts custom endpoints within an IdentityServer implementation that have explicitly used the LocalApiAuthenticationHandler for authentication. This vulnerability is patched in IdentityServer 7.0.8. Version 6.3 and below are unaffected, as they do not support DPoP in Local APIs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39205 | An issue in pyload-ng v0.5.0b3.dev85 running under python3.11 or below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTTP request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39205</link><description>An issue in pyload-ng v0.5.0b3.dev85 running under python3.11 or below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48825 | Tenda AC7 v.15.03.06.44 ate_ifconfig_set has pre-authentication command injection allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48825</link><description>Tenda AC7 v.15.03.06.44 ate_ifconfig_set has pre-authentication command injection allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48826 | Tenda AC7 v.15.03.06.44 ate_iwpriv_set has pre-authentication command injection allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48826</link><description>Tenda AC7 v.15.03.06.44 ate_iwpriv_set has pre-authentication command injection allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5532 | A stored XSS vulnerability has been discovered on OpenText™ Operations Agent (OA).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5532</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OpenText™ Operations Agent. 

The XSS vulnerability could allow an attacker with local admin permissions to manipulate the content of the internal status page of the Agent on the local system. 

This issue affects Operations Agent: 12.20, 12.21, 12.22, 12.23, 12.24, 12.25, 12.26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9825 | The Chef Habitat builder is impacted by Indirect Object reference(IDOR) by deletion of personal access token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9825</link><description>The Chef Habitat builder-api on-prem-builder package  with any version lower than habitat/builder-api/10315/20240913162802 is vulnerable to indirect object reference (IDOR) by un-authorized deletion of personal token.  Habitat builder consumes builder-api habitat package as a dependency and the vulnerability was specifically due to builder-api habitat package.

The fix was made available in habitat/builder-api/10315/20240913162802 and all the subsequent versions after that. We would recommend user to always use on-prem stable channel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50429 | WordPress Magazine Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50429</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPBlockArt Magazine Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Magazine Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50431 | WordPress Breeze plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50431</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cloudways Breeze allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Breeze: from n/a through 2.1.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50432 | WordPress Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.93 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50432</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 2.2.93.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50433 | WordPress Sky Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50433</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wowDevs Sky Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sky Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.5.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50437 | WordPress GeoDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.80 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AyeCode GeoDirectory allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GeoDirectory: from n/a through 2.3.80.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50438 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt; 5.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50438</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a before 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50439 | WordPress Astra Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.14 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50439</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Astra Widgets allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Astra Widgets: from n/a through 1.2.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50440 | WordPress CodePen Embedded Pens Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50440</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chris Coyier CodePen Embedded Pens Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CodePen Embedded Pens Shortcode: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50441 | WordPress Cozy Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50441</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CozyThemes Cozy Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cozy Blocks: from n/a through 2.0.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50445 | WordPress Selection Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50445</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Merkulove Selection Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Selection Lite: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50446 | WordPress Futurio Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50446</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FuturioWP Futurio Extra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Futurio Extra: from n/a through 2.0.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50447 | WordPress Envo&amp;#x27;s Elementor Templates &amp;amp; Widgets for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.19 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50447</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EnvoThemes Envo's Elementor Templates &amp; Widgets for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Envo's Elementor Templates &amp; Widgets for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50448 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons plugin &amp;lt;= 4.14.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50448</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons: from n/a through 4.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50449 | WordPress PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50449</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RedefiningTheWeb PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50451 | WordPress MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50451</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 WordPress Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter (MDTF) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter (MDTF): from n/a through 1.3.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50458 | WordPress Advanced Sermons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50458</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Codeus Advanced Sermons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Sermons: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50460 | WordPress Firelight Lightbox plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FirelightWP Firelight Lightbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Firelight Lightbox: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50461 | WordPress EmbedPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50461</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects EmbedPress: from n/a through 4.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50462 | WordPress Interactive World Map plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50462</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fla-shop Interactive World Map allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Interactive World Map: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50464 | WordPress Kodex Posts likes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50464</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pierre Lebedel Kodex Posts likes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kodex Posts likes: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50467 | WordPress Scrollbar by webxapp plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50467</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebXApp Scrollbar by webxapp – Best vertical/horizontal scrollbars plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Scrollbar by webxapp – Best vertical/horizontal scrollbars plugin: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50468 | WordPress Raptor Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50468</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Robinson Raptor Editor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Raptor Editor: from n/a through 1.0.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50469 | WordPress Textboxes plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50469</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Team Bright Vessel Textboxes allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Textboxes: from n/a through 0.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9629 | Contact Form 7 + Telegram &amp;lt;= 0.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Subscription Approve/Pause/Refuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9629</link><description>The Contact Form 7 + Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wpcf7_Telegram::ajax' function in versions up to, and including, 0.8.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to approve, pause and refuse subscriptions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49771 | MPXJ has a Potential Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49771</link><description>MPXJ is an open source library to read and write project plans from a variety of file formats and databases. The patch for the historical vulnerability CVE-2020-35460 in MPXJ is incomplete as there is still a possibility that a malicious path could be constructed which would not be picked up by the original fix and allow files to be written to arbitrary locations. The issue is addressed in MPXJ version 13.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6245 | Default Credentials in ssh service for SmartPlay in Maruti Suzuki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6245</link><description>Use of Default Credentials vulnerability in Maruti Suzuki SmartPlay on Linux (Infotainment Hub modules) allows attacker to try common or default usernames and passwords.The issue was detected on a 2022 Maruti Suzuki Brezza in India Market.

This issue affects SmartPlay: 66T0.05.50.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 16:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42028 | A Local privilege escalation vulnerability found in a Self-Hosted UniFi Network Server with UniFi Network Application (Version 8.4.62 and ea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42028</link><description>A Local privilege escalation vulnerability found in a Self-Hosted UniFi Network Server with UniFi Network Application (Version 8.4.62 and earlier) allows a malicious actor with a local operational system user to execute high privilege actions on UniFi Network Server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10469 | CERT/CC VINCE versions before 3.0.9 allows authenticated user to access User Management view.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10469</link><description>VINCE versions before 3.0.9 is vulnerable to exposure of User information to authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 15:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47827 | Argo Workflows Controller: Denial of Service via malicious daemon Workflows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47827</link><description>Argo Workflows is an open source container-native workflow engine for orchestrating parallel jobs on Kubernetes. Due to a race condition in a global variable in 3.6.0-rc1, the argo workflows controller can be made to crash on-command by any user with access to execute a workflow. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.0-rc2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10450 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System POST Parameter edit_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10450</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /kortex_lite/control/edit_profile.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 15:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45802 | Squid Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45802</link><description>Squid is an open source caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to Input Validation, Premature Release of Resource During Expected Lifetime, and Missing Release of Resource after Effective Lifetime bugs, Squid is vulnerable to Denial of Service attacks by a trusted server against all clients using the proxy. This bug is fixed in the default build configuration of Squid version 6.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10449 | Codezips Hospital Appointment System loginAction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10449</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Codezips Hospital Appointment System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /loginAction.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10214 | Incorrect Session Creation with Desktop SSO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10214</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.X &lt;= 9.11.1, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 icorrectly issues two sessions when using desktop SSO - one in the browser and one in desktop with incorrect settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48291 | dingfanzu CMS 1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/doAdminAction.php?act=editAdmin&amp;id=17</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48291</link><description>dingfanzu CMS 1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/doAdminAction.php?act=editAdmin&amp;amp;id=17</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49761 | REXML ReDoS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49761</link><description>REXML is an XML toolkit for Ruby. The REXML gem before 3.3.9 has a ReDoS vulnerability when it parses an XML that has many digits between &amp;# and x...; in a hex numeric character reference (&amp;#x...;). This does not happen with Ruby 3.2 or later. Ruby 3.1 is the only affected maintained Ruby. The REXML gem 3.3.9 or later include the patch to fix the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48191 | dingfanzu CMS 1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/doAdminAction.php?act=delAdmin&amp;id=1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48191</link><description>dingfanzu CMS 1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/doAdminAction.php?act=delAdmin&amp;amp;id=17</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10448 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System delete.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10448</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /file/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other endpoints might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10455 | Reachable Assertion in µD3TN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10455</link><description>Reachable Assertion in BPv7 parser in µD3TN v0.14.0 allows attacker to disrupt service via malformed Extension Block</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34537 | TYPO3 before 13.3.1 allows denial of service (interface error) in the Bookmark Toolbar (ext:backend), exploitable by an administrator-level ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34537</link><description>TYPO3 before 13.3.1 allows denial of service (interface error) in the Bookmark Toolbar (ext:backend), exploitable by an administrator-level backend user account via manipulated data saved in the bookmark toolbar of the backend user interface. The fixed versions are 10.4.46 ELTS, 11.5.40 LTS, 12.4.21 LTS, and 13.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50443 | WordPress PostX plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50443</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Post Grid Team by WPXPO PostX allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PostX: from n/a through 4.1.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10447 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator staffdashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10447</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /timetable/staff/staffdashboard.php?info=updateprofile. The manipulation of the argument n leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50573 | In JetBrains Hub before 2024.3.47707 improper access control allowed users to generate permanent tokens for unauthorized services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50573</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2024.3.47707 improper access control allowed users to generate permanent tokens for unauthorized services</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50574 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 potential ReDoS exploit was possible via email header parsing in Helpdesk functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50574</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 potential ReDoS exploit was possible via email header parsing in Helpdesk functionality</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50575 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 reflected XSS was possible in Widget API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50575</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 reflected XSS was possible in Widget API</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50576 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible via vendor URL in App manifest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50576</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible via vendor URL in App manifest</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50577 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible via Angular template injection in Hub settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50577</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible via Angular template injection in Hub settings</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50578 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible via sprint value on agile boards page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50578</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible via sprint value on agile boards page</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50579 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 reflected XSS due to insecure link sanitization was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50579</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 reflected XSS due to insecure link sanitization was possible</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50580 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 multiple XSS were possible due to insecure markdown parsing and custom rendering rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50580</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 multiple XSS were possible due to insecure markdown parsing and custom rendering rule</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50581 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 improper HTML sanitization could lead to XSS attack via comment tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50581</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 improper HTML sanitization could lead to XSS attack via comment tag</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50582 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible due to improper HTML sanitization in markdown elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50582</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47707 stored XSS was possible due to improper HTML sanitization in markdown elements</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8013 | CSFLE and Queryable Encryption self-lookup may fail to encrypt values in subpipelines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8013</link><description>A bug in query analysis of certain complex self-referential $lookup subpipelines may result in literal values in expressions for encrypted fields to be sent to the server as plaintext instead of ciphertext. Should this occur, no documents would be returned or written. This issue affects mongocryptd binary (v5.0 versions prior to 5.0.29, v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.17, v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.12 and v7.3 versions prior to 7.3.4) and mongo_crypt_v1.so shared libraries (v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.17, v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.12 and v7.3 versions prior to 7.3.4) released alongside MongoDB Enterprise Server versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50463 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50463</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in WP Sunshine Sunshine Photo Cart.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: from n/a through 3.2.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50465 | WordPress Premium SEO Pack plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.001 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50465</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WP SEO – Calin Vingan Premium SEO Pack allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Premium SEO Pack: from n/a through 1.6.001.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50470 | WordPress Themes4WP YouTube External Subtitles plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50470</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themes4WP Themes4WP YouTube External Subtitles allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themes4WP YouTube External Subtitles: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50471 | WordPress Trip Plan plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50471</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Checklist Trip Plan allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Trip Plan: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50472 | WordPress Amilia Store plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.8 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50472</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Martin Drapeau Amilia Store allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Amilia Store: from n/a through 2.9.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50478 | WordPress 1-Click Login: Passwordless Authentication plugin 1.4.5 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50478</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness vulnerability in Swoop 1-Click Login: Passwordless Authentication allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects 1-Click Login: Passwordless Authentication: 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50479 | WordPress Woocommerce Quote Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50479</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mansur Ahamed Woocommerce Quote Calculator allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Woocommerce Quote Calculator: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50483 | WordPress Meetup plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50483</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Meetup allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Meetup: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50491 | WordPress RSVP ME plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50491</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Micah Blu RSVP ME allows SQL Injection.This issue affects RSVP ME: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50497 | WordPress Advanced Online Ordering and Delivery Platform plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50497</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BuyNowDepot Advanced Online Ordering and Delivery Platform allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Advanced Online Ordering and Delivery Platform: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50501 | WordPress Kata Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50501</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Climax Themes Kata Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kata Plus: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50502 | WordPress Cozy Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.18 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50502</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CozyThemes Cozy Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cozy Blocks: from n/a through 2.0.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50488 | WordPress Token Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50488</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Priyabrata Sarkar Token Login allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Token Login: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 12:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48074 | An authorized RCE vulnerability exists in the DrayTek Vigor2960 router version 1.4.4, where an attacker can place a malicious command into t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48074</link><description>An authorized RCE vulnerability exists in the DrayTek Vigor2960 router version 1.4.4, where an attacker can place a malicious command into the table parameter of the doPPPoE function in the cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi route, and finally the command is executed by the system function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 12:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10446 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator admindashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10446</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /timetable/admin/admindashboard.php?info=add_course. The manipulation of the argument c leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50408 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50408</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Object Injection.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50416 | WordPress WPC Shop as a Customer for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50416</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WPClever WPC Shop as a Customer for WooCommerce allows Object Injection.This issue affects WPC Shop as a Customer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50450 | WordPress MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3.4 - Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50450</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in realmag777 WordPress Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter (MDTF) allows Code Injection.This issue affects WordPress Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter (MDTF): from n/a through 1.3.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50477 | WordPress Stacks Mobile App Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50477</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Stacks Stacks Mobile App Builder stacks-mobile-app-builder allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Stacks Mobile App Builder: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50486 | WordPress Acnoo Flutter API plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50486</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Acnoo Acnoo Flutter API allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Acnoo Flutter API: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50487 | WordPress MaanStore API plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50487</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in MaanTheme MaanStore API allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MaanStore API: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50492 | WordPress ScottCart plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50492</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Scott Paterson ScottCart allows Code Injection.This issue affects ScottCart: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50498 | WordPress WP Query Console plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50498</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in LUBUS WP Query Console allows Code Injection.This issue affects WP Query Console: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50442 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.980 - XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50442</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows XML Injection.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.3.980.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50489 | WordPress Realty Workstation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.45 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50489</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Realty Workstation allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Realty Workstation: from n/a through 1.0.45.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38821 | Authorization Bypass of Static Resources in WebFlux Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38821</link><description>Spring WebFlux applications that have Spring Security authorization rules on static resources can be bypassed under certain circumstances.

For this to impact an application, all of the following must be true:

  *  It must be a WebFlux application
  *  It must be using Spring's static resources support
  *  It must have a non-permitAll authorization rule applied to the static resources support</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 07:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9162 | All-in-One WP Migration and Backup &amp;lt;= 7.86 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary PHP Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9162</link><description>The All-in-One WP Migration and Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary PHP Code Injection due to missing file type validation during the export in all versions up to, and including, 7.86. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to create an export file with the .php extension on the affected site's server, adding an arbitrary PHP code to it, which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 05:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50307 | Use of potentially dangerous function issue exists in Chatwork Desktop Application (Windows) versions prior to 2.9.2. If a user clicks a spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50307</link><description>Use of potentially dangerous function issue exists in Chatwork Desktop Application (Windows) versions prior to 2.9.2. If a user clicks a specially crafted link in the application, an arbitrary file may be downloaded from an external website and executed. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed on the device that runs Chatwork Desktop Application (Windows).</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48936 | SchedMD Slurm before 24.05.4 has Incorrect Authorization. A mistake in authentication handling in stepmgr could permit an attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48936</link><description>SchedMD Slurm before 24.05.4 has Incorrect Authorization. A mistake in authentication handling in stepmgr could permit an attacker to execute processes under other users' jobs. This is limited to jobs explicitly running with --stepmgr, or on systems that have globally enabled stepmgr via SlurmctldParameters=enable_stepmgr in their configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 03:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10438 | Sunnet eHRD CTMS - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10438</link><description>The eHRD CTMS from Sunnet has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to bypass authentication by satisfying specific conditions in order to access certain functionalities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10439 | Sunnet eHRD CTMS - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10439</link><description>The eHRD CTMS from Sunnet has an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to modify a specific parameter to access arbitrary files uploaded by any user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10440 | Sunnet eHRD CTMS - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10440</link><description>The eHDR CTMS from Sunnet has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL command to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 03:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23843 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Genians Genian NAC V5.0, Genians Genia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23843</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Genians Genian NAC V5.0, Genians Genian NAC LTS V5.0.This issue affects Genian NAC V5.0: from V5.0.0 through V5.0.60; Genian NAC LTS V5.0: from 5.0.0 LTS through 5.0.55 LTS(Revision 125558), from 5.0.0 LTS through 5.0.56 LTS(Revision 125560).</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 02:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50067 | uprobe: avoid out-of-bounds memory access of fetching args</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50067</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

uprobe: avoid out-of-bounds memory access of fetching args

Uprobe needs to fetch args into a percpu buffer, and then copy to ring
buffer to avoid non-atomic context problem.

Sometimes user-space strings, arrays can be very large, but the size of
percpu buffer is only page size. And store_trace_args() won't check
whether these data exceeds a single page or not, caused out-of-bounds
memory access.

It could be reproduced by following steps:
1. build kernel with CONFIG_KASAN enabled
2. save follow program as test.c

```
\#include 
\#include 
\#include 

// If string length large than MAX_STRING_SIZE, the fetch_store_strlen()
// will return 0, cause __get_data_size() return shorter size, and
// store_trace_args() will not trigger out-of-bounds access.
// So make string length less than 4096.
\#define STRLEN 4093

void generate_string(char *str, int n)
{
    int i;
    for (i = 0; i &lt; n; ++i)
    {
        char c = i % 26 + 'a';
        str[i] = c;
    }
    str[n-1] = '\0';
}

void print_string(char *str)
{
    printf("%s\n", str);
}

int main()
{
    char tmp[STRLEN];

    generate_string(tmp, STRLEN);
    print_string(tmp);

    return 0;
}
```
3. compile program
`gcc -o test test.c`

4. get the offset of `print_string()`
```
objdump -t test | grep -w print_string
0000000000401199 g     F .text  000000000000001b              print_string
```

5. configure uprobe with offset 0x1199
```
off=0x1199

cd /sys/kernel/debug/tracing/
echo "p /root/test:${off} arg1=+0(%di):ustring arg2=\$comm arg3=+0(%di):ustring"
 &gt; uprobe_events
echo 1 &gt; events/uprobes/enable
echo 1 &gt; tracing_on
```

6. run `test`, and kasan will report error.
==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in strncpy_from_user+0x1d6/0x1f0
Write of size 8 at addr ffff88812311c004 by task test/499CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 499 Comm: test Not tainted 6.12.0-rc3+ #18
Hardware name: Red Hat KVM, BIOS 1.16.0-4.al8 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x55/0x70
 print_address_description.constprop.0+0x27/0x310
 kasan_report+0x10f/0x120
 ? strncpy_from_user+0x1d6/0x1f0
 strncpy_from_user+0x1d6/0x1f0
 ? rmqueue.constprop.0+0x70d/0x2ad0
 process_fetch_insn+0xb26/0x1470
 ? __pfx_process_fetch_insn+0x10/0x10
 ? _raw_spin_lock+0x85/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock+0x10/0x10
 ? __pte_offset_map+0x1f/0x2d0
 ? unwind_next_frame+0xc5f/0x1f80
 ? arch_stack_walk+0x68/0xf0
 ? is_bpf_text_address+0x23/0x30
 ? kernel_text_address.part.0+0xbb/0xd0
 ? __kernel_text_address+0x66/0xb0
 ? unwind_get_return_address+0x5e/0xa0
 ? __pfx_stack_trace_consume_entry+0x10/0x10
 ? arch_stack_walk+0xa2/0xf0
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x8b/0xf0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x10/0x10
 ? depot_alloc_stack+0x4c/0x1f0
 ? _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0xe/0x30
 ? stack_depot_save_flags+0x35d/0x4f0
 ? kasan_save_stack+0x34/0x50
 ? kasan_save_stack+0x24/0x50
 ? mutex_lock+0x91/0xe0
 ? __pfx_mutex_lock+0x10/0x10
 prepare_uprobe_buffer.part.0+0x2cd/0x500
 uprobe_dispatcher+0x2c3/0x6a0
 ? __pfx_uprobe_dispatcher+0x10/0x10
 ? __kasan_slab_alloc+0x4d/0x90
 handler_chain+0xdd/0x3e0
 handle_swbp+0x26e/0x3d0
 ? __pfx_handle_swbp+0x10/0x10
 ? uprobe_pre_sstep_notifier+0x151/0x1b0
 irqentry_exit_to_user_mode+0xe2/0x1b0
 asm_exc_int3+0x39/0x40
RIP: 0033:0x401199
Code: 01 c2 0f b6 45 fb 88 02 83 45 fc 01 8b 45 fc 3b 45 e4 7c b7 8b 45 e4 48 98 48 8d 50 ff 48 8b 45 e8 48 01 d0 ce
RSP: 002b:00007ffdf00576a8 EFLAGS: 00000206
RAX: 00007ffdf00576b0 RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: 0000000000000ff2
RDX: 0000000000000ffc RSI: 0000000000000ffd RDI: 00007ffdf00576b0
RBP: 00007ffdf00586b0 R08: 00007feb2f9c0d20 R09: 00007feb2f9c0d20
R10: 0000000000000001 R11: 0000000000000202 R12: 0000000000401040
R13: 00007ffdf0058780 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000000
 

This commit enforces the buffer's maxlen less than a page-size to avoid
store_trace_args() out-of-memory access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10434 | Tenda AC1206 ate ate_Tenda_mfg_check_usb3 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10434</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC1206 up to 20241027. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function ate_Tenda_mfg_check_usb/ate_Tenda_mfg_check_usb3 of the file /goform/ate. The manipulation of the argument arg leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10435 | didi Super-Jacoco triggerEnvCov command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10435</link><description>A vulnerability was found in didi Super-Jacoco 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cov/triggerEnvCov. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 01:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10433 | Project Worlds Simple Web-Based Chat Application index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Simple Web-Based Chat Application 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument Name/Comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions different parameters to be affected which do not correlate with the screenshots of a successful attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 01:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50624 | ispdbservice.cpp in KDE Kmail before 6.2.0 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to trigger use of an attacker-controlled mail server because c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50624</link><description>ispdbservice.cpp in KDE Kmail before 6.2.0 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to trigger use of an attacker-controlled mail server because cleartext HTTP is used for a URL such as http://autoconfig.example.com or http://example.com/.well-known/autoconfig for retrieving the configuration. This is related to kmail-account-wizard.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10432 | Project Worlds Simple Web-Based Chat Application index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10432</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Project Worlds Simple Web-Based Chat Application 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50623 | In Cleo Harmony before 5.8.0.20, VLTrader before 5.8.0.20, and LexiCom before 5.8.0.20, there is a JavaScript Injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50623</link><description>In Cleo Harmony before 5.8.0.20, VLTrader before 5.8.0.20, and LexiCom before 5.8.0.20, there is a JavaScript Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10430 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System animalsupdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10430</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /animalsupdate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10431 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System deletebird.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10431</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /deletebird.php. The manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50616 | Ironman PowerShell Universal 5.x before 5.0.12 allows an authenticated attacker to elevate their privileges and view job information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50616</link><description>Ironman PowerShell Universal 5.x before 5.0.12 allows an authenticated attacker to elevate their privileges and view job information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50612 | libsndfile through 1.2.2 has an ogg_vorbis.c vorbis_analysis_wrote out-of-bounds read.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50612</link><description>libsndfile through 1.2.2 has an ogg_vorbis.c vorbis_analysis_wrote out-of-bounds read.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50613 | libsndfile through 1.2.2 has a reachable assertion, that may lead to application exit, in mpeg_l3_encode.c mpeg_l3_encoder_close.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50613</link><description>libsndfile through 1.2.2 has a reachable assertion, that may lead to application exit, in mpeg_l3_encode.c mpeg_l3_encoder_close.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50614 | TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/16, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharacterR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50614</link><description>TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/16, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharacterRef.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50615 | TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/digit, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50615</link><description>TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/digit, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharacterRef.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50611 | CycloneDX cdxgen through 10.10.7, when run against an untrusted codebase, may execute code contained within build-related files such as buil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50611</link><description>CycloneDX cdxgen through 10.10.7, when run against an untrusted codebase, may execute code contained within build-related files such as build.gradle.kts, a similar issue to CVE-2022-24441. cdxgen is used by, for example, OWASP dep-scan. NOTE: this has been characterized as a design limitation, rather than an implementation mistake.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50610 | GSL (GNU Scientific Library) through 2.8 has an integer signedness error in gsl_siman_solve_many in siman/siman.c. When params.n_tries is ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50610</link><description>GSL (GNU Scientific Library) through 2.8 has an integer signedness error in gsl_siman_solve_many in siman/siman.c. When params.n_tries is negative, incorrect memory allocation occurs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10429 | WAVLINK WN530H4/WN530HG4/WN572HG3 internet.cgi set_ipv6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10429</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in WAVLINK WN530H4, WN530HG4 and WN572HG3 up to 20221028. Affected is the function set_ipv6 of the file internet.cgi. The manipulation of the argument IPv6OpMode/IPv6IPAddr/IPv6WANIPAddr/IPv6GWAddr leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10428 | WAVLINK WN530H4/WN530HG4/WN572HG3 firewall.cgi set_ipv6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10428</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WAVLINK WN530H4, WN530HG4 and WN572HG3 up to 20221028. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function set_ipv6 of the file firewall.cgi. The manipulation of the argument dhcpGateway leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 20:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10427 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System deleteanimal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10427</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /deleteanimal.php. The manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions the parameter "refno" to be affected. But further inspection indicates that the name of the affected parameter is "t1".</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10426 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System animalsadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10426</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /animalsadd.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions the parameter "refno" to be affected. But further inspection indicates that the name of the affected parameter is "id".</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 19:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10425 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Project Selection Page move_up_project.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10425</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /student/project_selection/move_up_project.php of the component Project Selection Page. The manipulation of the argument up leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10424 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Project Selection Page remove_project.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10424</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /student/project_selection/remove_project.php of the component Project Selection Page. The manipulation of the argument no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 18:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10423 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Project Selection Page project_selection.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10423</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /student/project_selection/project_selection.php of the component Project Selection Page. The manipulation of the argument project_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10422 | SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System overtime_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10422</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/overtime_add.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 17:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10421 | SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System overtime_row.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10421</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/overtime_row.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 17:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10420 | SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System update.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10420</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System 1.0. This affects the function upload of the file /marimar/guest/update.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 15:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10419 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System bloodrequest.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10419</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /bloodrequest.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 14:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10418 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System infoAdd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10418</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /file/infoAdd.php. The manipulation of the argument bg leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10417 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10417</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /file/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10416 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System cancel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10416</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /file/cancel.php. The manipulation of the argument reqid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10415 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System accept.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10415</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /file/accept.php. The manipulation of the argument reqid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 11:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10414 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System edit-brand.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10414</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-brand.php. The manipulation of the argument Brand Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions the parameter "phone_number" to be affected. But this might be a mistake because the textbox field label is "Brand Name".</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10413 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System update.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10413</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function upload of the file /guest/update.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 09:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10412 | Poco-z Guns-Medical File Upload upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10412</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Poco-z Guns-Medical 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /mgr/upload of the component File Upload. The manipulation of the argument picture leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 08:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10411 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System controller.php doCheckout sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10411</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function doCancelRoom/doCancel/doConfirm/doCancel/doCheckin/doCheckout of the file /marimar/admin/mod_room/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 05:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50602 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.4. There is a crash within the XML_ResumeParser function because XML_StopParser can stop/susp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50602</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.4. There is a crash within the XML_ResumeParser function because XML_StopParser can stop/suspend an unstarted parser.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 04:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10410 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System controller.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10410</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /admin/mod_room/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10409 | code-projects Blood Bank Management accept.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10409</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /file/accept.php. The manipulation of the argument reqid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 02:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10408 | code-projects Blood Bank Management abs.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10408</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /abs.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 02:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>