<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 15:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-6611 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6611</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file pda/pad/email/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument EMAIL_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-247246 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 15:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6608 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6608</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file general/notify/manage/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247244. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6609 | osCommerce all-products cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6609</link><description>A vulnerability was found in osCommerce 4. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /b2b-supermarket/catalog/all-products. The manipulation of the argument keywords with the input %27%22%3E%3Cimg%2Fsrc%3D1+onerror%3Dalert%28document.cookie%29%3E leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247245 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6146 | Stored XSS Vulnerability in QualysGuard VM/PC </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6146</link><description>A Qualys web application was found to have a stored XSS vulnerability resulting from the absence of HTML encoding in the presentation of logging information to users. This vulnerability allowed a user with login access to the application to introduce XSS payload via browser details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6245 | Infinite decoding loop through specially crafted payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6245</link><description>The Candid library causes a Denial of Service while 
parsing a specially crafted payload with 'empty' data type. For example,
 if the payload is `record { * ; empty }` and the canister interface expects `record { * }` then the Rust candid decoder treats empty as an extra field required by the type.  The problem with the type empty is that the candid Rust library wrongly categorizes empty as a recoverable error when skipping the field and thus causing an infinite decoding loop.


Canisters using affected versions of candid
 are exposed to denial of service by causing the decoding to run 
indefinitely until the canister traps due to reaching maximum 
instruction limit per execution round. Repeated exposure to the payload 
will result in degraded performance of the canister. Note: Canisters written in Motoko are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49443 | DoraCMS v2.1.8 was discovered to re-use the same code for verification of valid usernames and passwords. This vulnerability allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49443</link><description>DoraCMS v2.1.8 was discovered to re-use the same code for verification of valid usernames and passwords. This vulnerability allows attackers to gain access to the application via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49444 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in DoraCMS v2.1.8 allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML or image fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49444</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in DoraCMS v2.1.8 allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML or image file to the user avatar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6607 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6607</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/wiki/cp/manage/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument TERM_ID_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247243. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49007 | In Netgear Orbi RBR750 firmware before V7.2.6.21, there is a stack-based buffer overflow in /usr/sbin/httpd.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49007</link><description>In Netgear Orbi RBR750 firmware before V7.2.6.21, there is a stack-based buffer overflow in /usr/sbin/httpd.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46157 | File-Manager in MGT CloudPanel 2.0.0 through 2.3.2 allows the lowest privilege user to achieve OS command injection by changing file ownersh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46157</link><description>File-Manager in MGT CloudPanel 2.0.0 through 2.3.2 allows the lowest privilege user to achieve OS command injection by changing file ownership and changing file permissions to 4755.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32460 | Dell PowerEdge BIOS contains an improper privilege management security vulnerability. An unauthenticated local attacker could potentially ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32460</link><description>Dell PowerEdge BIOS contains an improper privilege management security vulnerability. An unauthenticated local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45866 | Bluetooth HID Hosts in BlueZ may permit an unauthenticated Peripheral role HID Device to initiate and establish an encrypted connection, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45866</link><description>Bluetooth HID Hosts in BlueZ may permit an unauthenticated Peripheral role HID Device to initiate and establish an encrypted connection, and accept HID keyboard reports, potentially permitting injection of HID messages when no user interaction has occurred in the Central role to authorize such access. An example affected package is bluez 5.64-0ubuntu1 in Ubuntu 22.04LTS. NOTE: in some cases, a CVE-2020-0556 mitigation would have already addressed this Bluetooth HID Hosts issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26158 | All versions of the package mockjs are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the Util.extend function due to missing check if the attribute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26158</link><description>All versions of the package mockjs are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the Util.extend function due to missing check if the attribute resolves to the object prototype. By adding or modifying attributes of an object prototype, it is possible to create attributes that exist on every object, or replace critical attributes with malicious ones. This can be problematic if the software depends on existence or non-existence of certain attributes, or uses pre-defined attributes of object prototype (such as hasOwnProperty, toString or valueOf).&#13;&#13;User controlled inputs inside the extend() method of the Mock.Handler, Mock.Random, Mock.RE.Handler or Mock.Util, will allow an attacker to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;&#13; Workaround&#13;&#13;By using a denylist of dangerous attributes, this weakness can be eliminated.&#13;&#13;Add the following line in the Util.extend function:&#13;&#13;js&#13;js if (["__proto__", "constructor", "prototype"].includes(name)) continue&#13;&#13;&#13;js&#13;// src/mock/handler.js&#13;Util.extend = function extend() {&#13;        var target = arguments[0] || {},&#13;            i = 1,&#13;            length = arguments.length,&#13;            options, name, src, copy, clone&#13;&#13;        if (length === 1) {&#13;            target = this&#13;            i = 0&#13;        }&#13;&#13;        for (; i &lt; length; i++) {&#13;            options = arguments[i]&#13;            if (!options) continue&#13;&#13;            for (name in options) {&#13;            if (["__proto__", "constructor", "prototype"].includes(name)) continue&#13;                src = target[name]&#13;                copy = options[name]&#13;&#13;                if (target === copy) continue&#13;                if (copy === undefined) continue&#13;&#13;                if (Util.isArray(copy) || Util.isObject(copy)) {&#13;                    if (Util.isArray(copy)) clone = src &amp;&amp; Util.isArray(src) ? src : []&#13;                    if (Util.isObject(copy)) clone = src &amp;&amp; Util.isObject(src) ? src : {}&#13;&#13;                    target[name] = Util.extend(clone, copy)&#13;                } else {&#13;                    target[name] = copy&#13;                }&#13;            }&#13;        }&#13;&#13;        return target&#13;    }</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48928 | Franklin Fueling Systems System Sentinel AnyWare (SSA) version 1.6.24.492 is vulnerable to Open Redirect. The 'path' parameter of the prefs....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48928</link><description>Franklin Fueling Systems System Sentinel AnyWare (SSA) version 1.6.24.492 is vulnerable to Open Redirect. The 'path' parameter of the prefs.asp resource allows an attacker to redirect a victim user to an arbitrary web site using a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48929 | Franklin Fueling Systems System Sentinel AnyWare (SSA) version 1.6.24.492 is vulnerable to Session Fixation. The 'sid' parameter in the grou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48929</link><description>Franklin Fueling Systems System Sentinel AnyWare (SSA) version 1.6.24.492 is vulnerable to Session Fixation. The 'sid' parameter in the group_status.asp resource allows an attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48122 | An issue in microweber v.2.0.1 and fixed in v.2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the HTTP GET method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48122</link><description>An issue in microweber v.2.0.1 and fixed in v.2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the HTTP GET method.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43305 | An issue in studio kent mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43305</link><description>An issue in studio kent mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43742 | An authentication bypass in Zultys MX-SE, MX-SE II, MX-E, MX-Virtual, MX250, and MX30 with firmware versions prior to 17.0.10 patch 17161 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43742</link><description>An authentication bypass in Zultys MX-SE, MX-SE II, MX-E, MX-Virtual, MX250, and MX30 with firmware versions prior to 17.0.10 patch 17161 and 16.04 patch 16109 allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain an administrative session via a protection mechanism failure in the authentication function. In normal operation, the Zultys MX Administrator Windows client connects to port 7505 and attempts authentication, submitting the administrator username and password to the server. Upon authentication failure, the server sends a login failure message prompting the client to disconnect. However, if the client ignores the failure message instead and attempts to continue, the server does not forcibly close the connection and processes all subsequent requests from the client as if authentication had been successful.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43743 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Zultys MX-SE, MX-SE II, MX-E, MX-Virtual, MX250, and MX30 with firmware versions prior to 17.0.10 patch 171...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43743</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Zultys MX-SE, MX-SE II, MX-E, MX-Virtual, MX250, and MX30 with firmware versions prior to 17.0.10 patch 17161 and 16.04 patch 16109 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the backend database via the filter parameter in requests to the /newapi/ endpoint in the Zultys MX web interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43744 | An OS command injection vulnerability in Zultys MX-SE, MX-SE II, MX-E, MX-Virtual, MX250, and MX30 with firmware versions prior to 17.0.10 p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43744</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Zultys MX-SE, MX-SE II, MX-E, MX-Virtual, MX250, and MX30 with firmware versions prior to 17.0.10 patch 17161 and 16.04 patch 16109 allows an administrator to execute arbitrary OS commands via a file name parameter in a patch application function. The Zultys MX Administrator client has a "Patch Manager" section that allows administrators to apply patches to the device. The user supplied filename for the patch file is passed to a shell script without validation. Including bash command substitution characters in a patch file name results in execution of the provided command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6599 | Missing Standardized Error Handling Mechanism in microweber/microweber</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6599</link><description>Missing Standardized Error Handling Mechanism in GitHub repository microweber/microweber prior to 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 01:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5008 | Student Information System v1.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5008</link><description>Student Information System v1.0 is vulnerable to an unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability on the 'regno' parameter of index.php page, allowing an external attacker to dump all the contents of the database contents and bypass the login control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6061 | Phantom DLL Vulnerability in Iconics Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6061</link><description>Multiple components of Iconics SCADA Suite are prone to a Phantom DLL loading vulnerability. This issue arises from the applications improperly searching for and loading dynamic link libraries, potentially allowing an attacker to execute malicious code via a DLL with a matching name in an accessible search path. The affected components are:
  *  MMXFax.exe  *  winfax.dll




  *  MelSim2ComProc.exe
  *  Sim2ComProc.dll




  *  MMXCall_in.exe  *  libdxxmt.dll
  *  libsrlmt.dll</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4122 | Student Information System v1.0 - Insecure File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4122</link><description>Student Information System v1.0 is vulnerable to an Insecure File Upload vulnerability on the 'photo' parameter of my-profile page, allowing an authenticated attacker to obtain Remote Code Execution on the server hosting the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5058 | Improper Input Validation in the processing of user-supplied splash screen during system boot in Phoenix SecureCore™ Technology™ 4 potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5058</link><description>Improper Input Validation in the processing of user-supplied splash screen during system boot in Phoenix SecureCore™ Technology™ 4 potentially allows denial-of-service attacks or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6581 | D-Link DAR-7000 workidajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6581</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20231126 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/inc/workidajax.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247162 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46693 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FormaLMS before 4.0.5 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via title parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46693</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FormaLMS before 4.0.5 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via title parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6579 | osCommerce POST Parameter shopping-cart sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6579</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in osCommerce 4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /b2b-supermarket/shopping-cart of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument estimate[country_id] leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247160. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6580 | D-Link DIR-846 QoS POST deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6580</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-846 FW100A53DBR. This affects an unknown part of the file /HNAP1/ of the component QoS POST Handler. The manipulation of the argument smartqos_express_devices/smartqos_normal_devices leads to deserialization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247161 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6578 | Software AG WebMethods access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6578</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Software AG WebMethods 10.11.x/10.15.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file wm.server/connect/. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. To access a file like /assets/ a popup may request username and password. By just clicking CANCEL you will be redirected to the directory. If you visited /invoke/wm.server/connect, you'll be able to see details like internal IPs, ports, and versions. In some cases if access to /assets/ is refused, you may enter /assets/x as a wrong value, then come back to /assets/ which we will show the requested data. It appears that insufficient access control is depending on referrer header data. VDB-247158 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 21:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35618 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35618</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36880 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36880</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38174 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38174</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6576 | Beijing Baichuo S210 HTTP POST Request uploadfile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6576</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo S210 up to 20231123. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Tool/uploadfile.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247156. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6577 | Beijing Baichuo PatrolFlow 2530Pro mailsendview.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6577</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo PatrolFlow 2530Pro up to 20231126. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /log/mailsendview.php. The manipulation of the argument file with the input /boot/phpConfig/tb_admin.txt leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247157 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6575 | Beijing Baichuo S210 HTTP POST Request repair.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6575</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo S210 up to 20231121. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /Tool/repair.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument txt leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247155. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4486 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in Metasys and Facility Explorer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4486</link><description>Under certain circumstances, invalid authentication credentials could be sent to the login endpoint of Johnson Controls Metasys NAE55, SNE, and SNC engines prior to version 12.0.4 and Facility Explorer F4-SNC engines prior to versions 11.0.6 and 12.0.4 to cause denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49464 | libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function UncompressedImageCodec::get_luma_bits_per_pixel_from_con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49464</link><description>libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function UncompressedImageCodec::get_luma_bits_per_pixel_from_configuration_unci.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49465 | Libde265 v1.0.14 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the derive_spatial_luma_vector_prediction function at mot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49465</link><description>Libde265 v1.0.14 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the derive_spatial_luma_vector_prediction function at motion.cc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49467 | Libde265 v1.0.14 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the derive_combined_bipredictive_merging_candidates funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49467</link><description>Libde265 v1.0.14 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the derive_combined_bipredictive_merging_candidates function at motion.cc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49468 | Libde265 v1.0.14 was discovered to contain a global buffer overflow vulnerability in the read_coding_unit function at slice.cc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49468</link><description>Libde265 v1.0.14 was discovered to contain a global buffer overflow vulnerability in the read_coding_unit function at slice.cc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49460 | libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function UncompressedImageCodec::decode_uncompressed_image.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49460</link><description>libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function UncompressedImageCodec::decode_uncompressed_image.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49462 | libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component /libheif/exif.cc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49462</link><description>libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component /libheif/exif.cc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49463 | libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function find_exif_tag at /libheif/exif.cc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49463</link><description>libheif v1.17.5 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function find_exif_tag at /libheif/exif.cc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6574 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S20 HTTP POST Request updateos.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6574</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S20 up to 20231120 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/updateos.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument 1_file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6333 | Cross-site Scripting in ControlByWeb Relays</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6333</link><description>The affected ControlByWeb Relay products are vulnerable to a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability, which could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary scripts into the endpoint of a web interface that could run malicious javascript code during a user's session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 18:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39909 | Ericsson Network Manager before 23.2 mishandles Access Control and thus unauthenticated low-privilege users can access the NCM application.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39909</link><description>Ericsson Network Manager before 23.2 mishandles Access Control and thus unauthenticated low-privilege users can access the NCM application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 18:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49408 | Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.11 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function set_device_name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49408</link><description>Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.11 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function set_device_name.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41171 | NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 3 of 4).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41171</link><description>NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 3 of 4).</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41172 | NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 4 of 4).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41172</link><description>NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 4 of 4).</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41905 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Reflected Cross-Site scripting (XSS) vulnerability by an authenticated user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41905</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Reflected Cross-Site scripting (XSS) vulnerability by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49409 | Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.11 was discovered to contain a Command Execution vulnerability via the function /goform/telnet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49409</link><description>Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.11 was discovered to contain a Command Execution vulnerability via the function /goform/telnet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49411 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) contains a stack overflow vulnerability via the function formDeleteMeshNode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49411</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) contains a stack overflow vulnerability via the function formDeleteMeshNode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40300 | NETSCOUT nGeniusPULSE 3.8 has a Hardcoded Cryptographic Key.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40300</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusPULSE 3.8 has a Hardcoded Cryptographic Key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40301 | NETSCOUT nGeniusPULSE 3.8 has a Command Injection Vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40301</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusPULSE 3.8 has a Command Injection Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40302 | NETSCOUT nGeniusPULSE 3.8 has Weak File Permissions Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40302</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusPULSE 3.8 has Weak File Permissions Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41168 | NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 1 of 4).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41168</link><description>NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 1 of 4).</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41169 | NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 2 of 4).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41169</link><description>NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Stored Cross-Site scripting vulnerability (issue 2 of 4).</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41170 | NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Reflected Cross-Site scripting vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41170</link><description>NetScout nGeniusONE 6.3.4 build 2298 allows a Reflected Cross-Site scripting vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49404 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formAdvancedSetListSet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49404</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formAdvancedSetListSet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49405 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function UploadCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49405</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function UploadCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49406 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a Command Execution vulnerability via the function /goform/telnet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49406</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a Command Execution vulnerability via the function /goform/telnet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47440 | Gladys Assistant v4.27.0 and prior is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The patch of CVE-2023-43256 was found to be incomplete, allowing au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47440</link><description>Gladys Assistant v4.27.0 and prior is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The patch of CVE-2023-43256 was found to be incomplete, allowing authenticated attackers to extract sensitive files in the host machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48958 | gpac 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master contains memory leaks in gf_mpd_resolve_url media_tools/mpd.c:4589.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48958</link><description>gpac 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master contains memory leaks in gf_mpd_resolve_url media_tools/mpd.c:4589.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33411 | A web server in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) baseboard management controller (BMC) implementation on Supermicro X11 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33411</link><description>A web server in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) baseboard management controller (BMC) implementation on Supermicro X11 and M11 based devices, with firmware versions up to 3.17.02, allows remote unauthenticated users to perform directory traversal, potentially disclosing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33412 | The web interface in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) baseboard management controller (BMC) implementation on Supermicro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33412</link><description>The web interface in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) baseboard management controller (BMC) implementation on Supermicro X11 and M11 based devices, with firmware versions before 3.17.02, allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request targeting vulnerable cgi endpoints.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33413 | The configuration functionality in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) baseboard management controller (BMC) implementation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33413</link><description>The configuration functionality in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) baseboard management controller (BMC) implementation on Supermicro X11 and M11 based devices, with firmware versions through 3.17.02, allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46871 | GPAC version 2.3-DEV-rev602-ged8424300-master in MP4Box contains a memory leak in NewSFDouble scenegraph/vrml_tools.c:300. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46871</link><description>GPAC version 2.3-DEV-rev602-ged8424300-master in MP4Box contains a memory leak in NewSFDouble scenegraph/vrml_tools.c:300. This vulnerability may lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49410 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function via the function set_wan_status.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49410</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function via the function set_wan_status.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49999 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function setUmountUSBPartition.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49999</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function setUmountUSBPartition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50000 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formResetMeshNode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50000</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formResetMeshNode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50001 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formUpgradeMeshOnline.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50001</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formUpgradeMeshOnline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49402 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function localMsg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49402</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function localMsg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49403 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function setFixTools.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49403</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function setFixTools.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50002 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formRebootMeshNode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50002</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.12(4843) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formRebootMeshNode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49431 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'mac' parameter at /goform/SetOnlineDevName.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49431</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'mac' parameter at /goform/SetOnlineDevName.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49432 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'deviceList' parameter at /goform/setMacFilterCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49432</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'deviceList' parameter at /goform/setMacFilterCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49433 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49433</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49434 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetNetControlList.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49434</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetNetControlList.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49492 | DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the imgstick parameter at selectimages....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49492</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the imgstick parameter at selectimages.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49493 | DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the v parameter at selectimages.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49493</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the v parameter at selectimages.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49967 | Typecho v1.2.1 was discovered to be vulnerable to an XML Quadratic Blowup attack via the component /index.php/action/xmlrpc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49967</link><description>Typecho v1.2.1 was discovered to be vulnerable to an XML Quadratic Blowup attack via the component /index.php/action/xmlrpc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6588 | Offline mode is always enabled, even if permission disallows it, in 
Devolutions Server data source in Devolutions Workspace 2023.3.2.0 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6588</link><description>Offline mode is always enabled, even if permission disallows it, in 
Devolutions Server data source in Devolutions Workspace 2023.3.2.0 and 
earlier. This allows an attacker with access to the Workspace 
application to access credentials when offline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49429 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a SQL command injection vulnerability in the 'setDeviceInfo' feature through the 'mac' para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49429</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a SQL command injection vulnerability in the 'setDeviceInfo' feature through the 'mac' parameter at /goform/setModules.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49430 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49430</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been found to contain a stack overflow vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49435 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 is vulnerable to command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49435</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 is vulnerable to command injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49436 | Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetNetControlList...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49436</link><description>Tenda AX9 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetNetControlList.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49425 | Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the deviceList parameter at /goform/setMacFilterCfg .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49425</link><description>Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the deviceList parameter at /goform/setMacFilterCfg .</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49426 | Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49426</link><description>Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49428 | Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'mac' parameter at /goform/SetOnlineDevName.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49428</link><description>Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'mac' parameter at /goform/SetOnlineDevName.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49437 | Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetNetControlLis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49437</link><description>Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 has been discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the 'list' parameter at /goform/SetNetControlList.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39171 | SENEC Storage Box V1,V2 and V3 accidentially expose a management interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39171</link><description>SENEC Storage Box V1,V2 and V3 accidentially expose a management UI accessible with publicly known admin credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39169 | SENEC: Storage Box V1,V2 and V3 using default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39169</link><description>The affected devices use publicly available default credentials with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39167 | SENEC: Storage Box V1,V2 and V3 affected by improper access control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39167</link><description>In SENEC Storage Box V1,V2 and V3 an unauthenticated remote attacker can obtain the devices' logfiles that contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39172 | SENEC: Storage Box V1,V2 and V3 transmitting sensitive data unencrypted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39172</link><description>The affected devices transmit sensitive information unencrypted allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to capture and modify network traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49424 | Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49424</link><description>Tenda AX12 V22.03.01.46 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46974 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Best Courier Management System v.1.000 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46974</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Best Courier Management System v.1.000 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the page parameter in the URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 13:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49957 | An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core before 1.3.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. It permits multiple t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49957</link><description>An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core before 1.3.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. It permits multiple transactions with the same connectorId and idTag, contrary to the expected ConcurrentTx status. This could result in critical transaction management and billing errors. NOTE: the vendor's perspective is "Imagine you've got two cars in your family and want to charge both in parallel on the same account/token? Why should that be rejected?"</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49958 | An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core through 1.2.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. The server processes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49958</link><description>An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core through 1.2.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. The server processes mishandle StartTransaction messages containing additional, arbitrary properties, or duplicate properties. The last occurrence of a duplicate property is accepted. This could be exploited to alter transaction records or impact system integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 13:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49955 | An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core before 1.2.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. It does not validate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49955</link><description>An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core before 1.2.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. It does not validate the length of the chargePointVendor field in a BootNotification message, potentially leading to server instability and a denial of service when processing excessively large inputs. NOTE: the vendor's perspective is "OCPP.Core is intended for use in a protected environment/network."</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49956 | An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core before 1.3.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. A StopTransaction mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49956</link><description>An issue was discovered in Dalmann OCPP.Core before 1.3.0 for OCPP (Open Charge Point Protocol) for electric vehicles. A StopTransaction message with any random transactionId terminates active transactions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45762 | WordPress Responsive Column Widgets Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45762</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Michael Uno (miunosoft) Responsive Column Widgets.This issue affects Responsive Column Widgets: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47548 | WordPress Integrate Google Drive Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47548</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in SoftLab Integrate Google Drive – Browse, Upload, Download, Embed, Play, Share, Gallery, and Manage Your Google Drive Files Into Your WordPress Site.This issue affects Integrate Google Drive – Browse, Upload, Download, Embed, Play, Share, Gallery, and Manage Your Google Drive Files Into Your WordPress Site: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47779 | WordPress Integration for Contact Form 7 and Constant Contact Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47779</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in CRM Perks. Integration for Constant Contact and Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Ninja Forms.This issue affects Integration for Constant Contact and Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Ninja Forms: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48325 | WordPress Landing Page Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1.5 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48325</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in PluginOps Landing Page Builder – Lead Page – Optin Page – Squeeze Page – WordPress Landing Pages.This issue affects Landing Page Builder – Lead Page – Optin Page – Squeeze Page – WordPress Landing Pages: from n/a through 1.5.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35039 | WordPress Password Reset with Code for WordPress REST API Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.15 is vulnerable to Broken Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35039</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Be Devious Web Development Password Reset with Code for WordPress REST API allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Password Reset with Code for WordPress REST API: from n/a through 0.0.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35909 | WordPress Ninja Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.25 is vulnerable to Denial of Service Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35909</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Saturday Drive Ninja Forms Contact Form – The Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress leading to DoS.This issue affects Ninja Forms Contact Form – The Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress: from n/a through 3.6.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45362 | WordPress Paytm Payment Gateway Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45362</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Paytm Paytm Payment Gateway.This issue affects Paytm Payment Gateway: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41804 | WordPress Starter Templates Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41804</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates.This issue affects Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46641 | WordPress 12 Step Meeting List Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.24 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46641</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Code for Recovery 12 Step Meeting List.This issue affects 12 Step Meeting List: from n/a through 3.14.24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49746 | WordPress SpeedyCache Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49746</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Softaculous Team SpeedyCache – Cache, Optimization, Performance.This issue affects SpeedyCache – Cache, Optimization, Performance: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 10:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50164 | Apache Struts: File upload component had a directory traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50164</link><description>An attacker can manipulate file upload params to enable paths traversal and under some circumstances this can lead to uploading a malicious file which can be used to perform Remote Code Execution.
Users are recommended to upgrade to versions Struts 2.5.33 or Struts 6.3.0.2 or greater to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48861 | DLL hijacking vulnerability in TTplayer version 7.0.2, allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code via urlmon.d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48861</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerability in TTplayer version 7.0.2, allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code via urlmon.dll.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48860 | TOTOLINK N300RT version 3.2.4-B20180730.0906 has a post-authentication RCE due to incorrect access control, allows attackers can bypass fron...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48860</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT version 3.2.4-B20180730.0906 has a post-authentication RCE due to incorrect access control, allows attackers can bypass front-end security restrictions and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48841 | Appointment Scheduler 3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection via a Language &gt; Labels &gt; Export action.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48841</link><description>Appointment Scheduler 3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection via a Language &gt; Labels &gt; Export action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43298 | An issue in SCOL Members Card mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43298</link><description>An issue in SCOL Members Card mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43299 | An issue in DA BUTCHERS mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43299</link><description>An issue in DA BUTCHERS mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48838 | Appointment Scheduler 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via the SMS API Key or Default Country Code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48838</link><description>Appointment Scheduler 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via the SMS API Key or Default Country Code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48839 | Appointment Scheduler 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48839</link><description>Appointment Scheduler 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, calendar_id, title, country name, or customer_name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48840 | A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAjaxSend in Appointment Scheduler 3.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48840</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAjaxSend in Appointment Scheduler 3.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43304 | An issue in PARK DANDAN mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43304</link><description>An issue in PARK DANDAN mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48836 | Car Rental Script 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_countr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48836</link><description>Car Rental Script 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, calendar_id, title, country name, or customer_name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48837 | Car Rental Script 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via SMS API Key or Default Country Code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48837</link><description>Car Rental Script 3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via SMS API Key or Default Country Code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43303 | An issue in craftbeer bar canvas mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43303</link><description>An issue in craftbeer bar canvas mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48833 | A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAJaxSend in Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48833</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAJaxSend in Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48834 | A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAjaxSend in Car Rental v3.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48834</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAjaxSend in Car Rental v3.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48835 | Car Rental Script v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection via a Language &gt; Labels &gt; Export action.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48835</link><description>Car Rental Script v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection via a Language &gt; Labels &gt; Export action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43302 | An issue in sanTas mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43302</link><description>An issue in sanTas mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48828 | Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48828</link><description>Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, calendar_id, title, country name, or customer_name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48830 | Shuttle Booking Software 2.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection in the Languages section via an export.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48830</link><description>Shuttle Booking Software 2.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection in the Languages section via an export.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48831 | A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAJaxSend in Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48831</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in pjActionAJaxSend in Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 allows attackers to cause resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43300 | An issue in urban_project mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43300</link><description>An issue in urban_project mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43301 | An issue in DARTS SHOP MAXIM mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43301</link><description>An issue in DARTS SHOP MAXIM mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48826 | Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection via the unique ID field of the Reservations List.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48826</link><description>Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection via the unique ID field of the Reservations List.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48827 | Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48827</link><description>Time Slots Booking Calendar 4.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, calendar_id, title, country name, or customer_name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48823 | A Blind SQL injection issue in ajax.php in GaatiTrack Courier Management System 1.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject a payload v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48823</link><description>A Blind SQL injection issue in ajax.php in GaatiTrack Courier Management System 1.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject a payload via the email parameter during login.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48824 | BoidCMS 2.0.1 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the title, subtitle, footer, or keywords parameter in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48824</link><description>BoidCMS 2.0.1 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issues via the title, subtitle, footer, or keywords parameter in a page=create action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48825 | Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via SMS API Key or Default Country Code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48825</link><description>Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection issues via SMS API Key or Default Country Code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49225 | A cross-site-scripting vulnerability exists in Ruckus Access Point products (ZoneDirector, SmartZone, and AP Solo). If this vulnerability is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49225</link><description>A cross-site-scripting vulnerability exists in Ruckus Access Point products (ZoneDirector, SmartZone, and AP Solo). If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is logging in the product. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the information provided by the vendor listed under [References] section or the list under [Product Status] section.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48205 | Jorani Leave Management System 1.0.2 allows a remote attacker to spoof a Host header associated with password reset emails.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48205</link><description>Jorani Leave Management System 1.0.2 allows a remote attacker to spoof a Host header associated with password reset emails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48206 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in GaatiTrack Courier Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to inject JavaScript via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48206</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in GaatiTrack Courier Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to inject JavaScript via the page parameter to login.php or header.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48207 | Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 allows CSV injection via the unique ID field in the Reservations list component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48207</link><description>Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 allows CSV injection via the unique ID field in the Reservations list component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48208 | A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 allows an attacker to inject JavaScript via the name, plugin_sms_a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48208</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Availability Booking Calendar 5.0 allows an attacker to inject JavaScript via the name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, uuid, title, or country name parameter to index.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46916 | Maxima Max Pro Power 1.0 486A devices allow BLE traffic replay. An attacker can use GATT characteristic handle 0x0012 to perform potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46916</link><description>Maxima Max Pro Power 1.0 486A devices allow BLE traffic replay. An attacker can use GATT characteristic handle 0x0012 to perform potentially disruptive actions such as starting a Heart Rate monitor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48172 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Shuttle Booking Software 2.0 allows a remote attacker to inject JavaScript via the name, descr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48172</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Shuttle Booking Software 2.0 allows a remote attacker to inject JavaScript via the name, description, title, or address parameter to index.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46857 | Squidex before 7.9.0 allows XSS via an SVG document to the Upload Assets feature. This occurs because there is an incomplete blacklist in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46857</link><description>Squidex before 7.9.0 allows XSS via an SVG document to the Upload Assets feature. This occurs because there is an incomplete blacklist in the SVG inspection, allowing JavaScript in the SRC attribute of an IFRAME element. An authenticated attack with assets.create permission is required for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46307 | An issue was discovered in server.js in etcd-browser 87ae63d75260. By supplying a /../../../ Directory Traversal input to the URL's GET requ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46307</link><description>An issue was discovered in server.js in etcd-browser 87ae63d75260. By supplying a /../../../ Directory Traversal input to the URL's GET request while connecting to the remote server port specified during setup, an attacker can retrieve local operating system files from the remote system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43102 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 10.0.4. An XSS issue can be exploited to access the mailbox of an authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43102</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 10.0.4. An XSS issue can be exploited to access the mailbox of an authenticated user. This is also fixed in 8.8.15 Patch 43 and 9.0.0 Patch 36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43103 | An XSS issue was discovered in a web endpoint in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 10.0.4 via an unsanitized parameter. This is also fixed i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43103</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in a web endpoint in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 10.0.4 via an unsanitized parameter. This is also fixed in 8.8.15 Patch 43 and 9.0.0 Patch 36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41106 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 10.0.3. An attacker can gain access to a Zimbra account. This is also fixed in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41106</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 10.0.3. An attacker can gain access to a Zimbra account. This is also fixed in 9.0.0 Patch 35 and 8.8.15 Patch 42.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41913 | strongSwan before 5.9.12 has a buffer overflow and possible unauthenticated remote code execution via a DH public value that exceeds the int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41913</link><description>strongSwan before 5.9.12 has a buffer overflow and possible unauthenticated remote code execution via a DH public value that exceeds the internal buffer in charon-tkm's DH proxy. The earliest affected version is 5.3.0. An attack can occur via a crafted IKE_SA_INIT message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6568 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6568</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository mlflow/mlflow prior to 2.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28017 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28017</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting attack where an attacker may leverage this issue to execute arbitrary script code in the browser of an unsuspecting user after visiting the vulnerable URL which leads to executing malicious script code. This may let the attacker steal cookie-based authentication credentials and comprise a user's account then launch other attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 04:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40238 | A LogoFAIL issue was discovered in BmpDecoderDxe in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.2 before 05.28.47, 5.3 before 05.37.47, 5.4 before 05.45....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40238</link><description>A LogoFAIL issue was discovered in BmpDecoderDxe in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.2 before 05.28.47, 5.3 before 05.37.47, 5.4 before 05.45.47, 5.5 before 05.53.47, and 5.6 before 05.60.47 for certain Lenovo devices. Image parsing of crafted BMP logo files can copy data to a specific address during the DXE phase of UEFI execution. This occurs because of an integer signedness error involving PixelHeight and PixelWidth during RLE4/RLE8 compression.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5710 | The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_constants...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5710</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_constants() function hooked via an AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive information such as database credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5711 | The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_php_info(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5711</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_php_info() function hooked via an AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive information provided by PHP info.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5712 | The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_global_va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5712</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_global_value() function hooked via an AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive global value information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5713 | The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_option_va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5713</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_option_value() function hooked via an AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve potentially sensitive option values, and deserialize the content of those values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5714 | The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_db_specs(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5714</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the sd_db_specs() function hooked via an AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve data key specs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5761 | The Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'url' parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5761</link><description>The Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'url' parameter in versions 1.4.0 to 1.4.6.1 (free) and versions 1.4.0 to 1.5.0 (pro) due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46218 | This flaw allows a malicious HTTP server to set "super cookies" in curl that
are then passed back to more origins than what is otherwise all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46218</link><description>This flaw allows a malicious HTTP server to set "super cookies" in curl that
are then passed back to more origins than what is otherwise allowed or
possible. This allows a site to set cookies that then would get sent to
different and unrelated sites and domains.

It could do this by exploiting a mixed case flaw in curl's function that
verifies a given cookie domain against the Public Suffix List (PSL). For
example a cookie could be set with `domain=co.UK` when the URL used a lower
case hostname `curl.co.uk`, even though `co.uk` is listed as a PSL domain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 01:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6566 | Business Logic Errors in microweber/microweber</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6566</link><description>Business Logic Errors in GitHub repository microweber/microweber prior to 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46353 | In the module "Product Tag Icons Pro" (ticons) before 1.8.4 from MyPresta.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46353</link><description>In the module "Product Tag Icons Pro" (ticons) before 1.8.4 from MyPresta.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method TiconProduct::getTiconByProductAndTicon() has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46354 | In the module "Orders (CSV, Excel) Export PRO" (ordersexport) &lt; 5.2.0 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46354</link><description>In the module "Orders (CSV, Excel) Export PRO" (ordersexport) &lt; 5.2.0 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal information without restriction. Due to a lack of permissions control, a guest can access exports from the module which can lead to a leak of personal information from ps_customer/ps_address tables such as name / surname / email / phone number / full postal address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46751 | An issue was discovered in the function gdev_prn_open_printer_seekable() in Artifex Ghostscript through 10.02.0 allows remote attackers to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46751</link><description>An issue was discovered in the function gdev_prn_open_printer_seekable() in Artifex Ghostscript through 10.02.0 allows remote attackers to crash the application via a dangling pointer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48123 | An issue in Netgate pfSense Plus v.23.05.1 and before and pfSense CE v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48123</link><description>An issue in Netgate pfSense Plus v.23.05.1 and before and pfSense CE v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the packet_capture.php file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49096 | Argument Injection in FFmpeg codec parameters in Jellyfin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49096</link><description>Jellyfin is a Free Software Media System for managing and streaming media. In affected versions there is an argument injection in the VideosController, specifically the `/Videos/&lt;itemId&gt;/stream` and `/Videos/&lt;itemId&gt;/stream.&lt;container&gt;` endpoints which are present in the current Jellyfin version. Additional endpoints in the AudioController might also be vulnerable, as they differ only slightly in execution. Those endpoints are reachable by an unauthenticated user. In order to exploit this vulnerability an unauthenticated attacker has to guess an itemId, which is a completely random GUID. It’s a very unlikely case even for a large media database with lots of items. Without an additional information leak, this vulnerability shouldn’t be directly exploitable, even if the instance is reachable from the Internet. There are a lot of query parameters that get accepted by the method. At least two of those, videoCodec and audioCodec are vulnerable to the argument injection. The values can be traced through a lot of code and might be changed in the process. However, the fallback is to always use them as-is, which means we can inject our own arguments. Those arguments land in the command line of FFmpeg. Because UseShellExecute is always set to false, we can’t simply terminate the FFmpeg command and execute our own. It should only be possible to add additional arguments to FFmpeg, which is powerful enough as it stands. There is probably a way of overwriting an arbitrary file with malicious content. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 10.8.13. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 19:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6393 | Quarkus: potential invalid reuse of context when @cacheresult on a uni is used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6393</link><description>A flaw was found in the Quarkus Cache Runtime. When request processing utilizes a Uni cached using @CacheResult and the cached Uni reuses the initial "completion" context, the processing switches to the cached Uni instead of the request context. This is a problem if the cached Uni context contains sensitive information, and could allow a malicious user to benefit from a POST request returning the response that is meant for another user, gaining access to sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39326 | Denial of service via chunk extensions in net/http</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39326</link><description>A malicious HTTP sender can use chunk extensions to cause a receiver reading from a request or response body to read many more bytes from the network than are in the body. A malicious HTTP client can further exploit this to cause a server to automatically read a large amount of data (up to about 1GiB) when a handler fails to read the entire body of a request. Chunk extensions are a little-used HTTP feature which permit including additional metadata in a request or response body sent using the chunked encoding. The net/http chunked encoding reader discards this metadata. A sender can exploit this by inserting a large metadata segment with each byte transferred. The chunk reader now produces an error if the ratio of real body to encoded bytes grows too small.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45285 | Command &amp;#x27;go get&amp;#x27; may unexpectedly fallback to insecure git in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45285</link><description>Using go get to fetch a module with the ".git" suffix may unexpectedly fallback to the insecure "git://" protocol if the module is unavailable via the secure "https://" and "git+ssh://" protocols, even if GOINSECURE is not set for said module. This only affects users who are not using the module proxy and are fetching modules directly (i.e. GOPROXY=off).</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36655 | The login REST API in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 (when LDAP or Active Directory is used as the users store) allows a remote blocked user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36655</link><description>The login REST API in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 (when LDAP or Active Directory is used as the users store) allows a remote blocked user to login and obtain an authentication token by specifying a username with different uppercase/lowercase character combination.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39538 | Failure when uploading a Logo image file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39538</link><description>AMI AptioV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where a User may cause an unrestricted upload of a BMP Logo file with dangerous type by Local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of Confidentiality, Integrity, and/or Availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39539 | Failure when uploading a Logo image file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39539</link><description>AMI AptioV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where a User may cause an unrestricted upload of a PNG Logo file with dangerous type by Local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of Confidentiality, Integrity, and/or Availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48859 | TOTOLINK A3002RU version 2.0.0-B20190902.1958 has a post-authentication RCE due to incorrect access control, allows attackers to bypass fron...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48859</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002RU version 2.0.0-B20190902.1958 has a post-authentication RCE due to incorrect access control, allows attackers to bypass front-end security restrictions and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6288 | Code injection in Remote Desktop Manager 2023.3.9.3 and earlier on macOS allows an attacker to execute code via the DYLIB_INSERT_LIBRARIES e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6288</link><description>Code injection in Remote Desktop Manager 2023.3.9.3 and earlier on macOS allows an attacker to execute code via the DYLIB_INSERT_LIBRARIES environment variable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32268 | Administrator equivalent Filr user can access proxy administrator credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32268</link><description>Exposure of Proxy Administrator Credentials

An authenticated administrator equivalent Filr user can access the credentials of proxy administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49240 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in the launcher module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49240</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in the launcher module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6273 | Permission management vulnerability in the module for disabling Sound Booster. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause featu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6273</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the module for disabling Sound Booster. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49239 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in the card management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49239</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in the card management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49244 | Permission management vulnerability in the multi-user module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49244</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the multi-user module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49245 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in the Huawei Share module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49245</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in the Huawei Share module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49246 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in the card management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49246</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in the card management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49243 | Vulnerability of unauthorized access to email attachments in the email module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49243</link><description>Vulnerability of unauthorized access to email attachments in the email module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49241 | API permission control vulnerability in the network management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49241</link><description>API permission control vulnerability in the network management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49242 | Free broadcast vulnerability in the running management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49242</link><description>Free broadcast vulnerability in the running management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34439 | Pleasanter 1.3.47.0 and earlier contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34439</link><description>Pleasanter 1.3.47.0 and earlier contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44113 | Vulnerability of missing permission verification for APIs in the Designed for Reliability (DFR) module. Successful exploitation of this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44113</link><description>Vulnerability of missing permission verification for APIs in the Designed for Reliability (DFR) module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45210 | Pleasanter 1.3.47.0 and earlier contains an improper access control vulnerability, which may allow a remote authenticated attacker to view t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45210</link><description>Pleasanter 1.3.47.0 and earlier contains an improper access control vulnerability, which may allow a remote authenticated attacker to view the temporary files uploaded by other users who are not permitted to access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46688 | Open redirect vulnerability in Pleasanter 1.3.47.0 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46688</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in Pleasanter 1.3.47.0 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arbitrary web sites via a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44099 | Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause WLAN interruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44099</link><description>Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause WLAN interruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46773 | Permission management vulnerability in the PMS module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46773</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the PMS module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49247 | Permission verification vulnerability in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49247</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49248 | Vulnerability of unauthorized file access in the Settings app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49248</link><description>Vulnerability of unauthorized file access in the Settings app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6514 | The Bluetooth module of some Huawei Smart Screen products has an identity authentication bypass vulnerability. Successful exploitation of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6514</link><description>The Bluetooth module of some Huawei Smart Screen products has an identity authentication bypass vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow attackers to access restricted functions. 

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow attackers to access restricted functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6458 | Client side path traversal due to lack of route parameters validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6458</link><description>Mattermost webapp fails to validate route parameters in/&lt;TEAM_NAME&gt;/channels/&lt;CHANNEL_NAME&gt; allowing an attacker to perform a client-side path traversal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6459 | Public endpoint /metrics of Calls plugin reveals channel IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6459</link><description>Mattermost is grouping calls in the /metrics endpoint by id and reports that id in the response. Since this id is the channelID, the public /metrics endpoint is revealing channelIDs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48849 | Ruijie EG Series Routers version EG_3.0(1)B11P216 and before allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely execute arbitrary code due to inco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48849</link><description>Ruijie EG Series Routers version EG_3.0(1)B11P216 and before allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely execute arbitrary code due to incorrect filtering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49897 | An OS command injection vulnerability exists in AE1021PE firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier and AE1021 firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier. I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49897</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in AE1021PE firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier and AE1021 firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by an attacker who can log in to the product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2861 | Qemu: 9pfs: improper access control on special files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2861</link><description>A flaw was found in the 9p passthrough filesystem (9pfs) implementation in QEMU. The 9pfs server did not prohibit opening special files on the host side, potentially allowing a malicious client to escape from the exported 9p tree by creating and opening a device file in the shared folder.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22522 | This Template Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker, including one with anonymous access, to inject unsafe user input int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22522</link><description>This Template Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker, including one with anonymous access, to inject unsafe user input into a Confluence page. Using this approach, an attacker is able to achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) on an affected instance. Publicly accessible Confluence Data Center and Server versions as listed below are at risk and require immediate attention. See the advisory for additional details

Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22523 | This vulnerability, if exploited, allows an attacker to perform privileged RCE (Remote Code Execution) on machines with the Assets Discovery...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22523</link><description>This vulnerability, if exploited, allows an attacker to perform privileged RCE (Remote Code Execution) on machines with the Assets Discovery agent installed. The vulnerability exists between the Assets Discovery application (formerly known as Insight Discovery) and the Assets Discovery agent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22524 | Certain versions of the Atlassian Companion App for MacOS were affected by a remote code execution vulnerability. An attacker could utilize ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22524</link><description>Certain versions of the Atlassian Companion App for MacOS were affected by a remote code execution vulnerability. An attacker could utilize WebSockets to bypass Atlassian Companion’s blocklist and MacOS Gatekeeper to allow execution of code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26154 | Versions of the package pubnub before 7.4.0; all versions of the package com.pubnub:pubnub; versions of the package pubnub before 6.19.0; al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26154</link><description>Versions of the package pubnub before 7.4.0; all versions of the package com.pubnub:pubnub; versions of the package pubnub before 6.19.0; all versions of the package github.com/pubnub/go; versions of the package github.com/pubnub/go/v7 before 7.2.0; versions of the package pubnub before 7.3.0; versions of the package pubnub/pubnub before 6.1.0; versions of the package pubnub before 5.3.0; versions of the package pubnub before 0.4.0; versions of the package pubnub/c-core before 4.5.0; versions of the package com.pubnub:pubnub-kotlin before 7.7.0; versions of the package pubnub/swift before 6.2.0; versions of the package pubnub before 5.2.0; versions of the package pubnub before 4.3.0 are vulnerable to Insufficient Entropy via the getKey function, due to inefficient implementation of the AES-256-CBC cryptographic algorithm. The provided encrypt function is less secure when hex encoding and trimming are applied, leaving half of the bits in the key always the same for every encoded message or file.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs to invest resources in preparing the attack and brute-force the encryption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6527 | The Email Subscription Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP_REFERER header in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6527</link><description>The Email Subscription Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP_REFERER header in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41268 | Possible stack overflow due to insufficient input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41268</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Escargot allows stack overflow and segmentation fault. This issue affects Escargot: from 3.0.0 through 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40053 | HTML injection Vulnerability in Serv-U 15.4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40053</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Serv-U 15.4 that allows an authenticated actor to insert content on the file share function feature of Serv-U, which could be used maliciously.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27795 | License forgery in Brocade Fabric OS (FOS) hardware platforms running any version of Brocade Fabric OS software, </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27795</link><description>Brocade Fabric OS (FOS) hardware 
platforms running any version of Brocade Fabric OS software, which 
supports the license string format; contain cryptographic 
issues that could allow for the installation of forged or fraudulent 
license keys. This would allow attackers or a malicious party to forge a
 counterfeit license key that the Brocade Fabric OS platform would 
authenticate and activate as if it were a legitimate license key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48940 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /admin.php of DaiCuo v2.5.15 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48940</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /admin.php of DaiCuo v2.5.15 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6508 | Use after free in Media Stream in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6508</link><description>Use after free in Media Stream in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6509 | Use after free in Side Panel Search in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6509</link><description>Use after free in Side Panel Search in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI interaction to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI interaction. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6510 | Use after free in Media Capture in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6510</link><description>Use after free in Media Capture in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI interaction to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI interaction. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6511 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Autofill restrictions v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6511</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Autofill restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6512 | Inappropriate implementation in Web Browser UI in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially spoof the co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6512</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Web Browser UI in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially spoof the contents of an iframe dialog context menu via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28875 | A Stored XSS issue in shared files download terms in Filerun Update 20220202 allows attackers to inject JavaScript code that is executed whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28875</link><description>A Stored XSS issue in shared files download terms in Filerun Update 20220202 allows attackers to inject JavaScript code that is executed when a user follows the crafted share link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28876 | A Broken Access Control issue in comments to uploaded files in Filerun through Update 20220202 allows attackers to delete comments on files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28876</link><description>A Broken Access Control issue in comments to uploaded files in Filerun through Update 20220202 allows attackers to delete comments on files uploaded by other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48930 | xinhu xinhuoa 2.2.1 contains a File upload vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48930</link><description>xinhu xinhuoa 2.2.1 contains a File upload vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>