<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:56:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-27418 | WordPress Side Menu Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27418</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Side Menu Lite – add sticky fixed buttons plugin &lt;= 4.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27623 | WordPress WP Page Numbers Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27623</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jens Törnell WP Page Numbers plugin &lt;= 0.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27632 | WordPress Daily Prayer Time Plugin &amp;lt;= 2023.03.08 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27632</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mmrs151 Daily Prayer Time plugin &lt;= 2023.03.08 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27611 | WordPress Reusable Blocks Extended Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27611</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in audrasjb Reusable Blocks Extended plugin &lt;= 0.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28134 | Local Privliege Escalation in Check Point Endpoint Security Remediation Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28134</link><description>Local attacker can escalate privileges on affected installations of Check Point Harmony Endpoint/ZoneAlarm Extreme Security. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28167 | WordPress CF7 Invisible reCAPTCHA Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28167</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Vsourz Digital CF7 Invisible reCAPTCHA plugin &lt;= 1.3.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28172 | WordPress WP Google Map Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28172</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flippercode WordPress Plugin for Google Maps – WP MAPS (formerly WP Google Map Plugin) plugin &lt;= 4.4.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28173 | WordPress Google XML Sitemap for Images Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28173</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Amit Agarwal Google XML Sitemap for Images plugin &lt;= 2.1.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28419 | WordPress Force First and Last Name as Display Name Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28419</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Stranger Studios Force First and Last Name as Display Name plugin &lt;= 1.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28420 | WordPress Custom Options Plus Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28420</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Leo Caseiro Custom Options Plus plugin &lt;= 1.8.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28495 | WordPress WP Shortcode by MyThemeShop Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.16 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28495</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MyThemeShop WP Shortcode by MyThemeShop plugin &lt;= 1.4.16 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28497 | WordPress Slideshow Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28497</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tribulant Slideshow Gallery LITE plugin &lt;= 1.7.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28498 | WordPress Hotel Booking Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28498</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MotoPress Hotel Booking Lite plugin &lt;= 4.6.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28618 | WordPress Enhanced Plugin Admin Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28618</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marios Alexandrou Enhanced Plugin Admin plugin &lt;= 1.16 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28694 | WordPress Wbcom Designs – BuddyPress Activity Social Share Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28694</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wbcom Designs Wbcom Designs – BuddyPress Activity Social Share plugin &lt;= 3.5.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28696 | WordPress I Recommend This Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28696</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Harish Chouhan, Themeist I Recommend Tplugin &lt;= 3.9.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28930 | WordPress Mobile Banner Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28930</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Robin Phillips Mobile Banner plugin &lt;= 1.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28987 | WordPress Wp Ultimate Review Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28987</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wpmet Wp Ultimate Review plugin &lt;= 2.0.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29238 | WordPress Whydonate – FREE Donate button Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.12.15 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29238</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Whydonate Whydonate – FREE Donate button – Crowdfunding – Fundraising plugin &lt;= 3.12.15 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29425 | WordPress ShiftController Employee Shift Scheduling Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.23 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29425</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in plainware.Com ShiftController Employee Shift Scheduling plugin &lt;= 4.9.23 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42781 | Apache Airflow: Permission verification bypass allows viewing dagruns of other dags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42781</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.7.3, has a vulnerability that allows an authorized user who has access to read specific DAGs only, to read information about task instances in other DAGs.  This is a different issue than CVE-2023-42663 but leading to similar outcome.
Users of Apache Airflow are advised to upgrade to version 2.7.3 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47037 | Apache Airflow missing fix for CVE-2023-40611 in 2.7.1 (DAG run broken access)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47037</link><description>We failed to apply CVE-2023-40611 in 2.7.1 and this vulnerability was marked as fixed then. 

Apache Airflow, versions before 2.7.3, is affected by a vulnerability that allows authenticated and DAG-view authorized Users to modify some DAG run detail values when submitting notes. This could have them alter details such as configuration parameters, start date, etc. 

Users should upgrade to version 2.7.3 or later which has removed the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6084 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6084</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file general/vehicle/checkup/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument VU_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-244994 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47390 | Headscale through 0.22.3 writes bearer tokens to info-level logs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47390</link><description>Headscale through 0.22.3 writes bearer tokens to info-level logs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 17:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43057 | IBM QRadar SIEM cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43057</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  267484.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 15:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5959 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S85F Management Platform login.php password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5959</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S85F Management Platform V31R02B10-01. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument txt_newpwd leads to weak password recovery. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244992. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 09:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46849 | Using the --fragment option in certain configuration setups OpenVPN version 2.6.0 to 2.6.6 allows an attacker to trigger a divide by zero be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46849</link><description>Using the --fragment option in certain configuration setups OpenVPN version 2.6.0 to 2.6.6 allows an attacker to trigger a divide by zero behaviour which could cause an application crash, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 02:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46850 | Use after free in OpenVPN version 2.6.0 to 2.6.6 may lead to undefined behavoir, leaking memory buffers or remote execution when sending net...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46850</link><description>Use after free in OpenVPN version 2.6.0 to 2.6.6 may lead to undefined behavoir, leaking memory buffers or remote execution when sending network buffers to a remote peer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 02:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4804 | Quantum HD Unity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4804</link><description>An unauthorized user could access debug features in Quantum HD Unity products that were accidentally exposed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 22:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47122 | Gitsign&amp;#x27;s Rekor public keys fetched from upstream API instead of local TUF client.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47122</link><description>Gitsign is software for keyless Git signing using Sigstore. In versions of gitsign starting with 0.6.0 and prior to 0.8.0, Rekor public keys were fetched via the Rekor API, instead of through the local TUF client. If the upstream Rekor server happened to be compromised, gitsign clients could potentially be tricked into trusting incorrect signatures. There is no known compromise the default public good instance (`rekor.sigstore.dev`) - anyone using this instance is unaffected. This issue was fixed in v0.8.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 21:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36027 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36027</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47129 | Statamic CMS remote code execution via front-end form uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47129</link><description>Statmic is a core Laravel content management system Composer package. Prior to versions 3.4.13 and 4.33.0, on front-end forms with an asset upload field, PHP files crafted to look like images may be uploaded. This only affects forms using the "Forms" feature and not just _any_ arbitrary form. This does not affect the control panel. This issue has been patched in 3.4.13 and 4.33.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 18:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47108 | DoS vulnerability in otelgrpc (uncontrolled resource consumption) due to unbound cardinality metrics </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47108</link><description>OpenTelemetry-Go Contrib is a collection of third-party packages for OpenTelemetry-Go. Prior to version 0.46.0, the grpc Unary Server Interceptor out of the box adds labels `net.peer.sock.addr` and `net.peer.sock.port` that have unbound cardinality. It leads to the server's potential memory exhaustion when many malicious requests are sent. An attacker can easily flood the peer address and port for requests. Version 0.46.0 contains a fix for this issue. As a workaround to stop being affected, a view removing the attributes can be used. The other possibility is to disable grpc metrics instrumentation by passing `otelgrpc.WithMeterProvider` option with `noop.NewMeterProvider`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47128 | piccolo SQL Injection via named transaction savepoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47128</link><description>Piccolo is an object-relational mapping and query builder which supports asyncio. Prior to version 1.1.1, the handling of named transaction `savepoints` in all database implementations is vulnerable to SQL Injection via f-strings. While the likelihood of an end developer exposing a `savepoints` `name` parameter to a user is highly unlikely, it would not be unheard of. If a malicious user was able to abuse this functionality they would have essentially direct access to the database and the ability to modify data to the level of permissions associated with the database user. A non exhaustive list of actions possible based on database permissions is: Read all data stored in the database, including usernames and password hashes; insert arbitrary data into the database, including modifying existing records; and gain a shell on the underlying server. Version 1.1.1 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 18:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46735 | Symfony potential Cross-site Scripting in WebhookController</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46735</link><description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Starting in version 6.0.0 and prior to version 6.3.8, the error message in `WebhookController` returns unescaped user-submitted input. As of version 6.3.8, `WebhookController` now doesn't return any user-submitted input in its response.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 18:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46734 | Symfony potential Cross-site Scripting vulnerabilities in CodeExtension filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46734</link><description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Starting in versions 2.0.0, 5.0.0, and 6.0.0 and prior to versions 4.4.51, 5.4.31, and 6.3.8, some Twig filters in CodeExtension use `is_safe=html` but don't actually ensure their input is safe. As of versions 4.4.51, 5.4.31, and 6.3.8, Symfony now escapes the output of the affected filters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 17:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46733 | Symfony possible session fixation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46733</link><description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Starting in versions 5.4.21 and 6.2.7 and prior to versions 5.4.31 and 6.3.8, `SessionStrategyListener` does not migrate the session after every successful login. It does so only in case the logged in user changes by means of checking the user identifier. In some use cases, the user identifier doesn't change between the verification phase and the successful login, while the token itself changes from one type (partially-authenticated) to another (fully-authenticated). When this happens, the session id should be regenerated to prevent possible session fixations, which is not the case at the moment. As of versions 5.4.31 and 6.3.8, Symfony now checks the type of the token in addition to the user identifier before deciding whether the session id should be regenerated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4949 | Memory Corruption Vulnerability in Grub-Legacy&amp;#x27;s XFS Implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4949</link><description>An attacker with local access to a system (either through a disk or external drive) can present a modified XFS partition to grub-legacy in such a way to exploit a memory corruption in grub’s XFS file system implementation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47611 | A CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists in Telit Cinterion BGS5, Telit Cinterion EHS5/6/8, Telit Cinterion PDS5/6/8, T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47611</link><description>A CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists in Telit Cinterion BGS5, Telit Cinterion EHS5/6/8, Telit Cinterion PDS5/6/8, Telit Cinterion ELS61/81, Telit Cinterion PLS62 that could allow a local, low privileged attacker to elevate privileges to "manufacturer" level on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39295 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39295</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.1.3 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41284 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41284</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.1.4 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 16:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41285 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41285</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.1.4 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 16:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47614 | A CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability exists in Telit Cinterion BGS5, Telit Cinterion EHS5/6/8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47614</link><description>A CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability exists in Telit Cinterion BGS5, Telit Cinterion EHS5/6/8, Telit Cinterion PDS5/6/8, Telit Cinterion ELS61/81, Telit Cinterion PLS62 that could allow a local, low privileged attacker to disclose hidden virtual paths and file names on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6076 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System Reservation Status booking-details.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6076</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file booking-details.php of the component Reservation Status Handler. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-244945 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47120 | Discourse DoS through Onebox favicon URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47120</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In versions 3.1.0 through 3.1.2 of the `stable` branch and versions 3.1.0,beta6 through 3.2.0.beta2 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, Redis memory can be depleted by crafting a site with an abnormally long favicon URL and drafting multiple posts which Onebox it. The issue is patched in version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47121 | Discourse SSRF vulnerability in Embedding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47121</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Prior to version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, the embedding feature is susceptible to server side request forgery. The issue is patched in version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. As a workaround, disable the Embedding feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47119 | HTML injection in oneboxed links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47119</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Prior to version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, some links can inject arbitrary HTML tags when rendered through our Onebox engine. The issue is patched in version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6075 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System Reservation Request index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6075</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php of the component Reservation Request Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244944.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23367 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23367</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.0.1.2376 build 20230421 and later
QuTS hero h5.0.1.2376 build 20230421 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.0.2498 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45816 | Unread bookmark reminder notifications that the user cannot access can be seen</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45816</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Prior to version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, there is an edge case where a bookmark reminder is sent and an unread notification is generated, but the underlying bookmarkable (e.g. post, topic, chat message) security has changed, making it so the user can no longer access the underlying resource. As of version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, bookmark reminders are now no longer sent if the user does not have access to the underlying bookmarkable, and also the unread bookmark notifications are always filtered by access. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46130 | Bypassing height value allowed in some theme components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46130</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Prior to version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, some theme components allow users to add svgs with unlimited `height` attributes, and this can affect the availability of subsequent replies in a topic. Most Discourse instances are unaffected, only instances with the svgbob or the mermaid theme component are within scope. The issue is patched in version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. As a workaround, disable or remove the relevant theme components.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45806 | Discourse vulnerable to DoS via Regexp Injection in Full Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45806</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Prior to version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, if a user has been quoted and uses a `|` in their full name, they might be able to trigger a bug that generates a lot of duplicate content in all the posts they've been quoted by updating their full name again. Version 3.1.3 of the `stable` branch and version 3.2.0.beta3 of the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches contain a patch for this issue. No known workaround exists, although one can stop the "bleeding" by ensuring users only use alphanumeric characters in their full name field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6074 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System Booking Reservation check-status.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6074</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file check-status.php of the component Booking Reservation Handler. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244943.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 14:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29426 | WordPress Spreadshop Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29426</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Robert Schulz (sprd.Net AG) Spreadshop plugin &lt;= 1.6.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29428 | WordPress Superb Social Media Share Buttons and Follow Buttons Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29428</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SuPlugins Superb Social Media Share Buttons and Follow Buttons for WordPress plugin &lt;= 1.1.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29440 | WordPress Simple Job Board Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29440</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Job Board plugin &lt;= 2.10.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30478 | WordPress Newsletters Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30478</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tribulant Newsletters plugin &lt;= 4.8.8 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31077 | WordPress Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31077</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ReCorp Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS plugin &lt;= 2.1.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31078 | WordPress WP BrowserUpdate Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31078</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marco Steinbrecher WP BrowserUpdate plugin &lt;= 4.4.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47164 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in HOTELDRUID 3.0.5 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47164</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in HOTELDRUID 3.0.5 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 09:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6073 | DoS and Control of Volume Settings for VW ID.3 ICAS3 IVI ECU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6073</link><description>Attacker can perform a Denial of Service attack to crash the ICAS 3 IVI ECU in a Volkswagen ID.3 (and other vehicles of the VW Group with the same hardware) and spoof volume setting commands to irreversibly turn on audio volume to maximum via REST API calls.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 07:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47800 | Natus NeuroWorks and SleepWorks before 8.4 GMA3 utilize a default password of xltek for the Microsoft SQL Server service sa account, allowin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47800</link><description>Natus NeuroWorks and SleepWorks before 8.4 GMA3 utilize a default password of xltek for the Microsoft SQL Server service sa account, allowing a threat actor to perform remote code execution, data exfiltration, or other nefarious actions such as tampering with data or destroying/disrupting MSSQL services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47246 | In SysAid On-Premise before 23.3.36, a path traversal vulnerability leads to code execution after an attacker writes a file to the Tomcat we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47246</link><description>In SysAid On-Premise before 23.3.36, a path traversal vulnerability leads to code execution after an attacker writes a file to the Tomcat webroot, as exploited in the wild in November 2023.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39796 | SQL injection vulnerability in the miniform module in WBCE CMS v.1.6.0 allows remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39796</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the miniform module in WBCE CMS v.1.6.0 allows remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DB_RECORD_TABLE parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45167 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45167</link><description>IBM AIX's 7.3 Python implementation could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267965.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 04:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46729 | Sentry Next.js vulnerable to SSRF via Next.js SDK tunnel endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46729</link><description>sentry-javascript provides Sentry SDKs for JavaScript. An unsanitized input of Next.js SDK tunnel endpoint allows sending HTTP requests to arbitrary URLs and reflecting the response back to the user. This issue only affects users who have Next.js SDK tunneling feature enabled. The problem has been fixed in version 7.77.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 02:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6069 | Improper Input Validation in froxlor/froxlor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6069</link><description>Improper Input Validation in GitHub repository froxlor/froxlor prior to 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 02:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>