<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:50:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-24272 | An issue in iTop DualSafe Password Manager &amp; Digital Vault before 1.4.24 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via leaked ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24272</link><description>An issue in iTop DualSafe Password Manager &amp; Digital Vault before 1.4.24 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via leaked credentials as plaintext in a log file that can be accessed by the local user without knowledge of the master secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28116 | Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) with Grav CMS security sandbox bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28116</link><description>Grav is an open-source, flat-file content management system. Grav CMS prior to version 1.7.45 is vulnerable to a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI), which allows any authenticated user (editor permissions are sufficient) to execute arbitrary code on the remote server bypassing the existing security sandbox. Version 1.7.45 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27921 | Grav File Upload Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27921</link><description>Grav is an open-source, flat-file content management system. A file upload path traversal vulnerability has been identified in the application prior to version 1.7.45, enabling attackers to replace or create files with extensions like .json, .zip, .css, .gif, etc. This critical security flaw poses severe risks, that can allow attackers to inject arbitrary code on the server, undermine integrity of backup files by overwriting existing files or creating new ones, and exfiltrate sensitive data using CSS exfiltration techniques. Upgrading to patched version 1.7.45 can mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2768 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System edit-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2768</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-services.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257604.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28521 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Netcome NS-ASG Application Security Gateway v.6.3.1 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28521</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Netcome NS-ASG Application Security Gateway v.6.3.1 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the loginid parameter of the /singlelogin.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28756 | The SolarEdge mySolarEdge application before 2.20.1 for Android has a certificate verification issue that allows a Machine-in-the-middle (Mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28756</link><description>The SolarEdge mySolarEdge application before 2.20.1 for Android has a certificate verification issue that allows a Machine-in-the-middle (MitM) attacker to read and alter all network traffic between the application and the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2766 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2766</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2767 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2767</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257603.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2763 | Tenda AC10U setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2763</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48. Affected by this issue is the function formSetCfm of the file goform/setcfm. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2764 | Tenda AC10U SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2764</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48. This affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument endIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1727 | Tighten CORS rules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1727</link><description>To prevent malicious 3rd party websites from making requests to Gradio applications running locally, this PR tightens the CORS rules around Gradio applications. In particular, it checks to see if the host header is localhost (or one of its aliases) and if so, it requires the origin header (if present) to be localhost (or one of its aliases) as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29374 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the way MOODLE 3.10.9 handles user input within the "GET /?lang=" URL parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29374</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the way MOODLE 3.10.9 handles user input within the "GET /?lang=" URL parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24883 | WordPress Prime Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.11.10 - Broken Access Control on Duplicate Post vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24883</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 3.11.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25907 | WordPress WP Media folder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Plugin Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25907</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Media folder.This issue affects WP Media folder: from n/a through 5.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29937 | NFS in a BSD derived codebase, as used in OpenBSD through 7.4 and FreeBSD through 14.0-RELEASE, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29937</link><description>NFS in a BSD derived codebase, as used in OpenBSD through 7.4 and FreeBSD through 14.0-RELEASE, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a bug that is unrelated to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24850 | WordPress Quicksand Post Filter jQuery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24850</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mark Stockton Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin.This issue affects Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44633 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Gift Cards Premium plugin &amp;lt;= 3.23.1 - Unauth. Gift Card Creation Leading to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44633</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Gift Cards Premium.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Gift Cards Premium: from n/a through 3.23.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47604 | WordPress AJAX Thumbnail Rebuild plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47604</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in junkcoder, ristoniinemets AJAX Thumbnail Rebuild.This issue affects AJAX Thumbnail Rebuild: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25908 | WordPress WP Media folder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Post/Page Modification vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25908</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Media folder.This issue affects WP Media folder: from n/a through 5.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25912 | WordPress MoveTo plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary WordPress Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25912</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Skymoonlabs MoveTo.This issue affects MoveTo: from n/a through 6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25922 | WordPress Peach Payments Gateway plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25922</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Peach Payments Peach Payments Gateway.This issue affects Peach Payments Gateway: from n/a through 3.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25935 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.5.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25935</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.2.5.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51672 | WordPress FunnelKit Checkout plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post/Page Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51672</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FunnelKit FunnelKit Checkout.This issue affects FunnelKit Checkout: from n/a through 3.10.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27607 | WordPress Points and Rewards for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27607</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Swings Points and Rewards for WooCommerce.This issue affects Points and Rewards for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44595 | WordPress WP2FA plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44595</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Melapress WP 2FA allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects WP 2FA: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49837 | WordPress embed-code plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Denial of Service Attack vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49837</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in David Artiss Code Embed.This issue affects Code Embed: from n/a through 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27277 | IBM Storage Protect Plus Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27277</link><description>The private key for the IBM Storage Protect Plus Server 10.1.0 through 10.1.16 certificate can be disclosed, undermining the security of the certificate.  IBM X-Force ID:  285205.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27190 | WordPress Download Media plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27190</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jean-David Daviet Download Media.This issue affects Download Media: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27956 | WordPress Automatic plugin &amp;lt;= 3.92.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary SQL Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27956</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ValvePress Automatic allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Automatic: from n/a through 3.92.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27968 | WordPress Super Page Cache for Cloudflare plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27968</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Optimole Super Page Cache for Cloudflare allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Super Page Cache for Cloudflare: from n/a through 4.7.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29916 | The dormakaba Saflok system before the November 2023 software update allows an attacker to unlock arbitrary doors at a property via forged k...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29916</link><description>The dormakaba Saflok system before the November 2023 software update allows an attacker to unlock arbitrary doors at a property via forged keycards, if the attacker has obtained one active or expired keycard for the specific property, aka the "Unsaflok" issue. This occurs, in part, because the key derivation function relies only on a UID. This affects, for example, Saflok MT, and the Confidant, Quantum, RT, and Saffire series.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29180 | webpack-dev-middleware Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29180</link><description>Prior to versions 7.1.0, 6.1.2, and 5.3.4, the webpack-dev-middleware development middleware for devpack does not validate the supplied URL address sufficiently before returning the local file. It is possible to access any file on the developer's machine. The middleware can either work with the physical filesystem when reading the files or it can use a virtualized in-memory `memfs` filesystem. If `writeToDisk` configuration option is set to `true`, the physical filesystem is used. The `getFilenameFromUrl` method is used to parse URL and build the local file path. The public path prefix is stripped from the URL, and the `unsecaped` path suffix is appended to the `outputPath`. As the URL is not unescaped and normalized automatically before calling the midlleware, it is possible to use `%2e` and `%2f` sequences to perform path traversal attack.

Developers using `webpack-dev-server` or `webpack-dev-middleware` are affected by the issue. When the project is started, an attacker might access any file on the developer's machine and exfiltrate the content. If the development server is listening on a public IP address (or `0.0.0.0`), an attacker on the local network can access the local files without any interaction from the victim (direct connection to the port). If the server allows access from third-party domains, an attacker can send a malicious link to the victim. When visited, the client side script can connect to the local server and exfiltrate the local files. Starting with fixed versions 7.1.0, 6.1.2, and 5.3.4, the URL is unescaped and normalized before any further processing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2578 | WordPress WP Coder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2578</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPCoder WP Coder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Coder: from n/a through 3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2579 | WordPress Tracking Code Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2579</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Data443 Tracking Code Manager.This issue affects Tracking Code Manager: from n/a through 2.0.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2580 | WordPress Recover WooCommerce Cart Abandonment, Newsletter, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation By FunnelKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2580</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelKit Automation By Autonami allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Automation By Autonami: from n/a through 2.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27962 | WordPress wp-mpdf plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27962</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Florian 'fkrauthan' Krauthan allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects wp-mpdf: from n/a through 3.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27963 | WordPress Crisp – Live Chat and Chatbot plugin &amp;lt;= 0.44 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27963</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Crisp allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Crisp: from n/a through 0.44.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27964 | WordPress Zippy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27964</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Gesundheit Bewegt GmbH Zippy.This issue affects Zippy: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27965 | WordPress WPFunnels plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27965</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFunnels Team WPFunnels allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPFunnels: from n/a through 3.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29019 | ESPHome vulnerable to Authentication bypass via Cross site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29019</link><description>ESPHome is a system to control microcontrollers remotely through Home Automation systems. API endpoints in dashboard component of ESPHome version 2023.12.9 (command line installation) are vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) allowing remote attackers to carry out attacks against a logged user of the dashboard to perform operations on configuration files (create, edit, delete). It is possible for a malicious actor to create a specifically crafted web page that triggers a cross site request against ESPHome, this allows bypassing the authentication for API calls on the platform. This vulnerability allows bypassing authentication on API calls accessing configuration file operations on the behalf of a logged user. In order to trigger the vulnerability, the victim must visit a weaponized page. In addition to this, it is possible to chain this vulnerability with GHSA-9p43-hj5j-96h5/ CVE-2024-27287 to obtain a complete takeover of the user account. Version 2024.3.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27966 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27966</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through 8.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27967 | WordPress DSGVO All in one for WP plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27967</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Leithold DSGVO All in one for WP.This issue affects DSGVO All in one for WP: from n/a through 4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27969 | WordPress Free Downloads WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27969</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Enhanced Free Downloads WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Free Downloads WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.5.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27970 | WordPress WP SendFox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27970</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BogdanFix WP SendFox.This issue affects WP SendFox: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27985 | WordPress PropertyHive plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27985</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PropertyHive.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27988 | WordPress WEN Responsive Columns plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27988</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WEN Themes WEN Responsive Columns allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WEN Responsive Columns: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28402 | TOTOLINK X2000R before V1.0.0-B20231213.1013 contains a Stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IP/Port Filtering under the Firew...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28402</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R before V1.0.0-B20231213.1013 contains a Stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IP/Port Filtering under the Firewall Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27989 | WordPress WP Responsive Tabs horizontal vertical and accordion Tabs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in I Thirteen Web Solution WP Responsive Tabs horizontal vertical and accordion Tabs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Responsive Tabs horizontal vertical and accordion Tabs: from n/a through 1.1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27990 | WordPress The Moneytizer plugin &amp;lt;= 9.5.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27990</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Moneytizer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects The Moneytizer: from n/a through 9.5.20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27991 | WordPress SupportCandy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27991</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SupportCandy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SupportCandy: from n/a through 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27992 | WordPress Link Whisper Free plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27992</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Link Whisper Link Whisper Free allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Link Whisper Free: from n/a through 0.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27993 | WordPress Calendarista Basic Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27993</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Typps Calendarista Basic Edition.This issue affects Calendarista Basic Edition: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27994 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27994</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons: from n/a through 4.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27995 | WordPress ARMember plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.23 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27995</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Repute Infosystems ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp; User signup allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp; User signup: from n/a through 4.0.23.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2463 | Weak password recovery mechanism in CDeX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2463</link><description>Weak password recovery mechanism in CDeX application allows to retrieve password reset token.This issue affects CDeX application versions through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2464 | Application users enumeration in CDeX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2464</link><description>This issue occurs during password recovery, where a difference in messages could allow an attacker to determine if the user is valid or not, enabling a brute force attack with valid users.This issue affects CDeX application versions through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2465 | Open redirection in CDeX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2465</link><description>Open redirection vulnerability in CDeX application allows to redirect users to arbitrary websites via a specially crafted URL.This issue affects CDeX application versions through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29243 | Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the vpn_client_ip parameter at /ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29243</link><description>Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the vpn_client_ip parameter at /apply.cgi.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29244 | Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the pin_code_3g parameter at /appl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29244</link><description>Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the pin_code_3g parameter at /apply.cgi.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47715 | IBM Storage Protect Plus Server improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47715</link><description>IBM Storage Protect Plus Server 10.1.0 through 10.1.16 could allow an authenticated user with read-only permissions to add or delete entries from an existing HyperVisor configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  271538.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29880 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11 users with access to the agent machine might obtain permissions of the user running the agent process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29880</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11 users with access to the agent machine might obtain permissions of the user running the agent process</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29877 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29877</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through   /sentrifugo/index.php/expenses/expensecategories/edit, 'expense_category_name' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted URL to the victim and steal their session data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29878 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29878</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through   /sentrifugo/index.php/sitepreference/add, 'description' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted URL to the victim and steal their session data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29879 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29879</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through   /sentrifugo/index.php/index/getdepartments/format/html,  'business_id' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted URL to the victim and steal their session data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29870 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29870</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through /sentrifugo/index.php/index/getdepartments/format/html, 'business_id' parameter./sentrifugo/index.php/index/getdepartments/format/html, 'business_id' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29871 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29871</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through /sentrifugo/index.php/index/getdepartments/sentrifugo/index.php/index/updatecontactnumber, 'id' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29872 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29872</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through /sentrifugo/index.php/empscreening/add, 'agencyids' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29873 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29873</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through /sentrifugo/index.php/reports/businessunits/format/html, 'bunitname' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29874 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29874</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through /sentrifugo/index.php/default/reports/activeuserrptpdf, 'sort_name' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29875 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29875</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through  /sentrifugo/index.php/default/reports/exportactiveuserrpt, 'sort_name' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29876 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29876</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Sentrifugo 3.2, through   /sentrifugo/index.php/reports/activitylogreport, 'sortby' parameter. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow  a remote user to send a specially crafted query to the server and extract all the data from it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2494 | Libvirt: negative g_new0 length can lead to unbounded memory allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2494</link><description>A flaw was found in the RPC library APIs of libvirt. The RPC server deserialization code allocates memory for arrays before the non-negative length check is performed by the C API entry points. Passing a negative length to the g_new0 function results in a crash due to the negative length being treated as a huge positive number. This flaw allows a local, unprivileged user to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29866 | Datalust Seq before 2023.4.11151 and 2024 before 2024.1.11146 has Incorrect Access Control because a Project Owner or Organization Owner can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29866</link><description>Datalust Seq before 2023.4.11151 and 2024 before 2024.1.11146 has Incorrect Access Control because a Project Owner or Organization Owner can escalate to System privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28834 | Gnutls: vulnerable to minerva side-channel information leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28834</link><description>A flaw was found in GnuTLS. The Minerva attack is a cryptographic vulnerability that exploits deterministic behavior in systems like GnuTLS, leading to side-channel leaks. In specific scenarios, such as when using the GNUTLS_PRIVKEY_FLAG_REPRODUCIBLE flag, it can result in a noticeable step in nonce size from 513 to 512 bits, exposing a potential timing side-channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1394 | Golang-fips/openssl: memory leaks in code encrypting and decrypting rsa payloads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1394</link><description>A memory leak flaw was found in Golang in the RSA encrypting/decrypting code, which might lead to a resource exhaustion vulnerability using attacker-controlled inputs​. The memory leak happens in github.com/golang-fips/openssl/openssl/rsa.go#L113. The objects leaked are pkey​ and ctx​. That function uses named return parameters to free pkey​ and ctx​ if there is an error initializing the context or setting the different properties. All return statements related to error cases follow the "return nil, nil, fail(...)" pattern, meaning that pkey​ and ctx​ will be nil inside the deferred function that should free them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51141 | An issue in ZKTeko BioTime v.8.5.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Authentication &amp; Authorizatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51141</link><description>An issue in ZKTeko BioTime v.8.5.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Authentication &amp; Authorization component</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51142 | An issue in ZKTeco BioTime v.8.5.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51142</link><description>An issue in ZKTeco BioTime v.8.5.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2742 | OS Command Injection in Planet IGS-4215-16T2S</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2742</link><description>Operating system command injection vulnerability in Planet IGS-4215-16T2S, affecting firmware version 1.305b210528. An authenticated attacker could execute arbitrary code on the remote host by exploiting IP address functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2740 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Planet IGS-4215-16T2S</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2740</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in Planet IGS-4215-16T2S, affecting firmware version 1.305b210528. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to access some administrative resources due to lack of proper management of the Switch web interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2741 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in Planet IGS-4215-16T2S</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2741</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Planet IGS-4215-16T2S, affecting firmware version 1.305b210528. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to trick some authenticated users into performing actions in their session, such as adding or updating accounts through the Switch web interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27683 | D-Link Go-RT-AC750 GORTAC750_A1_FW_v101b03 contains a stack-based buffer overflow via the function hnap_main. An attacker can send a POST re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27683</link><description>D-Link Go-RT-AC750 GORTAC750_A1_FW_v101b03 contains a stack-based buffer overflow via the function hnap_main. An attacker can send a POST request to trigger the vulnerablilify.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52620 | netfilter: nf_tables: disallow timeout for anonymous sets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52620</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: disallow timeout for anonymous sets

Never used from userspace, disallow these parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26642 | netfilter: nf_tables: disallow anonymous set with timeout flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26642</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: disallow anonymous set with timeout flag

Anonymous sets are never used with timeout from userspace, reject this.
Exception to this rule is NFT_SET_EVAL to ensure legacy meters still work.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26643 | netfilter: nf_tables: mark set as dead when unbinding anonymous set with timeout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26643</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: mark set as dead when unbinding anonymous set with timeout

While the rhashtable set gc runs asynchronously, a race allows it to
collect elements from anonymous sets with timeouts while it is being
released from the commit path.

Mingi Cho originally reported this issue in a different path in 6.1.x
with a pipapo set with low timeouts which is not possible upstream since
7395dfacfff6 ("netfilter: nf_tables: use timestamp to check for set
element timeout").

Fix this by setting on the dead flag for anonymous sets to skip async gc
in this case.

According to 08e4c8c5919f ("netfilter: nf_tables: mark newset as dead on
transaction abort"), Florian plans to accelerate abort path by releasing
objects via workqueue, therefore, this sets on the dead flag for abort
path too.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29732 | SQL Injection vulnerability on SCAN_VISIO eDocument Suite Web Viewer from Abast</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29732</link><description>A SQL Injection has been found on SCAN_VISIO eDocument Suite Web Viewer of Abast. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated user to retrieve, update and delete all the information of database. This vulnerability was found on login page via "user" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27438 | Apache Doris: Downloading arbitrary remote jar files resulting in remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27438</link><description>Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability in Apache Doris.
The jdbc driver files used for JDBC catalog is not checked and may resulting in remote command execution.
Once the attacker is authorized to create a JDBC catalog, he/she can use arbitrary driver jar file with unchecked code snippet. This code snippet will be run when catalog is initializing without any check.
This issue affects Apache Doris: from 1.2.0 through 2.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.5 or 2.1.x, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26307 | Apache Doris: Possible race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26307</link><description>Possible race condition vulnerability in Apache Doris.
Some of code using `chmod()` method. This method run the risk of someone renaming the file out from under user and chmodding the wrong file.
This could theoretically happen, but the impact would be minimal.
This issue affects Apache Doris: before 1.2.8, before 2.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.4, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29131 | Apache Commons Configuration: StackOverflowError adding property in AbstractListDelimiterHandler.flattenIterator()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29131</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Apache Commons Configuration.This issue affects Apache Commons Configuration: from 2.0 before 2.10.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29133 | Apache Commons Configuration: StackOverflowError calling ListDelimiterHandler.flatten(Object, int) with a cyclical object tree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29133</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Apache Commons Configuration.This issue affects Apache Commons Configuration: from 2.0 before 2.10.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1148 | Weak Access Control - Arbitrary file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1148</link><description>Weak access control in OpenText PVCS Version Manager allows potential bypassing of authentication and uploading of files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 07:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1147 | Weak Access Control - Arbitrary file download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1147</link><description>Weak access control in OpenText PVCS Version Manager allows potential bypassing of authentication and download of files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 07:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2754 | SourceCodester Complete E-Commerce Site users_photo.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2754</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Complete E-Commerce Site 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/users_photo.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257544.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 07:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28835 | Gnutls: potential crash during chain building/verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28835</link><description>A flaw has been discovered in GnuTLS where an application crash can be induced when attempting to verify a specially crafted .pem bundle using the "certtool --verify-chain" command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 06:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2161 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Kiloview NDI N series products API middleware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2161</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Kiloview NDI allows un-authenticated users to bypass authenticationThis issue affects Kiloview NDI N3, N3-s, N4, N20, N30, N40 and was fixed in Firmware version 2.02.0227 .</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 06:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2162 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in Kiloview NDI N series products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2162</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in Kiloview NDI allows a low-privileged user to execute arbitrary code remotely on the device with high privileges.

This issue affects Kiloview NDI N3, N3-s, N4, N20, N30, N40 and was fixed in Firmware version 2.02.0227 .</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 06:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28635 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SurveyJS Survey Creator v.1.9.132 and before, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28635</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SurveyJS Survey Creator v.1.9.132 and before, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the title parameter in form.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29864 | Distrobox before 1.7.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via command injection into exported executables.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29864</link><description>Distrobox before 1.7.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via command injection into exported executables.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1538 | The File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.4. This is due t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1538</link><description>The File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wp_file_manager page that includes files through the 'lang' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include local JavaScript files that can be leveraged to achieve RCE via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This issue was partially patched in version 7.2.4, and fully patched in 7.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22724 | An issue was discovered in osCommerce v4, allows local attackers to bypass file upload restrictions and execute arbitrary code via administr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22724</link><description>An issue was discovered in osCommerce v4, allows local attackers to bypass file upload restrictions and execute arbitrary code via administrator profile photo upload feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29862 | The Kerlink firewall in ChirpStack chirpstack-mqtt-forwarder before 4.2.1 and chirpstack-gateway-bridge before 4.0.11 wrongly accepts certai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29862</link><description>The Kerlink firewall in ChirpStack chirpstack-mqtt-forwarder before 4.2.1 and chirpstack-gateway-bridge before 4.0.11 wrongly accepts certain TCP packets when a connection is not in the ESTABLISHED state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48901 | A SQL injection vulnerability in tramyardg Autoexpress version 1.3.0, allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48901</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in tramyardg Autoexpress version 1.3.0, allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the parameter "id" within the getPhotosByCarId function call in details.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48902 | An issue was discovered in tramyardg autoexpress version 1.3.0, allows unauthenticated remote attackers to escalate privileges, update car d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48902</link><description>An issue was discovered in tramyardg autoexpress version 1.3.0, allows unauthenticated remote attackers to escalate privileges, update car data, delete vehicles, and upload car images via authentication bypass in uploadCarImages.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48903 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tramyardg autoexpress 1.3.0, allows remote unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48903</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tramyardg autoexpress 1.3.0, allows remote unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML within parameter "imgType" via in uploadCarImages.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29858 | In MISP before 2.4.187, __uploadLogo in app/Controller/OrganisationsController.php does not properly check for a valid logo upload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29858</link><description>In MISP before 2.4.187, __uploadLogo in app/Controller/OrganisationsController.php does not properly check for a valid logo upload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29859 | In MISP before 2.4.187, add_misp_export in app/Controller/EventsController.php does not properly check for a valid file upload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29859</link><description>In MISP before 2.4.187, add_misp_export in app/Controller/EventsController.php does not properly check for a valid file upload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28916 | Xbox Gaming Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28916</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2748 | CSRF vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed performing actions on behalf of a user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2748</link><description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2443 | Improper input validation vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2443</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2469 | Remote Code Execution in GitHub Enterprise Server Allowed Administrators to gain SSH access to the appliance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2469</link><description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29026 | Owncast cross origin request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29026</link><description>Owncast is an open source, self-hosted, decentralized, single user live video streaming and chat server. In versions 0.1.2 and prior, a lenient CORS policy allows attackers to make a cross origin request, reading privileged information. This can be used to leak the admin password. Commit 9215d9ba0f29d62201d3feea9e77dcd274581624 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24050 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Workout Journal App 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via parameters fir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24050</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Workout Journal App 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via parameters firstname and lastname in /add-user.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 21:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2720 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System aboutus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2720</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257473 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 21:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2719 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System admin-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2719</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument adminname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257472.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 21:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29036 | Saleor Storefront session leak in cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29036</link><description>Saleor Storefront is software for building e-commerce experiences. Prior to commit 579241e75a5eb332ccf26e0bcdd54befa33f4783, when any user authenticates in the storefront, anonymous users are able to access their data. The session is leaked through cache and can be accessed by anyone. Users should upgrade to a version that incorporates commit 579241e75a5eb332ccf26e0bcdd54befa33f4783 or later to receive a patch. A possible workaround is to temporarily disable authentication by changing the usage of `createSaleorAuthClient()`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29037 | Default secret use for initial deployment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29037</link><description>datahub-helm provides the Kubernetes Helm charts for deploying Datahub and its dependencies on a Kubernetes cluster. Starting in version 0.1.143 and prior to version 0.2.182, due to configuration issues in the helm chart, if there was a successful initial deployment during a limited window of time, personal access tokens were possibly created with a default secret key. Since the secret key is a static, publicly available value, someone could inspect the algorithm used to generate personal access tokens and generate their own for an instance. Deploying with Metadata Service Authentication enabled would have been difficult during window of releases. If someone circumvented the helm settings and manually set Metadata Service Authentication to be enabled using environment variables directly, this would skip over the autogeneration logic for the Kubernetes Secrets and DataHub GMS would default to the signing key specified statically in the application.yml. Most deployments probably did not attempt to circumvent the helm settings to enable Metadata Service Authentication during this time, so impact is most likely limited. Any deployments with Metadata Service Authentication enabled should ensure that their secret values are properly randomized. Version 0.2.182 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, one may reset the token signing key to be a random value, which will invalidate active personal access tokens.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29469 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OneBlog v2.3.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29469</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OneBlog v2.3.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Category List parameter under the Lab module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29470 | OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component {{rootpath}}/links.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29470</link><description>OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component {{rootpath}}/links.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29471 | OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Notice Manage module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29471</link><description>OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Notice Manage module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29472 | OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Privilege Management module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29472</link><description>OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Privilege Management module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29473 | OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Role Management module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29473</link><description>OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Role Management module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29474 | OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the User Management module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29474</link><description>OneBlog v2.3.4 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the User Management module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25294 | An SSRF issue in REBUILD v.3.5 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the FileDownloader.ja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25294</link><description>An SSRF issue in REBUILD v.3.5 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the FileDownloader.java, proxyDownload,URL parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29033 | GoogleOAuthenticator.hosted_domain incorrectly verifies membership of an Google organization/workspace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29033</link><description>OAuthenticator provides plugins for JupyterHub to use common OAuth providers, as well as base classes for writing one's own Authenticators with any OAuth 2.0 provider. `GoogleOAuthenticator.hosted_domain` is used to restrict what Google accounts can be authorized access to a JupyterHub. The restriction is intented to be to Google accounts part of one or more Google organization verified to control specified domain(s). Prior to version 16.3.0, the actual restriction has been to Google accounts with emails ending with the domain. Such accounts could have been created by anyone which at one time was able to read an email associated with the domain. This was described by Dylan Ayrey (@dxa4481) in this [blog post] from 15th December 2023). OAuthenticator 16.3.0 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, restrict who can login another way, such as `allowed_users` or `allowed_google_groups`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2717 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System booking-search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2717</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/booking-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257470 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2718 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System booking-bwdates-reports-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2718</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/booking-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257471.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29018 | External DNS requests from &amp;#x27;internal&amp;#x27; networks could lead to data exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29018</link><description>Moby is an open source container framework that is a key component of Docker Engine, Docker Desktop, and other distributions of container tooling or runtimes. Moby's networking implementation allows for many networks, each with their own IP address range and gateway, to be defined. This feature is frequently referred to as custom networks, as each network can have a different driver, set of parameters and thus behaviors. When creating a network, the `--internal` flag is used to designate a network as _internal_. The `internal` attribute in a docker-compose.yml file may also be used to mark a network _internal_, and other API clients may specify the `internal` parameter as well.

When containers with networking are created, they are assigned unique network interfaces and IP addresses. The host serves as a router for non-internal networks, with a gateway IP that provides SNAT/DNAT to/from container IPs.

Containers on an internal network may communicate between each other, but are precluded from communicating with any networks the host has access to (LAN or WAN) as no default route is configured, and firewall rules are set up to drop all outgoing traffic. Communication with the gateway IP address (and thus appropriately configured host services) is possible, and the host may communicate with any container IP directly.

In addition to configuring the Linux kernel's various networking features to enable container networking, `dockerd` directly provides some services to container networks. Principal among these is serving as a resolver, enabling service discovery, and resolution of names from an upstream resolver.

When a DNS request for a name that does not correspond to a container is received, the request is forwarded to the configured upstream resolver. This request is made from the container's network namespace: the level of access and routing of traffic is the same as if the request was made by the container itself.

As a consequence of this design, containers solely attached to an internal network will be unable to resolve names using the upstream resolver, as the container itself is unable to communicate with that nameserver. Only the names of containers also attached to the internal network are able to be resolved.

Many systems run a local forwarding DNS resolver. As the host and any containers have separate loopback devices, a consequence of the design described above is that containers are unable to resolve names from the host's configured resolver, as they cannot reach these addresses on the host loopback device. To bridge this gap, and to allow containers to properly resolve names even when a local forwarding resolver is used on a loopback address, `dockerd` detects this scenario and instead forward DNS requests from the host namework namespace. The loopback resolver then forwards the requests to its configured upstream resolvers, as expected.

Because `dockerd` forwards DNS requests to the host loopback device, bypassing the container network namespace's normal routing semantics entirely, internal networks can unexpectedly forward DNS requests to an external nameserver. By registering a domain for which they control the authoritative nameservers, an attacker could arrange for a compromised container to exfiltrate data by encoding it in DNS queries that will eventually be answered by their nameservers.

Docker Desktop is not affected, as Docker Desktop always runs an internal resolver on a RFC 1918 address.

Moby releases 26.0.0, 25.0.4, and 23.0.11 are patched to prevent forwarding any DNS requests from internal networks. As a workaround, run containers intended to be solely attached to internal networks with a custom upstream address, which will force all upstream DNS queries to be resolved from the container's network namespace.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29032 | `qiskit_ibm_runtime.RuntimeDecoder` can execute arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29032</link><description>Qiskit IBM Runtime is an environment that streamlines quantum computations and provides optimal implementations of the Qiskit quantum computing SDK. Starting in version 0.1.0 and prior to version 0.21.2, deserializing json data using `qiskit_ibm_runtime.RuntimeDecoder` can lead to arbitrary code execution given a correctly formatted input string. Version 0.21.2 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23721 | A Directory Traversal issue was discovered in process_post on Draytek Vigor3910 4.3.2.5 devices. When sending a certain POST request, it cal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23721</link><description>A Directory Traversal issue was discovered in process_post on Draytek Vigor3910 4.3.2.5 devices. When sending a certain POST request, it calls the function and exports information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28231 | Manipulated DATA Submessage causes a heap-buffer-overflow error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28231</link><description>eprosima Fast DDS is a C++ implementation of the Data Distribution Service standard of the Object Management Group. Prior to versions 2.14.0, 2.13.4, 2.12.3, 2.10.4, and 2.6.8, manipulated DATA Submessage can cause a heap overflow error in the Fast-DDS process, causing the process to be terminated remotely. Additionally, the payload_size in the DATA Submessage packet is declared as uint32_t. When a negative number, such as -1, is input into this variable, it results in an Integer Overflow (for example, -1 gets converted to 0xFFFFFFFF). This eventually leads to a heap-buffer-overflow, causing the program to terminate. Versions 2.14.0, 2.13.4, 2.12.3, 2.10.4, and 2.6.8 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28868 | Umbraco possible user enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28868</link><description>Umbraco is an ASP.NET content management system. Umbraco 10 prior to 10.8.4 with access to the native login screen is vulnerable to a possible user enumeration attack. This issue was fixed in version 10.8.5. As a workaround, one may disable the native login screen by exclusively using external logins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2715 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System user-search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2715</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/user-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257468.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2716 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System contactus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2716</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257469 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28179 | Jupyter Server Proxy&amp;#x27;s Websocket Proxying does not require authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28179</link><description>Jupyter Server Proxy allows users to run arbitrary external processes alongside their Jupyter notebook servers and provides authenticated web access. Prior to versions 3.2.3 and 4.1.1, Jupyter Server Proxy did not check user authentication appropriately when proxying websockets, allowing unauthenticated access to anyone who had network access to the Jupyter server endpoint. This vulnerability can allow unauthenticated remote access to any websocket endpoint set up to be accessible via Jupyter Server Proxy. In many cases, this leads to remote unauthenticated arbitrary code execution, due to how affected instances use websockets. The websocket endpoints exposed by `jupyter_server` itself is not affected. Projects that do not rely on websockets are also not affected. Versions 3.2.3 and 4.1.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 19:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27286 | Moving single messages from public to private streams leaves them accessible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27286</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration. When a user moves a Zulip message, they have the option to move all messages in the topic, move only subsequent messages as well, or move just a single message.  If the user chose to just move one message, and was moving it from a public stream to a private stream, Zulip would successfully move the message, -- but active users who did not have access to the private stream, but whose client had already received the message, would continue to see the message in the public stream until they reloaded their client.  Additionally, Zulip did not remove view permissions on the message from recently-active users, allowing the message to show up in the "All messages" view or in search results, but not in "Inbox" or "Recent conversations" views. While the bug has been present since moving messages between streams was first introduced in version 3.0, this option became much more common starting in Zulip 8.0, when the default option in the picker for moving the very last message in a conversation was changed. This issue is fixed in Zulip Server 8.3. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 19:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2714 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System booking-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2714</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/booking-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257467.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 19:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2713 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System booking-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2713</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/booking-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257466 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 19:07:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28286 | In mz-automation libiec61850 v1.4.0, a NULL Pointer Dereference was detected in the mmsServer_handleFileCloseRequest.c function of src/mms/i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28286</link><description>In mz-automation libiec61850 v1.4.0, a NULL Pointer Dereference was detected in the mmsServer_handleFileCloseRequest.c function of src/mms/iso_mms/server/mms_file_service.c. The vulnerability manifests as SEGV and causes the application to crash</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4963 | Folio Spring Module Core Schema Name HibernateSchemaService.java dropSchema sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4963</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Folio Spring Module Core up to 1.1.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function dropSchema of the file tenant/src/main/java/org/folio/spring/tenant/hibernate/HibernateSchemaService.java of the component Schema Name Handler. The manipulation leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 2.0.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is d374a5f77e6b58e36f0e0e4419be18b95edcd7ff. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257516.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2712 | Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System user-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2712</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Complete Online DJ Booking System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/user-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257465 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24813 | Frappe SQL Injection from reporting logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24813</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.64.0 and 15.0.0, SQL injection from a particular whitelisted method can result in access to data which the user doesn't have permission to access. Versions 14.64.0 and 15.0.0 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27105 | Frappe File Permissions can by bypassed using certain endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27105</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.66.3 and 15.16.0, file permission can be bypassed using certain endpoints, granting less privileged users permission to delete or clone a file. Versions 14.66.3 and 15.16.0 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23819 | GeoServer Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MapML HTML Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23819</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the MapML HTML Page. The MapML extension must be installed and access to the MapML HTML Page is available to all users although data security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23821 | GeoServer&amp;#x27;s GWC Demos Page vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23821</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the GWC Demos Page.  Access to the GWC Demos Page is available to all users although data security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2710 | Tenda AC10U openSchedWifi setSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2710</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. The manipulation of the argument schedStartTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257461 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2711 | Tenda AC10U addWifiMacFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2711</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function addWifiMacFilter of the file /goform/addWifiMacFilter. The manipulation of the argument deviceMac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257462 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23818 | GeoServer Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WMS OpenLayers Format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23818</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.3 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the WMS GetMap OpenLayers Output Format.  Access to the WMS OpenLayers Format is available to all users by default although data and service security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.3 and 2.24.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23643 | GeoServer Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in GWC Seed Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23643</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.2 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another administrator’s browser when viewed in the GWC Seed Form. Access to the GWC Seed Form is limited to full administrators by default and granting non-administrators access to this endpoint is not recommended. Versions 2.23.2 and 2.24.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23642 | GeoServer Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple SVG Renderer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23642</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the WMS GetMap SVG Output Format when the Simple SVG renderer is enabled. Access to the WMS SVG Format is available to all users by default although data and service security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2708 | Tenda AC10U execCommand formexeCommand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2708</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257459. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2709 | Tenda AC10U SetStaticRouteCfg fromSetRouteStatic stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2709</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromSetRouteStatic of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257460. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45177 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45177</link><description>IBM MQ 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, 9.2 LTS, 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD is vulnerable to a denial-of-service attack due to an error within the MQ clustering logic.  IBM X-Force ID:  268066.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2625 | Object lifecycle issue in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2625</link><description>Object lifecycle issue in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2626 | Out of bounds read in Swiftshader in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2626</link><description>Out of bounds read in Swiftshader in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2627 | Use after free in Canvas in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2627</link><description>Use after free in Canvas in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2628 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2628</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted URL. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2629 | Incorrect security UI in iOS in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML pag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2629</link><description>Incorrect security UI in iOS in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2630 | Inappropriate implementation in iOS in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2630</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in iOS in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2631 | Inappropriate implementation in iOS in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted H...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2631</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in iOS in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2707 | Tenda AC10U WriteFacMac formWriteFacMac os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2707</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formWriteFacMac of the file /goform/WriteFacMac. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2705 | Tenda AC10U SetNetControlList formSetQosBand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2705</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC10U 1.0/15.03.06.49. Affected by this issue is the function formSetQosBand of the file /goform/SetNetControlList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257456. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2706 | Tenda AC10U WifiWpsStart formWifiWpsStart stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2706</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. This affects the function formWifiWpsStart of the file /goform/WifiWpsStart. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257457 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2703 | Tenda AC10U SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2703</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. Affected is the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2704 | Tenda AC10U SetFirewallCfg formSetFirewallCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2704</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetFirewallCfg of the file /goform/SetFirewallCfg. The manipulation of the argument firewallEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257455. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23634 | GeoServer arbitrary file renaming vulnerability in REST Coverage/Data Store API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23634</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. An arbitrary file renaming vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.5 and 2.24.2 that enables an authenticated administrator with permissions to modify stores through the REST Coverage Store or Data Store API to rename arbitrary files and directories with a name that does not end in `.zip`. Store file uploads rename zip files to have a `.zip` extension if it doesn't already have one before unzipping the file.  This is fine for file and url upload methods where the files will be in a specific subdirectory of the data directory but, when using the external upload method, this allows arbitrary files and directories to be renamed. Renaming GeoServer files will most likely result in a denial of service, either completely preventing GeoServer from running or effectively deleting specific resources (such as a workspace, layer or style).  In some cases, renaming GeoServer files could revert to the default settings for that file which could be relatively harmless like removing contact information or have more serious consequences like allowing users to make OGC requests that the customized settings would have prevented them from making. The impact of renaming non-GeoServer files depends on the specific environment although some sort of denial of service is a likely outcome. Versions 2.23.5 and 2.24.2 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23640 | GeoServer Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Style Publisher</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23640</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in uploaded style/legend resources or in a specially crafted datastore file that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the Style Publisher. Access to the Style Publisher is available to all users although data security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50967 | latchset jose through version 11 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption) via a large p2c (aka PBES2 Count) value.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50967</link><description>latchset jose through version 11 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption) via a large p2c (aka PBES2 Count) value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51445 | GeoServer Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in REST Resources API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51445</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in uploaded style/legend resources that will execute in the context of another administrator's browser when viewed in the REST Resources API.  Access to the REST Resources API is limited to full administrators by default and granting non-administrators access to this endpoint should be carefully considered as it may allow access to files containing sensitive information. Versions 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51444 | GeoServer arbitrary file upload vulnerability in REST Coverage Store API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51444</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with permissions to modify coverage stores through the REST Coverage Store API to upload arbitrary file contents to arbitrary file locations which can lead to remote code execution. Coverage stores that are configured using relative paths use a GeoServer Resource implementation that has validation to prevent path traversal but coverage stores that are configured using absolute paths use a different Resource implementation that does not prevent path traversal. This vulnerability can lead to executing arbitrary code. An administrator with limited privileges could also potentially exploit this to overwrite GeoServer security files and obtain full administrator privileges. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2291 | MOVEit Transfer Logging Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2291</link><description>In Progress MOVEit Transfer versions released before 2022.0.11 (14.0.11), 2022.1.12 (14.1.12), 2023.0.9 (15.0.9), 2023.1.4 (15.1.4), a logging bypass vulnerability has been discovered.  An authenticated user could manipulate a request to bypass the logging mechanism within the web application which results in user activity not being logged properly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28735 | An incorrect access control issue in Unit4 Financials by Coda v.2023Q4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28735</link><description>An incorrect access control issue in Unit4 Financials by Coda v.2023Q4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the change password function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29419 | There is a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Wireless settings under the Easy Setup Page of TOTOLINK X2000R before v1.0.0-B202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29419</link><description>There is a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Wireless settings under the Easy Setup Page of TOTOLINK X2000R before v1.0.0-B20231213.1013.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41038 | Server crash when using specific form of SET BIND statement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41038</link><description>Firebird is a relational database. Versions 4.0.0 through 4.0.3 and version 5.0 beta1 are vulnerable to a server crash when a user uses a specific form of SET BIND statement. Any non-privileged user with minimum access to a server may type a statement with a long `CHAR` length, which causes the server to crash due to stack corruption. Versions 4.0.4.2981 and 5.0.0.117 contain fixes for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41877 | GeoServer log file path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41877</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A path traversal vulnerability in versions 2.23.4 and prior requires GeoServer Administrator with access to the admin console to misconfigure the Global Settings for log file location to an arbitrary location. The admin console GeoServer Logs page provides a preview of these contents. As this issue requires GeoServer administrators access, often representing a trusted party, the vulnerability has not received a patch as of time of publication. As a workaround, a system administrator responsible for running GeoServer can use the `GEOSERVER_LOG_FILE` setting to override any configuration option provided by the Global Settings page. The `GEOSERVER_LOG_LOCATION` parameter can be set as system property, environment variables, or servlet context parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28395 | SQL injection vulnerability in Best-Kit bestkit_popup v.1.7.2 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the bestkit_pop...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28395</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Best-Kit bestkit_popup v.1.7.2 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the bestkit_popup.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28392 | SQL injection vulnerability in pscartabandonmentpro v.2.0.11 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the pscartabando...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28392</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in pscartabandonmentpro v.2.0.11 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the pscartabandonmentproFrontCAPUnsubscribeJobModuleFrontController::setEmailVisualized() method.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28396 | An issue in MyPrestaModules ordersexport v.6.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the download.php componen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28396</link><description>An issue in MyPrestaModules ordersexport v.6.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the download.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35888 | IBM Security Verify Governance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35888</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  258375.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1800 | Progress Telerik Report Server Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1800</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q1 (10.0.24.130), a remote code execution attack is possible through an insecure deserialization vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1801 | Progress Telerik Reporting Local Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1801</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q1 (18.0.24.130), a code execution attack is possible by a local threat actor through an insecure deserialization vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1856 | Progress Telerik Reporting Remote Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1856</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q1 (18.0.24.130), a code execution attack is possible by a remote threat actor through an insecure deserialization vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1811 | OpenText ArcSight Platform Remote Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1811</link><description>A potential vulnerability has been identified in OpenText ArcSight Platform. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2721 | WordPress Social Media Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2721</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Social Media Share Buttons By Sygnoos Social Media Share Buttons.This issue affects Social Media Share Buttons: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 11:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52229 | WordPress Word Replacer Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52229</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd Word Replacer Pro.This issue affects Word Replacer Pro: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 11:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46840 | VT-d: Failure to quarantine devices in !HVM builds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46840</link><description>Incorrect placement of a preprocessor directive in source code results
in logic that doesn't operate as intended when support for HVM guests is
compiled out of Xen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46841 | x86: shadow stack vs exceptions from emulation stubs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46841</link><description>Recent x86 CPUs offer functionality named Control-flow Enforcement
Technology (CET).  A sub-feature of this are Shadow Stacks (CET-SS).
CET-SS is a hardware feature designed to protect against Return Oriented
Programming attacks. When enabled, traditional stacks holding both data
and return addresses are accompanied by so called "shadow stacks",
holding little more than return addresses.  Shadow stacks aren't
writable by normal instructions, and upon function returns their
contents are used to check for possible manipulation of a return address
coming from the traditional stack.

In particular certain memory accesses need intercepting by Xen.  In
various cases the necessary emulation involves kind of replaying of
the instruction.  Such replaying typically involves filling and then
invoking of a stub.  Such a replayed instruction may raise an
exceptions, which is expected and dealt with accordingly.

Unfortunately the interaction of both of the above wasn't right:
Recovery involves removal of a call frame from the (traditional) stack.
The counterpart of this operation for the shadow stack was missing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46839 | pci: phantom functions assigned to incorrect contexts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46839</link><description>PCI devices can make use of a functionality called phantom functions,
that when enabled allows the device to generate requests using the IDs
of functions that are otherwise unpopulated.  This allows a device to
extend the number of outstanding requests.

Such phantom functions need an IOMMU context setup, but failure to
setup the context is not fatal when the device is assigned.  Not
failing device assignment when such failure happens can lead to the
primary device being assigned to a guest, while some of the phantom
functions are assigned to a different domain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2690 | SourceCodester Online Discussion Forum Site uupdate.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2690</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Discussion Forum Site 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /uupdate.php. The manipulation of the argument ima leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257388.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2686 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2686</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/applicants/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument JOBREGID leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2687 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2687</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/applicants/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257387.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2702 | WordPress Olive One Click Demo Import plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2702</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Olive Themes Olive One Click Demo Import allows importing settings and data, ultimately leading to XSS.This issue affects Olive One Click Demo Import: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2685 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2685</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/applicants/index.php. The manipulation of the argument view leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257385 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2683 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2683</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/company/index.php. The manipulation of the argument view leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257383.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2684 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2684</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/category/index.php. The manipulation of the argument view leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257384.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2682 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2682</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/employee/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument EMPLOYEEID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2680 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2680</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/user/index.php. The manipulation of the argument view leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257380.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2681 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2681</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/employee/index.php. The manipulation of the argument view leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257381 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2678 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/applicants/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument JOBREGID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257378 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2679 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2679</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/vacancy/index.php. The manipulation of the argument view leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257379.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1119 | The Order Tip for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1119</link><description>The Order Tip for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_tips_to_csv() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export the plugin's order fees.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1181 | The Coming Soon, Under Construction &amp; Maintenance Mode By Dazzler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to maintenance mode bypass in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1181</link><description>The Coming Soon, Under Construction &amp; Maintenance Mode By Dazzler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to maintenance mode bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to the plugin relying on the REQUEST_URI to determine if the page being accesses is an admin area.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass maintenance mode and access the site which may be considered confidential when in maintenance mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1205 | The Management App for WooCommerce – Order notifications, Order management, Lead management, Uptime Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1205</link><description>The Management App for WooCommerce – Order notifications, Order management, Lead management, Uptime Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the nouvello_upload_csv_file function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1325 | The Live Sales Notification for Woocommerce – Woomotiv plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1325</link><description>The Live Sales Notification for Woocommerce – Woomotiv plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ajax_cancel_review' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the site's review count via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1379 | The Website Article Monetization By MageNet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'abp_auth_key' paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1379</link><description>The Website Article Monetization By MageNet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'abp_auth_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping and a missing authorization check. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1473 | The Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance Mode by Colorlib plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1473</link><description>The Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance Mode by Colorlib plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.99 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain post and page contents via REST API thus bypassing maintenance mode protection provided by the plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1477 | The Easy Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1477</link><description>The Easy Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 via the REST API. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to obtain post and page content via REST API thus bypassign the protection provided by the plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1711 | The Create by Mediavine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1711</link><description>The Create by Mediavine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1844 | The RevivePress – Keep your Old Content Evergreen plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1844</link><description>The RevivePress – Keep your Old Content Evergreen plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the import_data and copy_data functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access or higher, to overwrite plugin settings and view them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2129 | The WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's heading widg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2129</link><description>The WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2304 | The Animated Headline plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'animated-headline' shortcode in al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2304</link><description>The Animated Headline plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'animated-headline' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2459 | The UX Flat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2459</link><description>The UX Flat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2677 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2677</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/category/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument CATEGORYID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257377 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28562 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Imf_2_2::c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28562</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Imf_2_2::copyIntoFrameBuffer() component when reading images in EXR format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28563 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28563</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the Imf_2_2::DwaCompressor::Classifier::Classifier() function when reading images in EXR format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28564 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28564</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the Imf_2_2::CharPtrIO::readChars() function when reading images in EXR format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28565 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28565</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the psdParser::ReadImageData() function when reading images in PSD format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28566 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AssignPixe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28566</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AssignPixel() function when reading images in TIFF format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28567 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28567</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the FreeImage_CreateICCProfile() function when reading images in TIFF format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28568 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28568</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the read_iptc_profile() function when reading images in TIFF format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28569 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Imf_2_2::X...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28569</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Imf_2_2::Xdr::read() function when reading images in EXR format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28570 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28570</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the processMakerNote() function when reading images in JPEG format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28571 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28571</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the fill_input_buffer() function when reading images in JPEG format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28572 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28572</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the FreeImage_SetTagValue() function when reading images in JPEG format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28573 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the j...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28573</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the jpeg_read_exif_profile() function when reading images in JPEG format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28574 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28574</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the opj_j2k_copy_default_tcp_and_create_tcd() function when reading images in J2K format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28575 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28575</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the opj_j2k_read_mct() function when reading images in J2K format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28576 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28576</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the opj_j2k_tcp_destroy() function when reading images in J2K format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28577 | Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28577</link><description>Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the jpeg_read_exif_profile_raw() function when reading images in JPEG format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28578 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Load() fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28578</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Load() function when reading images in RAS format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28579 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28579</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the FreeImage_Unload() function when reading images in HDR format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28580 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ReadData()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28580</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ReadData() function when reading images in RAS format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28581 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the _assignPix...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28581</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the _assignPixel&lt;&gt;() function when reading images in TARGA format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28582 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the rgbe_RGBET...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28582</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the rgbe_RGBEToFloat() function when reading images in HDR format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28583 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the readLine()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28583</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the readLine() function when reading images in XPM format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28584 | Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28584</link><description>Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in open source FreeImage v.3.19.0 [r1909] allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the J2KImageToFIBITMAP() function when reading images in J2K format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2675 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2675</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/company/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257375.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2676 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2676</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/company/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257376.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2538 | The Permalink Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2538</link><description>The Permalink Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_save_permalink' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author access and above, to modify the permalinks of arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2674 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2674</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/employee/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257374 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7246 | System Dashboard &amp;lt; 2.8.10 - XSS via Header Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7246</link><description>The System Dashboard WordPress plugin before 2.8.10 does not sanitize and escape some parameters, which could allow administrators in multisite WordPress configurations to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0337 | Travelpayouts &amp;lt;= 1.1.15 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0337</link><description>The Travelpayouts: All Travel Brands in One Place WordPress plugin through 1.1.15 is vulnerable to Open Redirect due to insufficient validation on the travelpayouts_redirect variable. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0856 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt; 1.3.83 - CSRF appointment scheduling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0856</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar WordPress plugin before 1.3.83 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks such as adding a booking to the calendar without paying.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1983 | Simple Ajax Chat &amp;lt; 20240223 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1983</link><description>The Simple Ajax Chat  WordPress plugin before 20240223 does not prevent visitors from using malicious Names when using the chat, which will be reflected unsanitized to other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2673 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2673</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257373 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22077 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. The SQLite database file has weak permissions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22077</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. The SQLite database file has weak permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22078 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Privilege escalation can occur via world writable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22078</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Privilege escalation can occur via world writable files. The network configuration script has weak filesystem permissions. This results in write access for all authenticated users and the possibility to escalate from user privileges to administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22079 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Directory traversal can occur via the system logs ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22079</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Directory traversal can occur via the system logs download mechanism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22080 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Unauthenticated memory corruption can occur during...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22080</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Unauthenticated memory corruption can occur during XML body parsing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22081 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Unauthenticated memory corruption can occur in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22081</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Unauthenticated memory corruption can occur in the HTTP header parsing mechanism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22082 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Unauthenticated directory listing can occur: the w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22082</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Unauthenticated directory listing can occur: the web interface cay be abused be an attacker get a better understanding of the operating system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22083 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. A hardcoded backdoor session ID exists that can be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22083</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. A hardcoded backdoor session ID exists that can be used for further access to the device, including reconfiguration tasks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22084 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Cleartext passwords and hashes are exposed through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22084</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. Cleartext passwords and hashes are exposed through log files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22085 | An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. The shadow file is world readable.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22085</link><description>An issue was discovered in Elspec G5 digital fault recorder versions 1.1.4.15 and before. The shadow file is world readable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2124 | The Translate WordPress and go Multilingual – Weglot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2124</link><description>The Translate WordPress and go Multilingual – Weglot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget/block in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'className'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2474 | The Standout Color Boxes and Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'color-button' short...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2474</link><description>The Standout Color Boxes and Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'color-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2672 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2672</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/user/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument UESRID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257372.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2670 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2670</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/vacancy/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257370 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2671 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2671</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/user/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257371.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22258 | CVE-2024-22258: PKCE Downgrade in Spring Authorization Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22258</link><description>Spring Authorization Server versions 1.0.0 - 1.0.5, 1.1.0 - 1.1.5, 1.2.0 - 1.2.2 and older unsupported versions are susceptible to a PKCE Downgrade Attack for Confidential Clients.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when a Confidential Client uses PKCE for the Authorization Code Grant.

An application is not vulnerable when a Public Client uses PKCE for the Authorization Code Grant.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2255 | The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2255</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as listStyle. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1799 | The GamiPress – The #1 gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1799</link><description>The GamiPress – The #1 gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'achievement_types' attribute of the gamipress_earnings shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.8.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2384 | The WooCommerce POS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.11. This is due t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2384</link><description>The WooCommerce POS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.11. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying the authentication and authorization of the current user This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with customer-level access and above, to view potentially sensitive information about other users by leveraging their order id</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2460 | The GamiPress – Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gamipress_button' shortcode in al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2460</link><description>The GamiPress – Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gamipress_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1785 | The Contests by Rewards Fuel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.62. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1785</link><description>The Contests by Rewards Fuel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.62. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ajax_handler() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site's user with the edit_posts capability into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1787 | The Contests by Rewards Fuel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'update_rewards_fuel_api_key' paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1787</link><description>The Contests by Rewards Fuel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'update_rewards_fuel_api_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.64 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1995 | The Smart Custom Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the relationa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1995</link><description>The Smart Custom Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the relational_posts_search() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscrber-level access and above, to retrieve post content that is password protected and/or private.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2387 | The Advanced Form Integration – Connect WooCommerce and Contact Form 7 to Google Sheets and other platforms plugin for WordPress is vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2387</link><description>The Advanced Form Integration – Connect WooCommerce and Contact Form 7 to Google Sheets and other platforms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘integration_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.82.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries and subsequently inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2668 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2668</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/vacancy/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument id/CATEGORY leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257368.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2669 | Campcodes Online Job Finder System GET Parameter controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2669</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Job Finder System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/employee/controller.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument EMPLOYEEID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257369 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 02:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2197 | Chirp Systems Chirp Access Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2197</link><description>Chirp Access improperly stores credentials within its source code, potentially exposing sensitive information to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 23:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2649 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway deleteonlineuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /protocol/iscdevicestatus/deleteonlineuser.php. The manipulation of the argument messagecontent leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257287. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 23:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2647 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway singlelogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2647</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/singlelogin.php. The manipulation of the argument loginId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257285 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 23:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2648 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway naccheck.php xpath injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2648</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /nac/naccheck.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to improper neutralization of data within xpath expressions. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257286 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 23:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2645 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway resetpwd.php xpath injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2645</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /vpnweb/resetpwd/resetpwd.php. The manipulation of the argument UserId leads to improper neutralization of data within xpath expressions. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257283. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 22:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2646 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2646</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /vpnweb/index.php?para=index. The manipulation of the argument check_VirtualSiteId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257284. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 22:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2644 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway addfirewall.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2644</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /protocol/firewall/addfirewall.php. The manipulation of the argument FireWallTableArray leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257282 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50811 | An issue discovered in SELESTA Visual Access Manager 4.38.6 allows attackers to modify the “computer” POST parameter related to the ID of a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50811</link><description>An issue discovered in SELESTA Visual Access Manager 4.38.6 allows attackers to modify the “computer” POST parameter related to the ID of a specific reception by POST HTTP request interception. Iterating that parameter, it has been possible to access to the application and take control of many other receptions in addition the assigned one.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2642 | Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P EXCU_SHELL command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2642</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P up to 20240305. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /EXCU_SHELL. The manipulation of the argument Command1 leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257281 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28283 | There is stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in pc_change_act function in Linksys E1000 router firmware version v.2.1.03 and before, l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28283</link><description>There is stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in pc_change_act function in Linksys E1000 router firmware version v.2.1.03 and before, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28092 | UBEE DDW365 XCNDDW365 8.14.3105 software on hardware 3.13.1 allows a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity to conduct stored XSS attacks vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28092</link><description>UBEE DDW365 XCNDDW365 8.14.3105 software on hardware 3.13.1 allows a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity to conduct stored XSS attacks via RgFirewallEL.asp, RgDdns.asp, RgTime.asp, RgDiagnostics.asp, or RgParentalBasic.asp. The affected fields are SMTP Server Name, SMTP Username, Host Name, Time Server 1, Time Server 2, Time Server 3, Target, Add Keyword, Add Domain, and Add Allowed Domain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28389 | SQL injection vulnerability in KnowBand spinwheel v.3.0.3 and before allows a remote attacker to gain escalated privileges and obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28389</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in KnowBand spinwheel v.3.0.3 and before allows a remote attacker to gain escalated privileges and obtain sensitive information via the SpinWheelFrameSpinWheelModuleFrontController::sendEmail() method.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28715 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DOraCMS v.2.18 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the markdown0 functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28715</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DOraCMS v.2.18 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the markdown0 function in the /app/public/apidoc/oas3/wrap-components/markdown.jsx endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2641 | Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P Password passwdManage.htm improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2641</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P up to 20240305. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/passwdManage.htm of the component Password Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257280. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 20:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24336 | A multiple Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the '/members/moremember.pl', and ‘/members/members-home.pl’ endpoints within Koha Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24336</link><description>A multiple Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the '/members/moremember.pl', and ‘/members/members-home.pl’ endpoints within Koha Library Management System version 23.05.05 and earlier allows malicious staff users to carry out CSRF attacks, including unauthorized changes to usernames and passwords of users visiting the affected page, via the 'Circulation note' and ‘Patrons Restriction’ components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 20:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28595 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the admin_id parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28595</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the admin_id parameter in update-admin.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 20:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2169 | Implementations of UDP application protocols are susceptible to network loops and denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2169</link><description>Implementations of UDP application protocol are vulnerable to network loops.   An unauthenticated attacker can use maliciously-crafted packets against a vulnerable implementation that can lead to Denial of Service (DOS) and/or abuse of resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28394 | An issue in Advanced Plugins reportsstatistics v1.3.20 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sales Reports, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28394</link><description>An issue in Advanced Plugins reportsstatistics v1.3.20 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sales Reports, Statistics, Custom Fields &amp; Export module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28303 | Open Source Medicine Ordering System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the date parameter at /admin/reports/i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28303</link><description>Open Source Medicine Ordering System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the date parameter at /admin/reports/index.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29027 | Parse Server crash and RCE via invalid Cloud Function or Cloud Job name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29027</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. Prior to versions 6.5.5 and 7.0.0-alpha.29, calling an invalid Parse Server Cloud Function name or Cloud Job name crashes the server and may allow for code injection, internal store manipulation or remote code execution. The patch in versions 6.5.5 and 7.0.0-alpha.29 added string sanitation for Cloud Function name and Cloud Job name. As a workaround, sanitize the Cloud Function name and Cloud Job name before it reaches Parse Server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21677 | This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link><description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27996 | WordPress Survey Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27996</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Survey Maker team Survey Maker allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Survey Maker: from n/a through 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42920 | Claris International has fixed a dylib hijacking vulnerability in the FileMaker Pro.app and Claris Pro.app versions on macOS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42920</link><description>Claris International has fixed a dylib hijacking vulnerability in the FileMaker Pro.app and Claris Pro.app versions on macOS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27997 | WordPress Visual Composer plugin &amp;lt;= 45.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27997</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Visualcomposer Visual Composer Website Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Visual Composer Website Builder: from n/a through 45.6.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27998 | WordPress Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27998</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29089 | WordPress Restaurant Menu and Food Ordering plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29089</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Five Star Plugins Five Star Restaurant Menu allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Five Star Restaurant Menu: from n/a through 2.4.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29091 | WordPress WP Armour plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.13 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dnesscarkey WP Armour – Honeypot Anti Spam allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Armour – Honeypot Anti Spam: from n/a through 2.1.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29092 | WordPress Permalink Manager Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29092</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Maciej Bis Permalink Manager Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Permalink Manager Lite: from n/a through 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29093 | WordPress Builder for WooCommerce reviews shortcodes – ReviewShort plugin &amp;lt;= 1.01.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29093</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tobias Conrad Builder for WooCommerce reviews shortcodes – ReviewShort.This issue affects Builder for WooCommerce reviews shortcodes – ReviewShort: from n/a through 1.01.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29094 | WordPress HT Easy GA4  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29094</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HasThemes HT Easy GA4 ( Google Analytics 4 ) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects HT Easy GA4 ( Google Analytics 4 ): from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41793 | Path Traversal and Untrusted Upload File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41793</link><description>: Path Traversal vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Path Traversal. This vulnerability allowed changing directories and creating files and downloading them outside the allowed directories. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;776.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44091 | Unauth Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows SQL Injection. This ulnerability allowed SQL injections to be made even if authentication failed.This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;776.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44092 | OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44092</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows OS Command Injection. This vulnerability allowed to create a reverse shell and execute commands in the OS. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;776.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44090 | UnautH SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44090</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows CVE-2008-5817. This vulnerability allowed SQL changes to be made to several files in the Grafana module. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;776.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2442 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Franklin Fueling System EVO 550/5000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2442</link><description>Franklin Fueling System EVO 550 and EVO 5000 are vulnerable to a Path Traversal vulnerability that could allow an attacker to access sensitive files on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2307 | Osbuild-composer: race condition may disable gpg verification for package repositories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2307</link><description>A flaw was found in osbuild-composer. A condition can be triggered that disables GPG verification for package repositories, which can expose the build phase to a Man-in-the-Middle attack, allowing untrusted code to be installed into an image being built.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29095 | WordPress Site Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 6.11.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29095</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Paul Ryley Site Reviews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Site Reviews: from n/a through 6.11.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29096 | WordPress MJM Clinic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29096</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Manning MJM Clinic.This issue affects MJM Clinic: from n/a through 1.1.22.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29097 | WordPress User profile plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.20 - Subscriber+ Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29097</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins User profile allows Stored XSS.This issue affects User profile: from n/a through 2.0.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29098 | WordPress WP Calameo plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29098</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Calameo WP Calameo allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Calameo: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29099 | WordPress Evergreen Content Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29099</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Evergreen Content Poster allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Evergreen Content Poster: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32259 | Potential Insufficient Access Control  vulnerability has been identified in OpenText™ SMAX/AMX products.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32259</link><description>Insufficient Granularity of Access Control vulnerability in OpenText™ Service Management Automation X (SMAX), OpenText™ Asset Management X (AMX) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Service Management Automation X (SMAX) versions 2020.05, 2020.08, 2020.11, 2021.02, 2021.05, 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11; and Asset Management X (AMX) versions 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32260 | A potential Misinterpretation of Input vulnerability has been identified in SMAX, AMX, and HCMX products.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32260</link><description>Misinterpretation of Input vulnerability in OpenText™ Service Management Automation X (SMAX), OpenText™ Asset Management X (AMX), and OpenText™ Hybrid Cloud Management X (HCMX) products. The vulnerability could allow Input data manipulation.This issue affects Service Management Automation X (SMAX) versions: 2020.05, 2020.08, 2020.11, 2021.02, 2021.05, 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11, 2023.05; Asset Management X (AMX) versions: 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11, 2023.05; and Hybrid Cloud Management X (HCMX) versions: 2020.05, 2020.08, 2020.11, 2021.02, 2021.05, 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11, 2023.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29101 | WordPress Jeg Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29101</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jegtheme Jeg Elementor Kit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jeg Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29102 | WordPress Extensions For CF7 plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Unauthenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29102</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HasThemes Extensions For CF7 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Extensions For CF7: from n/a through 3.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6597 | An issue was found in the CPython `tempfile.TemporaryDirectory` class affecting versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.13, 3.9.18, and 3.8.18 and pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6597</link><description>An issue was found in the CPython `tempfile.TemporaryDirectory` class affecting versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.13, 3.9.18, and 3.8.18 and prior.

The tempfile.TemporaryDirectory class would dereference symlinks during cleanup of permissions-related errors. This means users which can run privileged programs are potentially able to modify permissions of files referenced by symlinks in some circumstances.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29103 | WordPress Database for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Unauthenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29103</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NinjaTeam Database for Contact Form 7 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Database for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 3.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29104 | WordPress Ticket Tailor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29104</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zimma Ltd. Ticket Tailor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ticket Tailor: from n/a through 1.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29105 | WordPress WP Popups – WordPress Popup builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29105</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Timersys WP Popups allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Popups: from n/a through 2.1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29106 | WordPress Premium Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29106</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29107 | WordPress Elementor Addon Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29107</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPVibes Elementor Addon Elements allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Addon Elements: from n/a through 1.12.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29108 | WordPress Happy Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29108</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leevio Happy Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Happy Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 3.10.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0450 | Quoted zip-bomb protection for zipfile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0450</link><description>An issue was found in the CPython `zipfile` module affecting versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.13, 3.9.18, and 3.8.18 and prior.

The zipfile module is vulnerable to “quoted-overlap” zip-bombs which exploit the zip format to create a zip-bomb with a high compression ratio. The fixed versions of CPython makes the zipfile module reject zip archives which overlap entries in the archive.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29109 | WordPress Shariff Wrapper plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.10 - Contributor+ Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29109</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jan-Peter Lambeck &amp; 3UU Shariff Wrapper allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Shariff Wrapper: from n/a through 4.6.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29110 | WordPress Tablesome plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.27 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29110</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pauple Table &amp; Contact Form 7 Database – Tablesome allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Table &amp; Contact Form 7 Database – Tablesome: from n/a through 1.0.27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29111 | WordPress Sitekit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29111</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webvitaly Sitekit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sitekit: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29112 | WordPress WooCommerce Google Feed Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29112</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Marketing Robot WooCommerce Google Feed Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Google Feed Manager: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29113 | WordPress RegistrationMagic  plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.5.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29113</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.2.5.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29114 | WordPress Download Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.84 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29114</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in W3 Eden, Inc. Download Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Download Manager: from n/a through 3.2.84.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2639 | Bdtask Wholesale Inventory Management System session fixiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2639</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Wholesale Inventory Management System up to 20240311. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257245 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29115 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29115</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Smart Online Order for Clover: from n/a through 1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29116 | WordPress WooThumbs for WooCommerce by Iconic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29116</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in IconicWP WooThumbs for WooCommerce by Iconic allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooThumbs for WooCommerce by Iconic: from n/a through 5.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29117 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29117</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cimatti Consulting Contact Forms by Cimatti allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Forms by Cimatti: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29118 | WordPress Scrollsequence plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29118</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scrollsequence allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Scrollsequence: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29121 | WordPress WooCommerce License Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Firassaidi WooCommerce License Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce License Manager: from n/a through 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29122 | WordPress FV Player plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.41.7212 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Foliovision: Making the web work for you FV Flowplayer Video Player allows Stored XSS.This issue affects FV Flowplayer Video Player: from n/a through 7.5.41.7212.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29123 | WordPress Link Library plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29123</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1401 | Profile Box Shortcode And Widget &amp;lt; 1.2.1 Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1401</link><description>The Profile Box Shortcode And Widget WordPress plugin before 1.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29124 | WordPress Advanced Access Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AAM Advanced Access Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Access Manager: from n/a through 6.9.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29125 | WordPress Coupon Affiliates plugin &amp;lt;= 5.12.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elliot Sowersby, RelyWP Coupon Affiliates allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Coupon Affiliates: from n/a through 5.12.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50966 | erlang-jose (aka JOSE for Erlang and Elixir) through 1.11.6 allow attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption) via a large p2c (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50966</link><description>erlang-jose (aka JOSE for Erlang and Elixir) through 1.11.6 allow attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption) via a large p2c (aka PBES2 Count) value in a JOSE header.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29126 | WordPress Specific Content For Mobile plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.9.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29126</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jose Mortellaro Specific Content For Mobile – Customize the mobile version without redirections allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Specific Content For Mobile – Customize the mobile version without redirections: from n/a through 0.1.9.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29127 | WordPress Advanced Access Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.20 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AAM Advanced Access Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Advanced Access Manager: from n/a through 6.9.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29128 | WordPress POST SMTP Mailer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29128</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Post SMTP POST SMTP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects POST SMTP: from n/a through 2.8.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29129 | WordPress OxyExtras plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29129</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPLIT Pty Ltd OxyExtras allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects OxyExtras: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29130 | WordPress Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe Add-on plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29130</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scott Paterson Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp; Stripe Add-on allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp; Stripe Add-on: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29134 | WordPress Tourfic plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themefic Tourfic allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tourfic: from n/a through 2.11.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29135 | WordPress Tourfic plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.15 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29135</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Tourfic.This issue affects Tourfic: from n/a through 2.11.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29136 | WordPress Tourfic plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.17 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29136</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Themefic Tourfic.This issue affects Tourfic: from n/a through 2.11.17.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29137 | WordPress Tourfic plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themefic Tourfic allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tourfic: from n/a through 2.11.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29138 | WordPress Restrict User Access plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29138</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DEV Institute Restrict User Access – Membership Plugin with Force allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Restrict User Access – Membership Plugin with Force: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29139 | WordPress MyCurator Content Curation plugin &amp;lt;= 3.76 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29139</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mark Tilly MyCurator Content Curation allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects MyCurator Content Curation: from n/a through 3.76.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29140 | WordPress MJM Clinic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29140</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Manning MJM Clinic allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MJM Clinic: from n/a through 1.1.22.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28734 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Unit4 Financials by Coda v.2024Q1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28734</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Unit4 Financials by Coda v.2024Q1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the cols parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29141 | WordPress PDF Embedder plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29141</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PDF Embedder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PDF Embedder: from n/a through 4.6.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29142 | WordPress Better Search plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29142</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebberZone Better Search – Relevant search results for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Better Search – Relevant search results for WordPress: from n/a through 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29143 | WordPress Passwordless Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29143</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cozmoslabs, sareiodata Passwordless Login passwordless-login allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Passwordless Login: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40279 | An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An attacker can perform a directory path traversal via the Page parameter in a GET reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40279</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An attacker can perform a directory path traversal via the Page parameter in a GET request to main.do.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2636 | Multiple vulnerabilities on Meta4 HR from Cegid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2636</link><description>An Unrestricted Upload of File vulnerability has been found on Cegid Meta4 HR, that allows an attacker to upload malicios files to the server via '/config/espanol/update_password.jsp' file. Modifying the 'M4_NEW_PASSWORD' parameter, an attacker could store a malicious JSP file inside the file directory, to be executed the the file is loaded in the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5388 | NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recov...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5388</link><description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2605 | An attacker could have leveraged the Windows Error Reporter to run arbitrary code on the system escaping the sandbox. *Note:* This issue onl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2605</link><description>An attacker could have leveraged the Windows Error Reporter to run arbitrary code on the system escaping the sandbox. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2606 | Passing invalid data could have led to invalid wasm values being created, such as arbitrary integers turning into pointer values. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2606</link><description>Passing invalid data could have led to invalid wasm values being created, such as arbitrary integers turning into pointer values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2607 | Return registers were overwritten which could have allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary code. *Note:* This issue only affected Armv7-A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2607</link><description>Return registers were overwritten which could have allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary code. *Note:* This issue only affected Armv7-A systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2608 | `AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2608</link><description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2609 | The permission prompt input delay could have expired while the window is not in focus, which made the prompt vulnerable to clickjacking by m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2609</link><description>The permission prompt input delay could have expired while the window is not in focus, which made the prompt vulnerable to clickjacking by malicious websites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2610 | Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2610</link><description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2611 | A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2611</link><description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2612 | If an attacker could find a way to trigger a particular code path in `SafeRefPtr`, it could have triggered a crash or potentially be leverag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2612</link><description>If an attacker could find a way to trigger a particular code path in `SafeRefPtr`, it could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2613 | Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2613</link><description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2614 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123, Firefox ESR 115.8, and Thunderbird 115.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2614</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123, Firefox ESR 115.8, and Thunderbird 115.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2615 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2615</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2616 | To harden ICU against exploitation, the behavior for out-of-memory conditions was changed to crash instead of attempt to continue. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2616</link><description>To harden ICU against exploitation, the behavior for out-of-memory conditions was changed to crash instead of attempt to continue. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9 and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2633 | Multiple vulnerabilities on Meta4 HR from Cegid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2633</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability has been found on Meta4 HR affecting version 819.001.022 and earlier. The endpoint '/sitetest/english/dumpenv.jsp' is vulnerable to XSS attack by 'lang' query, i.e. '/sitetest/english/dumpenv.jsp?snoop=yes&amp;lang=%27%3Cimg%20src/onerror=alert(1)%3E&amp;params'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2634 | Multiple vulnerabilities on Meta4 HR from Cegid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2634</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability has been found on Meta4 HR affecting version 819.001.022 and earlier. The endpoint '/sse_generico/generico_login.jsp' is vulnerable to XSS attack via 'lang' query, i.e. '/sse_generico/generico_login.jsp?lang=%27%3balert(%27BLEUSS%27)%2f%2f&amp;params='.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2635 | Multiple vulnerabilities on Meta4 HR from Cegid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2635</link><description>The configuration pages available are not intended to be placed on an Internet facing web server, as they expose file paths to the client, who can be an attacker. Instead of rewriting these pages to avoid this vulnerability, they will be dismissed from future releases of Cegid Meta4 HR, as they do not offer product functionality</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40278 | An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An Information Disclosure vulnerability has been identified in the printAppointmentPdf.js...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40278</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An Information Disclosure vulnerability has been identified in the printAppointmentPdf.jsp component of OpenClinic GA. By changing the AppointmentUid parameter, an attacker can determine whether a specific appointment exists based on the error message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2632 | Information Exposure Vulnerability on Meta4 HR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2632</link><description>A Information Exposure Vulnerability has been found on Meta4 HR. This vulnerability allows an attacker to obtain a lot of information about the application such as the variables set in the process, the Tomcat versions, library versions and underlying operation system via HTTP GET '/sitetest/english/dumpenv.jsp'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1144 | Improper Access Control at Alma Devklan Blog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1144</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Devklan's Alma Blog that affects versions 2.1.10 and earlier. This vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated user to access the application's functionalities without the need for credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1145 | Observable Response Discrepancy at Alma Devklan Blog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1145</link><description>User enumeration vulnerability in Devklan's Alma Blog that affects versions 2.1.10 and earlier. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to retrieve all valid users registered in the application just by looking at the request response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1146 | Cross-site Scripting at Alma Devklan Blog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1146</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in Devklan's Alma Blog that affects versions 2.1.10 and earlier. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to store a malicious JavaScript payload within the application by adding the payload to 'Community Description' or 'Community Rules'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27439 | Apache Wicket: Possible bypass of CSRF protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27439</link><description>An error in the evaluation of the fetch metadata headers could allow a bypass of the CSRF protection in Apache Wicket.
This issue affects Apache Wicket: from 9.1.0 through 9.16.0, and the milestone releases for the 10.0 series.
Apache Wicket 8.x does not support CSRF protection via the fetch metadata headers and as such is not affected.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.17.0 or 10.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24683 | Apache Hop Engine: ID isn&amp;#x27;t escaped when generating HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24683</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Hop Engine.This issue affects Apache Hop Engine: before 2.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.0, which fixes the issue.

When Hop Server writes links to the PrepareExecutionPipelineServlet page one of the parameters provided to the user was not properly escaped.
The variable not properly escaped is the "id", which is not directly accessible by users creating pipelines making the risk of exploiting this low.

This issue only affects users using the Hop Server component and does not directly affect the client.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25942 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS contains an Improper SMM communication buffer verification vulnerability. A physical high privileged attacker cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25942</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS contains an Improper SMM communication buffer verification vulnerability. A physical high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to arbitrary writes to SMRAM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22453 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS contains a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22453</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS contains a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to write to otherwise unauthorized memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0055 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX APIs mediaclip.cgi and playclip.cgi was vulnerable for file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0055</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX APIs mediaclip.cgi and playclip.cgi was vulnerable for file globbing which could lead to a resource exhaustion attack. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 06:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0054 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX APIs local_list.cgi, create_overlay.cgi and irissetup.cgi w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0054</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX APIs local_list.cgi, create_overlay.cgi and irissetup.cgi was vulnerable for file globbing which could lead to a resource exhaustion attack. Axis has released patched AXIS OS
versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory
for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 06:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24042 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Devan-Kerman ARRP v.0.8.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dumpDir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24042</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Devan-Kerman ARRP v.0.8.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dumpDirect in RuntimeResourcePackImpl component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 06:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24043 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Speedy11CZ MCRPX v.1.4.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24043</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Speedy11CZ MCRPX v.1.4.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 06:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26369 | An issue in the HistoryQosPolicy component of FastDDS v2.12.x, v2.11.x, v2.10.x, and v2.6.x leads to a SIGABRT (signal abort) upon receiving...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26369</link><description>An issue in the HistoryQosPolicy component of FastDDS v2.12.x, v2.11.x, v2.10.x, and v2.6.x leads to a SIGABRT (signal abort) upon receiving DataWriter's data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 05:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28446 | Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini1 v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via lan_netmask parameter at /apply.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28446</link><description>Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini1 v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via lan_netmask parameter at /apply.cgi.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 05:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28447 | Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini1 v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via lan_ipaddr parameters at /apply.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28447</link><description>Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-mini1 v1.2.9 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via lan_ipaddr parameters at /apply.cgi.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 05:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21503 | Versions of the package black before 24.3.0 are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) via the lines_with_leading_tabs_e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21503</link><description>Versions of the package black before 24.3.0 are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) via the lines_with_leading_tabs_expanded function in the strings.py file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious input that causes a denial of service.&#13;&#13;Exploiting this vulnerability is possible when running Black on untrusted input, or if you habitually put thousands of leading tab characters in your docstrings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 05:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21504 | Versions of the package livewire/livewire from 3.3.5 and before 3.4.9 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when a page uses [Url] fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21504</link><description>Versions of the package livewire/livewire from 3.3.5 and before 3.4.9 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when a page uses [Url] for a property. An attacker can inject HTML code in the context of the user's browser session by crafting a malicious link and convincing the user to click on it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 05:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22017 | setuid() does not affect libuv's internal io_uring operations if initialized before the call to setuid().
This allows the process to perform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22017</link><description>setuid() does not affect libuv's internal io_uring operations if initialized before the call to setuid().
This allows the process to perform privileged operations despite presumably having dropped such privileges through a call to setuid().
This vulnerability affects all users using version greater or equal than Node.js 18.18.0, Node.js 20.4.0 and Node.js 21.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22025 | A vulnerability in Node.js has been identified, allowing for a Denial of Service (DoS) attack through resource exhaustion when using the fet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22025</link><description>A vulnerability in Node.js has been identified, allowing for a Denial of Service (DoS) attack through resource exhaustion when using the fetch() function to retrieve content from an untrusted URL.
The vulnerability stems from the fact that the fetch() function in Node.js always decodes Brotli, making it possible for an attacker to cause resource exhaustion when fetching content from an untrusted URL.
An attacker controlling the URL passed into fetch() can exploit this vulnerability to exhaust memory, potentially leading to process termination, depending on the system configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2622 | Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform editemedia.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2622</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240318. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/client/editemedia.php. The manipulation of the argument number/enterprise_uuid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257199.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 02:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2620 | Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform down_file.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2620</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240318 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/client/down_file.php. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257197 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 01:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2621 | Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform pwd_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2621</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240318 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file api/client/user/pwd_update.php. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257198 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 01:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40275 | An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. It allows retrieval of patient lists via queries such as findFirstname= to _common/search...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40275</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. It allows retrieval of patient lists via queries such as findFirstname= to _common/search/searchByAjax/patientslistShow.jsp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40276 | An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An Unauthenticated File Download vulnerability has been discovered in pharmacy/exportFile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40276</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An Unauthenticated File Download vulnerability has been discovered in pharmacy/exportFile.jsp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40277 | An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been discovered in the login.jsp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40277</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been discovered in the login.jsp message parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40280 | An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An attacker can perform a directory path traversal via the Page parameter in a GET reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40280</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenClinic GA 5.247.01. An attacker can perform a directory path traversal via the Page parameter in a GET request to popup.jsp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>