<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-45170 | An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401. Due to improper or missing access control, low privileged users can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45170</link><description>An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401. Due to improper or missing access control, low privileged users can use administrative functions of the C-MOR web interface. It was found out that different functions are only available to administrative users. However, access those functions is restricted via the web application user interface and not checked on the server side. Thus, by sending corresponding HTTP requests to the web server of the C-MOR web interface, low privileged users can also use administrative functionality, for instance downloading backup files or changing configuration settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45174 | An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401 and 6.00PL01. Due to improper validation of user-supplied data, diffe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45174</link><description>An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401 and 6.00PL01. Due to improper validation of user-supplied data, different functionalities of the C-MOR web interface are vulnerable to SQL injection attacks. This kind of attack allows an authenticated user to execute arbitrary SQL commands in the context of the corresponding MySQL database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8415 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System add-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8415</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /routers/add-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20439 | Cisco Smart Licensing Utility Static Credential Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20439</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Smart Licensing Utility could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to log in to an affected system by using a static administrative credential.

This vulnerability is due to an undocumented static user credential for an administrative account. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the static credentials to log in to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to log in to the affected system with administrative privileges over the API of the Cisco Smart Licensing Utility application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20440 | Cisco Smart Licensing Utility Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20440</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Smart Licensing Utility could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information.

This vulnerability is due to excessive verbosity in a debug log file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain log files that contain sensitive data, including credentials that can be used to access the API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20469 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20469</link><description>A vulnerability in specific CLI commands in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20497 | Cisco Expressway Edge Improper Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20497</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to masquerade as another user on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to inadequate authorization checks for Mobile and Remote Access (MRA) users. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a series of crafted commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to intercept calls that are destined for a particular phone number or to make phone calls and have that phone number appear on the caller ID. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be an MRA user on an affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20503 | Cisco Duo Epic for Hyperdrive Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20503</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Duo Epic for Hyperdrive could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive information in cleartext on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to improper storage of an unencrypted registry key. A low-privileged attacker could exploit this vulnerability by viewing or querying the registry key on the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive information in cleartext.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8414 | SourceCodester Insurance Management System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8414</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Insurance Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45053 | Remote Code Execution Vulnerability via SSTI in Fides Webserver Jinja Email Templating Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45053</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. Starting in version 2.19.0 and prior to version 2.44.0, the Email Templating feature uses Jinja2 without proper input sanitization or rendering environment restrictions, allowing for Server-Side Template Injection that grants Remote Code Execution to privileged users. A privileged user refers to an Admin UI user with the default `Owner` or `Contributor` role, who can escalate their access and execute code on the underlying Fides Webserver container where the Jinja template rendering function is executed. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.44.0`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45074 | IBM webMethods Integration directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45074</link><description>IBM webMethods Integration 10.15 could allow an authenticated user to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45075 | IBM webMethods Integration privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45075</link><description>IBM webMethods Integration 10.15 could allow an authenticated user to create scheduler tasks that would allow them to escalate their privileges to administrator due to missing authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45314 | Flask-AppBuilder login form allows browser to cache sensitive fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45314</link><description>Flask-AppBuilder is an application development framework. Prior to version 4.5.1, the auth DB login form default cache directives allows browser to locally store sensitive data. This can be an issue on environments using shared computer resources. Version 4.5.1 contains a patch for this issue. If upgrading is not possible, configure one's web server to send the specific HTTP headers for `/login` per the directions provided in the GitHub Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44808 | An issue in Vypor Attack API System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the user GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44808</link><description>An issue in Vypor Attack API System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the user GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45076 | IBM webMethods Integration code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45076</link><description>IBM webMethods Integration 10.15 could allow an authenticated user to upload and execute arbitrary files which could be executed on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45050 | Ringer Server Does Not Check Members When Loading Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45050</link><description>Ringer server is the server code for the Ringer messaging app. Prior to version 1.3.1, there is an issue with the messages loading route where Ringer Server does not check to ensure that the user loading the conversation is actually a member of that conversation. This allows any user with a Lif Account to load any conversation between two users without permission. This issue had been patched in version 1.3.1. There is no action required for users. Lif Platforms will update their servers with the patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45052 | Fides Webserver Authentication Timing-Based Username Enumeration Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45052</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. Prior to version 2.44.0, a timing-based username enumeration vulnerability exists in Fides Webserver authentication. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to determine the existence of valid usernames by analyzing the time it takes for the server to respond to login requests. The discrepancy in response times between valid and invalid usernames can be leveraged to enumerate users on the system. This vulnerability enables a timing-based username enumeration attack. An attacker can systematically guess and verify which usernames are valid by measuring the server's response time to authentication requests. This information can be used to conduct further attacks on authentication such as password brute-forcing and credential stuffing. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.44.0`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43402 | Rust OS Command Injection/Argument Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43402</link><description>Rust is a programming language. The fix for CVE-2024-24576, where `std::process::Command` incorrectly escaped arguments when invoking batch files on Windows, was incomplete. Prior to Rust version 1.81.0, it was possible to bypass the fix when the batch file name had trailing whitespace or periods (which are ignored and stripped by Windows). To determine whether to apply the `cmd.exe` escaping rules, the original fix for the vulnerability checked whether the command name ended with `.bat` or `.cmd`. At the time that seemed enough, as we refuse to invoke batch scripts with no file extension. Windows removes trailing whitespace and periods when parsing file paths. For example, `.bat. .` is interpreted by Windows as `.bat`, but the original fix didn't check for that. Affected users who are using Rust 1.77.2 or greater can remove the trailing whitespace (ASCII 0x20) and trailing periods (ASCII 0x2E) from the batch file name to bypass the incomplete fix and enable the mitigations. Users are affected if their code or one of their dependencies invoke a batch script on Windows with trailing whitespace or trailing periods in the name, and pass untrusted arguments to it. Rust 1.81.0 will update the standard library to apply the CVE-2024-24576 mitigations to all batch files invocations, regardless of the trailing chars in the file name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43405 | Nuclei Template Signature Verification Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43405</link><description>Nuclei is a vulnerability scanner powered by YAML based templates. Starting in version 3.0.0 and prior to version 3.3.2, a vulnerability in Nuclei's template signature verification system could allow an attacker to bypass the signature check and possibly execute malicious code via custom code template. The vulnerability is present in the template signature verification process, specifically in the `signer` package. The vulnerability stems from a discrepancy between how the signature verification process and the YAML parser handle newline characters, combined with the way multiple signatures are processed. This allows an attacker to inject malicious content into a template while maintaining a valid signature for the benign part of the template. CLI users are affected if they execute custom code templates from unverified sources. This includes templates authored by third parties or obtained from unverified repositories. SDK Users are affected if they are developers integrating Nuclei into their platforms, particularly if they permit the execution of custom code templates by end-users. The vulnerability is addressed in Nuclei v3.3.2. Users are strongly recommended to update to this version to mitigate the security risk. As an interim measure, users should refrain from using custom templates if unable to upgrade immediately. Only trusted, verified templates should be executed. Those who are unable to upgrade Nuclei should disable running custom code templates as a workaround.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44859 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 has a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in `formWrlExtraGet`.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44859</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 has a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in `formWrlExtraGet`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8412 | LinuxOSsk Shakal-NG views.py redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8412</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in LinuxOSsk Shakal-NG up to 1.3.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file comments/views.py. The manipulation of the argument next leads to open redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The name of the patch is ebd1c2cba59cbac198bf2fd5a10565994d4f02cb. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44817 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ZZCMS v.2023 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the id parameter in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44817</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ZZCMS v.2023 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the id parameter in the adv2.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8391 | Eclipse Vert.x gRPC server does not limit the maximum message size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8391</link><description>In Eclipse Vert.x version 4.3.0 to 4.5.9, the gRPC server does not limit the maximum length of message payload (Maven GAV: io.vertx:vertx-grpc-server and io.vertx:vertx-grpc-client). 




This is fixed in the 4.5.10 version. 




Note this does not affect the Vert.x gRPC server based grpc-java and Netty libraries (Maven GAV: io.vertx:vertx-grpc)</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44818 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ZZCMS v.2023 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the HTTP_Referer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44818</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ZZCMS v.2023 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the HTTP_Referer header of the caina.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44821 | ZZCMS 2023 contains a vulnerability in the captcha reuse logic located in /inc/function.php. The checkyzm function does not properly refresh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44821</link><description>ZZCMS 2023 contains a vulnerability in the captcha reuse logic located in /inc/function.php. The checkyzm function does not properly refresh the captcha value after a failed validation attempt. As a result, an attacker can exploit this flaw by repeatedly submitting the same incorrect captcha response, allowing them to capture the correct captcha value through error messages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44820 | A sensitive information disclosure vulnerability exists in ZZCMS v.2023 and before within the eginfo.php file located at /3/E_bak5.1/upload/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44820</link><description>A sensitive information disclosure vulnerability exists in ZZCMS v.2023 and before within the eginfo.php file located at /3/E_bak5.1/upload/. When accessed with the query parameter phome=ShowPHPInfo, the application executes the phpinfo() function, which exposes detailed information about the PHP environment, including server configuration, loaded modules, and environment variables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8410 | ABCD ABCD2 otros_sitios.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8410</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ABCD ABCD2 up to 2.2.0-beta-1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /abcd/opac/php/otros_sitios.php. The manipulation of the argument sitio leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8411 | ABCD ABCD2 buscar_integrada.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8411</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ABCD ABCD2 up to 2.2.0-beta-1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /buscar_integrada.php. The manipulation of the argument Sub_Expresion leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44819 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ZZCMS v.2023 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44819</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ZZCMS v.2023 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the pagename parameter of the admin/del.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45506 | HAProxy 2.9.x before 2.9.10, 3.0.x before 3.0.4, and 3.1.x through 3.1-dev6 allows a remote denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45506</link><description>HAProxy 2.9.x before 2.9.10, 3.0.x before 3.0.4, and 3.1.x through 3.1-dev6 allows a remote denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7078 | Unauthenticate SQLi in Semtek Informatics Software&amp;#x27;s Semtek Sempos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7078</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Semtek Informatics Software Consulting Inc. Semtek Sempos allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Semtek Sempos: through 31072024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7077 | Reflected XSS in Semtek Informatics Software&amp;#x27;s Semtek Sempos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7077</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Semtek Informatics Software Consulting Inc. Semtek Sempos allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Semtek Sempos: through 31072024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8409 | ABCD ABCD2 show_image.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8409</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ABCD ABCD2 up to 2.2.0-beta-1. This affects an unknown part of the file /common/show_image.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8418 | Containers/aardvark-dns: tcp query handling flaw in aardvark-dns leading to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8418</link><description>A flaw was found in Aardvark-dns versions 1.12.0 and 1.12.1. They contain a denial of service vulnerability due to serial processing of TCP DNS queries. This flaw allows a malicious client to keep a TCP connection open indefinitely, causing other DNS queries to time out and resulting in a denial of service for all other containers using aardvark-dns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7076 | SQLi in Semtek Informatics Software&amp;#x27;s Semtek Sempos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7076</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Semtek Informatics Software Consulting Inc. Semtek Sempos allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Semtek Sempos: through 31072024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8407 | alwindoss akademy handlers.go cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8407</link><description>A vulnerability was found in alwindoss akademy up to 35caccea888ed63d5489e211c99edff1f62efdba. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file cmd/akademy/handler/handlers.go. The manipulation of the argument emailAddress leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8408 | Linksys WRT54G POST Parameter apply.cgi validate_services_port stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8408</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys WRT54G 4.21.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function validate_services_port of the file /apply.cgi of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument services_array leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7012 | Puppet-foreman: an authentication bypass vulnerability exists in foreman</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7012</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability has been identified in Foreman when deployed with Gunicorn versions prior to 22.0, due to the puppet-foreman configuration. This issue arises from Apache's mod_proxy not properly unsetting headers because of restrictions on underscores in HTTP headers, allowing authentication through a malformed header. This flaw impacts all active Satellite deployments (6.13, 6.14 and 6.15) and could potentially enable unauthorized users to gain administrative access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7923 | Puppet-pulpcore: an authentication bypass vulnerability exists in pulpcore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7923</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability has been identified in Foreman when deployed with Gunicorn versions prior to 22.0, due to the puppet-foreman configuration. This issue arises from Apache's mod_proxy not properly unsetting headers because of restrictions on underscores in HTTP headers, allowing authentication through a malformed header. This flaw impacts all active Satellite deployments (6.13, 6.14 and 6.15) which are using Pulpcore version 4.0+ and could potentially enable unauthorized users to gain administrative access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44383 | WAYOS FBM-291W v19.09.11 is vulnerable to Command Execution via msp_info_htm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44383</link><description>WAYOS FBM-291W v19.09.11 is vulnerable to Command Execution via msp_info_htm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44400 | D-Link DI-8400 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Command Injection via upgrade_filter_asp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44400</link><description>D-Link DI-8400 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Command Injection via upgrade_filter_asp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7834 | Local privilege escalation in Overwolf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7834</link><description>A local privilege escalation is caused by Overwolf
loading and executing certain dynamic link library files from a user-writeable
folder in SYSTEM context on launch. This allows an attacker with unprivileged
access to the system to run arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges by placing a
malicious .dll file in the respective location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8413 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Raspcontrol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8413</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the action parameter in index.php. Affected product codebase  https://github.com/Bioshox/Raspcontrol  and forks such as  https://github.com/harmon25/raspcontrol . An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted JavaScript payload to an authenticated user and partially hijacking their session details.

References list</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7870 | PixelYourSite – Your smart PIXEL (TAG) &amp;amp; API Manager &amp;lt;= 9.7.1 and PixelYourSite PRO &amp;lt;= 10.4.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure and Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7870</link><description>The PixelYourSite – Your smart PIXEL (TAG) &amp; API Manager and the PixelYourSite PRO plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 9.7.1 and 10.4.2, respectively, through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed log files, and to delete log files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 08:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8289 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Limited Vendor Privilege Escalation/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8289</link><description>The MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation/de-escalation and account takeover due to an insufficient capability check on the update_item_permissions_check and create_item_permissions_check functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the password of any user with the vendor role, create new users with the vendor role, and demote other users like administrators to the vendor role.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 08:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45195 | Apache OFBiz: Confused controller-view authorization logic (forced browsing)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45195</link><description>Direct Request ('Forced Browsing') vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.

This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.16.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.16, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 08:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45507 | Apache OFBiz: Prevent use of URLs in files when loading them from Java or Groovy, leading to a RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45507</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF), Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.

This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.16.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.16, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 08:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8318 | Attributes for Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via attributesForBlocks Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8318</link><description>The Attributes for Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘attributesForBlocks’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 07:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8102 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8102</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the module_all_toggle_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8104 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8104</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 via the download_file_ajax function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8106 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8106</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 via the download_user_ajax function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including usernames, hashed passwords, and emails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8117 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via selected_option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8117</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘selected_option’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8119 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8119</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the page parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8121 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Missing Authorization to Admin Username Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8121</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of user names due to a missing capability check on the wpext_change_admin_name() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change an admin's username to a username of their liking as long as the default 'admin' was used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8123 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8123</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 via the duplicate_post function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to duplicate posts written by other authors including admins. This includes the ability to duplicate password-protected posts, which reveals their contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6020 | Sign-up Sheets &amp;lt; 2.2.13 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6020</link><description>The Sign-up Sheets WordPress plugin before 2.2.13 does not escape some generated URLs, as well as the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting them back in attributes, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6722 | Chatbot Support AI &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6722</link><description>The Chatbot Support AI: Free ChatGPT Chatbot, Woocommerce Chatbot WordPress plugin through 1.0.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6888 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt; 4.1.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6888</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking WordPress plugin before 4.1.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6889 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt; 4.1.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6889</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking WordPress plugin before 4.1.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6926 | Viral Signup &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6926</link><description>The Viral Signup  WordPress plugin through 2.1 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7786 | Sensei LMS &amp;lt; 4.24.2 - Unauthenticated Email Template Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7786</link><description>The Sensei LMS  WordPress plugin before 4.24.2 does not properly protect some its REST API routes, allowing unauthenticated attackers to leak email templates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34637 | Improper access control in WindowManagerService prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 in Android 12, and SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 in Android 13 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34637</link><description>Improper access control in WindowManagerService prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 in Android 12, and SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 in Android 13 and Android 14 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34638 | Improper handling of exceptional conditions in ThemeCenter prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to delete non-preloaded ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34638</link><description>Improper handling of exceptional conditions in ThemeCenter prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to delete non-preloaded applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34639 | Improper handling of exceptional conditions in Setupwizard prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass proper valida...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34639</link><description>Improper handling of exceptional conditions in Setupwizard prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass proper validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34640 | Improper access control vulnerability in BGProtectManager prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restriction of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34640</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in BGProtectManager prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restriction of process expiration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34641 | Improper Export of Android Application Components in FeliCaTest prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable NFC configu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34641</link><description>Improper Export of Android Application Components in FeliCaTest prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable NFC configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34642 | Improper authorization in One UI Home prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to temporarily access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34642</link><description>Improper authorization in One UI Home prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to temporarily access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34643 | Improper access control in key input related function in Dressroom prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34643</link><description>Improper access control in key input related function in Dressroom prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34644 | Improper access control in item selection related in Dressroom prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34644</link><description>Improper access control in item selection related in Dressroom prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34645 | Improper input validation in ThemeCenter prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to install privileged applications.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34645</link><description>Improper input validation in ThemeCenter prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to install privileged applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34646 | Improper access control in DualDarManagerProxy prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause local permanent denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34646</link><description>Improper access control in DualDarManagerProxy prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause local permanent denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34647 | Incorrect use of privileged API in DualDarManagerProxy prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access privileged APIs rela...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34647</link><description>Incorrect use of privileged API in DualDarManagerProxy prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access privileged APIs related to knox without proper license.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34648 | Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions in KnoxMiscPolicy prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34648</link><description>Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions in KnoxMiscPolicy prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34649 | Improper access control in new Dex Mode in multitasking framework prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to temporarily a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34649</link><description>Improper access control in new Dex Mode in multitasking framework prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to temporarily access an unlocked screen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34650 | Incorrect authorization in CocktailbarService prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access privileged APIs related to Ed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34650</link><description>Incorrect authorization in CocktailbarService prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access privileged APIs related to Edge panel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34651 | Improper authorization in My Files prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access restricted data in My Files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34651</link><description>Improper authorization in My Files prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access restricted data in My Files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34652 | Incorrect authorization in kperfmon prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access information related to performance incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34652</link><description>Incorrect authorization in kperfmon prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access information related to performance including app usage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34653 | Path Traversal in My Files prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access directories with My Files' privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34653</link><description>Path Traversal in My Files prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access directories with My Files' privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34654 | Improper Export of android application component in My Files prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access files with My ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34654</link><description>Improper Export of android application component in My Files prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access files with My Files' privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34655 | Incorrect use of privileged API in UniversalCredentialManager prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access privileged AP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34655</link><description>Incorrect use of privileged API in UniversalCredentialManager prior to SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access privileged API related to UniversalCredentialManager.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34656 | Path traversal in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34656</link><description>Path traversal in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34657 | Stack-based out-of-bounds write in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34657</link><description>Stack-based out-of-bounds write in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34658 | Out-of-bounds read in Samsung Notes allows local attackers to bypass ASLR.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34658</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in Samsung Notes allows local attackers to bypass ASLR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34659 | Exposure of sensitive information in GroupSharing prior to version 13.6.13.3 allows remote attackers can force the victim to join the group.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34659</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in GroupSharing prior to version 13.6.13.3 allows remote attackers can force the victim to join the group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34660 | Heap-based out-of-bounds write in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34660</link><description>Heap-based out-of-bounds write in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34661 | Improper handling of insufficient permissions in Samsung Assistant prior to version 9.1.00.7 allows remote attackers to access location data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34661</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permissions in Samsung Assistant prior to version 9.1.00.7 allows remote attackers to access location data. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8325 | Gutenberg Page Builder Blocks &amp;amp; Ready-Made Patterns Library &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8325</link><description>The Blockspare: Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns for Blogs, Magazines, Business Sites – Post Grids, Sliders, Carousels, Counters, Page Builder &amp; Starter Site Imports, No Coding Needed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in the ‘blockspare_render_social_sharing_block’ function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 05:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45448 | Page table protection configuration vulnerability in the trusted firmware module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45448</link><description>Page table protection configuration vulnerability in the trusted firmware module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45449 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the ringtone setting module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45449</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the ringtone setting module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7950 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion, Arbitrary Settings Update, and User Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7950</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion, Arbitrary Settings Update, and User Creation in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 via several functions called by the 'checkFormRequest' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. Attackers can also update arbitrary settings and create user accounts even when registration is disabled, leading to user creation with a default role of Administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8298 | Memory request vulnerability in the memory management module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8298</link><description>Memory request vulnerability in the memory management module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39921 | Observable timing discrepancy issue exists in IPCOM EX2 Series V01L02NF0001 to V01L06NF0401, V01L20NF0001 to V01L20NF0401, V02L20NF0001 to V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39921</link><description>Observable timing discrepancy issue exists in IPCOM EX2 Series V01L02NF0001 to V01L06NF0401, V01L20NF0001 to V01L20NF0401, V02L20NF0001 to V02L21NF0301, and IPCOM VE2 Series V01L04NF0001 to V01L06NF0112. If this vulnerability is exploited, some of the encrypted communication may be decrypted by an attacker who can obtain the contents of the communication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45443 | Directory traversal vulnerability in the cust module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45443</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in the cust module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45444 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the WMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45444</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the WMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45445 | Vulnerability of resources not being closed or released in the keystore module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45445</link><description>Vulnerability of resources not being closed or released in the keystore module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45446 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the camera driver module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45446</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the camera driver module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45447 | Access control vulnerability in the camera framework module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45447</link><description>Access control vulnerability in the camera framework module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42039 | Access control vulnerability in the SystemUI module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42039</link><description>Access control vulnerability in the SystemUI module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45441 | Input verification vulnerability in the system service module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45441</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the system service module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45442 | Vulnerability of permission verification for APIs in the DownloadProviderMain module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45442</link><description>Vulnerability of permission verification for APIs in the DownloadProviderMain module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45450 | Permission control vulnerability in the software update module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45450</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the software update module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41927 | Cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability exists in multiple IDEC PLCs. If an attacker sends a specific command to PLC's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41927</link><description>Cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability exists in multiple IDEC PLCs. If an attacker sends a specific command to PLC's serial communication port, user credentials may be obtained. As a result, the program of the PLC may be obtained, and the PLC may be manipulated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 01:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41716 | Cleartext storage of sensitive information vulnerability exists in WindLDR and WindO/I-NV4. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41716</link><description>Cleartext storage of sensitive information vulnerability exists in WindLDR and WindO/I-NV4. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker who obtained the product's project file may obtain user credentials of the PLC or Operator Interfaces. As a result, an attacker may be able to manipulate and/or suspend the PLC and Operator Interfaces by accessing or hijacking them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 01:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7970 | Out of bounds write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.119 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7970</link><description>Out of bounds write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.119 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8362 | Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.119 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8362</link><description>Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.119 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45615 | Libopensc: pkcs15init: usage of uninitialized values in libopensc and pkcs15init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45615</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSC, OpenSC tools, PKCS#11 module, minidriver, and CTK. An attacker could use a crafted USB Device or Smart Card, which would present the system with a specially crafted response to APDUs. When buffers are partially filled with data, initialized parts of the buffer can be incorrectly accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45616 | Libopensc: uninitialized values after incorrect check or usage of apdu response values in libopensc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45616</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSC, OpenSC tools, PKCS#11 module, minidriver, and CTK. An attacker could use a crafted USB Device or Smart Card, which would present the system with a specially crafted response to APDUs. When buffers are partially filled with data, initialized parts of the buffer can be incorrectly accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45617 | Libopensc: uninitialized values after incorrect or missing checking return values of functions in libopensc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45617</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSC, OpenSC tools, PKCS#11 module, minidriver, and CTK. An attacker could use a crafted USB Device or Smart Card, which would present the system with a specially crafted response to APDUs. When buffers are partially filled with data, initialized parts of the buffer can be incorrectly accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45618 | Libopensc: uninitialized values after incorrect or missing checking return values of functions in pkcs15init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45618</link><description>A vulnerability was found in pkcs15-init in OpenSC. An attacker could use a crafted USB Device or Smart Card, which would present the system with a specially crafted response to APDUs. When buffers are partially filled with data, initialized parts of the buffer can be incorrectly accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45619 | Libopensc: incorrect handling length of buffers or files in libopensc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45619</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSC, OpenSC tools, PKCS#11 module, minidriver, and CTK. An attacker could use a crafted USB Device or Smart Card, which would present the system with a specially crafted response to APDUs. When buffers are partially filled with data, initialized parts of the buffer can be incorrectly accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45620 | Libopensc: incorrect handling of the length of buffers or files in pkcs15init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45620</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the pkcs15-init tool in OpenSC. An attacker could use a crafted USB Device or Smart Card, which would present the system with a specially crafted response to APDUs. When buffers are partially filled with data, initialized parts of the buffer can be incorrectly accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44809 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the Pi Camera project, version 1.0, maintained by RECANTHA. The issue arises from impr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44809</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the Pi Camera project, version 1.0, maintained by RECANTHA. The issue arises from improper sanitization of user input passed to the "position" GET parameter in the tilt.php script. An attacker can exploit this by sending crafted input data that includes malicious command sequences, allowing arbitrary commands to be executed on the server with the privileges of the web server user. This vulnerability is exploitable remotely and poses significant risk if the application is exposed to untrusted networks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41433 | PingCAP TiDB v8.1.0 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component expression.ExplainExpressionList. This vulnerability allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41433</link><description>PingCAP TiDB v8.1.0 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component expression.ExplainExpressionList. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45394 | Secret encryption vulnerable to brute-force attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45394</link><description>Authenticator is a browser extensions that generates two-step verification codes. In versions 7.0.0 and below, encryption keys for user data were stored encrypted at-rest using only AES-256 and the EVP_BytesToKey KDF. Therefore, attackers with a copy of a user's data are able to brute-force the user's encryption key. Users on version 8.0.0 and above are automatically migrated away from the weak encoding on first login. Users should destroy encrypted backups made with versions prior to 8.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41434 | PingCAP TiDB v8.1.0 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component (*Column).GetDecimal. This allows attackers to cause a Den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41434</link><description>PingCAP TiDB v8.1.0 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component (*Column).GetDecimal. This allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input to the 'RemoveUnnecessaryFirstRow', it will check the expression between 'Agg' and 'GroupBy', but does not check the return type.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8399 | Websites could utilize Javascript links to spoof URL addresses in the Focus navigation bar This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 130.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8399</link><description>Websites could utilize Javascript links to spoof URL addresses in the Focus navigation bar This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 130.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45391 | Tina search token leak via lock file in TinaCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45391</link><description>Tina is an open-source content management system (CMS). Sites building with Tina CMS's command line interface (CLI) prior to version 1.6.2 that use a search token may be vulnerable to the search token being leaked via lock file (tina-lock.json). Administrators of Tina-enabled websites with search setup should rotate their key immediately. This issue has been patched in @tinacms/cli version 1.6.2. Upgrading and rotating the search token is required for the proper fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4629 | Keycloak: potential bypass of brute force protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4629</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak. This flaw allows attackers to bypass brute force protection by exploiting the timing of login attempts. By initiating multiple login requests simultaneously, attackers can exceed the configured limits for failed attempts before the system locks them out. This timing loophole enables attackers to make more guesses at passwords than intended, potentially compromising account security on affected systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45389 | Pagefind DOM clobbering could escalate to Cross-site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45389</link><description>Pagefind, a fully static search library, initializes its dynamic JavaScript and WebAssembly files relative to the location of the first script the user loads. This information is gathered by looking up the value of `document.currentScript.src`. Prior to Pagefind version 1.1.1, it is possible to "clobber" this lookup with otherwise benign HTML on the page. This will cause `document.currentScript.src` to resolve as an external domain, which will then be used by Pagefind to load dependencies. This exploit would only work in the case that an attacker could inject HTML to a live, hosted, website. In these cases, this would act as a way to escalate the privilege available to an attacker. This assumes they have the ability to add some elements to the page (for example, `img` tags with a `name` attribute), but not others, as adding a `script` to the page would itself be the cross-site scripting vector. Pagefind has tightened this resolution in version 1.1.1 by ensuring the source is loaded from a valid script element. There are no reports of this being exploited in the wild via Pagefind.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45390 | @blakeembrey/template vulnerable to code injection when attacker controls template input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45390</link><description>@blakeembrey/template is a string template library. Prior to version 1.2.0, it is possible to inject and run code within the template if the attacker has access to write the template name. Version 1.2.0 contains a patch. As a workaround, don't pass untrusted input as the template display name, or don't use the display name feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45678 | Yubico YubiKey 5 Series devices with firmware before 5.7.0 and YubiHSM 2 devices with firmware before 2.4.0 allow an ECDSA secret-key extrac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45678</link><description>Yubico YubiKey 5 Series devices with firmware before 5.7.0 and YubiHSM 2 devices with firmware before 2.4.0 allow an ECDSA secret-key extraction attack (that requires physical access and expensive equipment) in which an electromagnetic side channel is present because of a non-constant-time modular inversion for the Extended Euclidean Algorithm, aka the EUCLEAK issue. Other uses of an Infineon cryptographic library may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45180 | SquaredUp DS for SCOM 6.2.1.11104 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45180</link><description>SquaredUp DS for SCOM 6.2.1.11104 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41435 | YugabyteDB v2.21.1.0 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the "insert into" parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41435</link><description>YugabyteDB v2.21.1.0 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the "insert into" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45310 | runc can be confused to create empty files/directories on the host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45310</link><description>runc is a CLI tool for spawning and running containers according to the OCI specification. runc 1.1.13 and earlier, as well as 1.2.0-rc2 and earlier, can be tricked into creating empty files or directories in arbitrary locations in the host filesystem by sharing a volume between two containers and exploiting a race with `os.MkdirAll`. While this could be used to create empty files, existing files would not be truncated. An attacker must have the ability to start containers using some kind of custom volume configuration. Containers using user namespaces are still affected, but the scope of places an attacker can create inodes can be significantly reduced. Sufficiently strict LSM policies (SELinux/Apparmor) can also in principle block this attack -- we suspect the industry standard SELinux policy may restrict this attack's scope but the exact scope of protection hasn't been analysed. This is exploitable using runc directly as well as through Docker and Kubernetes. The issue is fixed in runc v1.1.14 and v1.2.0-rc3.

Some workarounds are available. Using user namespaces restricts this attack fairly significantly such that the attacker can only create inodes in directories that the remapped root user/group has write access to. Unless the root user is remapped to an actual
user on the host (such as with rootless containers that don't use `/etc/sub[ug]id`), this in practice means that an attacker would only be able to create inodes in world-writable directories. A strict enough SELinux or AppArmor policy could in principle also restrict the scope if a specific label is applied to the runc runtime, though neither the extent to which the standard existing policies block this attack nor what exact policies are needed to sufficiently restrict this attack have been thoroughly tested.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41436 | ClickHouse v24.3.3.102 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component DB::evaluateConstantExpressionImpl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41436</link><description>ClickHouse v24.3.3.102 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component DB::evaluateConstantExpressionImpl.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43803 | BMO can expose particularly named secrets from other namespaces via BMH CRD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43803</link><description>The Bare Metal Operator (BMO) implements a Kubernetes API for managing bare metal hosts in Metal3. The `BareMetalHost` (BMH) CRD allows the `userData`, `metaData`, and `networkData` for the provisioned host to be specified as links to Kubernetes Secrets. There are fields for both the `Name` and `Namespace` of the Secret, meaning that versions of the baremetal-operator prior to 0.8.0, 0.6.2, and 0.5.2 will read a `Secret` from any namespace. A user with access to create or edit a `BareMetalHost` can thus exfiltrate a `Secret` from another namespace by using it as e.g. the `userData` for provisioning some host (note that this need not be a real host, it could be a VM somewhere).

BMO will only read a key with the name `value` (or `userData`, `metaData`, or `networkData`), so that limits the exposure somewhat. `value` is probably a pretty common key though. Secrets used by _other_ `BareMetalHost`s in different namespaces are always vulnerable. It is probably relatively unusual for anyone other than cluster administrators to have RBAC access to create/edit a `BareMetalHost`. This vulnerability is only meaningful, if the cluster has users other than administrators and users' privileges are limited to their respective namespaces.

The patch prevents BMO from accepting links to Secrets from other namespaces as BMH input. Any BMH configuration is only read from the same namespace only. The problem is patched in BMO releases v0.7.0, v0.6.2 and v0.5.2 and users should upgrade to those versions. Prior upgrading, duplicate the BMC Secrets to the namespace where the corresponding BMH is. After upgrade, remove the old Secrets. As a workaround, an operator can configure BMO RBAC to be namespace scoped for Secrets, instead of cluster scoped, to prevent BMO from accessing Secrets from other namespaces.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45307 | SudoBot missing authorization check in `-config` command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45307</link><description>SudoBot, a Discord moderation bot, is vulnerable to privilege escalation and exploit of the `-config` command in versions prior to 9.26.7. Anyone is theoretically able to update any configuration of the bot and potentially gain control over the bot's settings. Every version of v9 before v9.26.7 is affected. Other versions (e.g. v8) are not affected. Users should upgrade to version 9.26.7 to receive a patch. A workaround would be to create a command permission overwrite in the Database. A SQL statement provided in the GitHub Security Advisor can be executed to create a overwrite that disallows users without `ManageGuild` permission to run the `-config` command. Run the SQL statement for every server the bot is in, and replace `` with the appropriate Guild ID each time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43413 | Xibo CMS XSS vulnerability using DataSet HTML columns</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43413</link><description>Xibo is an open source digital signage platform with a web content management system (CMS). Prior to version 4.1.0, a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Xibo CMS allows authorized users to execute JavaScript via the DataSet functionality. Users can design a DataSet with a HTML column which contains JavaScript, which is intended functionality. The JavaScript gets executed on the Data Entry page and in any Layouts which reference it. This behavior has been changed in 4.1.0 to show HTML/CSS/JS as code on the Data Entry page. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42901 | A CSV injection vulnerability in Lime Survey v6.5.12 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted CSV file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42901</link><description>A CSV injection vulnerability in Lime Survey v6.5.12 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted CSV file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38456 | HIGH-LEIT V05.08.01.03 and HIGH-LEIT V04.25.00.00 to 4.25.01.01 for Windows from Vivavis contain an insecure file and folder permissions vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38456</link><description>HIGH-LEIT V05.08.01.03 and HIGH-LEIT V04.25.00.00 to 4.25.01.01 for Windows from Vivavis contain an insecure file and folder permissions vulnerability in prunsrv.exe. A regular user (non-admin) can exploit the weak folder and file permissions to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42902 | An issue in the js_localize.php function of LimeSurvey v6.6.2 and before allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42902</link><description>An issue in the js_localize.php function of LimeSurvey v6.6.2 and before allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted payload into the lng parameter of the js_localize.php function</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42903 | A Host header injection vulnerability in the password reset function of LimeSurvey v.6.6.1+240806 and before allows attackers to send users ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42903</link><description>A Host header injection vulnerability in the password reset function of LimeSurvey v.6.6.1+240806 and before allows attackers to send users a crafted password reset link that will direct victims to a malicious domain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42904 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SysPass 3.2.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42904</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SysPass 3.2.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the name parameter at /Controllers/ClientController.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49233 | Insufficient access checks in Visual Planning Admin Center 8 before v.1 Build 240207 allow attackers in possession of a non-administrative V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49233</link><description>Insufficient access checks in Visual Planning Admin Center 8 before v.1 Build 240207 allow attackers in possession of a non-administrative Visual Planning account to utilize functions normally reserved for administrators. The affected functions allow attackers to obtain different types of configured credentials and potentially elevate their privileges to administrator level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43412 | Xibo CMS XSS vulnerability when previewing files uploaded to the library containing HTML/JS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43412</link><description>Xibo is an open source digital signage platform with a web content management system (CMS). Prior to version 4.1.0, a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Xibo CMS allows authorized users to execute arbitrary JavaScript via the file preview function. Users can upload HTML/CSS/JS files into the Xibo Library via the Generic File module to be referenced on Displays and in Layouts. This is intended functionality. When previewing these resources from the Library and Layout editor they are executed in the users browser. This will be disabled in future releases, and users are encouraged to use the new developer tools in 4.1 to design their widgets which require this type of functionality. This behavior has been changed in 4.1.0 to preview previewing of generic files. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6119 | Possible denial of service in X.509 name checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6119</link><description>Issue summary: Applications performing certificate name checks (e.g., TLS
clients checking server certificates) may attempt to read an invalid memory
address resulting in abnormal termination of the application process.

Impact summary: Abnormal termination of an application can a cause a denial of
service.

Applications performing certificate name checks (e.g., TLS clients checking
server certificates) may attempt to read an invalid memory address when
comparing the expected name with an `otherName` subject alternative name of an
X.509 certificate. This may result in an exception that terminates the
application program.

Note that basic certificate chain validation (signatures, dates, ...) is not
affected, the denial of service can occur only when the application also
specifies an expected DNS name, Email address or IP address.

TLS servers rarely solicit client certificates, and even when they do, they
generally don't perform a name check against a reference identifier (expected
identity), but rather extract the presented identity after checking the
certificate chain.  So TLS servers are generally not affected and the severity
of the issue is Moderate.

The FIPS modules in 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42991 | MCMS v5.4.1 has front-end file upload vulnerability which can lead to remote command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42991</link><description>MCMS v5.4.1 has front-end file upload vulnerability which can lead to remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7345 | Direct local client connections to MS Agents can bypass authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7345</link><description>Local ABL Client bypass of the required PASOE security checks may allow an attacker to commit unauthorized code injection into Multi-Session Agents on supported OpenEdge LTS platforms up to OpenEdge LTS 11.7.18 and LTS 12.2.13 on all supported release platforms</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7346 | Client connections using default TLS certificates from OpenEdge may bypass TLS host name validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7346</link><description>Host name validation for TLS certificates is bypassed when the installed OpenEdge default certificates are used to perform the TLS handshake for a networked connection.  This has been corrected so that default certificates are no longer capable of overriding host name validation and will need to be replaced where full TLS certificate validation is needed for network security.  The existing certificates should be replaced with CA-signed certificates from a recognized certificate authority that contain the necessary information to support host name validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7654 | Unauthenticated Content Injection in OpenEdge Management web interface via ActiveMQ discovery service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7654</link><description>An ActiveMQ Discovery service was reachable by default from an OpenEdge Management installation when an OEE/OEM auto-discovery feature was activated.  Unauthorized access to the discovery service's UDP port allowed content injection into parts of the OEM web interface making it possible for other types of attack that could spoof or deceive web interface users.   Unauthorized use of the OEE/OEM discovery service was remediated by deactivating the discovery service by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34463 | BPL Personal Weighing Scale PWS-01BT IND/09/18/599 devices send sensitive information in unencrypted BLE packets. (The packet data also lack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34463</link><description>BPL Personal Weighing Scale PWS-01BT IND/09/18/599 devices send sensitive information in unencrypted BLE packets. (The packet data also lacks authentication and integrity protection.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4259 | Sensetive Data Exposure in SAMPAS&amp;#x27;s AKOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4259</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in SAMPAŞ Holding AKOS allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects AKOS: through 20240902. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6232 | Regular-expression DoS when parsing TarFile headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6232</link><description>There is a MEDIUM severity vulnerability affecting CPython.





Regular expressions that allowed excessive backtracking during tarfile.TarFile header parsing are vulnerable to ReDoS via specifically-crafted tar archives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8381 | A potentially exploitable type confusion could be triggered when looking up a property name on an object being used as the `with` environmen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8381</link><description>A potentially exploitable type confusion could be triggered when looking up a property name on an object being used as the `with` environment. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8382 | Internal browser event interfaces were exposed to web content when privileged EventHandler listener callbacks ran for those events. Web cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8382</link><description>Internal browser event interfaces were exposed to web content when privileged EventHandler listener callbacks ran for those events. Web content that tried to use those interfaces would not be able to use them with elevated privileges, but their presence would indicate certain browser features had been used, such as when a user opened the Dev Tools console. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8383 | Firefox normally asks for confirmation before asking the operating system to find an application to handle a scheme that the browser does no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8383</link><description>Firefox normally asks for confirmation before asking the operating system to find an application to handle a scheme that the browser does not support. It did not ask before doing so for the Usenet-related schemes news: and snews:. Since most operating systems don't have a trusted newsreader installed by default, an unscrupulous program that the user downloaded could register itself as a handler. The website that served the application download could then launch that application at will This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8384 | The JavaScript garbage collector could mis-color cross-compartment objects if OOM conditions were detected at the right point between two pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8384</link><description>The JavaScript garbage collector could mis-color cross-compartment objects if OOM conditions were detected at the right point between two passes. This could have led to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8385 | A difference in the handling of StructFields and ArrayTypes in WASM could be used to trigger an exploitable type confusion vulnerability. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8385</link><description>A difference in the handling of StructFields and ArrayTypes in WASM could be used to trigger an exploitable type confusion vulnerability. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8386 | If a site had been granted the permission to open popup windows, it could cause Select elements to appear on top of another site to perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8386</link><description>If a site had been granted the permission to open popup windows, it could cause Select elements to appear on top of another site to perform a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8387 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 129, Firefox ESR 128.1, and Thunderbird 128.1. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8387</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 129, Firefox ESR 128.1, and Thunderbird 128.1. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8388 | Multiple prompts and panels from both Firefox and the Android OS could be used to obscure the notification announcing the transition to full...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8388</link><description>Multiple prompts and panels from both Firefox and the Android OS could be used to obscure the notification announcing the transition to fullscreen mode after the fix for CVE-2023-6870 in Firefox 121. This could lead to spoofing the browser UI if the sudden appearance of the prompt distracted the user from noticing the visual transition happening behind the prompt. These notifications now use the Android Toast feature. 
*This bug only affects Firefox on Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8389 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 129. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8389</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 129. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 130.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44920 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_collect_news.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44920</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_collect_news.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the siteurl parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44921 | SeaCMS v12.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /dmplayer/dmku/index.php?ac=del.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44921</link><description>SeaCMS v12.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /dmplayer/dmku/index.php?ac=del.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6473 | DLL Hijacking in Yandex Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6473</link><description>Yandex Browser for Desktop before 24.7.1.380 has a DLL Hijacking Vulnerability because an untrusted search path is used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45588 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45588</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Symphony XTS Web Trading platform version 2.0.0.1_P160 due to improper access controls on APIs in the Preference module of the application. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters through HTTP request which could lead to unauthorized access and modification of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45586 | Account Take Over Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45586</link><description>This vulnerability exists due to improper access controls on APIs in the Authentication module of Symphony XTS Web Trading and Mobile Trading platforms (version 2.0.0.1_P160). An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters through HTTP request which could lead to unauthorized account take over belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45587 | Unauthorized Modification Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45587</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Symphony XTS Web Trading platform version 2.0.0.1_P160 due to improper access controls on APIs in the Transaction module of vulnerable application. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters through HTTP request which could lead to compromise of other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8374 | Arbitrary Code Injection in Cura</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8374</link><description>UltiMaker Cura slicer versions 5.7.0-beta.1 through 5.7.2 are vulnerable to code injection via the 3MF format reader (/plugins/ThreeMFReader.py). The vulnerability arises from improper handling of the drop_to_buildplate property within 3MF files, which are ZIP archives containing the model data. When a 3MF file is loaded in Cura, the value of the drop_to_buildplate property is passed to the Python eval() function without proper sanitization, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code by crafting a malicious 3MF file. This vulnerability poses a significant risk as 3MF files are commonly shared via 3D model databases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38811 | Code-execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38811</link><description>VMware Fusion (13.x before 13.6) contains a code-execution vulnerability due to the usage of an insecure environment variable. A malicious actor with standard user privileges may exploit this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the Fusion application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 09:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3655 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3655</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r43p0 through r49p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r43p0 through r49p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r43p0 through r49p0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37136 | Dell Path to PowerProtect, versions 1.1, 1.2, contains an Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37136</link><description>Dell Path to PowerProtect, versions 1.1, 1.2, contains an Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information exposure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 05:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42061 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program "dynamic_script.cgi" of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42061</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program "dynamic_script.cgi" of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an attacker to trick a user into visiting a crafted URL with the XSS payload. The attacker could obtain browser-based information if the malicious script is executed on the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7261 | The improper neutralization of special elements in the parameter "host" in the CGI program of Zyxel NWA1123ACv3 firmware version 6.70(ABVT.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7261</link><description>The improper neutralization of special elements in the parameter "host" in the CGI program of Zyxel NWA1123ACv3 firmware version 6.70(ABVT.4) and earlier, WAC500 firmware version 6.70(ABVS.4) 

and earlier, WAX655E firmware version 7.00(ACDO.1) and earlier, WBE530 firmware version 7.00(ACLE.1) 

and earlier, and USG LITE 60AX firmware version V2.00(ACIP.2) could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute OS commands by sending a crafted cookie to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42057 | A command injection vulnerability in the IPSec VPN feature of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42057</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the IPSec VPN feature of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some OS commands on an affected device by sending a crafted username to the vulnerable device. Note that this attack could be successful only if the device was configured in User-Based-PSK authentication mode and a valid user with a long username exceeding 28 characters exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42058 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42058</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V5.20 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V5.20 through V5.38 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause DoS conditions by sending crafted packets to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42059 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42059</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some OS commands on an affected device by uploading a crafted compressed language file via FTP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42060 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42060</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some OS commands on an affected device by uploading a crafted internal user agreement file to the vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6343 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6343</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7203 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.60 through V5.38 and USG FLEX series fir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7203</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.60 through V5.38 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.60 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by executing a crafted CLI command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5412 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the library "libclinkc" of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware version 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5412</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the library "libclinkc" of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware version 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8380 | SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF Delete Contact delete-account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8380</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-account.php of the component Delete Contact Handler. The manipulation of the argument contact leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 01:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45623 | D-Link DAP-2310 Hardware A Firmware 1.16RC028 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a stack-based buffer overflow in the ATP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45623</link><description>D-Link DAP-2310 Hardware A Firmware 1.16RC028 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a stack-based buffer overflow in the ATP binary that handles PHP HTTP GET requests for the Apache HTTP Server (httpd). NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 20:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1621 | uniFLOW Online device registration susceptible to compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1621</link><description>The registration process of uniFLOW Online (NT-ware product) apps, prior to and including version 2024.1.0, can be compromised when email login is enabled on the tenant. Those tenants utilising email login in combination with Microsoft Safe Links or similar are impacted. This vulnerability may allow the attacker to register themselves against a genuine user in the system and allow malicious users with similar access and capabilities via the app to the existing genuine user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 20:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45622 | ASIS (aka Aplikasi Sistem Sekolah using CodeIgniter 3) 3.0.0 through 3.2.0 allows index.php username SQL injection for Authentication Bypass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45622</link><description>ASIS (aka Aplikasi Sistem Sekolah using CodeIgniter 3) 3.0.0 through 3.2.0 allows index.php username SQL injection for Authentication Bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 19:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45621 | The Electron desktop application of Rocket.Chat through 6.3.4 allows stored XSS via links in an uploaded file, related to failure to use a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45621</link><description>The Electron desktop application of Rocket.Chat through 6.3.4 allows stored XSS via links in an uploaded file, related to failure to use a separate browser upon encountering third-party external actions from PDF documents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 18:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44947 | fuse: Initialize beyond-EOF page contents before setting uptodate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44947</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fuse: Initialize beyond-EOF page contents before setting uptodate

fuse_notify_store(), unlike fuse_do_readpage(), does not enable page
zeroing (because it can be used to change partial page contents).

So fuse_notify_store() must be more careful to fully initialize page
contents (including parts of the page that are beyond end-of-file)
before marking the page uptodate.

The current code can leave beyond-EOF page contents uninitialized, which
makes these uninitialized page contents visible to userspace via mmap().

This is an information leak, but only affects systems which do not
enable init-on-alloc (via CONFIG_INIT_ON_ALLOC_DEFAULT_ON=y or the
corresponding kernel command line parameter).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45313 | Insecure default setting for Server Pro installed via Overleaf toolkit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45313</link><description>Overleaf is a web-based collaborative LaTeX editor. When installing Server Pro using the Overleaf Toolkit from before 2024-07-17 or legacy docker-compose.yml from before 2024-08-28, the configuration for LaTeX compiles was insecure by default, requiring the administrator to enable the security features via a configuration setting (`SIBLING_CONTAINERS_ENABLED` in Toolkit, `SANDBOXED_COMPILES` in legacy docker-compose/custom deployments). If these security features are not enabled then users have access to the `sharelatex` container resources (filesystem, network, environment variables) when running compiles, leading to multiple file access vulnerabilities, either directly or via symlinks created during compiles. The setting has now been changed to be secure by default for new installs in the Toolkit and legacy docker-compose deployment. The Overleaf Toolkit has been updated to set `SIBLING_CONTAINERS_ENABLED=true` by default for new installs. It is recommended that any existing installations using the previous default setting migrate to using sibling containers. Existing installations can set `SIBLING_CONTAINERS_ENABLED=true` in `config/overleaf.rc` as a mitigation. In legacy docker-compose/custom deployments `SANDBOXED_COMPILES=true` should be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 17:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45311 | Denial of service in quinn-proto when using `Endpoint::retry()`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45311</link><description>Quinn is a pure-Rust, async-compatible implementation of the IETF QUIC transport protocol. As of quinn-proto 0.11, it is possible for a server to `accept()`, `retry()`, `refuse()`, or `ignore()` an `Incoming` connection. However, calling `retry()` on an unvalidated connection exposes the server to a likely panic in the following situations:  1. Calling `refuse` or `ignore` on the resulting validated connection, if a duplicate initial packet is received. This issue can go undetected until a server's `refuse()`/`ignore()` code path is exercised, such as to stop a denial of service attack. 2. Accepting when the initial packet for the resulting validated connection fails to decrypt or exhausts connection IDs, if a similar initial packet that successfully decrypts and doesn't exhaust connection IDs is received. This issue can go undetected if clients are well-behaved. The former situation was observed in a real application, while the latter is only theoretical.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45312 | Arbitrary language parameter can passed to `aspell` executable via spelling requests in overleaf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45312</link><description>Overleaf is a web-based collaborative LaTeX editor. Overleaf Community Edition and Server Pro prior to version 5.0.7 (or 4.2.7 for the 4.x series) contain a vulnerability that allows an arbitrary language parameter in client spelling requests to be passed to the `aspell` executable running on the server.  This causes `aspell` to attempt to load  a dictionary file with an arbitrary filename. File access is limited to the scope of the overleaf server. The problem is patched in versions 5.0.7 and 4.2.7.  Previous versions can be upgraded using the Overleaf toolkit `bin/upgrade` command. Users unable to upgrade may block POST requests to `/spelling/check` via a Web Application Firewall will prevent access to the vulnerable spell check feature.  However, upgrading is advised.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45306 | heap-buffer-overflow in Vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45306</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. Patch v9.1.0038 optimized how the cursor position is calculated and removed a loop, that verified that the cursor position always points inside a line and does not become invalid by pointing beyond the end of
a line. Back then we assumed this loop is unnecessary. However, this change made it possible that the cursor position stays invalid and points beyond the end of a line, which would eventually cause a heap-buffer-overflow when trying to access the line pointer at
the specified cursor position. It's not quite clear yet, what can lead to this situation that the cursor points to an invalid position. That's why patch v9.1.0707 does not include a test case. The only observed impact has been a program crash. This issue has been addressed in with the patch v9.1.0707. All users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45308 | MySQL &amp;amp; free URL mode allows to hide existing notes in hedgedoc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45308</link><description>HedgeDoc is an open source, real-time, collaborative, markdown notes application. When using HedgeDoc 1 with MySQL or MariaDB, it is possible to create notes with an alias matching the ID of existing notes. The affected existing note can then not be accessed anymore and is effectively hidden by the new one. When the freeURL feature is enabled (by setting the `allowFreeURL` config option or the `CMD_ALLOW_FREEURL` environment variable to `true`), any user with the appropriate permissions can create a note with an arbitrary alias, e.g. by accessing it in the browser. When MySQL or MariaDB are used, it is possible to create a new note with an alias that matches the lower-cased ID of a different note. HedgeDoc then always presents the new note to users, as these databases perform case-insensitive matching and the lower-cased alias is found first. This issue only affects HedgeDoc instances that use MySQL or MariaDB. Depending on the permission settings of the HedgeDoc instance, the issue can be exploited only by logged-in users or by all (including non-logged-in) users. The exploit requires knowledge of the ID of the target note. Attackers could use this issue to present a manipulated copy of the original note to the user, e.g. by replacing the links with malicious ones. Attackers can also use this issue to prevent access to the original note, causing a denial of service. No data is lost, as the original content of the affected notes is still present in the database. Users are advised to upgrade to version 1.10.0 which addresses this issue. Users unable to upgrade may disable freeURL mode which prevents the exploitation of this issue. The impact can also be limited by restricting freeURL note creation to trusted, logged-in users by enabling `requireFreeURLAuthentication`/`CMD_REQUIRE_FREEURL_AUTHENTICATION`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43797 | Path Traversal in audiobookshelf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43797</link><description>audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. A non-admin user is not allowed to create libraries (or access only the ones they have permission to). However, the `LibraryController` is missing the check for admin user and thus allows a path traversal issue. Allowing non-admin users to write to any directory in the system can be seen as a form of path traversal. However, since it can be restricted to only admin permissions, fixing this is relatively simple and falls more into the realm of Role-Based Access Control (RBAC). This issue has been addressed in release version 2.13.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43801 | Privilege escalation to admin from a low-privileged user via SVG upload in Jellyfin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43801</link><description>Jellyfin is an open source self hosted media server. The Jellyfin user profile image upload accepts SVG files, allowing for a stored XSS attack against an admin user via a specially crafted malicious SVG file. When viewed by an admin outside of the Jellyfin Web UI (e.g. via "view image" in a browser), this malicious SVG file could interact with the browser's LocalStorage and retrieve an AccessToken, which in turn can be used in an API call to elevate the target user to a Jellyfin administrator. The actual attack vector is unlikely to be exploited, as it requires specific actions by the administrator to view the SVG image outside of Jellyfin's WebUI, i.e. it is not a passive attack. The underlying exploit mechanism is solved by PR #12490, which forces attached images (including the potential malicious SVG) to be treated as attachments and thus downloaded by browsers, rather than viewed. This prevents exploitation of the LocalStorage of the browser. This PR has been merged and the relevant code changes are included in release version 10.9.10. All users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45305 | gix-path uses local config across repos when it is the highest scope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45305</link><description>gix-path is a crate of the gitoxide project dealing with git paths and their conversions. `gix-path` executes `git` to find the path of a configuration file that belongs to the `git` installation itself, but mistakenly treats the local repository's configuration as system-wide if no higher scoped configuration is found. In rare cases, this causes a less trusted repository to be treated as more trusted, or leaks sensitive information from one repository to another, such as sending credentials to another repository's remote. In `gix_path::env`, the underlying implementation of the `installation_config` and `installation_config_prefix` functions calls `git config -l --show-origin` and parses the first line of the output to extract the path to the configuration file holding the configuration variable of highest scope. It is believed to be very difficult to exploit this vulnerability deliberately, due to the need either to anticipate a situation in which higher-scoped configuration variables would be absent, or to arrange for this to happen. Although any operating system may be affected, users running Apple Git on macOS are much less likely to be affected. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.10.10. All users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28100 | Stored Cross-site Scripting leading to arbitrary actions taken on behalf of users in elabftw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28100</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. By uploading specially crafted files, a regular user can create a circumstance where a visitor's browser runs arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the eLabFTW application. This can be triggered by the visitor viewing a list of experiments. Viewing this allows the malicious script to act on behalf of the visitor in any way, including the creation of API keys for persistence, or other options normally available to the user. If the user viewing the page has the sysadmin role in eLabFTW, the script can act as a sysadmin (including system configuration and extensive user management roles). Users are advised to upgrade to at least version 5.0.0. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42471 | Arbitrary File Write via artifact extraction in actions/artifact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42471</link><description>actions/artifact is the GitHub ToolKit for developing GitHub Actions.  Versions of `actions/artifact` before 2.1.7 are vulnerable to arbitrary file write when using `downloadArtifactInternal`, `downloadArtifactPublic`, or `streamExtractExternal` for extracting a specifically crafted artifact that contains path traversal filenames. Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.1.7 or higher. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43792 | Halo&amp;#x27;s editor has a stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43792</link><description>Halo is an open source website building tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in versions prior to 2.17.0 of the Halo project. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts in the user's browser through specific HTML and JavaScript code, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.17.0+. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45388 | Arbitrary file read in the `/api/v2/simulation` endpoint in hoverfly (`GHSL-2023-274`)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45388</link><description>Hoverfly is a lightweight service virtualization/ API simulation / API mocking tool for developers and testers. The `/api/v2/simulation` POST handler allows users to create new simulation views from the contents of a user-specified file. This feature can be abused by an attacker to read arbitrary files from the Hoverfly server. Note that, although the code prevents absolute paths from being specified, an attacker can escape out of the `hf.Cfg.ResponsesBodyFilesPath` base path by using `../` segments and reach any arbitrary files. This issue was found using the Uncontrolled data used in path expression CodeQL query for python. Users are advised to make sure the final path (`filepath.Join(hf.Cfg.ResponsesBodyFilesPath, filePath)`) is contained within the expected base path (`filepath.Join(hf.Cfg.ResponsesBodyFilesPath, "/")`). This issue is also tracked as GHSL-2023-274.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36830 | nescalante urlregex Backtracking index.js redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36830</link><description>A vulnerability was found in nescalante urlregex up to 0.5.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.js of the component Backtracking. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.5.1 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is e5a085afe6abfaea1d1a78f54c45af9ef43ca1f9. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7279 | Secure Systems Engineering Connaisseur Delegation Name targets_schema.json redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7279</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Secure Systems Engineering Connaisseur up to 3.3.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file connaisseur/res/targets_schema.json of the component Delegation Name Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 524b73ff7306707f6d3a4d1e86401479bca91b02. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 14:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6921 | Cleartext Username and Password in NAC Telecommunication&amp;#x27;s NACPremium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6921</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in NAC Telecommunication Systems Inc. NACPremium allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects NACPremium: through 01082024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6920 | Stored XSS in NAC Telecommunication&amp;#x27;s NACPremium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6920</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NAC Telecommunication Systems Inc. NACPremium allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NACPremium: through 01082024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6919 | SQLi in NAC Telecommunication&amp;#x27;s NACPremium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6919</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NAC Telecommunication Systems Inc. NACPremium allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects NACPremium: through 01082024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 12:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7932 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7932</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer Release on 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7938 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7938</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7939 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7939</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer Release on 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8004 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8004</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5148 | Gnome-remote-desktop: inadequate validation of session agents using d-bus methods may expose rdp tls certificate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5148</link><description>A flaw was found in the gnome-remote-desktop package. The gnome-remote-desktop system daemon performs inadequate validation of session agents using D-Bus methods related to transitioning a client connection from the login screen to the user session. As a result, the system RDP TLS certificate and key can be exposed to unauthorized users. This flaw allows a malicious user on the system to take control of the RDP client connection during the login screen-to-user session transition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23358 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23358</link><description>Transient DOS when registration accept OTA is received with incorrect ciphering key data IE in Modem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23359 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23359</link><description>Information disclosure while decoding Tracking Area Update Accept or Attach Accept message received from network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23362 | Improper Input Validation in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23362</link><description>Cryptographic issue while parsing RSA keys in COBR format.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23364 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23364</link><description>Transient DOS when processing the non-transmitted BSSID profile sub-elements present within the MBSSID Information Element (IE) of a beacon frame that is received from over-the-air (OTA).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23365 | Use After Free in SCE-Mink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23365</link><description>Memory corruption while releasing shared resources in MinkSocket listener thread.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33016 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33016</link><description>memory corruption when an invalid firehose patch command is invoked.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33035 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33035</link><description>Memory corruption while calculating total metadata size when a very high reserved size is requested by gralloc clients.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33038 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33038</link><description>Memory corruption while passing untrusted/corrupted pointers from DSP to EVA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33042 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in FM Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33042</link><description>Memory corruption when Alternative Frequency offset value is set to 255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33043 | Buffer Over-read in FM Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33043</link><description>Transient DOS while handling PS event when Program Service name length offset value is set to 255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33045 | Return of Stack Variable Address in Buses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33045</link><description>Memory corruption when BTFM client sends new messages over Slimbus to ADSP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33047 | Buffer Over-read in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33047</link><description>Memory corruption when the captureRead QDCM command is invoked from user-space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33048 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33048</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the received TID-to-link mapping element of beacon/probe response frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33050 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33050</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing MBSSID during new IE generation in beacon/probe frame when IE length check is either missing or improper.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33051 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33051</link><description>Transient DOS while processing TIM IE from beacon frame as there is no check for IE length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33052 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in FM Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33052</link><description>Memory corruption when user provides data for FM HCI command control operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33054 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33054</link><description>Memory corruption during the handshake between the Primary Virtual Machine and Trusted Virtual Machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33057 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33057</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the multi-link element Control field when common information length check is missing before updating the location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33060 | Use After Free in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33060</link><description>Memory corruption when two threads try to map and unmap a single node simultaneously.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38401 | Use After Free in Qualcomm IPC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38401</link><description>Memory corruption while processing concurrent IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38402 | Use After Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38402</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL call for getting group info.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38858 | Cross-site scripting in Robotmk logs view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38858</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Checkmk before version 2.3.0p14 allows attackers to inject and run malicious scripts in the Robotmk logs view.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 09:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7354 | Ninja Forms 3.8.6-3.8.10 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7354</link><description>The Ninja Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.8.11 does not escape an URL before outputting it back in an attribute, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7690 | DN Popup &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7690</link><description>The DN Popup WordPress plugin through 1.2.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7691 | Flaming Forms &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7691</link><description>The Flaming Forms WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks against administrators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7692 | Flaming Forms &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7692</link><description>The Flaming Forms WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43772 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43772</link><description>SQL Injection in download student learning course function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the uid parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43773 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43773</link><description>SQL Injection in download class learning course function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the cstr parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43774 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43774</link><description>SQL Injection in download personal learning course function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the uid parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43775 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43775</link><description>SQL Injection in search course titles function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the search parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43776 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43776</link><description>SQL Injection in mock exam function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the qlevel parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7871 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7871</link><description>SQL Injection in online dictionary function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the word parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28044 | Liteos-A has an integer  overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28044</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause crash through integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38382 | Ability Runtime has an out-of-bounds read permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38382</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38386 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38386</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39612 | Background Task Manager has an out-of-bounds read permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39612</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39775 | Net Manager has an out-of-bounds read permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39775</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39816 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39816</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41157 | Liteos-A has an use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41157</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause the common permission is upgraded to root and sensitive information leak through use after free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41160 | Liteos-A has an use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41160</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause the common permission is upgraded to root and sensitive information leak through use after free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20084 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20084</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08944210; Issue ID: MSV-1561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20085 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20085</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08944204; Issue ID: MSV-1560.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20086 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20086</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932916; Issue ID: MSV-1551.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20087 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20087</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932916; Issue ID: MSV-1550.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20088 | In keyinstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20088</link><description>In keyinstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932099; Issue ID: MSV-1543.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20089 | In wlan, there is a possible denial of service due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20089</link><description>In wlan, there is a possible denial of service due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08861558; Issue ID: MSV-1526.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45527 | REDCap 14.7.0 allows HTML injection via the project title of a New Project action. This can lead to resultant logout CSRF via index.php?logo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45527</link><description>REDCap 14.7.0 allows HTML injection via the project title of a New Project action. This can lead to resultant logout CSRF via index.php?logout=1, and can also be used to insert a link to an external phishing website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45528 | CodeAstro MembershipM-PHP (aka Membership Management System in PHP) 1.0 allows add_members.php fullname stored XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45528</link><description>CodeAstro MembershipM-PHP (aka Membership Management System in PHP) 1.0 allows add_members.php fullname stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8365 | Vault Leaks AppRole Client Tokens And Accessor in Audit Log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8365</link><description>Vault Community Edition and Vault Enterprise experienced a regression where functionality that HMAC’d sensitive headers in the configured audit device, specifically client tokens and token accessors, was removed. This resulted in the plaintext values of client tokens and token accessors being stored in the audit log. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-8365, was fixed in Vault Community Edition and Vault Enterprise 1.17.5 and Vault Enterprise 1.16.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>