<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:38:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6473 | DLL Hijacking in Yandex Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6473</link><description>Yandex Browser for Desktop before 24.7.1.380 has a DLL Hijacking Vulnerability because an untrusted search path is used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45588 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45588</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Symphony XTS Web Trading platform version 2.0.0.1_P160 due to improper access controls on APIs in the Preference module of the application. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters through HTTP request which could lead to unauthorized access and modification of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45586 | Account Take Over Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45586</link><description>This vulnerability exists due to improper access controls on APIs in the Authentication module of Symphony XTS Web Trading and Mobile Trading platforms (version 2.0.0.1_P160). An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters through HTTP request which could lead to unauthorized account take over belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45587 | Unauthorized Modification Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45587</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Symphony XTS Web Trading platform version 2.0.0.1_P160 due to improper access controls on APIs in the Transaction module of vulnerable application. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters through HTTP request which could lead to compromise of other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8374 | Arbitrary Code Injection in Cura</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8374</link><description>UltiMaker Cura slicer versions 5.7.0-beta.1 through 5.7.2 are vulnerable to code injection via the 3MF format reader (/plugins/ThreeMFReader.py). The vulnerability arises from improper handling of the drop_to_buildplate property within 3MF files, which are ZIP archives containing the model data. When a 3MF file is loaded in Cura, the value of the drop_to_buildplate property is passed to the Python eval() function without proper sanitization, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code by crafting a malicious 3MF file. This vulnerability poses a significant risk as 3MF files are commonly shared via 3D model databases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 10:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38811 | Code-execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38811</link><description>VMware Fusion (13.x before 13.6) contains a code-execution vulnerability due to the usage of an insecure environment variable. A malicious actor with standard user privileges may exploit this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the Fusion application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 09:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3655 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3655</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r43p0 through r49p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r43p0 through r49p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r43p0 through r49p0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37136 | Dell Path to PowerProtect, versions 1.1, 1.2, contains an Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37136</link><description>Dell Path to PowerProtect, versions 1.1, 1.2, contains an Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information exposure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 05:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42061 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program "dynamic_script.cgi" of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42061</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program "dynamic_script.cgi" of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an attacker to trick a user into visiting a crafted URL with the XSS payload. The attacker could obtain browser-based information if the malicious script is executed on the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7261 | The improper neutralization of special elements in the parameter "host" in the CGI program of Zyxel NWA1123ACv3 firmware version 6.70(ABVT.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7261</link><description>The improper neutralization of special elements in the parameter "host" in the CGI program of Zyxel NWA1123ACv3 firmware version 6.70(ABVT.4) and earlier, WAC500 firmware version 6.70(ABVS.4) 

and earlier, WAX655E firmware version 7.00(ACDO.1) and earlier, WBE530 firmware version 7.00(ACLE.1) 

and earlier, and USG LITE 60AX firmware version V2.00(ACIP.2) could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute OS commands by sending a crafted cookie to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42057 | A command injection vulnerability in the IPSec VPN feature of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42057</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the IPSec VPN feature of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some OS commands on an affected device by sending a crafted username to the vulnerable device. Note that this attack could be successful only if the device was configured in User-Based-PSK authentication mode and a valid user with a long username exceeding 28 characters exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42058 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42058</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V5.20 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V5.20 through V5.38 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause DoS conditions by sending crafted packets to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42059 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42059</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V5.00 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some OS commands on an affected device by uploading a crafted compressed language file via FTP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42060 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42060</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some OS commands on an affected device by uploading a crafted internal user agreement file to the vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6343 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6343</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7203 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.60 through V5.38 and USG FLEX series fir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7203</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.60 through V5.38 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.60 through V5.38 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by executing a crafted CLI command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 02:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5412 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the library "libclinkc" of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware version 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5412</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the library "libclinkc" of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware version 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8380 | SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF Delete Contact delete-account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8380</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-account.php of the component Delete Contact Handler. The manipulation of the argument contact leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 01:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45623 | D-Link DAP-2310 Hardware A Firmware 1.16RC028 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a stack-based buffer overflow in the ATP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45623</link><description>D-Link DAP-2310 Hardware A Firmware 1.16RC028 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a stack-based buffer overflow in the ATP binary that handles PHP HTTP GET requests for the Apache HTTP Server (httpd). NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 20:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1621 | uniFLOW Online device registration susceptible to compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1621</link><description>The registration process of uniFLOW Online (NT-ware product) apps, prior to and including version 2024.1.0, can be compromised when email login is enabled on the tenant. Those tenants utilising email login in combination with Microsoft Safe Links or similar are impacted. This vulnerability may allow the attacker to register themselves against a genuine user in the system and allow malicious users with similar access and capabilities via the app to the existing genuine user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 20:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45622 | ASIS (aka Aplikasi Sistem Sekolah using CodeIgniter 3) 3.0.0 through 3.2.0 allows index.php username SQL injection for Authentication Bypass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45622</link><description>ASIS (aka Aplikasi Sistem Sekolah using CodeIgniter 3) 3.0.0 through 3.2.0 allows index.php username SQL injection for Authentication Bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 19:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45621 | The Electron desktop application of Rocket.Chat through 6.3.4 allows stored XSS via links in an uploaded file, related to failure to use a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45621</link><description>The Electron desktop application of Rocket.Chat through 6.3.4 allows stored XSS via links in an uploaded file, related to failure to use a separate browser upon encountering third-party external actions from PDF documents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 18:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44947 | fuse: Initialize beyond-EOF page contents before setting uptodate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44947</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fuse: Initialize beyond-EOF page contents before setting uptodate

fuse_notify_store(), unlike fuse_do_readpage(), does not enable page
zeroing (because it can be used to change partial page contents).

So fuse_notify_store() must be more careful to fully initialize page
contents (including parts of the page that are beyond end-of-file)
before marking the page uptodate.

The current code can leave beyond-EOF page contents uninitialized, which
makes these uninitialized page contents visible to userspace via mmap().

This is an information leak, but only affects systems which do not
enable init-on-alloc (via CONFIG_INIT_ON_ALLOC_DEFAULT_ON=y or the
corresponding kernel command line parameter).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45313 | Insecure default setting for Server Pro installed via Overleaf toolkit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45313</link><description>Overleaf is a web-based collaborative LaTeX editor. When installing Server Pro using the Overleaf Toolkit from before 2024-07-17 or legacy docker-compose.yml from before 2024-08-28, the configuration for LaTeX compiles was insecure by default, requiring the administrator to enable the security features via a configuration setting (`SIBLING_CONTAINERS_ENABLED` in Toolkit, `SANDBOXED_COMPILES` in legacy docker-compose/custom deployments). If these security features are not enabled then users have access to the `sharelatex` container resources (filesystem, network, environment variables) when running compiles, leading to multiple file access vulnerabilities, either directly or via symlinks created during compiles. The setting has now been changed to be secure by default for new installs in the Toolkit and legacy docker-compose deployment. The Overleaf Toolkit has been updated to set `SIBLING_CONTAINERS_ENABLED=true` by default for new installs. It is recommended that any existing installations using the previous default setting migrate to using sibling containers. Existing installations can set `SIBLING_CONTAINERS_ENABLED=true` in `config/overleaf.rc` as a mitigation. In legacy docker-compose/custom deployments `SANDBOXED_COMPILES=true` should be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 17:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45311 | Denial of service in quinn-proto when using `Endpoint::retry()`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45311</link><description>Quinn is a pure-Rust, async-compatible implementation of the IETF QUIC transport protocol. As of quinn-proto 0.11, it is possible for a server to `accept()`, `retry()`, `refuse()`, or `ignore()` an `Incoming` connection. However, calling `retry()` on an unvalidated connection exposes the server to a likely panic in the following situations:  1. Calling `refuse` or `ignore` on the resulting validated connection, if a duplicate initial packet is received. This issue can go undetected until a server's `refuse()`/`ignore()` code path is exercised, such as to stop a denial of service attack. 2. Accepting when the initial packet for the resulting validated connection fails to decrypt or exhausts connection IDs, if a similar initial packet that successfully decrypts and doesn't exhaust connection IDs is received. This issue can go undetected if clients are well-behaved. The former situation was observed in a real application, while the latter is only theoretical.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45312 | Arbitrary language parameter can passed to `aspell` executable via spelling requests in overleaf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45312</link><description>Overleaf is a web-based collaborative LaTeX editor. Overleaf Community Edition and Server Pro prior to version 5.0.7 (or 4.2.7 for the 4.x series) contain a vulnerability that allows an arbitrary language parameter in client spelling requests to be passed to the `aspell` executable running on the server.  This causes `aspell` to attempt to load  a dictionary file with an arbitrary filename. File access is limited to the scope of the overleaf server. The problem is patched in versions 5.0.7 and 4.2.7.  Previous versions can be upgraded using the Overleaf toolkit `bin/upgrade` command. Users unable to upgrade may block POST requests to `/spelling/check` via a Web Application Firewall will prevent access to the vulnerable spell check feature.  However, upgrading is advised.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45306 | heap-buffer-overflow in Vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45306</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. Patch v9.1.0038 optimized how the cursor position is calculated and removed a loop, that verified that the cursor position always points inside a line and does not become invalid by pointing beyond the end of
a line. Back then we assumed this loop is unnecessary. However, this change made it possible that the cursor position stays invalid and points beyond the end of a line, which would eventually cause a heap-buffer-overflow when trying to access the line pointer at
the specified cursor position. It's not quite clear yet, what can lead to this situation that the cursor points to an invalid position. That's why patch v9.1.0707 does not include a test case. The only observed impact has been a program crash. This issue has been addressed in with the patch v9.1.0707. All users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45308 | MySQL &amp;amp; free URL mode allows to hide existing notes in hedgedoc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45308</link><description>HedgeDoc is an open source, real-time, collaborative, markdown notes application. When using HedgeDoc 1 with MySQL or MariaDB, it is possible to create notes with an alias matching the ID of existing notes. The affected existing note can then not be accessed anymore and is effectively hidden by the new one. When the freeURL feature is enabled (by setting the `allowFreeURL` config option or the `CMD_ALLOW_FREEURL` environment variable to `true`), any user with the appropriate permissions can create a note with an arbitrary alias, e.g. by accessing it in the browser. When MySQL or MariaDB are used, it is possible to create a new note with an alias that matches the lower-cased ID of a different note. HedgeDoc then always presents the new note to users, as these databases perform case-insensitive matching and the lower-cased alias is found first. This issue only affects HedgeDoc instances that use MySQL or MariaDB. Depending on the permission settings of the HedgeDoc instance, the issue can be exploited only by logged-in users or by all (including non-logged-in) users. The exploit requires knowledge of the ID of the target note. Attackers could use this issue to present a manipulated copy of the original note to the user, e.g. by replacing the links with malicious ones. Attackers can also use this issue to prevent access to the original note, causing a denial of service. No data is lost, as the original content of the affected notes is still present in the database. Users are advised to upgrade to version 1.10.0 which addresses this issue. Users unable to upgrade may disable freeURL mode which prevents the exploitation of this issue. The impact can also be limited by restricting freeURL note creation to trusted, logged-in users by enabling `requireFreeURLAuthentication`/`CMD_REQUIRE_FREEURL_AUTHENTICATION`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43797 | Path Traversal in audiobookshelf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43797</link><description>audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. A non-admin user is not allowed to create libraries (or access only the ones they have permission to). However, the `LibraryController` is missing the check for admin user and thus allows a path traversal issue. Allowing non-admin users to write to any directory in the system can be seen as a form of path traversal. However, since it can be restricted to only admin permissions, fixing this is relatively simple and falls more into the realm of Role-Based Access Control (RBAC). This issue has been addressed in release version 2.13.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43801 | Privilege escalation to admin from a low-privileged user via SVG upload in Jellyfin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43801</link><description>Jellyfin is an open source self hosted media server. The Jellyfin user profile image upload accepts SVG files, allowing for a stored XSS attack against an admin user via a specially crafted malicious SVG file. When viewed by an admin outside of the Jellyfin Web UI (e.g. via "view image" in a browser), this malicious SVG file could interact with the browser's LocalStorage and retrieve an AccessToken, which in turn can be used in an API call to elevate the target user to a Jellyfin administrator. The actual attack vector is unlikely to be exploited, as it requires specific actions by the administrator to view the SVG image outside of Jellyfin's WebUI, i.e. it is not a passive attack. The underlying exploit mechanism is solved by PR #12490, which forces attached images (including the potential malicious SVG) to be treated as attachments and thus downloaded by browsers, rather than viewed. This prevents exploitation of the LocalStorage of the browser. This PR has been merged and the relevant code changes are included in release version 10.9.10. All users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45305 | gix-path uses local config across repos when it is the highest scope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45305</link><description>gix-path is a crate of the gitoxide project dealing with git paths and their conversions. `gix-path` executes `git` to find the path of a configuration file that belongs to the `git` installation itself, but mistakenly treats the local repository's configuration as system-wide if no higher scoped configuration is found. In rare cases, this causes a less trusted repository to be treated as more trusted, or leaks sensitive information from one repository to another, such as sending credentials to another repository's remote. In `gix_path::env`, the underlying implementation of the `installation_config` and `installation_config_prefix` functions calls `git config -l --show-origin` and parses the first line of the output to extract the path to the configuration file holding the configuration variable of highest scope. It is believed to be very difficult to exploit this vulnerability deliberately, due to the need either to anticipate a situation in which higher-scoped configuration variables would be absent, or to arrange for this to happen. Although any operating system may be affected, users running Apple Git on macOS are much less likely to be affected. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.10.10. All users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28100 | Stored Cross-site Scripting leading to arbitrary actions taken on behalf of users in elabftw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28100</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. By uploading specially crafted files, a regular user can create a circumstance where a visitor's browser runs arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the eLabFTW application. This can be triggered by the visitor viewing a list of experiments. Viewing this allows the malicious script to act on behalf of the visitor in any way, including the creation of API keys for persistence, or other options normally available to the user. If the user viewing the page has the sysadmin role in eLabFTW, the script can act as a sysadmin (including system configuration and extensive user management roles). Users are advised to upgrade to at least version 5.0.0. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42471 | Arbitrary File Write via artifact extraction in actions/artifact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42471</link><description>actions/artifact is the GitHub ToolKit for developing GitHub Actions.  Versions of `actions/artifact` before 2.1.7 are vulnerable to arbitrary file write when using `downloadArtifactInternal`, `downloadArtifactPublic`, or `streamExtractExternal` for extracting a specifically crafted artifact that contains path traversal filenames. Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.1.7 or higher. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43792 | Halo&amp;#x27;s editor has a stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43792</link><description>Halo is an open source website building tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in versions prior to 2.17.0 of the Halo project. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts in the user's browser through specific HTML and JavaScript code, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.17.0+. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45388 | Arbitrary file read in the `/api/v2/simulation` endpoint in hoverfly (`GHSL-2023-274`)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45388</link><description>Hoverfly is a lightweight service virtualization/ API simulation / API mocking tool for developers and testers. The `/api/v2/simulation` POST handler allows users to create new simulation views from the contents of a user-specified file. This feature can be abused by an attacker to read arbitrary files from the Hoverfly server. Note that, although the code prevents absolute paths from being specified, an attacker can escape out of the `hf.Cfg.ResponsesBodyFilesPath` base path by using `../` segments and reach any arbitrary files. This issue was found using the Uncontrolled data used in path expression CodeQL query for python. Users are advised to make sure the final path (`filepath.Join(hf.Cfg.ResponsesBodyFilesPath, filePath)`) is contained within the expected base path (`filepath.Join(hf.Cfg.ResponsesBodyFilesPath, "/")`). This issue is also tracked as GHSL-2023-274.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36830 | nescalante urlregex Backtracking index.js redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36830</link><description>A vulnerability was found in nescalante urlregex up to 0.5.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.js of the component Backtracking. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.5.1 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is e5a085afe6abfaea1d1a78f54c45af9ef43ca1f9. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7279 | Secure Systems Engineering Connaisseur Delegation Name targets_schema.json redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7279</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Secure Systems Engineering Connaisseur up to 3.3.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file connaisseur/res/targets_schema.json of the component Delegation Name Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 524b73ff7306707f6d3a4d1e86401479bca91b02. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 14:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6921 | Cleartext Username and Password in NAC Telecommunication&amp;#x27;s NACPremium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6921</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in NAC Telecommunication Systems Inc. NACPremium allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects NACPremium: through 01082024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6920 | Stored XSS in NAC Telecommunication&amp;#x27;s NACPremium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6920</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NAC Telecommunication Systems Inc. NACPremium allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NACPremium: through 01082024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6919 | SQLi in NAC Telecommunication&amp;#x27;s NACPremium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6919</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NAC Telecommunication Systems Inc. NACPremium allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects NACPremium: through 01082024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 12:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7932 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7932</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer Release on 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7938 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7938</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7939 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7939</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer Release on 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8004 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8004</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5148 | Gnome-remote-desktop: inadequate validation of session agents using d-bus methods may expose rdp tls certificate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5148</link><description>A flaw was found in the gnome-remote-desktop package. The gnome-remote-desktop system daemon performs inadequate validation of session agents using D-Bus methods related to transitioning a client connection from the login screen to the user session. As a result, the system RDP TLS certificate and key can be exposed to unauthorized users. This flaw allows a malicious user on the system to take control of the RDP client connection during the login screen-to-user session transition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23358 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23358</link><description>Transient DOS when registration accept OTA is received with incorrect ciphering key data IE in Modem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23359 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23359</link><description>Information disclosure while decoding Tracking Area Update Accept or Attach Accept message received from network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23362 | Improper Input Validation in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23362</link><description>Cryptographic issue while parsing RSA keys in COBR format.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23364 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23364</link><description>Transient DOS when processing the non-transmitted BSSID profile sub-elements present within the MBSSID Information Element (IE) of a beacon frame that is received from over-the-air (OTA).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23365 | Use After Free in SCE-Mink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23365</link><description>Memory corruption while releasing shared resources in MinkSocket listener thread.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33016 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33016</link><description>memory corruption when an invalid firehose patch command is invoked.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33035 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33035</link><description>Memory corruption while calculating total metadata size when a very high reserved size is requested by gralloc clients.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33038 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33038</link><description>Memory corruption while passing untrusted/corrupted pointers from DSP to EVA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33042 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in FM Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33042</link><description>Memory corruption when Alternative Frequency offset value is set to 255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33043 | Buffer Over-read in FM Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33043</link><description>Transient DOS while handling PS event when Program Service name length offset value is set to 255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33045 | Return of Stack Variable Address in Buses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33045</link><description>Memory corruption when BTFM client sends new messages over Slimbus to ADSP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33047 | Buffer Over-read in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33047</link><description>Memory corruption when the captureRead QDCM command is invoked from user-space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33048 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33048</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the received TID-to-link mapping element of beacon/probe response frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33050 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33050</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing MBSSID during new IE generation in beacon/probe frame when IE length check is either missing or improper.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33051 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33051</link><description>Transient DOS while processing TIM IE from beacon frame as there is no check for IE length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33052 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in FM Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33052</link><description>Memory corruption when user provides data for FM HCI command control operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33054 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33054</link><description>Memory corruption during the handshake between the Primary Virtual Machine and Trusted Virtual Machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33057 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33057</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the multi-link element Control field when common information length check is missing before updating the location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33060 | Use After Free in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33060</link><description>Memory corruption when two threads try to map and unmap a single node simultaneously.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38401 | Use After Free in Qualcomm IPC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38401</link><description>Memory corruption while processing concurrent IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38402 | Use After Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38402</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL call for getting group info.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38858 | Cross-site scripting in Robotmk logs view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38858</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Checkmk before version 2.3.0p14 allows attackers to inject and run malicious scripts in the Robotmk logs view.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 09:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7354 | Ninja Forms 3.8.6-3.8.10 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7354</link><description>The Ninja Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.8.11 does not escape an URL before outputting it back in an attribute, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7690 | DN Popup &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7690</link><description>The DN Popup WordPress plugin through 1.2.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7691 | Flaming Forms &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7691</link><description>The Flaming Forms WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks against administrators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7692 | Flaming Forms &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7692</link><description>The Flaming Forms WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43772 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43772</link><description>SQL Injection in download student learning course function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the uid parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43773 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43773</link><description>SQL Injection in download class learning course function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the cstr parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43774 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43774</link><description>SQL Injection in download personal learning course function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the uid parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43775 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43775</link><description>SQL Injection in search course titles function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the search parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43776 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43776</link><description>SQL Injection in mock exam function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the qlevel parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7871 | Huachu Easytest Online Learning Test Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7871</link><description>SQL Injection in online dictionary function of Easytest Online Test Platform ver.24E01 and earlier allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the word parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 04:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28044 | Liteos-A has an integer  overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28044</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause crash through integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38382 | Ability Runtime has an out-of-bounds read permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38382</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38386 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38386</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39612 | Background Task Manager has an out-of-bounds read permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39612</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39775 | Net Manager has an out-of-bounds read permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39775</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39816 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39816</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41157 | Liteos-A has an use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41157</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause the common permission is upgraded to root and sensitive information leak through use after free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41160 | Liteos-A has an use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41160</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause the common permission is upgraded to root and sensitive information leak through use after free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 03:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20084 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20084</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08944210; Issue ID: MSV-1561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20085 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20085</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08944204; Issue ID: MSV-1560.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20086 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20086</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932916; Issue ID: MSV-1551.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20087 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20087</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932916; Issue ID: MSV-1550.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20088 | In keyinstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20088</link><description>In keyinstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932099; Issue ID: MSV-1543.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20089 | In wlan, there is a possible denial of service due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20089</link><description>In wlan, there is a possible denial of service due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08861558; Issue ID: MSV-1526.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45527 | REDCap 14.7.0 allows HTML injection via the project title of a New Project action. This can lead to resultant logout CSRF via index.php?logo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45527</link><description>REDCap 14.7.0 allows HTML injection via the project title of a New Project action. This can lead to resultant logout CSRF via index.php?logout=1, and can also be used to insert a link to an external phishing website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45528 | CodeAstro MembershipM-PHP (aka Membership Management System in PHP) 1.0 allows add_members.php fullname stored XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45528</link><description>CodeAstro MembershipM-PHP (aka Membership Management System in PHP) 1.0 allows add_members.php fullname stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8365 | Vault Leaks AppRole Client Tokens And Accessor in Audit Log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8365</link><description>Vault Community Edition and Vault Enterprise experienced a regression where functionality that HMAC’d sensitive headers in the configured audit device, specifically client tokens and token accessors, was removed. This resulted in the plaintext values of client tokens and token accessors being stored in the audit log. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-8365, was fixed in Vault Community Edition and Vault Enterprise 1.17.5 and Vault Enterprise 1.16.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45269 | WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Carousel image selection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45269</link><description>WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Carousel image selection feature. While logged in to the WordPress site with Carousel Slider plugin enabled, accessing a crafted page may cause a user to alter the contents of the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45270 | WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Hero image selection feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45270</link><description>WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Hero image selection feature. While logged in to the WordPress site with Carousel Slider plugin enabled, accessing a crafted page may cause a user to alter the contents of the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45522 | Linen before cd37c3e does not verify that the domain is linen.dev or www.linen.dev when resetting a password. This occurs in create in apps/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45522</link><description>Linen before cd37c3e does not verify that the domain is linen.dev or www.linen.dev when resetting a password. This occurs in create in apps/web/pages/api/forgot-password/index.ts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8370 | Grocy SVG File Upload recipepictures cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8370</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Grocy up to 4.2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/files/recipepictures/ of the component SVG File Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument force_serve_as with the input picture' leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. NOTE: The project maintainer explains that "this is 'nonsense' and practically irrelevant according to the project's security policy" which expects additional authentication for the software.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 22:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45509 | In MISP through 2.4.196, app/Controller/BookmarksController.php does not properly restrict access to bookmarks data in the case where the us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45509</link><description>In MISP through 2.4.196, app/Controller/BookmarksController.php does not properly restrict access to bookmarks data in the case where the user is not an org admin.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45508 | HTMLDOC before 1.9.19 has an out-of-bounds write in parse_paragraph in ps-pdf.cxx because of an attempt to strip leading whitespace from a w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45508</link><description>HTMLDOC before 1.9.19 has an out-of-bounds write in parse_paragraph in ps-pdf.cxx because of an attempt to strip leading whitespace from a whitespace-only node.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5053 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.1.18 -  Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Mailchimp Integration Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5053</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Malichimp API key update due to an insufficient capability check on the verifyRequest function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.18. This makes it possible for Form Managers with a Subscriber-level access and above to modify the Mailchimp API key used for integration. At the same time, missing Mailchimp API key validation allows the redirect of the integration requests to the attacker-controlled server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8368 | code-projects Hospital Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8367 | HM Courts &amp;amp; Tribunals Service Probate Back Office Markdown NotificationService.java injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HM Courts &amp; Tribunals Service Probate Back Office up to c1afe0cdb2b2766d9e24872c4e827f8b82a6cd31. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/uk/gov/hmcts/probate/service/NotificationService.java of the component Markdown Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as d90230d7cf575e5b0852d56660104c8bd2503c34. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 04:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>