<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:38:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-8158 | User impersonation for lib9p based 9p fileservers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8158</link><description>A bug in the 9p authentication implementation within lib9p allows an attacker with an existing valid user within the configured auth server to impersonate any other valid filesystem user.

This is due to lib9p not properly verifying that the uname given in the Tauth and Tattach 9p messages matches the client UID returned from the factotum authentication handshake.


The only filesystem making use of these functions within the base 9front systems is the experimental hjfs disk filesystem, other disk filesystems (cwfs and gefs) are not affected by this bug.

This bug was inherited from Plan 9 and is present in all versions of 9front and is remedied fully in commit 9645ae07eb66a59015e3e118d0024790c37400da.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45258 | The req package before 3.43.4 for Go may send an unintended request when a malformed URL is provided, because cleanHost in http.go intention...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45258</link><description>The req package before 3.43.4 for Go may send an unintended request when a malformed URL is provided, because cleanHost in http.go intentionally uses a "garbage in, garbage out" design.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48957 | PureVPN Linux client 2.0.2-Productions fails to properly handle DNS queries, allowing them to bypass the VPN tunnel and be sent directly to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48957</link><description>PureVPN Linux client 2.0.2-Productions fails to properly handle DNS queries, allowing them to bypass the VPN tunnel and be sent directly to the ISP or default DNS servers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8011 | Logitech Options+ on MacOS prior 1.72 allows a local attacker to inject dynamic library within Options+ runtime and abuse permissions grante...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8011</link><description>Logitech Options+ on MacOS prior 1.72 allows a local attacker to inject dynamic library within Options+ runtime and abuse permissions granted by the user to Options+ such as Camera.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 11:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8147 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php?action=editPharmacist. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8146 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8146</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php?action=editSalesman. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 08:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42340 | CyberArk - CWE-602: Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42340</link><description>CyberArk - CWE-602: Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42337 | CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42337</link><description>CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42338 | CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42338</link><description>CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42339 | CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42339</link><description>CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8145 | ClassCMS Article admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8145</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ClassCMS 4.8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php/admin of the component Article Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 05:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8144 | ClassCMS Logo admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8144</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ClassCMS 4.8. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php/admin of the component Logo Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 03:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8142 | SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool delete-calorie.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8142</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/delete-calorie.php. The manipulation of the argument calorie leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 02:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8141 | SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool add-calorie.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8141</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/add-calorie.php. The manipulation of the argument calorie_date/calorie_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 02:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45244 | Hyperledger Fabric through 2.5.9 does not verify that a request has a timestamp within the expected time window.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45244</link><description>Hyperledger Fabric through 2.5.9 does not verify that a request has a timestamp within the expected time window.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8140 | SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker update-task.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8140</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file update-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8139 | itsourcecode E-Commerce Website search_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8139</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode E-Commerce Website 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search_list.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8138 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System Parameter index.php editManager sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8138</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. Affected is the function editManager of the file /index.php?action=editManager of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id as part of String leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8137 | SourceCodester Record Management System search_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file search_user.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 23:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45240 | The TikTok (aka com.zhiliaoapp.musically) application before 34.5.5 for Android allows the takeover of Lynxview JavaScript interfaces via de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45240</link><description>The TikTok (aka com.zhiliaoapp.musically) application before 34.5.5 for Android allows the takeover of Lynxview JavaScript interfaces via deeplink traversal (in the application's exposed WebView). (On Android 12 and later, this is only exploitable by third-party applications.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45234 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45234</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) an ROA or a Manifest containing a signedAttrs encoded in non-canonical form. This bypasses Fort's BER decoder, reaching a point in the code that panics when faced with data not encoded in DER. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a panic can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45235 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45235</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a resource certificate containing an Authority Key Identifier extension that lacks the keyIdentifier field. Fort references this pointer without sanitizing it first. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45236 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45236</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a signed object containing an empty signedAttributes field. Fort accesses the set's elements without sanitizing it first. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45237 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45237</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a resource certificate containing a Key Usage extension composed of more than two bytes of data. Fort writes this string into a 2-byte buffer without properly sanitizing its length, leading to a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45238 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45238</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a resource certificate containing a bit string that doesn't properly decode into a Subject Public Key. OpenSSL does not report this problem during parsing, and when compiled with OpenSSL libcrypto versions below 3, Fort recklessly dereferences the pointer. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45239 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45239</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) an ROA or a Manifest containing a null eContent field. Fort dereferences the pointer without sanitizing it first. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8136 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort1_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8136</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file sort1_user.php. The manipulation of the argument position leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8135 | Go-Tribe gotribe token.go Sign hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8135</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Go-Tribe gotribe up to cd3ccd32cd77852c9ea73f986eaf8c301cfb6310. Affected is the function Sign of the file pkg/token/token.go. The manipulation of the argument config.key leads to hard-coded credentials. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as 4fb9b9e80a2beedd09d9fde4b9cf5bd510baf18f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 21:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8134 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request hd_config.cgi cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8134</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 20:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8133 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request hd_config.cgi cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8133</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 19:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8132 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request webdav_mgr.cgi webdav_mgr command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8132</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function webdav_mgr of the file /cgi-bin/webdav_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 18:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8131 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request apkg_mgr.cgi module_enable_disable command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function module_enable_disable of the file /cgi-bin/apkg_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_module_name leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8130 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request s3.cgi cgi_s3 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8130</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_s3 of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_a_key leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 16:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8129 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request s3.cgi cgi_s3_modify command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8129</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_s3_modify of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_job_name leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7656 | Image Hotspot by DevVN &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Author+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7656</link><description>The Image Hotspot by DevVN plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'devvn_ihotspot_shortcode_func' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8128 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request webfile_mgr.cgi cgi_add_zip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8128</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_add_zip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43915 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43915</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container 5.0, 7.1, 7.2, 8.0, 8.1, 8.2, 9.0, 9.1, 9.2, 10.0, 10.1, 11.0, 11.1, 11.2, 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, 11.6, 12.0, and 12.1 does not limit calls to unshare in running Pods.  This can allow a user with access to execute commands in a running Pod to elevate their user privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8127 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request webfile_mgr.cgi cgi_unzip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8127</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_unzip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7351 | Simple Job Board &amp;lt;= 2.12.3 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7351</link><description>The Simple Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.3 via deserialization of untrusted input when editing job applications. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 07:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6499 | WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons &amp;lt;= 9.7.8 - Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6499</link><description>The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information exposure in all versions up to, and including, 9.7.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain the full path to instances, which they may be able to use in combination with other vulnerabilities or to simplify reconnaissance work. On its own, this information is of very limited use.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 03:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2254 | RT Easy Builder – Advanced addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2254</link><description>The RT Easy Builder – Advanced addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6631 | ImageRecycle pdf &amp;amp; image compression &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Missing Authorization in Several AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6631</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform unauthorized actions, such as updating plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8120 | ImageRecycle pdf &amp;amp; image compression &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Cross-Site Request in Several AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8120</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.14. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions in the class/class-image-otimizer.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings along with performing other actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0926 | Custom Permalinks &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Authenticated(Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0926</link><description>The Custom Permalinks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 2.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on tag names. This allows authenticated users, with editor-level permissions or greater to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, even when 'unfiltered_html' has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6987 | String Locator &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6987</link><description>The String locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'sql-column' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This required WP_DEBUG to be enabled in order to be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7568 | Favicon Generator &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7568</link><description>The Favicon Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the output_sub_admin_page_0 function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The plugin author deleted the functionality of the plugin to patch this issue and close the plugin, we recommend seeking an alternative to this plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38207 | Microsoft Edge (HTML-based) Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38207</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 23:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40111 | A persistent (stored) cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in Automad 2.0.0-alpha.4. This vulnerability enables an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40111</link><description>A persistent (stored) cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in Automad 2.0.0-alpha.4. This vulnerability enables an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into the template body. The injected code is stored within the flat file CMS and is executed in the browser of any user visiting the forum.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 21:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37392 | A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in SMSEagle software version &lt; 6.0. The vulnerability arises because t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37392</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in SMSEagle software version &lt; 6.0. The vulnerability arises because the application did not properly sanitize user input in the SMS messages in the inbox. This could allow an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into an SMS message, which gets executed when the SMS is viewed and specially interacted in web-GUI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45188 | Mage AI file content request remote arbitrary file leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45188</link><description>Mage AI allows remote users with the "Viewer" role to leak arbitrary files from the Mage server due to a path traversal in the "File Content" request</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45189 | Mage AI git content request remote arbitrary file leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45189</link><description>Mage AI allows remote users with the "Viewer" role to leak arbitrary files from the Mage server due to a path traversal in the "Git Content" request</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45190 | Mage AI pipeline interaction request remote arbitrary file leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45190</link><description>Mage AI allows remote users with the "Viewer" role to leak arbitrary files from the Mage server due to a path traversal in the "Pipeline Interaction" request</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45187 | Mage AI allows deleted users to use the terminal server with admin access, leading to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45187</link><description>Guest users in the Mage AI framework that remain logged in after their accounts are deleted, are mistakenly given high privileges and specifically given access to remotely execute arbitrary code through the Mage AI terminal server</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42845 | An eval Injection vulnerability in the component invesalius/reader/dicom.py of InVesalius 3.1.99991 through 3.1.99998 allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42845</link><description>An eval Injection vulnerability in the component invesalius/reader/dicom.py of InVesalius 3.1.99991 through 3.1.99998 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via loading a crafted DICOM file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 18:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42914 | A host header injection vulnerability exists in the forgot password functionality of ArrowCMS version 1.0.0. By sending a specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42914</link><description>A host header injection vulnerability exists in the forgot password functionality of ArrowCMS version 1.0.0. By sending a specially crafted host header in the forgot password request, it is possible to send password reset links to users which, once clicked, lead to an attacker-controlled server and thus leak the password reset token. This may allow an attacker to reset other users' passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 18:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7954 | SPIP porte_plume Plugin Arbitrary PHP Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7954</link><description>The porte_plume plugin used by SPIP before 4.30-alpha2, 4.2.13, and 4.1.16 is vulnerable to an arbitrary code execution vulnerability. A remote and unauthenticated attacker can execute arbitrary PHP as the SPIP user by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42852 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in AcuToWeb server v.10.5.0.7577C8b allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the index.php ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42852</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in AcuToWeb server v.10.5.0.7577C8b allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the index.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42992 | Python Pip Pandas v2.2.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42992</link><description>Python Pip Pandas v2.2.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42918 | itsourcecode Online Accreditation Management System contains a Cross Site Scripting vulnerability, which allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42918</link><description>itsourcecode Online Accreditation Management System contains a Cross Site Scripting vulnerability, which allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the SCHOOLNAME, EMAILADDRES, CONTACTNO, COMPANYNAME and COMPANYCONTACTNO parameters in controller.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7427 | Potential Cross-Site Scripting  vulnerability affect OpenText™ Network Node Manager i (NNMi).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7427</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OpenText™ Network Node Manager i (NNMi) could allow Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Network Node Manager i (NNMi): 2022.11, 2023.05, 23.4, 24.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7428 | Potential Open Redirect issues affect OpenText™ Network Node Manager i (NNMi).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7428</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in OpenText™ Network Node Manager i (NNMi) allows URL Redirector Abuse.This issue affects Network Node Manager i (NNMi): 2022.11, 2023.05, 23.4, 24.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41841 | AMS XSS - /libs/cq/personalization/components/profileloader/content/load.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41841</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If an attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41842 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability | AEM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41842</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41843 | Stored XSS in `libs/granite/ui/components/coral/foundation/clientlibs/foundation/js/layout/actionfield.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41843</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41844 | Stored XSS in `libs/dam/gui/coral/components/admin/clientlibs/actions/js/download.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41844</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41845 | Stored XSS in `libs/dam/gui/components/admin/collections/clientlibs/admin/js/collectionoperationsactivator.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41845</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41846 | AMS XSS - /libs/dam/gui/coral/components/admin/drm/licensefield/licensefield.jsp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41846</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41847 | Cloud Services - /libs/cq/contexthub/components/traits/generic-comparison/generic-comparison.jsp (retest 2132455 - not fixed)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41847</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If an attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41848 | AMS XSS - /libs/dam/gui/coral/components/admin/reports/viewreport/clientlibs/viewreport/js/viewreport.js (JS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41848</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If an attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41849 | HTML Injection on `https://author-bugbounty-65-prod.adobecqms.net/`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41849</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could lead to a security feature bypass. An low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to slightly affect the integrity of the page. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41875 | AMS XSS - /libs/dam/gui/components/admin/collections/clientlibs/admin/js/collectionoperationsactivator.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41875</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41876 | AMS XSS -  /libs/clientlibs/granite/richtext/externals/tests/resources/test/index.html (retest of 1969052 - not fixed)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41876</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If an attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41877 | AMS XSS - /libs/dam/gui/coral/components/admin/clientlibs/actions/js/download.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41877</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.19 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41878 | AMS XSS - /libs/granite/ui/components/foundation/clientlibs/foundation/js/admin/propertiesactivator.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41878</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.19 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's browser session. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, such as convincing a victim to click on a malicious link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42531 | Ezviz Internet PT Camera CS-CV246 D15655150 allows an unauthenticated host to access its live video stream by crafting a set of RTSP packets...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42531</link><description>Ezviz Internet PT Camera CS-CV246 D15655150 allows an unauthenticated host to access its live video stream by crafting a set of RTSP packets with a specific set of URLs that can be used to redirect the camera feed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44387 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN contains a Buffer Overflow vulnerability via the functino formWrlExtraGet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44387</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN contains a Buffer Overflow vulnerability via the functino formWrlExtraGet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32501 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the updateServiceHost functionality in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32501</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the updateServiceHost functionality in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x before 23.04.19, and 22.10.x before 22.10.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33852 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the Downtime component in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33852</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the Downtime component in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x before 23.04.19, and 22.10.x before 22.10.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33853 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the Timeperiod component in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33853</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the Timeperiod component in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x before 23.04.19, and 22.10.x before 22.10.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33854 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the Graph Template component in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33854</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the Graph Template component in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x before 23.04.19, and 22.10.x before 22.10.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39841 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the service configuration functionality in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39841</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the service configuration functionality in Centreon Web 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.13, 23.04.x before 23.04.19, and 22.10.x before 22.10.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43794 | OpenSearch Dashboards Security Plugin improper validation of nextUrl can lead to external redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43794</link><description>OpenSearch Dashboards Security Plugin adds a configuration management UI for the OpenSearch Security features to OpenSearch Dashboards. Improper validation of the nextUrl parameter can lead to external redirect on login to OpenSearch-Dashboards for specially crafted parameters. A patch is available in 1.3.19 and 2.16.0 for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44390 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN contains a Buffer Overflow vulnerability via the function formWrlsafeset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44390</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN contains a Buffer Overflow vulnerability via the function formWrlsafeset.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44386 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN contains a Buffer Overflow vulnerability via the function fromSetIpBind.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44386</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN contains a Buffer Overflow vulnerability via the function fromSetIpBind.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 16:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44381 | D-Link DI_8004W 16.07.26A1 contains a command execution vulnerability in jhttpd msp_info_htm function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44381</link><description>D-Link DI_8004W 16.07.26A1 contains a command execution vulnerability in jhttpd msp_info_htm function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44382 | D-Link DI_8004W 16.07.26A1 contains a command execution vulnerability in the jhttpd upgrade_filter_asp function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44382</link><description>D-Link DI_8004W 16.07.26A1 contains a command execution vulnerability in the jhttpd upgrade_filter_asp function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42364 | homepage DNS rebinding vulnerability (GHSL-2024-096)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42364</link><description>Homepage is a highly customizable homepage with Docker and service API integrations. The default setup of homepage 0.9.1 is vulnerable to DNS rebinding. Homepage is setup without certificate and authentication by default, leaving it to vulnerable to DNS rebinding. In this attack, an attacker will ask a user to visit his/her website. The attacker website will then change the DNS records of their domain from their IP address to the internal IP address of the homepage instance. To tell which IP addresses are valid, we can rebind a subdomain to each IP address we want to check, and see if there is a response. Once potential candidates have been found, the attacker can launch the attack by reading the response of the webserver after the IP address has changed. When the attacker domain is fetched, the response will be from the homepage instance, not the attacker website, because the IP address has been changed. Due to a lack of authentication, a user’s private information such as API keys (fixed after first report) and other private information can then be extracted by the attacker website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42523 | publiccms V4.0.202302.e and before is vulnerable to Any File Upload via publiccms/admin/cmsTemplate/saveMetaData</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42523</link><description>publiccms V4.0.202302.e and before is vulnerable to Any File Upload via publiccms/admin/cmsTemplate/saveMetaData</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42756 | An issue in Netgear DGN1000WW v.1.1.00.45 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Diagnostics page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42756</link><description>An issue in Netgear DGN1000WW v.1.1.00.45 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Diagnostics page</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43031 | autMan v2.9.6 was discovered to contain an access control issue.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43031</link><description>autMan v2.9.6 was discovered to contain an access control issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43032 | autMan v2.9.6 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted web request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43032</link><description>autMan v2.9.6 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted web request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42636 | DedeCMS V5.7.115 has a command execution vulnerability via file_manage_view.php?fmdo=newfile&amp;activepath.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42636</link><description>DedeCMS V5.7.115 has a command execution vulnerability via file_manage_view.php?fmdo=newfile&amp;amp;activepath.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42915 | A host header injection vulnerability in Staff Appraisal System v1.0 allows attackers to obtain the password reset token via user interactio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42915</link><description>A host header injection vulnerability in Staff Appraisal System v1.0 allows attackers to obtain the password reset token via user interaction with a crafted password reset link. This will allow attackers to arbitrarily reset other users' passwords and compromise their accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43791 | RequestStore has Incorrect Default Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43791</link><description>RequestStore provides per-request global storage for Rack. The files published as part of request_store 1.3.2 have 0666 permissions, meaning that they are world-writable, which allows local users to execute arbitrary code. This version was published in 2017, and most production environments do not allow access for local users, so the chances of this being exploited are very low, given that the vast majority of users will have upgraded, and those that have not, if any, are not likely to be exposed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42766 | Kashipara Bus Ticket Reservation System v1.0 0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /deleteTicket.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42766</link><description>Kashipara Bus Ticket Reservation System v1.0 0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /deleteTicket.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43782 | openedx-translations&amp;#x27;s Atlas translations for Open edX missing validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43782</link><description>This openedx-translations repository contains translation files from Open edX repositories to be kept in sync with Transifex. Before moving to pulling translations from the openedx-translations repository via openedx-atlas, translations in the edx-platform repository were validated using edx-i18n-tools. This validation included protection against malformed translations and translations-based script injections. Prior to this patch, the validation implemented in the openedx-translations repository did not include the same protections. The maintainer inspected the translations in the edx-platform directory of both the main and open-release/redwood.master branches of the openedx-translations repository and found no evidence of exploited translation strings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8112 | thinkgem JeeSite Cookie login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8112</link><description>A vulnerability was found in thinkgem JeeSite 5.3. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /js/a/login of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument skinName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37311 | Collabora Online&amp;#x27;s remote host TLS certificates are not fully verified</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37311</link><description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice. In affected versions of Collabora Online, https connections from coolwsd to other hosts may incompletely verify the remote host's certificate's against the full chain of trust. This vulnerability is fixed in Collabora Online 24.04.4.3, 23.05.14.1, and 22.05.23.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42764 | Kashipara Bus Ticket Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /deleteTicket.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42764</link><description>Kashipara Bus Ticket Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /deleteTicket.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8113 | Stored XSS in Placeholder Samples in Mail Preview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8113</link><description>Stored XSS in organizer and event settings of pretix up to 2024.7.0 allows malicious event organizers to inject HTML tags into e-mail previews on settings page. The default Content Security Policy of pretix prevents execution of attacker-provided scripts, making exploitation unlikely. However, combined with a CSP bypass (which is not currently known) the vulnerability could be used to impersonate other organizers or staff users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38869 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38869</link><description>An Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability affects Zohocorp ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus, ServiceDesk Plus MSP and SupportCenter Plus.This issue affects ServiceDesk Plus versions: through 14810; ServiceDesk Plus MSP: through 14800; SupportCenter Plus: through 14800.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41150 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41150</link><description>An Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in request module affects Zohocorp ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus, ServiceDesk Plus MSP and SupportCenter Plus.This issue affects ServiceDesk Plus versions: through 14810; ServiceDesk Plus MSP: through 14800; SupportCenter Plus: through 14800.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42040 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the net/bootp.c in DENEX U-Boot from its initial commit in 2002 (3861aa5) up to today on any platform allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42040</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the net/bootp.c in DENEX U-Boot from its initial commit in 2002 (3861aa5) up to today on any platform allows an attacker on the local network to leak memory from four up to 32 bytes of memory stored behind the packet to the network depending on the later use of DHCP-provided parameters via crafted DHCP responses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42765 | A SQL injection vulnerability in "/login.php" of the Kashipara Bus Ticket Reservation System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42765</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in "/login.php" of the Kashipara Bus Ticket Reservation System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands and bypass Login via the "email" or "password" Login page parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5556 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5556</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8000 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in reports module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5586 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5586</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8121 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in extranet lockouts report option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5490 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5490</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8000 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in aggregate reports option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36514 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36514</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8000 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in file summary option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36515 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36515</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8000 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in dashboard.
Note: This vulnerability is different from another vulnerability (CVE-2024-36516), both of which have affected ADAudit Plus' dashboard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36516 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36516</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8000 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in dashboard.
Note: This vulnerability is different from another vulnerability (CVE-2024-36515), both of which have affected ADAudit Plus' dashboard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36517 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36517</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8000 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in alerts module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5467 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5467</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8121 are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in account lockout report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5466 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5466</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine OpManager and Remote Monitoring and Management versions 128329 and below are vulnerable to the authenticated remote code execution in the deploy agent option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43883 | usb: vhci-hcd: Do not drop references before new references are gained</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43883</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: vhci-hcd: Do not drop references before new references are gained

At a few places the driver carries stale pointers
to references that can still be used. Make sure that does not happen.
This strictly speaking closes ZDI-CAN-22273, though there may be
similar races in the driver.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7986 | Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™ Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7986</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer that allows a threat actor to disclose sensitive information. A threat actor can exploit this vulnerability by abusing the ThinServer™ service to read arbitrary files by creating a junction that points to the target directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38807 | CVE-2024-38807: Signature Forgery Vulnerability in Spring Boot&amp;#x27;s Loader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38807</link><description>Applications that use spring-boot-loader or spring-boot-loader-classic and contain custom code that performs signature verification of nested jar files may be vulnerable to signature forgery where content that appears to have been signed by one signer has, in fact, been signed by another.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 08:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5502 | Piotnet Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.4.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5502</link><description>The Piotnet Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Accordion, Dual Heading, and Vertical Timeline widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 08:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43105 | Excessive Resource Consumption via `/export`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43105</link><description>Mattermost Plugin Channel Export versions &lt;=1.0.0 fail to restrict concurrent runs of the /export command which allows a user to consume excessive resource by running the /export command multiple times at once.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 07:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40766 | An improper access control vulnerability has been identified in the SonicWall SonicOS management access, potentially leading to unauthorized...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40766</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability has been identified in the SonicWall SonicOS management access, potentially leading to unauthorized resource access and in specific conditions, causing the firewall to crash. This issue affects SonicWall Firewall Gen 5 and Gen 6 devices, as well as Gen 7 devices running SonicOS 7.0.1-5035 and older versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3282 | WP Table Builder &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3282</link><description>The WP Table Builder  WordPress plugin through 1.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Table data, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6715 | Ditty 3.1.39-3.1.45 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6715</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.46 re-introduced a previously fixed security issue (https://wpscan.com/vulnerability/80a9eb3a-2cb1-4844-9004-ba2554b2d46c/) in v3.1.39</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7258 | WooCommerce Google Feed Manager &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7258</link><description>The WooCommerce Google Feed Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wppfm_removeFeedFile' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 04:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7559 | File Manager Pro &amp;lt;= 8.3.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7559</link><description>The File Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation and capability checks in the mk_file_folder_manager AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 02:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43477 | Entra ID Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43477</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 02:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>