<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-12503 | Digiwin｜EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12503</link><description>EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet developed by Digiwin has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12618 | Tenda AC8 DatabaseIniSet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12618</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/DatabaseIniSet. The manipulation of the argument Time leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12617 | itsourcecode Billing System login_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12617</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/app/login_crud.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Password can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12616 | PHPGurukul News Portal settings.py insertion of sensitive information into debugging code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12616</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /onps/settings.py. Performing manipulation results in insertion of sensitive information into debugging code. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12615 | PHPGurukul News Portal settings.py hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12615</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /onps/settings.py. Such manipulation of the argument SECRET_KEY leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack may be performed from remote. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12614 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php delete_payment sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12614</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Impacted is the function delete_payment of the file /admin_class.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12611 | Tenda AC21 SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12611</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This vulnerability affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument startIp leads to buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12612 | Campcodes School Fees Payment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12612</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes School Fees Payment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12610 | CodeAstro Gym Management System view-progress-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12610</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-progress-report.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12609 | CodeAstro Gym Management System update-progress.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12609</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-progress.php. Performing manipulation of the argument id/ini_weight results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12608 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12608</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /manage_user.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12607 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12607</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /manage_payment.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12606 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_borrower.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12606</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /manage_borrower.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12605 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_loan.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12605</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_loan.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12604 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System load_fields.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12604</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /load_fields.php. The manipulation of the argument loan_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12598 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php save_tenant sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12598</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function save_tenant of the file /admin_class.php. Executing manipulation of the argument firstname can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 12:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12597 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php save_category sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12597</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_category of the file /admin_class.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12596 | Tenda AC23 saveParentControlInfo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12596</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. Affected is the function saveParentControlInfo of the file /goform/saveParentControlInfo. Such manipulation of the argument Time leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12595 | Tenda AC23 SetVirtualServerCfg formSetVirtualSer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12595</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This impacts the function formSetVirtualSer of the file /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This manipulation of the argument list causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12594 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System add_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12594</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 2.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 08:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12593 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System Photo edit_room.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12593</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 2.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_room.php of the component Photo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12602 | /etc/avahi/services/z9.service can be Arbitrarily Written</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12602</link><description>/etc/avahi/services/z9.service can be Arbitrarily Written.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12603 | /etc/timezone can be Arbitrarily Written</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12603</link><description>/etc/timezone can be Arbitrarily Written.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12600 | Web UI Malfunction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12600</link><description>Web UI Malfunction when setting unexpected locale via API.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12601 | Denial of Service Due to SlowLoris</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12601</link><description>Denial of Service Due to SlowLoris.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12599 | Multiple Devices are Sharing the Same Secrets for SDKSocket (TCP/5000)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12599</link><description>Multiple Devices are Sharing the Same Secrets for SDKSocket (TCP/5000).This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36367 | IBM i is affected by a privilege escalation in IBM i SQL services []</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36367</link><description>IBM i 7.6, 7.5, 7.4, 7.3, and 7.2 is vulnerable to privilege escalation caused by an invalid IBM i SQL services authorization check.  A malicious actor can use the elevated privileges of another user profile to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 12:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6988 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.23.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6988</link><description>The kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several of the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 07:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6990 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.24.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6990</link><description>The kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.0 via the  `TH_PhpCode` pagebuilder widget. This is due to the theme not restricting access to the code editor widget for non-administrators. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 07:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10487 | Advanced Ads &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Unauthenticated Limited Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10487</link><description>The Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.12 via the select_one() function. This is due to the endpoint not properly restricting access to the AJAX endpoint or limiting the functions that can be called to safe functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call arbitrary functions beginning with get_the_ like get_the_excerpt which can make information exposure possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11499 | Tablesome Table – Contact Form DB – WPForms, CF7, Gravity, Forminator, Fluent &amp;lt;= 1.1.32 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11499</link><description>The Tablesome Table – Contact Form DB – WPForms, CF7, Gravity, Forminator, Fluent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the set_featured_image_from_external_url() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.32. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible in configurations where unauthenticated users have been provided with a method for adding featured images, and the workflow trigger is created.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11755 | Delicious Recipes &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11755</link><description>The WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads when importing recipes via CSV in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0. This flaw allows an attacker with at least Contributor-level permissions to upload a malicious PHP file by providing a remote URL during a recipe import process, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12137 | Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.14.16 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12137</link><description>The Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.16. This is due to the plugin's REST API endpoint accepting arbitrary absolute file paths without proper validation in the 'attach_file()' function when handling 'file_local' actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to read arbitrary files on the server's filesystem, including sensitive configuration files and system files via the 'local_url' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12171 | RESTful Content Syndication 1.1.0 - 1.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12171</link><description>The RESTful Content Syndication plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ingest_image() function in versions 1.1.0 to 1.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This requires the attacker have access to a defined third-party server as specified in the settings, so it is unlikely that this will be exploitable by contributor-level users, and more likely to be exploited by administrators who also have access to the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6574 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt; 6.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6574</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and excluding, 6.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11502 | Schema &amp;amp; Structured Data for WP &amp;amp; AMP &amp;lt;= 1.51 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11502</link><description>The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'saswp_tiny_multiple_faq' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.51 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11740 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.4.9 - Authenticated (Susbscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11740</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the Subscriptions Manager in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11983 | WP Discourse &amp;lt;= 2.5.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11983</link><description>The WP Discourse plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.9. This is due to the plugin unconditionally sending Discourse API credentials (Api-Key and Api-Username headers) to any host specified in a post's discourse_permalink custom field during comment synchronization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to exfiltrate sensitive Discourse API credentials to attacker-controlled servers, as well as query internal services and potentially perform further attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12038 | Folderly &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Term Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12038</link><description>The Folderly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an insufficient capability check on the /wp-json/folderly/v1/config/clear-all-data REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to clear all data like terms and categories.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12090 | Employee Spotlight – Team Member Showcase &amp;amp; Meet the Team Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12090</link><description>The Employee Spotlight – Team Member Showcase &amp; Meet the Team Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social URLs in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12180 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12180</link><description>The Qi Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This is due to the plugin storing arbitrary CSS styles submitted via the `qi-blocks/v1/update-styles` REST API endpoint without proper sanitization in the `update_global_styles_callback()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary CSS, which can be used to perform actions such as hiding content, overlaying fake UI elements, or exfiltrating sensitive information via CSS injection techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11377 | List category posts &amp;lt;= 0.92.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11377</link><description>The List category posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 0.92.0 via the 'catlist' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11927 | Flying Images: Optimize and Lazy Load Images for Faster Page Speed &amp;lt;= 2.4.14 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11927</link><description>The Flying Images: Optimize and Lazy Load Images for Faster Page Speed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11995 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11995</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via event details parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12118 | Schema Scalpel &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Title in JSON-LD Schema</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12118</link><description>The Schema Scalpel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the post title in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when outputting user-supplied data into JSON-LD schema markup. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5949 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via change_candidate_password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5949</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 6.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to processing a password change request. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber access or higher to reset other users' passwords, including those of admins.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11833 | Post SMTP – Complete SMTP Solution with Logs, Alerts, Backup SMTP &amp;amp; Mobile App &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Missing Authorization to Account Takeover via Unauthenticated Email Log Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11833</link><description>The Post SMTP – Complete SMTP Solution with Logs, Alerts, Backup SMTP &amp; Mobile App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the __construct function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary logged emails sent through the Post SMTP plugin, including password reset emails containing password reset links, which can lead to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11928 | CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript Toolbox &amp;lt;= 12.0.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11928</link><description>The CSS &amp; JavaScript Toolbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 12.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12367 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12367</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to enable or disable arbitrary SiteSEO features that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62275 | Blogs in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62275</link><description>Blogs in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions does not check permission of images in a blog entry, which allows remote attackers to view the images in a blog entry via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11174 | Document Library Lite &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11174</link><description>The Document Library Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This is due to the plugin exposing an unauthenticated AJAX action dll_load_posts which returns a JSON table of document data without performing nonce or capability checks. The handler accepts an attacker-controlled args array where the status option explicitly allows draft, pending, future, and any. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve unpublished document titles and content via the AJAX endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11816 | Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp;amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated API Disconnect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11816</link><description>The Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the disconnect_account_request() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disconnect the site from its API plan.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11920 | WPCOM Member &amp;lt;= 1.7.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11920</link><description>The WPCOM Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.14 via the action parameter in one of its shortcodes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11922 | Inactive Logout &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11922</link><description>The Inactive Logout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ina_redirect_page_individual_user' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>