<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-26264 | EBM Technologies RISWEB - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26264</link><description>EBM Technologies RISWEB's specific query function parameter does not properly restrict user input, and this feature page is accessible without login. This allows remote attackers to inject SQL commands without authentication, enabling them to read, modify, and delete database records.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26263 | EBM Technologies RISWEB - Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26263</link><description>EBM Technologies RISWEB's specific URL path is not properly controlled by permission, allowing attackers to browse specific pages and query sensitive data without login.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26262 | EBM Technologies Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26262</link><description>EBM Technologies Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer's query functionality lacks proper restrictions of user input, allowing remote attackers authenticated as regular user to inject SQL commands for reading, modifying, and deleting database records, as well as executing system commands. Attackers may even leverage the dbo privilege in the database for privilege escalation, elevating their privileges to administrator .</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26261 | Hgiga OAKlouds - Arbitrary File Read And Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26261</link><description>The functionality for file download in HGiga OAKlouds' certain modules contains an Arbitrary File Read and Delete vulnerability. Attackers can put file path in specific request parameters, allowing them to download the file without login. Furthermore, the file will be deleted after being downloaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26260 | Hgiga OAKlouds - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26260</link><description>The functionality for synchronization in HGiga OAKlouds' certain moudules has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to inject system commands within specific request parameters. This enables the execution of arbitrary code on the remote server without permission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1523 | EC-WEB  FS-EZViewer(Web) - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1523</link><description>EC-WEB FS-EZViewer(Web)'s query functionality lacks proper restrictions of user input, allowing remote attackers authenticated as regular user to inject SQL commands for reading, modifying, and deleting database records, as well as executing system commands. Attackers may even leverage the dbo privilege in the database for privilege escalation, elevating their privileges to administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:14:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25620 | Dependency management path traversal in helm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25620</link><description>Helm is a tool for managing Charts. Charts are packages of pre-configured Kubernetes resources. When either the Helm client or SDK is used to save a chart whose name within the `Chart.yaml` file includes a relative path change, the chart would be saved outside its expected directory based on the changes in the relative path. The validation and linting did not detect the path changes in the name. This issue has been resolved in Helm v3.14.1. Users unable to upgrade should check all charts used by Helm for path changes in their name as found in the `Chart.yaml` file. This includes dependencies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24300 | 4ipnet EAP-767 v3.42.00 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The device uses the same set of credentials, regardless of how many times...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24300</link><description>4ipnet EAP-767 v3.42.00 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The device uses the same set of credentials, regardless of how many times a user logs in, the content of the cookie remains unchanged.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48219 | Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48219</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusion detection bypass via a physical attack. HP is releasing firmware and guidance to mitigate these potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48220 | Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48220</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusion detection bypass via a physical attack. HP is releasing firmware and guidance to mitigate these potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24301 | Command Injection vulnerability discovered in 4ipnet EAP-767 device v3.42.00 within the web interface of the device allows attackers with va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24301</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability discovered in 4ipnet EAP-767 device v3.42.00 within the web interface of the device allows attackers with valid credentials to inject arbitrary shell commands to be executed by the device with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6138 | A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the system BIOS for certain HP Workstation PCs, which might allow escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6138</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the system BIOS for certain HP Workstation PCs, which might allow escalation of privilege, arbitrary code execution, or denial of service. HP is releasing mitigation for the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49721 | An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in LXD. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49721</link><description>An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in LXD. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48733 | An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in Ubuntu's EDK2. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48733</link><description>An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in Ubuntu's EDK2. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1471 | HTML Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1471</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges on the Security Center application could modify Repository parameters, which could lead to HTML redirection attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1367 | Command Injection Vulnerability in Tenable Security Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1367</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges on the Security Center application could modify Logging parameters, which could lead to the execution of arbitrary code on the Security Center host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25617 | Denial of Service in HTTP Header parser in squid proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25617</link><description>Squid is an open source caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to a Collapse of Data into Unsafe Value bug ,Squid may be vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against HTTP header parsing. This problem allows a remote client or a remote server to perform Denial of Service when sending oversized headers in HTTP messages. In versions of Squid prior to 6.5 this can be achieved if the request_header_max_size or reply_header_max_size settings are unchanged from the default. In Squid version 6.5 and later, the default setting of these parameters is safe. Squid will emit a critical warning in cache.log if the administrator is setting these parameters to unsafe values. Squid will not at this time prevent these settings from being changed to unsafe values. Users are advised to upgrade to version 6.5. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. This issue is also tracked as SQUID-2024:2</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25619 | Destroying OAuth Applications doesn&amp;#x27;t notify Streaming of Access Tokens being destroyed in mastodon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25619</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. When an OAuth Application is destroyed, the streaming server wasn't being informed that the Access Tokens had also been destroyed, this could have posed security risks to users by allowing an application to continue listening to streaming after the application had been destroyed. Essentially this comes down to the fact that when Doorkeeper sets up the relationship between Applications and Access Tokens, it uses a `dependent: delete_all` configuration, which means the `after_commit` callback setup on `AccessTokenExtension` didn't actually fire, since `delete_all` doesn't trigger ActiveRecord callbacks. To mitigate, we need to add a `before_destroy` callback to `ApplicationExtension` which announces to streaming that all the Application's Access Tokens are being "killed". Impact should be negligible given the affected application had to be owned by the user. None the less this issue has been addressed in versions 4.2.6, 4.1.14, 4.0.14, and 3.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workaround for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25618 | External OpenID Connect Account Takeover by E-Mail Change in mastodon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25618</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Mastodon allows new identities from configured authentication providers (CAS, SAML, OIDC) to attach to existing local users with the same e-mail address. This results in a possible account takeover if the authentication provider allows changing the e-mail address or multiple authentication providers are configured. When a user logs in through an external authentication provider for the first time, Mastodon checks the e-mail address passed by the provider to find an existing account. However, using the e-mail address alone means that if the authentication provider allows changing the e-mail address of an account, the Mastodon account can immediately be hijacked. All users logging in through external authentication providers are affected. The severity is medium, as it also requires the external authentication provider to misbehave. However, some well-known OIDC providers (like Microsoft Azure) make it very easy to accidentally allow unverified e-mail changes. Moreover, OpenID Connect also allows dynamic client registration. This issue has been addressed in versions 4.2.6, 4.1.14, 4.0.14, and 3.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1482 | Improper Authorization in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed unauthorized workflow execution </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1482</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to create new branches in public repositories and run arbitrary GitHub Actions workflows with permissions from the GITHUB_TOKEN. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need access to the Enterprise Server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server after 3.8 and prior to 3.12, and was fixed in versions 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25165 | A global-buffer-overflow vulnerability was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function LineText at lib/swf5compiler.flex.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25165</link><description>A global-buffer-overflow vulnerability was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function LineText at lib/swf5compiler.flex.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50926 | Unvalidated DIO prefix info length in RPL-Lite in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50926</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read can be caused by an incoming DIO message when using the RPL-Lite implementation in the Contiki-NG operating system. More specifically, the prefix information of the DIO message contains a field that specifies the length of an IPv6 address prefix. The value of this field is not validated, which means that an attacker can set a value that is longer than the maximum prefix length. Subsequently, a memcmp function call that compares different prefixes can be called with a length argument that surpasses the boundary of the array allocated for the prefix, causing an out-of-bounds read. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG, and is expected to be included in the next release. Users are advised to update as soon as they are able to or to manually apply the changes in Contiki-NG pull request #2721.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50927 | Insufficient boundary checks for DIO and DAO messages in RPL-Lite in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50927</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An attacker can trigger out-of-bounds reads in the RPL-Lite implementation of the RPL protocol in the Contiki-NG operating system. This vulnerability is caused by insufficient control of the lengths for DIO and DAO messages, in particular when they contain RPL sub-option headers. The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG 4.9. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should manually apply the code changes in PR #2484.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25300 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Redaxo v5.15.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25300</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Redaxo v5.15.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Name parameter in the Template section.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25301 | Redaxo v5.15.1 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /pages/templates.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25301</link><description>Redaxo v5.15.1 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /pages/templates.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48229 | Out-of-bounds write in the radio driver for Contiki-NG nRF platforms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48229</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds write exists in the driver for IEEE 802.15.4 radios on nRF platforms in the Contiki-NG operating system. The problem is triggered when parsing radio frames in the `read_frame` function in the `arch/cpu/nrf/net/nrf-ieee-driver-arch.c` module. More specifically, the `read_frame` function performs an incomplete validation of the payload length of the packet, which is a value that can be set by an external party that sends radio packets to a Contiki-NG system. Although the value is validated to be in the range of the MTU length, it is not validated to fit into the given buffer into which the packet will be copied. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG and is expected to be included in subsequent releases. Users are advised to update their develop branch or to update to a subsequent release when available. Users unable to upgrade should consider manually applying the changes in PR #2741.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0008 | PAN-OS: Insufficient Session Expiration Vulnerability in the Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0008</link><description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0009 | PAN-OS: Improper IP Address Verification in GlobalProtect Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0009</link><description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0010 | PAN-OS: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in GlobalProtect Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0010</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0011 | PAN-OS: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Captive Portal Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0007 | PAN-OS: Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in the Panorama Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0007</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0568 | CWE-287: Improper Authentication vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized tampering
of device configuration over NFC communication...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0568</link><description>CWE-287: Improper Authentication vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized tampering
of device configuration over NFC communication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27975 | CWE-522: Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to the project file in EcoStruxure C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27975</link><description>CWE-522: Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to the project file in EcoStruxure Control Expert when a local user tampers with the
memory of the engineering workstation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6408 | CWE-924: Improper Enforcement of Message Integrity During Transmission in a
Communication Channel vulnerability exists that could cause a de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6408</link><description>CWE-924: Improper Enforcement of Message Integrity During Transmission in a
Communication Channel vulnerability exists that could cause a denial of service and loss of
confidentiality, integrity of controllers when conducting a Man in the Middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6409 | CWE-798: Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to a project file protected with applicatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6409</link><description>CWE-798: Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to a project file protected with application password when opening the file with
EcoStruxure Control Expert.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23982 | BIG-IP PEM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23982</link><description>When a BIG-IP PEM classification profile is configured on a UDP virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. This issue affects classification engines using signatures released between 09-08-2022 and 02-16-2023. See the table in the F5 Security Advisory for a complete list of affected classification signature files.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21763 | BIG-IP AFM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21763</link><description>When BIG-IP AFM Device DoS or DoS profile is configured with NXDOMAIN attack vector and bad actor detection, undisclosed queries can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21771 | F5 AFM Signature Matching Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21771</link><description>For unspecified traffic patterns, BIG-IP AFM IPS engine may spend an excessive amount of time matching the traffic against signatures, resulting in Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) restarting and traffic disruption.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21782 | BIG-IP and BIG-IQ secure copy vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21782</link><description>BIG-IP or BIG-IQ Resource Administrators and Certificate Managers who have access to the secure copy (scp) utility but do not have access to Advanced shell (bash) can execute arbitrary commands with a specially crafted command string. This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-5873. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21789 | BIG-IP ASM and Advanced WAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21789</link><description>When a BIG-IP ASM/Advanced WAF security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.
 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21849 | BIG-IP Websockets vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21849</link><description>When an Advanced WAF/ASM security policy and a Websockets profile are configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22093 | Appliance mode iControl REST vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22093</link><description>When running in appliance mode, an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint on multi-bladed systems. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22389 | BIG-IP iControl REST API Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22389</link><description>When BIG-IP is deployed in high availability (HA) and an iControl REST API token is updated, the change does not sync to the peer device.  


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23306 | BIG-IP Next CNF &amp;amp; SPK vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23306</link><description>A vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next CNF and SPK systems that may allow access to undisclosed sensitive files.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23308 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23308</link><description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF or BIG-IP ASM policy with a Request Body Handling option is attached to a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the BD process to terminate. The condition results from setting the Request Body Handling option in the Header-Based Content Profile for an Allowed URL with "Apply value and content signatures and detect threat campaigns."  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23314 | BIG-IP HTTP/2 vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23314</link><description>When HTTP/2 is configured on BIG-IP or BIG-IP Next SPK systems, undisclosed responses can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23603 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM Configuration utility vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23603</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23607 | F5OS QKView utility vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23607</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the F5OS QKView utility that allows an authenticated attacker to read files outside the QKView directory.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23805 | F5 Application Visibility and Reporting module and BIG-IP Advanced WAF/ASM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23805</link><description>Undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. For the Application Visibility and Reporting module, this may occur when the HTTP Analytics profile with URLs enabled under Collected Entities is configured on a virtual server and the DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI or avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are enabled. For BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM, this may occur when either a DoS or Bot Defense profile is configured on a virtual server and the DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI or avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are enabled.

Note: The DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI and avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are not enabled by default. For more information about the HTTP Analytics profile and the Collect URLs setting, refer to  K30875743: Create a new Analytics profile and attach it to your virtual servers https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K30875743 .



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23976 | BIG-IP Appliance mode iAppsLX vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23976</link><description>When running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance
mode restrictions utilizing iAppsLX templates on a BIG-IP system.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23979 | BIG-IP SSL Client Certificate LDAP and CRLDP Authentication profiles vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23979</link><description>When SSL Client Certificate LDAP or Certificate Revocation List Distribution Point (CRLDP) authentication profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in CPU resource utilization. 

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24775 | BIG-IP TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24775</link><description>When a virtual server is enabled with VLAN group and SNAT listener is configured, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24966 | F5OS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24966</link><description>When LDAP remote authentication is configured on F5OS, a remote user without an assigned role will be incorrectly authorized.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24989 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24989</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.

Note: The HTTP/3 QUIC module is not enabled by default and is considered experimental. For more information, refer to  Support for QUIC and HTTP/3 https://nginx.org/en/docs/quic.html .



NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24990 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24990</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.

Note: The HTTP/3 QUIC module is not enabled by default and is considered experimental. For more information, refer to  Support for QUIC and HTTP/3 https://nginx.org/en/docs/quic.html .



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50868 | The Closest Encloser Proof aspect of the DNS protocol (in RFC 5155 when RFC 9276 guidance is skipped) allows remote attackers to cause a den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50868</link><description>The Closest Encloser Proof aspect of the DNS protocol (in RFC 5155 when RFC 9276 guidance is skipped) allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption for SHA-1 computations) via DNSSEC responses in a random subdomain attack, aka the "NSEC3" issue. The RFC 5155 specification implies that an algorithm must perform thousands of iterations of a hash function in certain situations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50387 | Certain DNSSEC aspects of the DNS protocol (in RFC 4035 and related RFCs) allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumpti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50387</link><description>Certain DNSSEC aspects of the DNS protocol (in RFC 4035 and related RFCs) allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption) via one or more DNSSEC responses when there is a zone with many DNSKEY and RRSIG records, aka the "KeyTrap" issue. The protocol specification implies that an algorithm must evaluate all combinations of DNSKEY and RRSIG records.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5122 | SSRF in CSV Datasource Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5122</link><description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. The CSV datasource plugin is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing CSV data from a remote endpoint configured by an administrator. If this plugin was configured to send requests to a bare host with no path (e.g.  https://www.example.com/ https://www.example.com/` ), requests to an endpoint other than the one configured by the administrator could be triggered by a specially crafted request from any user, resulting in an SSRF vector. AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5123 | Improper Path Sanitization in JSON Datasource Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5123</link><description>The JSON datasource plugin ( https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ ) is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing JSON data from a remote endpoint (including a specific sub-path) configured by an administrator. Due to inadequate sanitization of the dashboard-supplied path parameter, it was possible to include path traversal characters (../) in the path parameter and send requests to paths on the configured endpoint outside the configured sub-path. 





    
    
            






    
    
            This means that if the datasource was configured by an administrator to point at some sub-path of a domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ ), it was possible for an editor to create a dashboard referencing the datasource which issues queries containing path traversal characters, which would in turn cause the datasource to instead query arbitrary subpaths on the configured domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/admin_api/) https://example.com/api/admin_api/) .

In the rare case that this plugin is configured by an administrator to point back at the Grafana instance itself, this vulnerability becomes considerably more severe, as an administrator browsing a maliciously configured panel could be compelled to make requests to Grafana administrative API endpoints with their credentials, resulting in the potential for privilege escalation, hence the high score for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25207 | Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25207</link><description>Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function at /barangay-population-monitoring-system/masterlist.php. This vulnerabiity allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Contact Number parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25208 | Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25208</link><description>Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function at /barangay-population-monitoring-system/masterlist.php. This vulnerabiity allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Full Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25209 | Barangay Population Monitoring System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the resident parameter at /endpoint/de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25209</link><description>Barangay Population Monitoring System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the resident parameter at /endpoint/delete-resident.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25210 | Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the expense parameter at /endpoint/delete_expense.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25210</link><description>Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the expense parameter at /endpoint/delete_expense.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25211 | Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the category parameter at /endpoint/delete_category....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25211</link><description>Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the category parameter at /endpoint/delete_category.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25212 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /delete.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25212</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /delete.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25213 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25213</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25214 | An issue in Employee Managment System v1.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication via injecting a crafted payload into the E-mail and Pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25214</link><description>An issue in Employee Managment System v1.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication via injecting a crafted payload into the E-mail and Password parameters at /alogin.html.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25215 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pwd parameter at /aprocess.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25215</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pwd parameter at /aprocess.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25216 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the mailud parameter at /aprocess.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25216</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the mailud parameter at /aprocess.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25217 | Online Medicine Ordering System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /omos/?p=products/view_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25217</link><description>Online Medicine Ordering System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /omos/?p=products/view_product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25218 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25218</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Project Name parameter /TaskManager/Projects.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25219 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25219</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Task Name parameter /TaskManager/Task.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25220 | Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the taskID parameter at /TaskManager/EditTask.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25220</link><description>Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the taskID parameter at /TaskManager/EditTask.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25221 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25221</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Note Section parameter at /TaskManager/Tasks.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25222 | Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the projectID parameter at /TaskManager/EditProject.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25222</link><description>Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the projectID parameter at /TaskManager/EditProject.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25223 | Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderID parameter at /adminView/viewEachOrder.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25223</link><description>Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderID parameter at /adminView/viewEachOrder.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25224 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25224</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Size Number parameter under the Add Size function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25225 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25225</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Category Name parameter under the Add Category function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25226 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25226</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Category Name parameter under the Add Category function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46186 | IBM Jazz for Service Management information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46186</link><description>IBM Jazz for Service Management 1.1.3.20 could allow an unauthorized user to obtain sensitive file information using forced browsing due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  269929.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22293 | Improper access control in the Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22293</link><description>Improper access control in the Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22311 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem 100 Series Management Software before version 01.00.00.3547 may allow an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22311</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem 100 Series Management Software before version 01.00.00.3547 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22342 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22342</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22390 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22390</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22848 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22848</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24463 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24463</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24481 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24481</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24542 | Unquoted search path or element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24542</link><description>Unquoted search path or element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24589 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24589</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24591 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Binary Configuration Tool software before version 3.4.4 may allow an authenticated user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24591</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Binary Configuration Tool software before version 3.4.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25073 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25073</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25174 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25174</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25769 | Uncontrolled resource consumption in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25769</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25777 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25777</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25779 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25779</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25945 | Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25945</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25951 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow a privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25951</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26585 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26585</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26586 | Uncaught exception for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26586</link><description>Uncaught exception for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26591 | Unchecked return value in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26591</link><description>Unchecked return value in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via physical access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26592 | Deserialization of untrusted data in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26592</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26596 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26596</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27300 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27300</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27301 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27301</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27303 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27303</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27307 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27307</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27308 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27308</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27517 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem software before versions 01.00.00.3547, 02.00.00.3915, 03.00.00.0483 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27517</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem software before versions 01.00.00.3547, 02.00.00.3915, 03.00.00.0483 may allow an athenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28374 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28374</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28396 | Improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) Thunderbol(TM) Controllers versions before 41 may allow a privileged user to enable de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28396</link><description>Improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) Thunderbol(TM) Controllers versions before 41 may allow a privileged user to enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28407 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28407</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28715 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28715</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28720 | Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28720</link><description>Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access..</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28739 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28739</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28745 | Uncontrolled search path in Intel(R) QSFP+ Configuration Utility software, all versions, may allow an authenticated user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28745</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in Intel(R) QSFP+ Configuration Utility software, all versions, may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29153 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware before version SPS_E5_06.01.04.002.0 may allow a privileged user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29153</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware before version SPS_E5_06.01.04.002.0 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29162 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) C++ Compiler Classic before version 2021.8 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29162</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) C++ Compiler Classic before version 2021.8 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30767 | Improper buffer restrictions in Intel(R) Optimization for TensorFlow before version 2.13.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30767</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in Intel(R) Optimization for TensorFlow before version 2.13.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31189 | Improper authentication in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before version egs-1.09 may allow an authenticated user to enable e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31189</link><description>Improper authentication in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before version egs-1.09 may allow an authenticated user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31271 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31271</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32280 | Insufficiently protected credentials in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before versions egs-1.05 may allow an unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32280</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before versions egs-1.05 may allow an unauthenticated user to enable information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32618 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32618</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32642 | Insufficient adherence to expected conventions for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.24...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32642</link><description>Insufficient adherence to expected conventions for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32644 | Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32644</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32646 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32646</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32647 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32647</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32651 | Improper validation of specified type of input for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.24...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32651</link><description>Improper validation of specified type of input for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33870 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33870</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33875 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33875</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access..</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34315 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34315</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34351 | Buffer underflow in some Intel(R) PCM software before version 202307 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34351</link><description>Buffer underflow in some Intel(R) PCM software before version 202307 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34983 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34983</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35003 | Path transversal in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35003</link><description>Path transversal in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35060 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.3.1 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35060</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.3.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35061 | Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35061</link><description>Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35062 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35062</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35121 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software before version 2023.2.1 may allow authenticated user to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35121</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software before version 2023.2.1 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35769 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10577 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35769</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10577 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36490 | Improper initialization in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36490</link><description>Improper initialization in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36493 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) SDK for OpenCL(TM) Applications software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36493</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) SDK for OpenCL(TM) Applications software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38135 | Improper authorization in some Intel(R) PM software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38135</link><description>Improper authorization in some Intel(R) PM software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38561 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38561</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38566 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) ISPC software before version 1.21.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38566</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) ISPC software before version 1.21.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39425 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39425</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39432 | Improper access control element in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software, before versions 28.2, may allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39432</link><description>Improper access control element in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software, before versions 28.2, may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39932 | Uncontrolled search path in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow a privillaged user to potentially enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39932</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow a privillaged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39941 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) SUR software before version 2.4.10587 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39941</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) SUR software before version 2.4.10587 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40154 | Incorrect default permissions in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow privillaged user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40154</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow privillaged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40156 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) SSU software before version 3.0.0.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40156</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) SSU software before version 3.0.0.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40161 | Improper access control in some Intel Unite(R) Client software before version 4.2.35041 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40161</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel Unite(R) Client software before version 4.2.35041 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41090 | Race condition in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41090</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41091 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library Software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41091</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library Software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41231 | Incorrect default permissions in some ACAT software maintained by Intel(R) before version 2.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41231</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some ACAT software maintained by Intel(R) before version 2.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41252 | Out-of-bounds read in some Intel(R) QAT software drivers for Windows before version QAT1.7-W-1.11.0 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41252</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in some Intel(R) QAT software drivers for Windows before version QAT1.7-W-1.11.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42776 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) SGX DCAP software for Windows before version 1.19.100.3 may allow an authenticateed user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42776</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) SGX DCAP software for Windows before version 1.19.100.3 may allow an authenticateed user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6441 | SQLi in UNI-PA&amp;#x27;s University Information System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6441</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in UNI-PA University Marketing &amp; Computer Internet Trade Inc. University Information System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects University Information System: before 12.12.2023.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23952 | Apache Superset: Allows for uncontrolled resource consumption via a ZIP bomb (version range fix for CVE-2023-46104)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23952</link><description>This is a duplicate for CVE-2023-46104. With correct CVE version ranges for affected Apache Superset.
 
Uncontrolled resource consumption can be triggered by authenticated attacker that uploads a malicious ZIP to import database, dashboards or datasets.  
This vulnerability exists in Apache Superset versions up to and including 2.1.2 and versions 3.0.0, 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 11:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23789 | Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23789</link><description>Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary OS command on the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23784 | Improper access control vulnerability exists in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23784</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability exists in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier, which may allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain a username and its hashed password displayed on the management page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23785 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23785</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to change the product settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23786 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23786</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is accessing the management page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23787 | Path traversal vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23787</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain an arbitrary file in the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23788 | Server-side request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23788</link><description>Server-side request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to send an arbitrary HTTP request (GET) from the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23783 | Improper authentication vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23783</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to access the affected product without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48985 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48985</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48986 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48986</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the users.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48987 | Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48987</link><description>Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the pages.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44294 | In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44294</link><description>In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern has been identified, where a malicious user with a valid User session may inject malicious content in filters of Collection Rest API. 
This issue may potentially lead to unintentional information disclosure from the product database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44293 | In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44293</link><description>In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern has been identified, where a malicious user with a valid User session may inject malicious content in filters of IP Range Rest API. This issue may potentially lead to unintentional information disclosure from the product database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44283 | In Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs (between v3.0 and v3.14.1) and SupportAssist for Business PCs (between v3.0 and v3.4.1), a security conce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44283</link><description>In Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs (between v3.0 and v3.14.1) and SupportAssist for Business PCs (between v3.0 and v3.4.1), a security concern has been identified, impacting locally authenticated users on their respective PCs. This issue may potentially enable privilege escalation and the execution of arbitrary code, in the Windows system context, and confined to that specific local PC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39249 | Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs version 3.4.0 contains a local Authentication Bypass vulnerability that allows locally authenticated non...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39249</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs version 3.4.0 contains a local Authentication Bypass vulnerability that allows locally authenticated non-admin users to gain temporary privilege within the SupportAssist User Interface on their respective PC. The Run as Admin temporary privilege feature enables IT/System Administrators to perform driver scans and Dell-recommended driver installations without requiring them to log out of the local non-admin user session. However, the granted privilege is limited solely to the SupportAssist User Interface and automatically expires after 15 minutes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25535 | Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs Installer Executable file version prior to 3.13.2.19 used for initial installation has a high vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25535</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs Installer Executable file version prior to 3.13.2.19 used for initial installation has a high vulnerability that can result in local privilege escalation (LPE). This vulnerability only affects first-time installations done prior to 8th March 2023</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22455 | Dell E-Lab Navigator, [3.1.9, 3.2.0], contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference Vulnerability in Feedback submission. An attacker could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22455</link><description>Dell E-Lab Navigator, [3.1.9, 3.2.0], contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference Vulnerability in Feedback submission. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to manipulate the email's appearance, potentially deceiving recipients and causing reputational and security risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25125 | Absolute path traversal vulnerability in digdag server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25125</link><description>Digdag is an open source tool that to build, run, schedule, and monitor complex pipelines of tasks across various platforms. Treasure Data's digdag workload automation system is susceptible to a path traversal vulnerability if it's configured to store log files locally. This issue may lead to information disclosure and has been addressed in release version 0.10.5.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 01:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24690 | Zoom Clients  - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24690</link><description>Improper input validation in some Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24691 | Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows  - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24691</link><description>Improper input validation in Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24699 | Zoom Clients  - Business Logic Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24699</link><description>Business logic error in some Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24696 | Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24696</link><description>Improper input validation in Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24697 | Zoom Clients - Untrusted Search Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24697</link><description>Untrusted search path in some Zoom 32 bit Windows clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24698 | Zoom Clients  - Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24698</link><description>Improper authentication in some Zoom clients may allow a privileged user to conduct a disclosure of information via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24695 |  Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24695</link><description>Improper input validation in Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1485 | Registry-support: decompress can delete files outside scope via relative paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1485</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the decompression function of registry-support. This issue can be triggered by an unauthenticated remote attacker when tricking a user into opening a specially modified .tar archive, leading to the cleanup process following relative paths to overwrite or delete files outside the intended scope.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25118 | Information Disclosure of Hashed Passwords in TYPO3 Backend Forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25118</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. Password hashes were being reflected in the editing forms of the TYPO3 backend user interface. This allowed attackers to crack the plaintext password using brute force techniques. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, 13.0.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25119 | Information Disclosure of Encryption Key in TYPO3 Install Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25119</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. The plaintext value of `$GLOBALS['SYS']['encryptionKey']` was displayed in the editing forms of the TYPO3 Install Tool user interface. This allowed attackers to utilize the value to generate cryptographic hashes used for verifying the authenticity of HTTP request parameters. Exploiting this vulnerability requires an administrator-level backend user account with system maintainer permissions. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, 13.0.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25120 | Improper Access Control of Resources Referenced by t3:// URI Scheme in TYPO3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25120</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. The TYPO3-specific `t3://` URI scheme could be used to access resources outside of the users' permission scope. This encompassed files, folders, pages, and records (although only if a valid link-handling configuration was provided). Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, 13.0.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38960 | Insecure Permissions issue in Raiden Professional Server RaidenFTPD v.2.4 build 4005 allows a local attacker to gain privileges and execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38960</link><description>Insecure Permissions issue in Raiden Professional Server RaidenFTPD v.2.4 build 4005 allows a local attacker to gain privileges and execute arbitrary code via crafted executable running from the installation directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25121 | Improper Access Control Persisting File Abstraction Layer Entities via Data Handler in TYPO3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25121</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. In affected versions of TYPO3 entities of the File Abstraction Layer (FAL) could be persisted directly via `DataHandler`. This allowed attackers to reference files in the fallback storage directly and retrieve their file names and contents. The fallback storage ("zero-storage") is used as a backward compatibility layer for files located outside properly configured file storages and within the public web root directory. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 version 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, or 13.0.1 which fix the problem described. When persisting entities of the File Abstraction Layer directly via DataHandler, `sys_file` entities are now denied by default, and `sys_file_reference` &amp; `sys_file_metadata` entities are not permitted to reference files in the fallback storage anymore. When importing data from secure origins, this must be explicitly enabled in the corresponding DataHandler instance by using `$dataHandler-&gt;isImporting = true;`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6152 | A user changing their email after signing up and verifying it can change it without verification in profile settings.

The configuration opt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6152</link><description>A user changing their email after signing up and verifying it can change it without verification in profile settings.

The configuration option "verify_email_enabled" will only validate email only on sign up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 21:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24142 | Sourcecodester School Task Manager 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'subject' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24142</link><description>Sourcecodester School Task Manager 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'subject' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 20:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20579 | Improper
Access Control in the AMD SPI protection feature may allow a user with Ring0
(kernel mode) privileged access to bypass protections ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20579</link><description>Improper
Access Control in the AMD SPI protection feature may allow a user with Ring0
(kernel mode) privileged access to bypass protections potentially resulting in
loss of integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20587 | Improper
Access Control in System Management Mode (SMM) may allow an attacker access to
the SPI flash potentially leading to arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20587</link><description>Improper
Access Control in System Management Mode (SMM) may allow an attacker access to
the SPI flash potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46757 | Insufficient checking of memory buffer in ASP
Secure OS may allow an attacker with a malicious TA to read/write to the ASP
Secure OS kernel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46757</link><description>Insufficient checking of memory buffer in ASP
Secure OS may allow an attacker with a malicious TA to read/write to the ASP
Secure OS kernel virtual address space potentially leading to privilege
escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31346 | Failure to initialize
memory in SEV Firmware may allow a privileged attacker to access stale data
from other guests.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31346</link><description>Failure to initialize
memory in SEV Firmware may allow a privileged attacker to access stale data
from other guests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31347 | Due to a code bug in
Secure_TSC, SEV firmware may allow an attacker with high privileges to cause a
guest to observe an incorrect TSC when S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31347</link><description>Due to a code bug in
Secure_TSC, SEV firmware may allow an attacker with high privileges to cause a
guest to observe an incorrect TSC when Secure TSC is enabled potentially
resulting in a loss of guest integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25122 |  Cross-site Scripting sidekiq-unique-jobs UI server vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25122</link><description>sidekiq-unique-jobs is an open source project which prevents simultaneous Sidekiq jobs with the same unique arguments to run. Specially crafted GET request parameters handled by any of the following endpoints of sidekiq-unique-jobs' "admin" web UI, allow a super-user attacker, or an unwitting, but authorized, victim, who has received a disguised / crafted link, to successfully execute malicious code, which could potentially steal cookies, session data, or local storage data from the app the sidekiq-unique-jobs web UI is mounted in. 1. `/changelogs`, 2. `/locks` or 3. `/expiring_locks`. This issue has been addressed in versions 7.1.33 and 8.0.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1354 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1354</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the `syslog-ng` configuration file. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1355 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1355</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the actions-console docker container while setting a service URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1359 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1359</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting up an HTTP proxy. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1369 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1369</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting the username and password for collectd configurations. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1372 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1372</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring SAML settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1374 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1374</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring audit log forwarding. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1378 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Mangement Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1378</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring SMTP options. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1082 | Path traversal vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed arbitrary file read with a specially crafted GitHub Pages artifact upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1082</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to gain unauthorized read permission to files by deploying arbitrary symbolic links to a GitHub Pages site with a specially crafted artifact tarball. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.15, 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24814 | Denial of service when manipulating mod_auth_openidc_session_chunks cookie in mod_auth_openidc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24814</link><description>mod_auth_openidc is an OpenID Certified™ authentication and authorization module for the Apache 2.x HTTP server that implements the OpenID Connect Relying Party functionality. In affected versions missing input validation on mod_auth_openidc_session_chunks cookie value makes the server vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack. An internal security audit has been conducted and the reviewers found that if they manipulated the value of the mod_auth_openidc_session_chunks cookie to a very large integer, like 99999999, the server struggles with the request for a long time and finally gets back with a 500 error. Making a few requests of this kind caused our server to become unresponsive. Attackers can craft requests that would make the server work very hard (and possibly become unresponsive) and/or crash with minimal effort. This issue has been addressed in version 2.4.15.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1084 | Cross-site Scripting in the tag name pattern field in the tag protections UI in GitHub Enterprise Server allows a malicious website that req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1084</link><description>Cross-site Scripting in the tag name pattern field in the tag protections UI in GitHub Enterprise Server allows a malicious website that requires user interaction and social engineering to make changes to a user account via CSP bypass with created CSRF tokens. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12  and was fixed in all versions of 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1216 | Twister Antivirus v8.17 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1216</link><description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x80112044, 0x8011204B, 0x8011204F, 0x80112057, 0x8011205B, 0x8011205F, 0x80112063, 0x8011206F, 0x80112073, 0x80112077, 0x80112078, 0x8011207C and 0x80112080 IOCTL codes of the fildds.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24751 | Broken Access Control in Backend Module in sf_event_mgt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24751</link><description>sf_event_mgt is an event management and registration extension for the TYPO3 CMS based on ExtBase and Fluid. In affected versions the existing access control check for events in the backend module got broken during the update of the extension to TYPO3 12.4, because the `RedirectResponse` from the `$this-&gt;redirect()` function was never handled. This issue has been addressed in version 7.4.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20667 | Azure DevOps Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20667</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20673 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20673</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20679 | Azure Stack Hub Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20679</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20684 | Windows Hyper-V Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20684</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20695 | Skype for Business Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20695</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21304 | Trusted Compute Base Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21304</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21315 | Microsoft Defender for Endpoint Protection Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21315</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21327 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21327</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21328 | Dynamics 365 Sales Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21328</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21329 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21329</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21338 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21338</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21339 | Windows USB Generic Parent Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21339</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21340 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21340</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21341 | Windows Kernel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21341</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21342 | Windows DNS Client Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21342</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21343 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21343</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21344 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21344</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21345 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21345</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21346 | Win32k Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21346</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21347 | Microsoft ODBC Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21347</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21348 | Internet Connection Sharing (ICS) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21348</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21349 | Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21349</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21350 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21350</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21351 | Windows SmartScreen Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21351</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21352 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21352</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21353 | Microsoft WDAC ODBC Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21353</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21354 | Microsoft Message Queuing (MSMQ) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21354</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21355 | Microsoft Message Queuing (MSMQ) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21355</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21356 | Windows Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21356</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21357 | Windows Pragmatic General Multicast (PGM) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21357</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21358 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21358</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21359 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21359</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21360 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21360</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21361 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21361</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21362 | Windows Kernel Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21362</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21363 | Microsoft Message Queuing (MSMQ) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21363</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21364 | Microsoft Azure Site Recovery Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21364</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21365 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21365</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21366 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21366</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21367 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21367</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21368 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21368</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21369 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21369</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21370 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21370</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21371 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21371</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21372 | Windows OLE Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21372</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21374 | Microsoft Teams for Android Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21374</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21375 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21375</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21376 | Microsoft Azure Kubernetes Service Confidential Container Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21376</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21377 | Windows DNS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21377</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21378 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21378</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21379 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21379</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21380 | Microsoft Dynamics Business Central/NAV Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21380</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21381 | Microsoft Azure Active Directory B2C Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21381</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21384 | Microsoft Office OneNote Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21384</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21386 | .NET Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21386</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21389 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21389</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21391 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21391</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21393 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21393</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21394 | Dynamics 365 Field Service Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21394</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21395 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21395</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21396 | Dynamics 365 Sales Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21396</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21397 | Microsoft Azure File Sync Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21397</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21401 | Microsoft Entra Jira Single-Sign-On Plugin Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21401</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21402 | Microsoft Outlook Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21402</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21403 | Microsoft Azure Kubernetes Service Confidential Container Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21403</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21404 | .NET Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21404</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21405 | Microsoft Message Queuing (MSMQ) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21405</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21406 | Windows Printing Service Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21406</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21410 | Microsoft Exchange Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21410</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21412 | Internet Shortcut Files Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21412</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21413 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21413</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21420 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21420</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50808 | Zimbra Collaboration before Kepler 9.0.0 Patch 38 GA allows DOM-based JavaScript injection in the Modern UI.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50808</link><description>Zimbra Collaboration before Kepler 9.0.0 Patch 38 GA allows DOM-based JavaScript injection in the Modern UI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20570 | Insufficient verification of data authenticity in
the configuration state machine may allow a local attacker to potentially load
arbitrary b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20570</link><description>Insufficient verification of data authenticity in
the configuration state machine may allow a local attacker to potentially load
arbitrary bitstreams.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26562 | In Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15 and 9.0, a closed account (with 2FA and generated passwords) can send e-mail messages when configured f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26562</link><description>In Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15 and 9.0, a closed account (with 2FA and generated passwords) can send e-mail messages when configured for Imap/smtp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45206 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. Through the help document endpoint in webmail, an attacker can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45206</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. Through the help document endpoint in webmail, an attacker can inject JavaScript or HTML code that leads to cross-site scripting (XSS). (Adding an adequate message to avoid malicious code will mitigate this issue.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45207 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. An attacker can send a PDF document through mail that contains ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45207</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. An attacker can send a PDF document through mail that contains malicious JavaScript. While previewing this file in webmail in the Chrome browser, the stored XSS payload is executed. (This has been mitigated by sanitising the JavaScript code present in a PDF document.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48432 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. XSS, with resultant session stealing, can occur via JavaScript ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48432</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. XSS, with resultant session stealing, can occur via JavaScript code in a link (for a webmail redirection endpoint) within en email message, e.g., if a victim clicks on that link within Zimbra webmail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22923 | SQL injection vulnerability in adv radius v.2.2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22923</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in adv radius v.2.2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1140 | Twister Antivirus v8.17 - Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1140</link><description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability by triggering the 0x801120B8 IOCTL code of the filmfd.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23439 | Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 - Arbitrary Memory Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23439</link><description>Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 is vulnerable to an Arbitrary Memory Read vulnerability by triggering the 0x22201B, 0x22201F, 0x222023, 0x222027 ,0x22202B, 0x22202F, 0x22203F, 0x222057 and 0x22205B IOCTL codes of the Vba32m64.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23440 | Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 - Arbitrary Memory Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23440</link><description>Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 is vulnerable to an Arbitrary Memory Read vulnerability. The 0x22200B IOCTL code of the Vba32m64.sys driver allows to read up to 0x802 of memory from ar arbitrary user-supplied pointer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1096 | Twister Antivirus v8.17 - Elevation of Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1096</link><description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 allows Elevation of Privileges on the computer where it's installed by triggering the 0x80112067, 0x801120CB and 0x801120CC IOCTL codes of the fildds.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:06:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1163 | Path Traversal in mbloch/mapshaper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1163</link><description>Path Traversal in GitHub repository mbloch/mapshaper prior to 0.6.44.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4408 | Parsing large DNS messages may cause excessive CPU load</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4408</link><description>The DNS message parsing code in `named` includes a section whose computational complexity is overly high. It does not cause problems for typical DNS traffic, but crafted queries and responses may cause excessive CPU load on the affected `named` instance by exploiting this flaw. This issue affects both authoritative servers and recursive resolvers.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.16.45, 9.18.0 through 9.18.21, 9.19.0 through 9.19.19, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5517 | Querying RFC 1918 reverse zones may cause an assertion failure when &amp;quot;nxdomain-redirect&amp;quot; is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5517</link><description>A flaw in query-handling code can cause `named` to exit prematurely with an assertion failure when:

  - `nxdomain-redirect &lt;domain&gt;;` is configured, and
  - the resolver receives a PTR query for an RFC 1918 address that would normally result in an authoritative NXDOMAIN response.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.12.0 through 9.16.45, 9.18.0 through 9.18.21, 9.19.0 through 9.19.19, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5679 | Enabling both DNS64 and serve-stale may cause an assertion failure during recursive resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5679</link><description>A bad interaction between DNS64 and serve-stale may cause `named` to crash with an assertion failure during recursive resolution, when both of these features are enabled.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.12 through 9.16.45, 9.18.0 through 9.18.21, 9.19.0 through 9.19.19, 9.16.12-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5680 | Cleaning an ECS-enabled cache may cause excessive CPU load</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5680</link><description>If a resolver cache has a very large number of ECS records stored for the same name, the process of cleaning the cache database node for this name can significantly impair query performance. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6516 | Specific recursive query patterns may lead to an out-of-memory condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6516</link><description>To keep its cache database efficient, `named` running as a recursive resolver occasionally attempts to clean up the database. It uses several methods, including some that are asynchronous: a small chunk of memory pointing to the cache element that can be cleaned up is first allocated and then queued for later processing. It was discovered that if the resolver is continuously processing query patterns triggering this type of cache-database maintenance, `named` may not be able to handle the cleanup events in a timely manner. This in turn enables the list of queued cleanup events to grow infinitely large over time, allowing the configured `max-cache-size` limit to be significantly exceeded.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.0 through 9.16.45 and 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24781 | Hima: Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in multiple products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24781</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability to DoS the affected devices through excessive traffic on a single ethernet port.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24782 | HIMA: Origin Validation Error in multiple products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24782</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can send a ping request from one network to another through an error in the origin verification even though the ports are separated by VLAN.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1309 | Resource Consumption Identified in NTP before 4.2.4p8 and 4.2.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1309</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Honeywell Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Content Spoofing.This issue affects Niagara Framework: before Niagara AX 3.8.1, before Niagara 4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6072 | A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix Central Management (CM) prior to 9.1.3.97129 allows a remote authenticated attacker to craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6072</link><description>A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix Central Management (CM) prior to 9.1.3.97129 allows a remote authenticated attacker to craft CM dashboard internal requests causing arbitrary content to be injected into the response when accessing the CM dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1157 | The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button URL in all versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1157</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1159 | The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1159</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1160 | The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon Link in all versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1160</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon Link in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48363 | A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48363</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Route Control V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V18 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V19 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.4 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.5 (All versions &lt; V7.5 SP2 Update 15), SIMATIC WinCC V8.0 (All versions &lt; V8.0 SP4). The implementation of the RPC (Remote Procedure call) &#13;
communication protocol in the affected products do not &#13;
properly handle certain unorganized RPC messages. An &#13;
attacker could use this vulnerability to cause a denial of service &#13;
condition in the RPC server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48364 | A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48364</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Route Control V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V18 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V19 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.4 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.5 (All versions &lt; V7.5 SP2 Update 15), SIMATIC WinCC V8.0 (All versions &lt; V8.0 SP4). The implementation of the RPC (Remote Procedure call) communication protocol in the affected products do not properly handle certain malformed RPC messages. An attacker could use this vulnerability to cause a denial of service condition in the RPC server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49125 | A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.263), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.252), Parasolid V36...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49125</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.263), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.252), Parasolid V36.0 (All versions &lt; V36.0.198). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted files containing XT format. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50236 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The affected product is vulnerable due to weak file and folder permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50236</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The affected product is vulnerable due to weak file and folder permissions in the installation path. An attacker with local access could exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51440 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 343-1 (6GK7343-1EX30-0XE0) (All versions), SIMATIC CP 343-1 Lean (6GK7343-1CX10-0XE0) (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51440</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 343-1 (6GK7343-1EX30-0XE0) (All versions), SIMATIC CP 343-1 Lean (6GK7343-1CX10-0XE0) (All versions), SIPLUS NET CP 343-1 (6AG1343-1EX30-7XE0) (All versions), SIPLUS NET CP 343-1 Lean (6AG1343-1CX10-2XE0) (All versions). Affected products incorrectly validate TCP sequence numbers. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to create a denial of service condition by injecting spoofed TCP RST packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22042 | A vulnerability has been identified in Unicam FX (All versions). The windows installer agent used in affected product contains incorrect use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22042</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Unicam FX (All versions). The windows installer agent used in affected product contains incorrect use of privileged APIs that trigger the Windows Console Host (conhost.exe) as a child process with SYSTEM privileges. This could be exploited by an attacker to perform a local privilege escalation attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22043 | A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.251), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.170). The affected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22043</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.251), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.170). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted XT files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23795 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23795</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted WRL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23796 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23796</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected application is vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23797 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23797</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain a stack overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23798 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23798</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain a stack overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23799 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23799</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23800 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23800</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23801 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23801</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23802 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23802</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted SPP files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23803 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23803</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted SPP file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23804 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23804</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain a stack overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PSOBJ files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23810 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application is vulnerable to SQL injection. This co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23810</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application is vulnerable to SQL injection. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the server database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23811 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application allows users to upload arbitrary files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23811</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application allows users to upload arbitrary files via TFTP. This could allow an attacker to upload malicious firmware images or other files, that could potentially lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23812 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application incorrectly neutralizes special element...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23812</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application incorrectly neutralizes special elements when creating a report which could lead to command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23813 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The REST API endpoints of doorsconnector of the affected product lacks p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23813</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The REST API endpoints of doorsconnector of the affected product lacks proper authentication. An unauthenticated attacker could access the endpoints, and potentially execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23816 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence Perpetual Large (9DE5110-8CA13-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23816</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence Perpetual Large (9DE5110-8CA13-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence Perpetual Medium (9DE5110-8CA12-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence Perpetual Non-Prod (9DE5110-8CA10-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence Perpetual Small (9DE5110-8CA11-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Large (9DE5110-8CA13-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Medium (9DE5110-8CA12-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Non-Prod (9DE5110-8CA10-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Small (9DE5110-8CA11-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3). Affected products use a hard-coded secret value for the computation of a Keyed-Hash Message Authentication Code. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain full administrative access to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24920 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24920</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted Catia MODEL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-21710)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24921 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24921</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted Catia MODEL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-21712)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24922 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24922</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted Catia MODEL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-21715)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24923 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000), Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0001). The affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24923</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000), Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0001). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted Catia MODEL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-22055)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24924 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24924</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted Catia MODEL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-22059)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24925 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to uninitialized ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24925</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to uninitialized pointer access while parsing specially crafted Catia MODEL files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-22060)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22445 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain an OS command injection vulnerability. A remote high privileged at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22445</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain an OS command injection vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to a system take over by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22454 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain a weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten passwords. A remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22454</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain a weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten passwords. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access to the application with privileges of the compromised account. The attacker could retrieve the reset password token without authorization and then perform the password change</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6815 | Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-R Series Safety CPU R08/16/32/120SFCPU all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6815</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-R Series Safety CPU R08/16/32/120SFCPU all versions and MELSEC iQ-R Series SIL2 Process CPU R08/16/32/120PSFCPU all versions allows a remote authenticated attacker who has logged into the product as a non-administrator user to disclose the credentials (user ID and password) of a user with a lower access level than the attacker by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 06:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25914 | WordPress SMTP Mail Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25914</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Photoboxone SMTP Mail.This issue affects SMTP Mail: from n/a through 1.3.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 05:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21491 | Versions of the package svix before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to an issue in the verify function where signatures o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21491</link><description>Versions of the package svix before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to an issue in the verify function where signatures of different lengths are incorrectly compared. An attacker can bypass signature verification by providing a shorter signature that matches the beginning of the actual signature.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;The attacker would need to know a victim uses the Rust library for verification,no easy way to automatically check that; and uses webhooks by a service that uses Svix, and then figure out a way to craft a malicious payload that will actually include all of the correct identifiers needed to trick the receivers to cause actual issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 05:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48623 | The Cpanel::JSON::XS package before 4.33 for Perl performs out-of-bounds accesses in a way that allows attackers to obtain sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48623</link><description>The Cpanel::JSON::XS package before 4.33 for Perl performs out-of-bounds accesses in a way that allows attackers to obtain sensitive information or cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52431 | The Plack::Middleware::XSRFBlock package before 0.0.19 for Perl allows attackers to bypass a CSRF protection mechanism via an empty form val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52431</link><description>The Plack::Middleware::XSRFBlock package before 0.0.19 for Perl allows attackers to bypass a CSRF protection mechanism via an empty form value and an empty cookie (if signed cookies are disabled).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22024 | An XML external entity or XXE vulnerability in the SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x), Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x) and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22024</link><description>An XML external entity or XXE vulnerability in the SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x), Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x) and ZTA gateways which allows an attacker to access certain restricted resources without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22129 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Companion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22129</link><description>SAP Companion - version &lt;3.1.38, has a URL with parameter that could be vulnerable to XSS attack. The attacker could send a malicious link to a user that would possibly allow an attacker to retrieve the sensitive information and cause minor impact on the integrity of the web application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24741 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Master Data Governance Material</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24741</link><description>SAP Master Data Governance for Material Data - versions 618, 619, 620, 621, 622, 800, 801, 802, 803, 804, does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to read some sensitive information but no impact to integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25643 | Missing authorization check in SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Requests)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25643</link><description>The SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Request) - version 605, does not perform the necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user which may result in an escalation of privileges. It is possible to manipulate the URLs of data requests to access information that the user should not have access to. There is no impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47218 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47218</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50358 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50358</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QTS 4.3.6.2665 build 20240131 and later
QTS 4.3.4.2675 build 20240131 and later
QTS 4.3.3.2644 build 20240131 and later
QTS 4.2.6 build 20240131 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24742 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24742</link><description>SAP CRM WebClient UI - version S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to integrity of the application data after successful exploitation. There is no impact on confidentiality and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24743 | XXE vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Guided Procedures)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24743</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures) - version 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious request with a crafted XML file over the network, which when parsed will enable him to access sensitive files and data but not modify them. There are expansion limits in place so that availability is not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25642 | Improper Certificate Validation in SAP Cloud Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25642</link><description>Due to improper validation of certificate in SAP Cloud Connector - version 2.0, attacker can impersonate the genuine servers to interact with SCC breaking the mutual authentication. Hence, the attacker can intercept the request to view/modify sensitive information. There is no impact on the availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24740 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP (SAP Kernel)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24740</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP) - versions KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.93, KERNEL 7.94, KRNL64UC 7.53, under certain conditions, allows an attacker to access information which could otherwise be restricted with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22130 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP CRM WebClient UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22130</link><description>Print preview option in SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, S4FND 108, WEBCUIF 700, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 730, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the appliaction data after successful exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22131 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP ABA (Application Basis)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22131</link><description>In SAP ABA (Application Basis) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75I, an attacker authenticated as a user with a remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface. This allows the attacker to use the interface to invoke an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user/business data and can make the entire system unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22132 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP IDES Systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22132</link><description>SAP IDES ECC-systems contain code that permits the execution of arbitrary program code of user's choice.An attacker can therefore control the behaviour of the system by executing malicious code which can potentially escalate privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24739 | Missing authorization check in SAP BAM (Bank Account Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24739</link><description>SAP Bank Account Management (BAM) allows an authenticated user with restricted access to use functions which can result in escalation of privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22128 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Business Client for HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22128</link><description>SAP NWBC for HTML - versions SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, SAP_UI 758, SAP_BASIS 700, SAP_BASIS 701, SAP_BASIS 702, SAP_BASIS 731, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can inject malicious javascript to cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the application data after successful exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22126 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (User Admin Application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22126</link><description>The User Admin application of SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, insufficiently validates and improperly encodes the incoming URL parameters before including them into the redirect URL. This results in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and mild impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:04:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49339 | Ellucian Banner 9.17 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) via a modified bannerId to the /StudentSelfService/ssb/studentCard/retri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49339</link><description>Ellucian Banner 9.17 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) via a modified bannerId to the /StudentSelfService/ssb/studentCard/retrieveData endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42374 | An issue in mystenlabs Sui Blockchain before v.1.6.3 allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42374</link><description>An issue in mystenlabs Sui Blockchain before v.1.6.3 allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a crafted compressed script to the Sui node component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52059 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52059</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Description text field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52060 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to arbitrarily edit user profile information via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52060</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to arbitrarily edit user profile information via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25407 | SteVe v3.6.0 was discovered to use predictable transaction ID's when receiving a StartTransaction request. This vulnerability can allow atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25407</link><description>SteVe v3.6.0 was discovered to use predictable transaction ID's when receiving a StartTransaction request. This vulnerability can allow attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by using the predicted transaction ID's to terminate other transactions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>