<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-23840 | Movary vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting with `?categoryDeleted=` param</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23840</link><description>Movary is a web application to track, rate and explore your movie watch history. Due to insufficient input validation, attackers can trigger cross-site scripting payloads in versions prior to 0.70.0. The vulnerable parameter is `?categoryDeleted=`. Version 0.70.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23841 | Movary vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting with `?categoryCreated=` param</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23841</link><description>Movary is a web application to track, rate and explore your movie watch history. Due to insufficient input validation, attackers can trigger cross-site scripting payloads in versions prior to 0.70.0. The vulnerable parameter is `?categoryCreated=`. Version 0.70.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23842 | ChatterBot has Denial of Service via Database Connection Pool Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23842</link><description>ChatterBot is a machine learning, conversational dialog engine for creating chat bots. ChatterBot versions up to 1.2.10 are vulnerable to a denial-of-service condition caused by improper database session and connection pool management. Concurrent invocations of the get_response() method can exhaust the underlying SQLAlchemy connection pool, resulting in persistent service unavailability and requiring a manual restart to recover. Version 1.2.11 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23843 | teklifolustur_app&amp;#x27;s IDOR vulnerability allows unauthorized access to other users&amp;#x27; offers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23843</link><description>teklifolustur_app is a web-based PHP application that allows users to create, manage, and track quotes for their clients. Prior to commit dd082a134a225b8dcd401b6224eead4fb183ea1c, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in the offer view functionality. Authenticated users can manipulate the offer_id parameter to access offers belonging to other users. The issue is caused by missing authorization checks ensuring that the requested offer belonged to the currently authenticated user. Commit dd082a134a225b8dcd401b6224eead4fb183ea1c contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1171 | birkir prime GraphQL Field graphql denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1171</link><description>A flaw has been found in birkir prime up to 0.4.0.beta.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /graphql of the component GraphQL Field Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23839 | Movary vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting with `?categoryUpdated=` param</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23839</link><description>Movary is a web application to track, rate and explore your movie watch history. Due to insufficient input validation, attackers can trigger cross-site scripting payloads in versions prior to 0.70.0. The vulnerable parameter is `?categoryUpdated=`. Version 0.70.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55250 | HCL AION is affected by a Technical Error Disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55250</link><description>HCL AION version 2 is affected by a Technical Error Disclosure vulnerability. This can expose sensitive technical details, potentially resulting in information disclosure or aiding further attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55252 | HCL AION is affected by a Weak Password Policy vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55252</link><description>HCL AION  version 2 is affected by a Weak Password Policy vulnerability. This can  allow the use of easily guessable passwords, potentially resulting in unauthorized access</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23838 | Tandoor Recipes module allows SQLite database to be externally accessible with the default settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23838</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is a recipe manager than can be installed with the Nix package manager. Starting in version 23.05 and prior to version 26.05, when using the default configuration of Tandoor Recipes, specifically using SQLite and default `MEDIA_ROOT`, the full database file may be externally accessible, potentially on the Internet. The root cause is that the NixOS module configures the working directory of Tandoor Recipes, as well as the value of `MEDIA_ROOT`, to be `/var/lib/tandoor-recipes`. This causes Tandoor Recipes to create its `db.sqlite3` database file in the same directory as `MEDIA_ROOT` causing it to be accessible without authentication through HTTP like any other media file. This is the case when using `GUNICORN_MEDIA=1` or when using a web server like nginx to serve media files. NixOS 26.05 changes the default value of `MEDIA_ROOT` to a sub folder of the data directory. This only applies to configurations with `system.stateVersion` &gt;= 26.05. For older configurations, one of the workarounds should be applied instead. NixOS 25.11 has received a backport of this patch, though it doesn't fix this vulnerability without user intervention. A recommended workaround is to move `MEDIA_ROOT` into a subdirectory. Non-recommended workarounds include switching to PostgreSQL or disallowing access to `db.sqlite3`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23878 | HotCRP vulnerable to exposure of submitted documents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23878</link><description>HotCRP is conference review software. Starting in commit aa20ef288828b04550950cf67c831af8a525f508 and prior to commit ceacd5f1476458792c44c6a993670f02c984b4a0, authors with at least one submission on a HotCRP site could use the document API to download any documents (PDFs, attachments) associated with any submission. The problem was patched in commit ceacd5f1476458792c44c6a993670f02c984b4a0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52661 | HCL AION version 2 is affected by a JWT Token Expiry Too Long vulnerability. This may increase the risk of token misuse, potentially resulti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52661</link><description>HCL AION version 2 is affected by a JWT Token Expiry Too Long vulnerability. This may increase the risk of token misuse, potentially resulting in unauthorized access if the token is compromised.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55249 | HCL AION is affected by a Missing Security Response Headers vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55249</link><description>HCL AION is affected by a Missing Security Response Headers vulnerability. The absence of standard security headers may weaken the application’s overall security posture and increase its susceptibility to common web-based attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1170 | birkir prime GraphQL API graphql information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1170</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in birkir prime up to 0.4.0.beta.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /graphql of the component GraphQL API. Performing a manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23833 | ESPHome vulnerable to denial-of-service via out-of-bounds check bypass in the API component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23833</link><description>ESPHome is a system to control microcontrollers remotely through Home Automation systems. In versions 2025.9.0 through 2025.12.6, an integer overflow in the API component's protobuf decoder allows denial-of-service attacks when API encryption is not used. The bounds check `ptr + field_length &gt; end` in `components/api/proto.cpp` can overflow when a malicious client sends a large `field_length` value. This affects all ESPHome device platforms (ESP32, ESP8266, RP2040, LibreTiny). The overflow bypasses the out-of-bounds check, causing the device to read invalid memory and crash. When using the plaintext API protocol, this attack can be performed without authentication. When noise encryption is enabled, knowledge of the encryption key is required. Users should upgrade to ESPHome 2025.12.7 or later to receive a patch, enable API encryption with a unique key per device, and follow the Security Best Practices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23836 | HotCRP vulnerable to remote code execution through formulas</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23836</link><description>HotCRP is conference review software. A problem introduced in April 2024 in version 3.1 led to inadequately sanitized code generation for HotCRP formulas which allowed users to trigger the execution of arbitrary PHP code. The problem is patched in release version 3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52659 | HCL AION is affected by a Cacheable HTTP Response vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52659</link><description>HCL AION version 2 is affected by a Cacheable HTTP Response vulnerability. This may lead to unintended storage of sensitive or dynamic content, potentially resulting in unauthorized access or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23721 | OpenProject users with &amp;quot;View Members&amp;quot; permission in any project can view all Group memberships</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23721</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. When using groups in OpenProject to manage users, the group members should only be visible to users that have the View Members permission in any project that the group is also a member of. Prior to versions 17.0.1 and 16.6.5, due to a failed permission check, if a user had the View Members permission in any project, they could enumerate all Groups and view which other users are part of the group. The issue has been fixed in OpenProject 17.0.1 and 16.6.5. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52660 | HCL AION is affected by an Host Header Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52660</link><description>HCL AION is affected by an Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability. This can allow malicious file uploads, potentially resulting in unauthorized code execution or system compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23625 | OpenProject has stored XSS regression using attachments and script-src self</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23625</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Versions 16.3.0 through 16.6.4 are affected by a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Roadmap view. OpenProject’s roadmap view renders the “Related work packages” list for each version. When a version contains work packages from a different project (e.g., a subproject), the helper link_to_work_package prepends package.project.to_s to the link and returns the entire string with .html_safe. Because project names are user-controlled and no escaping happens before calling html_safe, any HTML placed in a subproject name is injected verbatim into the page. The underlying issue is mitigated in versions 16.6.5 and 17.0.0 by setting a `X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff` header, which was in place until a refactoring move to Rails standard content-security policy, which did not properly apply this header in the new configuration since OpenProject 16.3.0. Those who cannot upgrade their installations should ensure that they add a X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff header in their proxying web application server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23646 | OpenProject users can delete other user&amp;#x27;s session, causing them to be logged out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23646</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Users of OpenProject versions prior to 16.6.5 and 17.0.1 have the ability to view and end their active sessions via Account Settings → Sessions. When deleting a session, it was not properly checked if the session belongs to the user. As the ID that is used to identify these session objects use incremental integers, users could iterate requests using `DELETE /my/sessions/:id` and thus unauthenticate other users. Users did not have access to any sensitive information (like browser identifier, IP addresses, etc) of other users that are stored in the session. The problem was patched in OpenProject versions 16.6.5 and 17.0.1. No known workarounds are available as this does not require any permissions or other that can temporarily be disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55251 | HCL AION is affected by an Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55251</link><description>HCL AION is affected by an Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability. This can allow malicious file uploads, potentially resulting in unauthorized code execution or system compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1169 | birkir prime cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1169</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in birkir prime up to 0.4.0.beta.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code. Such manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22797 | An issue was discovered in OpenStack keystonemiddleware 10.5 through 10.7 before 10.7.2, 10.8 and 10.9 before 10.9.1, and 10.10 through 10.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22797</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenStack keystonemiddleware 10.5 through 10.7 before 10.7.2, 10.8 and 10.9 before 10.9.1, and 10.10 through 10.12 before 10.12.1. The external_oauth2_token middleware fails to sanitize incoming authentication headers before processing OAuth 2.0 tokens. By sending forged identity headers such as X-Is-Admin-Project, X-Roles, or X-User-Id, an authenticated attacker may escalate privileges or impersonate other users. All deployments using the external_oauth2_token middleware are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23883 | Heap-use-after-free in update_pointer_new</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23883</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, `xf_Pointer_New` frees `cursorPixels` on failure, then `pointer_free` calls `xf_Pointer_Free` and frees it again, triggering ASan UAF. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side use after free, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23884 | Heap-use-after-free in gdi_set_bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23884</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, offscreen bitmap deletion leaves `gdi-&gt;drawing` pointing to freed memory, causing UAF when related update packets arrive. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side use after free, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23533 | FreeRDP has heap-buffer-overflow in clear_decompress_residual_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23533</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, a client-side heap buffer overflow occurs in the RDPGFX ClearCodec decode path when maliciously crafted residual data causes out-of-bounds writes during color output. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side heap buffer overflow, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23534 | FreeRDP has heap-buffer-overflow in clear_decompress_bands_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23534</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, a client-side heap buffer overflow occurs in the ClearCodec bands decode path when crafted band coordinates allow writes past the end of the destination surface buffer. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side heap buffer overflow, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23732 | FreeRDP has heap-buffer-overflow in Glyph_Alloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23732</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, FastGlyph parsing trusts `cbData`/remaining length and never validates against the minimum size implied by `cx/cy`. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side global buffer overflow, causing a crash (DoS). Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23530 | FreeRDP vulnerable to heap-buffer-overflow in planar_decompress_plane_rle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23530</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0,`freerdp_bitmap_decompress_planar` does not validate `nSrcWidth`/`nSrcHeight` against `planar-&gt;maxWidth`/`maxHeight` before RLE decode. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side heap buffer overflow, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23531 | FreeRDP has heap-buffer-overflow in clear_decompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23531</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, in ClearCodec, when `glyphData` is present, `clear_decompress` calls `freerdp_image_copy_no_overlap` without validating the destination rectangle, allowing an out-of-bounds read/write via crafted RDPGFX surface updates. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side heap buffer overflow, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23532 | FreeRDP has heap-buffer-overflow in gdi_SurfaceToSurface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23532</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.21.0, a client-side heap buffer overflow occurs in the  FreeRDP client’s `gdi_SurfaceToSurface` path due to a mismatch between destination rectangle clamping and the actual copy size. A malicious server can trigger a client‑side heap buffer overflow, causing a crash (DoS) and potential heap corruption with code‑execution risk depending on allocator behavior and surrounding heap layout. Version 3.21.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22037 | @fastify/express vulnerable to Improper Handling of URL Encoding (Hex Encoding)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22037</link><description>The @fastify/express plugin adds full Express compatibility to Fastify. A security vulnerability exists in @fastify/express prior to version 4.0.3 where middleware registered with a specific path prefix can be bypassed using URL-encoded characters (e.g., `/%61dmin` instead of `/admin`). While the middleware engine fails to match the encoded path and skips execution, the underlying Fastify router correctly decodes the path and matches the route handler, allowing attackers to access protected endpoints without the middleware constraints. The vulnerability is caused by how @fastify/express matches requests against registered middleware paths. This vulnerability is similar to, but differs from, CVE-2026-22031 because this is a different npm module with its own code. Version 4.0.3 of @fastify/express contains a patch fort the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22850 | Koko Analytics vulnerable to arbitrary SQL execution through unescaped analytics export/import and permissive admin SQL import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22850</link><description>Koko Analytics is an open-source analytics plugin for WordPress. Versions prior to 2.1.3 are vulnerable to arbitrary SQL execution through unescaped analytics export/import and permissive admin SQL import. Unauthenticated visitors can submit arbitrary path (`pa`) and referrer (`r`) values to the public tracking endpoint in src/Resources/functions/collect.php, which stores those strings verbatim in the analytics tables. The admin export logic in src/Admin/Data_Export.php writes these stored values directly into SQL INSERT statements without escaping. A crafted path such as "),('999','x');DROP TABLE wp_users;-- breaks out of the value list. When an administrator later imports that export file, the import handler in src/Admin/Data_Import.php reads the uploaded SQL with file_get_contents, performs only a superficial header check, splits on semicolons, and executes each statement via $wpdb-&gt;query with no validation of table names or statement types. Additionally, any authenticated user with manage_koko_analytics can upload an arbitrary .sql file and have it executed in the same permissive way. Combined, attacker-controlled input flows from the tracking endpoint into exported SQL and through the import execution sink, or directly via malicious uploads, enabling arbitrary SQL execution. In a worst-case scenario, attackers can achieve arbitrary SQL execution on the WordPress database, allowing deletion of core tables (e.g., wp_users), insertion of backdoor administrator accounts, or other destructive/privilege-escalating actions. Version 2.1.3 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23522 | Lobe Chat has IDOR in Knowledge Base File Removal that Allows Cross User File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23522</link><description>LobeChat is an open source chat application platform. Prior to version 2.0.0-next.193, `knowledgeBase.removeFilesFromKnowledgeBase` tRPC ep allows authenticated users to delete files from any knowledge base without verifying ownership. `userId` filter in the database query is commented out, so it's enabling attackers to delete other users' KB files if they know the knowledge base ID and file ID. While the vulnerability is confirmed, practical exploitation requires knowing target's KB ID and target's file ID. These IDs are random and not easily enumerable. However, IDs may leak through shared links, logs, referrer headers and so on. Missing authorization check is a critical security flaw regardless. Users should upgrade to version 2.0.0-next.193 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1162 | UTT HiPER 810 setSysAdm strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1162</link><description>A flaw has been found in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/setSysAdm. This manipulation of the argument passwd1 causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1161 | pbrong hrms recruitment.go UpdateRecruitmentById cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1161</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in pbrong hrms 1.0.1. The affected element is the function UpdateRecruitmentById of the file /handler/recruitment.go. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11044 | Vulnerability on Automation Runtime my cause DoS Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11044</link><description>An Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in the ANSL-Server component of B&amp;amp;R Automation Runtime versions prior to 6.5 and prior to R4.93 could be exploited by an unauthenti-cated attacker on the network to win a race condition, resulting in permanent denial-of-service (DoS) conditions on affected devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11043 | Improper Server Certificate Validation in Automation Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11043</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in the OPC-UA client and ANSL over TLS client used in Automation Studio versions before 6.5 could allow an unauthenticated attacker on the network to position themselves to intercept and interfere with data exchanges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1160 | PHPGurukul Directory Management System Search index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1160</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /index.php of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61684 | Quicly has assertion failures</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61684</link><description>Quicly, an IETF QUIC protocol implementation, is susceptible to a denial-of-service attack prior to commit d9d3df6a8530a102b57d840e39b0311ce5c9e14e. A remote attacker can exploit these bugs to trigger an assertion failure that crashes process using Quicly. Commit d9d3df6a8530a102b57d840e39b0311ce5c9e14e fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68616 | WeasyPrint Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Protection Bypass via HTTP Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68616</link><description>WeasyPrint helps web developers to create PDF documents. Prior to version 68.0, a server-side request forgery (SSRF) protection bypass exists in WeasyPrint's `default_url_fetcher`. The vulnerability allows attackers to access internal network resources (such as `localhost` services or cloud metadata endpoints) even when a developer has implemented a custom `url_fetcher` to block such access. This occurs because the underlying `urllib` library follows HTTP redirects automatically without re-validating the new destination against the developer's security policy. Version 68.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22031 | Fastify Middie Middleware Path Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22031</link><description>@fastify/middie is the plugin that adds middleware support on steroids to Fastify. A security vulnerability exists in @fastify/middie prior to version 9.1.0 where middleware registered with a specific path prefix can be bypassed using URL-encoded characters (e.g., `/%61dmin` instead of `/admin`). While the middleware engine fails to match the encoded path and skips execution, the underlying Fastify router correctly decodes the path and matches the route handler, allowing attackers to access protected endpoints without the middleware constraints. Version 9.1.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1159 | itsourcecode Online Frozen Foods Ordering System order_online.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1159</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Online Frozen Foods Ordering System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /order_online.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument product_name can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0610 | SQL Injection vulnerability in remote-sessions in Devolutions Server.This issue affects Devolutions Server 2025.3.1 through 2025.3.12</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0610</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in remote-sessions in Devolutions Server.This issue affects Devolutions Server 2025.3.1 through 2025.3.12</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1007 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in virtual gateway component in Devolutions Server allows attackers to bypass deny IP rules.This issue...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1007</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in virtual gateway component in Devolutions Server allows attackers to bypass deny IP rules.This issue affects Server: from 2025.3.1 through 2025.3.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1158 | Totolink LR350 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setWizardCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1158</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Totolink LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309. This vulnerability affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument ssid results in buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21618 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) in OAuth Device Authorization screen</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21618</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hexpm hexpm/hexpm ('Elixir.HexpmWeb.SharedAuthorizationView' modules) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/hexpm_web/views/shared_authorization_view.ex and program routines 'Elixir.HexpmWeb.SharedAuthorizationView':render_grouped_scopes/3.

This issue affects hexpm: from 617e44c71f1dd9043870205f371d375c5c4d886d before c692438684ead90c3bcbfb9ccf4e63c768c668a8, from pkg:github/hexpm/hexpm@617e44c71f1dd9043870205f371d375c5c4d886d before pkg:github/hexpm/hexpm@c692438684ead90c3bcbfb9ccf4e63c768c668a8; hex.pm: from 2025-10-01 before 2026-01-19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1157 | Totolink LR350 cstecgi.cgi setWiFiEasyCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1157</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Totolink LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309. This affects the function setWiFiEasyCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1156 | Totolink LR350 cstecgi.cgi setWiFiBasicCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1156</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Totolink LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309. Affected by this issue is the function setWiFiBasicCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1155 | Totolink LR350 cstecgi.cgi setWiFiEasyGuestCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1155</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWiFiEasyGuestCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid results in buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1154 | SourceCodester E-Learning System Lesson index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1154</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/lesson/index.php of the component Lesson Module Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument Title/Description can lead to basic cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1153 | technical-laohu mpay cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1153</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in technical-laohu mpay up to 1.2.4. This affects an unknown function. Performing a manipulation results in cross-site request forgery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1181 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Altium 365 Forum Leading to Cross-Customer Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1181</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Altium Forum due to missing server-side input sanitization in forum post content. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript into forum posts, which is stored and executed when other users view the affected post.
Successful exploitation allows the attacker’s payload to execute in the context of the victim’s authenticated Altium 365 session, enabling unauthorized access to workspace data, including design files and workspace settings. Exploitation requires user interaction to view a malicious forum post.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1152 | technical-laohu mpay QR Code Image unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1152</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in technical-laohu mpay up to 1.2.4. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component QR Code Image Handler. Such manipulation of the argument codeimg leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1151 | technical-laohu mpay User Center cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1151</link><description>A weakness has been identified in technical-laohu mpay up to 1.2.4. The affected element is an unknown function of the component User Center. This manipulation of the argument Nickname causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1150 | Totolink LR350 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1150</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Totolink LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309. Impacted is the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument command results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1149 | Totolink LR350 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1149</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Totolink LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1148 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1148</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1147 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System api_patient_schedule.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /php/api_patient_schedule.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Reason results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29847 | Apache Linkis: Arbitrary File Read via Double URL Encoding Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29847</link><description>A vulnerability in Apache Linkis.

Problem Description
When using the JDBC engine and da
When using the JDBC engine and data source functionality, if the URL parameter configured on the frontend has undergone multiple rounds of URL encoding, it may bypass the system's checks. This bypass can trigger a vulnerability that allows unauthorized access to system files via JDBC parameters.

Scope of Impact


This issue affects Apache Linkis: from 1.3.0 through 1.7.0.

Severity level


moderate
Solution
Continuously check if the connection information contains the "%" character; if it does, perform URL decoding.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.




More questions about this vulnerability can be discussed here:  https://lists.apache.org/list?dev@linkis.apache.org:2025-9:cve</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59355 | Apache Linkis: Password Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59355</link><description>A vulnerability.

When org.apache.linkis.metadata.util.HiveUtils.decode() fails to perform Base64 decoding, it records the complete input parameter string in the log via logger.error(str + "decode failed", e). If the input parameter contains sensitive information such as Hive Metastore keys, plaintext passwords will be left in the log files when decoding fails, resulting in information leakage.


Affected Scope
Component: Sensitive fields in hive-site.xml (e.g., javax.jdo.option.ConnectionPassword) or other fields encoded in Base64.
Version: Apache Linkis 1.0.0 – 1.7.0


Trigger Conditions
The value of the configuration item is an invalid Base64 string.
Log files are readable by users other than hive-site.xml administrators.


Severity: Low
The probability of Base64 decoding failure is low.
The leakage is only triggered when logs at the Error level are exposed.

Remediation
Apache Linkis 1.8.0 and later versions have replaced the log with desensitized content.
logger.error("URL decode failed: {}", e.getMessage());   // 不再输出 str


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1146 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System api_register_patient.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1146</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /php/api_register_patient.php. Such manipulation of the argument firstName/lastName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1145 | quickjs-ng quickjs quickjs.c js_typed_array_constructor_ta heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1145</link><description>A flaw has been found in quickjs-ng quickjs up to 0.11.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function js_typed_array_constructor_ta of the file quickjs.c. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Patch name: 53aebe66170d545bb6265906fe4324e4477de8b4. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1144 | quickjs-ng quickjs Atomics Ops quickjs.c use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1144</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in quickjs-ng quickjs up to 0.11.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file quickjs.c of the component Atomics Ops Handler. The manipulation results in use after free. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The patch is identified as ea3e9d77454e8fc9cb3ef3c504e9c16af5a80141. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1143 | TOTOLINK A3700R cstecgi.cgi setWiFiEasyGuestCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1143</link><description>A weakness has been identified in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. This affects the function setWiFiEasyGuestCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Executing a manipulation of the argument ssid can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1142 | PHPGurukul News Portal cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1142</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function. Performing a manipulation results in cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1141 | PHPGurukul News Portal Add Sub-Admin add-subadmins.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1141</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-subadmins.php of the component Add Sub-Admin Page. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1140 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigExceptAli strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1140</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This issue affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptAli. The manipulation results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1139 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigExceptMSN strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1139</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This vulnerability affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptMSN. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1138 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigExceptQQ strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1138</link><description>A flaw has been found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptQQ. Executing a manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1137 | UTT 进取 520W formWebAuthGlobalConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1137</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formWebAuthGlobalConfig. Performing a manipulation results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1136 | lcg0124 BootDo ContentController save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1136</link><description>A weakness has been identified in lcg0124 BootDo up to e93dd428ef6f5c881aa74d49a2099ab0cf1e0fcb. Affected is the function Save of the file /blog/bContent/save of the component ContentController. This manipulation of the argument content/author/title causes cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0943 | HarfBuzz::Shaper versions before 0.032 for Perl contains a bundled library with a null pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0943</link><description>HarfBuzz::Shaper versions before 0.032 for Perl contains a bundled library with a null pointer dereference vulnerability. 

Versions before 0.032 contain HarfBuzz 8.4.0 or earlier bundled as hb_src.tar.gz in the source tarball, which is affected by CVE-2026-22693.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1134 | itsourcecode Society Management System expenses.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1134</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/expenses.php. The manipulation of the argument detail leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1135 | itsourcecode Society Management System activity.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1135</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/activity.php. The manipulation of the argument Title results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1133 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter folder.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1133</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /kmf/folder.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument folderid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1131 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter save_catalog.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1131</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /kmc/save_catalog.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Such manipulation of the argument catalogid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1132 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter edit_folder.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1132</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /kmf/edit_folder.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument folderid results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1129 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter worksadd.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1129</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /worksheet/worksadd.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1130 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter worksadd_plan.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1130</link><description>A flaw has been found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /worksheet/worksadd_plan.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15539 | Open5GS sgwc s11-handler.c sgwc_s11_handle_downlink_data_notification_ack denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15539</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Impacted is the function sgwc_s11_handle_downlink_data_notification_ack of the file src/sgwc/s11-handler.c of the component sgwc. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: b4707272c1caf6a7d4dca905694ea55557a0545f. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23829 | Mailpit has SMTP Header Injection via Regex Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23829</link><description>Mailpit is an email testing tool and API for developers. Prior to version 1.28. Mailpit's SMTP server is vulnerable to Header Injection due to an insufficient Regular Expression used to validate `RCPT TO` and `MAIL FROM` addresses. An attacker can inject arbitrary SMTP headers (or corrupt existing ones) by including carriage return characters (`\r`) in the email address. This header injection occurs because the regex intended to filter control characters fails to exclude `\r` and `\n` when used inside a character class. Version 1.28.3 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15538 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp LWOMaterial.cpp FindUVChannels use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15538</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Open Asset Import Library Assimp up to 6.0.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Assimp::LWOImporter::FindUVChannels of the file /src/assimp/code/AssetLib/LWO/LWOMaterial.cpp. Such manipulation leads to use after free. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This and similar defects are tracked and handled via issue #6128.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23733 | Lobe Chat has Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issue that may escalate to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23733</link><description>LobeChat is an open source chat application platform. Prior to version 2.0.0-next.180, a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Mermaid artifact renderer allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript within the application context. This XSS can be escalated to Remote Code Execution (RCE) by leveraging the exposed `electronAPI` IPC bridge, allowing attackers to run arbitrary system commands on the victim's machine. Version 2.0.0-next.180 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23644 | esm.sh has path traversal in `extractPackageTarball` that enables file writes from malicious packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23644</link><description>esm.sh is a no-build content delivery network (CDN) for web development. Prior to Go pseeudoversion 0.0.0-20260116051925-c62ab83c589e, the software has a path traversal vulnerability due to an incomplete fix. `path.Clean` normalizes a path but does not prevent absolute paths in a malicious tar file. Commit https://github.com/esm-dev/esm.sh/commit/9d77b88c320733ff6689d938d85d246a3af9af16, corresponding to pseudoversion 0.0.0-20260116051925-c62ab83c589e, fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23626 | Kimai Vulnerable to Authenticated Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23626</link><description>Kimai is a web-based multi-user time-tracking application. Prior to version 2.46.0, Kimai's export functionality uses a Twig sandbox with an overly permissive security policy (`DefaultPolicy`) that allows arbitrary method calls on objects available in the template context. An authenticated user with export permissions can deploy a malicious Twig template that extracts sensitive information including environment variables, all user password hashes, serialized session tokens, and CSRF tokens. Version 2.46.0 patches this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23525 | 1panel App Store vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23525</link><description>1Panel is an open-source, web-based control panel for Linux server management. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the 1Panel App Store when viewing application details. Malicious scripts can execute in the context of the user’s browser, potentially compromising session data or sensitive system interfaces. All versions of 1Panel up to and including v1.10.33-lts and v2.0.16 are affected. An attacker could publish a malicious application that, when loaded by users (locally or remotely), can execute arbitrary scripts. This may result in theft of user cookies, unauthorized access to system functions, or other actions that compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system. The vulnerability is caused by insufficient sanitization of content rendered by the MdEditor component with the `previewOnly` attribute enabled. Specifically, the App Store renders application README content without proper XSS protection, allowing script execution during content rendering; and similar issues exist in system upgrade-related components, which can be fixed by implementing proper XSS sanitization in the MdEditor component. These vulnerabilities can be mitigated by applying proper XSS protection and sanitization when rendering content in the MdEditor component. Safe versions with a patch incorporated are v1.10.34-lts and v2.0.17.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1126 | lwj flow SVG File FormResource.java uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1126</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in lwj flow up to a3d2fe8133db9d3b50fda4f66f68634640344641. This affects the function uploadFile of the file \flow-master\flow-front-rest\src\main\java\com\dragon\flow\web\resource\flow\FormResource.java of the component SVG File Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1125 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifidog_settings sub_412E7C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1125</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is the function sub_412E7C of the file /goform/set_wifidog_settings. Executing a manipulation of the argument wd_enable can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0863 | Sandbox escape in n8n Python task runner allows for arbitrary code execution on the underlying host.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0863</link><description>Using string formatting and exception handling, an attacker may bypass n8n's python-task-executor sandbox restrictions and run arbitrary unrestricted Python code in the underlying operating system.

The vulnerability can be exploited via the Code block by an authenticated user with basic permissions and can lead to a full n8n instance takeover on instances operating under "Internal" execution mode.

If the instance is operating under the  "External" execution mode (ex. n8n's official Docker image) - arbitrary code execution occurs inside a Sidecar container and not the main node, which significantly reduces the vulnerability impact.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1124 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter work_report.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1124</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /worksheet/work_report.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1123 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter work_mod.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1123</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /worksheet/work_mod.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1122 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter work_info.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1122</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /worksheet/work_info.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1121 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter del_workplan.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1121</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /worksheet/del_workplan.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1120 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter del_work.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1120</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /worksheet/del_work.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1119 | itsourcecode Society Management System delete_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1119</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_activity.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument activity_id can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1118 | itsourcecode Society Management System add_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1118</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/add_activity.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Title results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15537 | Mapnik dbfile.cpp string_value heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15537</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Mapnik up to 4.2.0. This issue affects the function mapnik::dbf_file::string_value of the file plugins/input/shape/dbfile.cpp. Such manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15536 | BYVoid OpenCC MaxMatchSegmentation.cpp MaxMatchSegmentation heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15536</link><description>A weakness has been identified in BYVoid OpenCC up to 1.1.9. This vulnerability affects the function opencc::MaxMatchSegmentation of the file src/MaxMatchSegmentation.cpp. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Patch name: 345c9a50ab07018f1b4439776bad78a0d40778ec. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15535 | nicbarker clay clay.h Clay__MeasureTextCached null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15535</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in nicbarker clay up to 0.14. This affects the function Clay__MeasureTextCached in the library clay.h. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15534 | raysan5 raylib rtext.c LoadFontData integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15534</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in raysan5 raylib up to 909f040. Affected by this issue is the function LoadFontData of the file src/rtext.c. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is 5a3391fdce046bc5473e52afbd835dd2dc127146. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1112 | Sanluan PublicCMS Trade Address Deletion Endpoint TradeAddressController.java delete improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1112</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 5.202506.d. Affected is the function delete of the file publiccms-trade/src/main/java/com/publiccms/controller/web/trade/TradeAddressController.java of the component Trade Address Deletion Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument ids results in improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1111 | Sanluan PublicCMS Task Template Management TaskTemplateAdminController.java save path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1111</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 5.202506.d. This impacts the function Save of the file com/publiccms/controller/admin/sys/TaskTemplateAdminController.java of the component Task Template Management Handler. Such manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15533 | raysan5 raylib rtext.c GenImageFontAtlas heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15533</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in raysan5 raylib up to 909f040. Affected by this vulnerability is the function GenImageFontAtlas of the file src/rtext.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called 5a3391fdce046bc5473e52afbd835dd2dc127146. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1110 | cijliu librtsp rtsp_parse_method buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1110</link><description>A flaw has been found in cijliu librtsp up to 2ec1a81ad65280568a0c7c16420d7c10fde13b04. This affects the function rtsp_parse_method. This manipulation causes buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 04:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1109 | cijliu librtsp rtsp_parse_request buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1109</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in cijliu librtsp up to 2ec1a81ad65280568a0c7c16420d7c10fde13b04. The impacted element is the function rtsp_parse_request. The manipulation results in buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 03:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1108 | cijliu librtsp rtsp_rely_dumps buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1108</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in cijliu librtsp up to 2ec1a81ad65280568a0c7c16420d7c10fde13b04. The affected element is the function rtsp_rely_dumps. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 03:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1106 | Chamilo LMS Legal Consent SocialController.php deleteLegal improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1106</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Chamilo LMS up to 2.0.0 Beta 1. This issue affects the function deleteLegal of the file src/CoreBundle/Controller/SocialController.php of the component Legal Consent Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument userId results in improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1107 | EyouCMS Member Avatar Diyajax.php check_userinfo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1107</link><description>A weakness has been identified in EyouCMS up to 1.7.1/5.0. Impacted is the function check_userinfo of the file Diyajax.php of the component Member Avatar Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument viewfile can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1105 | EasyCMS UserAction.class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1105</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in EasyCMS up to 1.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /UserAction.class.php. Such manipulation of the argument _order leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1066 | kalcaddle kodbox Compression zip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1066</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.61.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /?explorer/index/zip of the component Compression Handler. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1064 | bastillion-io Bastillion System Management SystemKtrl.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bastillion-io Bastillion up to 4.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/main/java/io/bastillion/manage/control/SystemKtrl.java of the component System Management Module. Performing a manipulation results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1063 | bastillion-io Bastillion Public Key Management System AuthKeysKtrl.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1063</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in bastillion-io Bastillion up to 4.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main/java/io/bastillion/manage/control/AuthKeysKtrl.java of the component Public Key Management System. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1062 | xiweicheng TMS HtmlUtil.java summary server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1062</link><description>A flaw has been found in xiweicheng TMS up to 2.28.0. This affects the function Summary of the file src/main/java/com/lhjz/portal/util/HtmlUtil.java. This manipulation of the argument url causes server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1061 | xiweicheng TMS FileController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1061</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in xiweicheng TMS up to 2.28.0. Affected by this issue is the function Upload of the file src/main/java/com/lhjz/portal/controller/FileController.java. The manipulation of the argument filename results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1059 | FeMiner wms chkuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1059</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FeMiner wms up to 9cad1f1b179a98b9547fd003c23b07c7594775fa. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/chkuser.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1050 | risesoft-y9 Digital-Infrastructure REST Authenticate Endpoint Y9PlatformUtil.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1050</link><description>A flaw has been found in risesoft-y9 Digital-Infrastructure up to 9.6.7. This affects an unknown function of the file source-code/src/main/java/net/risesoft/util/Y9PlatformUtil.java of the component REST Authenticate Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1049 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1049</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl. Such manipulation of the argument TicketID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1048 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1048</link><description>A weakness has been identified in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl?Action=AgentTicketZoom. This manipulation of the argument TicketID causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15532 | Open5GS Timer resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15532</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Timer Handler. The manipulation results in resource consumption. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is identified as c7c131f8d2cb1195ada5e0e691b6868ebcd8a845. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15531 | Open5GS context.c sgwc_bearer_add assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15531</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This vulnerability affects the function sgwc_bearer_add of the file src/sgwc/context.c. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15530 | Open5GS s11-handler.c assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15530</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This affects the function sgwc_s11_handle_create_indirect_data_forwarding_tunnel_request of the file /src/sgwc/s11-handler.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to reachable assertion. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10484 | Registration &amp;amp; Login with Mobile Phone Number for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10484</link><description>The Registration &amp; Login with Mobile Phone Number for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity prior to authenticating them via the fma_lwp_set_session_php_fun() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to authenticate as any user on the site, including administrators, without a valid password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14078 | PAYGENT for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Callback Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14078</link><description>The PAYGENT for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This is due to missing authorization checks on the paygent_check_webhook function combined with the paygent_permission_callback function unconditionally returning true on line 199. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate payment callbacks and modify order statuses by sending forged payment notifications via the `/wp-json/paygent/v1/check/` endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8615 | CubeWP &amp;lt;= 1.1.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cubewp_shortcode_taxonomy Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8615</link><description>The CubeWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cubewp_shortcode_taxonomy shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0725 | Integrate Dynamics 365 CRM &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Field Mapping Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0725</link><description>The Integrate Dynamics 365 CRM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12129 | CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12129</link><description>The CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.27 via the /cubewp-posts/v1/query-new and /cubewp-posts/v1/query REST API endpoints due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14478 | Demo Importer Plus &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Blind XML External Entity Injection via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14478</link><description>The Demo Importer Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to XML External Entity Injection (XXE) in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.9 via the SVG file upload functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to achieve code execution in vulnerable configurations. This only impacts sites on versions of PHP older than 8.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12984 | Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp;amp; AdSense &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12984</link><description>The Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0691 | CM E-Mail Blacklist &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;black_email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0691</link><description>The CM E-Mail Blacklist – Simple email filtering for safer registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'black_email' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0808 | Spin Wheel &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Unauthenticated Client-Side Prize Manipulation via &amp;#x27;prize_index&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0808</link><description>The Spin Wheel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to client-side prize manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This is due to the plugin trusting client-supplied prize selection data without server-side validation or randomization. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate which prize they win by modifying the 'prize_index' parameter sent to the server, allowing them to always select the most valuable prizes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0833 | Team Section Block &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Network Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0833</link><description>The Team Section Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied social network link URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12168 | Phrase TMS Integration for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.7.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12168</link><description>The Phrase TMS Integration for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_delete_log' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete log files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12825 | User Registration Using Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12825</link><description>The User Registration Using Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_cf7_form_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve form settings which includes Facebook app secrets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14029 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Event Approval via &amp;#x27;eventlist&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14029</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_admin_event_approval() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve arbitrary events via the 'eventlist' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13725 | Gutenberg Thim Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read via &amp;#x27;iconSVG&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13725</link><description>The Gutenberg Thim Blocks – Page Builder, Gutenberg Blocks for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file reads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient path validation in the server-side rendering of the thim-blocks/icon block. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server via the 'iconSVG' parameter, which can contain sensitive information such as wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14463 | Payment Button for PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.41 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Order Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14463</link><description>The Payment Button for PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized order creation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3.41. This is due to the plugin exposing a public AJAX endpoint (`wppaypalcheckout_ajax_process_order`) that processes checkout results without any authentication or server-side verification of the PayPal transaction. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary orders on the site with any chosen transaction ID, payment status, product name, amount, or customer information via direct POST requests to the AJAX endpoint, granted they can bypass basic parameter validation. If email sending is enabled, the plugin will also trigger purchase receipt emails to any email address supplied in the request, leading to order database corruption and unauthorized outgoing emails without any real PayPal transaction taking place.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0682 | Church Admin &amp;lt;= 5.0.28 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;audio_url&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0682</link><description>The Church Admin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.28 due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs in the 'audio_url' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0820 | RepairBuddy &amp;lt;= 4.1116 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Signature Upload to Orders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0820</link><description>The RepairBuddy – Repair Shop CRM &amp; Booking Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference due to missing capability checks on the wc_upload_and_save_signature_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1116. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary signatures to any order in the system, potentially modifying order metadata and triggering unauthorized status changes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12002 | Feeds for YouTube Pro &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12002</link><description>The Feeds for YouTube Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0 via the 'sby_check_wp_submit' AJAX action. This is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied data and the use of that data in a file operation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information, granted the 'Save Featured Images' setting is enabled and 'Disable WP Posts' is disabled. Note: This vulnerability only affects the Pro version of Feeds for YouTube.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12718 | Quick Contact Form &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Unauthenticated Open Mail Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12718</link><description>The Quick Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Mail Relay in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.6. This is due to the 'qcf_validate_form' AJAX endpoint allowing a user controlled parameter to set the 'from' email address. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails to arbitrary recipients utilizing the server. The information is limited to the contact form submission details.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14075 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14075</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.7. This is due to the plugin exposing the 'hotel_booking_fetch_customer_info' AJAX action to unauthenticated users without proper capability checks, relying only on a nonce for protection. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive customer information including full names, addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses by providing a valid email address and a publicly accessible nonce.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14450 | Wallet System for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Wallet Balance Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14450</link><description>The Wallet System for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'change_wallet_fund_request_status_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to manipulate wallet withdrawal requests and arbitrarily increase their wallet balance or decrease other users' balances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14632 | Filr – Secure document library &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14632</link><description>The Filr – Secure document library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via unrestricted file upload in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.11 due to insufficient file type restrictions in the FILR_Uploader class. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload malicious HTML files containing JavaScript that will execute whenever a user accesses the uploaded file, granted they have permission to create or edit posts with the 'filr' post type.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15403 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt;= 6.0.7.1 - Privilege Escalation via admin_order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15403</link><description>The RegistrationMagic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.7.1. This is due to the 'add_menu' function is accessible via the 'rm_user_exists' AJAX action and allows arbitrary updates to the 'admin_order' setting. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to injecting an empty slug into the order parameter, and manipulate the plugin's menu generation logic, and when the admin menu is subsequently built, the plugin adds 'manage_options' capability for the target role. Note: The vulnerability can only be exploited unauthenticated, but further privilege escalation requires at least a subscriber user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0518 | XSS in Secure Access Consoles prior to 14.20</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0518</link><description>CVE-2026-0518 is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in versions of 
Secure Access prior to 14.20. An attacker with administrative privileges
 can interfere with another administrator’s use of the console.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0519 | Information Disclosure in Secure Access Between 12.70 and 14.20</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0519</link><description>In Secure Access 12.70 and prior to 14.20, the logging 
subsystem may write an unredacted authentication token to logs under 
certain configurations. Any party with access to those logs could read 
the token and reuse it to access an integrated system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0517 | Denial of Service in Secure Access Servers Prior to 14.20.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0517</link><description>CVE-2026-0517 is a denial-of-service vulnerability in versions of Secure
 Access Server prior to 14.20. An attacker can send a specially crafted packet 
to a server and cause the server to crash</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>