<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 04:29:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-50445 | Shell Injection vulnerability GL.iNet A1300 v4.4.6, AX1800 v4.4.6, AXT1800 v4.4.6, MT3000 v4.4.6, MT2500 v4.4.6, MT6000 v4.5.0, MT1300 v4.3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50445</link><description>Shell Injection vulnerability GL.iNet A1300 v4.4.6, AX1800 v4.4.6, AXT1800 v4.4.6, MT3000 v4.4.6, MT2500 v4.4.6, MT6000 v4.5.0, MT1300 v4.3.7, MT300N-V2 v4.3.7, AR750S v4.3.7, AR750 v4.3.7, AR300M v4.3.7, and B1300 v4.3.7., allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code via the get_system_log and get_crash_log functions of the logread module, as well as the upgrade_online function of the upgrade module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 04:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51006 | An issue in the openFile method of Chinese Perpetual Calendar v9.0.0 allows attackers to read any file via unspecified vectors.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51006</link><description>An issue in the openFile method of Chinese Perpetual Calendar v9.0.0 allows attackers to read any file via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 04:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51010 | An issue in the export component AdSdkH5Activity of com.sdjictec.qdmetro v4.2.2 allows attackers to open a crafted URL without any filtering...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51010</link><description>An issue in the export component AdSdkH5Activity of com.sdjictec.qdmetro v4.2.2 allows attackers to open a crafted URL without any filtering or checking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 04:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49228 | An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. Console port authentication uses hard-coded credentials, which allows an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49228</link><description>An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. Console port authentication uses hard-coded credentials, which allows an attacker with physical access and sufficient knowledge to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 03:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49229 | An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. A missing authorization check in the administration web service allows read-onl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49229</link><description>An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. A missing authorization check in the administration web service allows read-only, unprivileged users to obtain sensitive information about the device configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 03:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49230 | An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. A missing authorization check in captive portals allows attackers to modify the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49230</link><description>An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. A missing authorization check in captive portals allows attackers to modify the portals' configurations without prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 03:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34829 | Incorrect access control in TP-Link Tapo before v3.1.315 allows attackers to access user credentials in plaintext.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34829</link><description>Incorrect access control in TP-Link Tapo before v3.1.315 allows attackers to access user credentials in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7124 | code-projects E-Commerce Site search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7124</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects E-Commerce Site 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument keyword with the input &lt;video/src=x onerror=alert(document.cookie)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249096.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 02:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7123 | SourceCodester Medicine Tracking System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7123</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Medicine Tracking System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Master.php? f=save_medicine. The manipulation of the argument id/name/description leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249095.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6879 | heap buffer overflow in libaom</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6879</link><description>Increasing the resolution of video frames, while performing a multi-threaded encode, can result in a heap overflow in av1_loop_restoration_dealloc().</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 22:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46918 | Phlox com.phlox.simpleserver.plus (aka Simple HTTP Server PLUS) 1.8.1-plus has an Android manifest file that contains an entry with the andr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46918</link><description>Phlox com.phlox.simpleserver.plus (aka Simple HTTP Server PLUS) 1.8.1-plus has an Android manifest file that contains an entry with the android:allowBackup attribute set to true. This could be leveraged by an attacker with physical access to the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49000 | An issue in ArtistScope ArtisBrowser v.34.1.5 and before allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49000</link><description>An issue in ArtistScope ArtisBrowser v.34.1.5 and before allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with the com.artis.browser.IntentReceiverActivity component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49001 | An issue in Indi Browser (aka kvbrowser) v.12.11.23 allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with the com.e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49001</link><description>An issue in Indi Browser (aka kvbrowser) v.12.11.23 allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with the com.example.gurry.kvbrowswer.webview component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49002 | An issue in Xenom Technologies (sinous) Phone Dialer-voice Call Dialer v.1.2.5 allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49002</link><description>An issue in Xenom Technologies (sinous) Phone Dialer-voice Call Dialer v.1.2.5 allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with com.funprime.calldialer.ui.activities.OutgoingActivity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49003 | An issue in simplemobiletools Simple Dialer 5.18.1 allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with com.simple...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49003</link><description>An issue in simplemobiletools Simple Dialer 5.18.1 allows an attacker to bypass intended access restrictions via interaction with com.simplemobiletools.dialer.activities.DialerActivity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51074 | json-path v2.8.0 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Criteria.parse() method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51074</link><description>json-path v2.8.0 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Criteria.parse() method.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51075 | hutool-core v5.8.23 was discovered to contain an infinite loop in the StrSplitter.splitByRegex function. This vulnerability allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51075</link><description>hutool-core v5.8.23 was discovered to contain an infinite loop in the StrSplitter.splitByRegex function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via manipulation of the first two parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51079 | A TimeOut error exists in the ParseTools.subCompileExpression method in mvel2 v2.5.0 Final.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51079</link><description>A TimeOut error exists in the ParseTools.subCompileExpression method in mvel2 v2.5.0 Final.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51080 | The NumberUtil.toBigDecimal method in hutool-core v5.8.23 was discovered to contain a stack overflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51080</link><description>The NumberUtil.toBigDecimal method in hutool-core v5.8.23 was discovered to contain a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51084 | hyavijava v6.0.07.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ResultConverter.convert2Xml method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51084</link><description>hyavijava v6.0.07.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ResultConverter.convert2Xml method.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47883 | The com.altamirano.fabricio.tvbrowser TV browser application through 4.5.1 for Android is vulnerable to JavaScript code execution via an exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47883</link><description>The com.altamirano.fabricio.tvbrowser TV browser application through 4.5.1 for Android is vulnerable to JavaScript code execution via an explicit intent due to an exposed MainActivity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47882 | The Kami Vision YI IoT com.yunyi.smartcamera application through 4.1.9_20231127 for Android allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary Ja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47882</link><description>The Kami Vision YI IoT com.yunyi.smartcamera application through 4.1.9_20231127 for Android allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via an implicit intent to the com.ants360.yicamera.activity.WebViewActivity component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46919 | Phlox com.phlox.simpleserver (aka Simple HTTP Server) 1.8 and com.phlox.simpleserver.plus (aka Simple HTTP Server PLUS) 1.8.1-plus have a ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46919</link><description>Phlox com.phlox.simpleserver (aka Simple HTTP Server) 1.8 and com.phlox.simpleserver.plus (aka Simple HTTP Server PLUS) 1.8.1-plus have a hardcoded aKySWb2jjrr4dzkYXczKRt7K encryption key. The threat is from a man-in-the-middle attacker who can intercept and potentially modify data during transmission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43481 | An issue in Shenzhen TCL Browser TV Web BrowseHere (aka com.tcl.browser) 6.65.022_dab24cc6_231221_gp allows a remote attacker to execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43481</link><description>An issue in Shenzhen TCL Browser TV Web BrowseHere (aka com.tcl.browser) 6.65.022_dab24cc6_231221_gp allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the com.tcl.browser.portal.browse.activity.BrowsePageActivity component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43955 | The com.phlox.tvwebbrowser TV Bro application through 2.0.0 for Android mishandles external intents through WebView. This allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43955</link><description>The com.phlox.tvwebbrowser TV Bro application through 2.0.0 for Android mishandles external intents through WebView. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, create arbitrary files. and perform arbitrary downloads via JavaScript that uses takeBlobDownloadData.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40038 | Arris DG860A and DG1670A devices have predictable default WPA2 PSKs that could lead to unauthorized remote access. (They use the first 6 cha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40038</link><description>Arris DG860A and DG1670A devices have predictable default WPA2 PSKs that could lead to unauthorized remote access. (They use the first 6 characters of the SSID and the last 6 characters of the BSSID, decrementing the last digit.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52075 | ReVanced API vulnerable to Denial of Service due to lack of error caching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52075</link><description>ReVanced API proxies requests needed to feed the ReVanced Manager and website with data. Up to and including commit 71f81f7f20cd26fd707335bca9838fa3e7df20d2, ReVanced API lacks error caching causing rate limit to be triggered thus increasing server load. This causes a denial of service for all users using the API.  It is recommended to implement proper error caching.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52077 | External apps using tokens issued by administrators and moderators can call admin APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52077</link><description>Nexkey is a lightweight fork of Misskey v12 optimized for small to medium size servers. Prior to 12.23Q4.5, Nexkey allows external apps using tokens issued by administrators and moderators to call admin APIs.  This allows malicious third-party apps to perform operations such as updating server settings, as well as compromise object storage and email server credentials. This issue has been patched in 12.23Q4.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 18:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51700 | WP-Mobile-BankID-Integration WordPress Database Deserialization: Potential for Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51700</link><description>Unofficial Mobile BankID Integration for WordPress lets users employ Mobile BankID to authenticate themselves on your WordPress site. Prior to 1.0.1, WP-Mobile-BankID-Integration is affected by a vulnerability classified as a Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability, specifically impacting scenarios where an attacker can manipulate the database. If unauthorized actors gain access to the database, they could exploit this vulnerability to execute object injection attacks. This could lead to unauthorized code execution, data manipulation, or data exfiltration within the WordPress environment.  Users of the plugin should upgrade to version 1.0.1 (or later), where the serialization and deserialization of OrderResponse objects have been switched out to an array stored as JSON.  A possible workaround for users unable to upgrade immediately is to enforce stricter access controls on the database, ensuring that only trusted and authorized entities can modify data. Additionally, implementing monitoring tools to detect unusual database activities could help identify and mitigate potential exploitation attempts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51665 | Audiobookshelf vulnerable to Blind SSRF in `Auth.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51665</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. Prior to 2.7.0, Audiobookshelf is vulnerable to unauthenticated blind server-side request (SSRF) vulnerability in Auth.js. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 2.7.0. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51697 | Audiobookshelf vulnerable to Blind SSRF in `podcastUtils.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51697</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. Prior to 2.7.0, Audiobookshelf is vulnerable to unauthenticated blind server-side request (SSRF) vulnerability in `podcastUtils.js`. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 2.7.0. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51664 | tj-actions/changed-files command injection in output filenames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51664</link><description>tj-actions/changed-files is a Github action to retrieve all files and directories. Prior to 41.0.0, the `tj-actions/changed-files` workflow allows for command injection in changed filenames, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code and potentially leak secrets. This issue may lead to arbitrary command execution in the GitHub Runner. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 41.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 17:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51443 | FreeSWITCH susceptible to Denial of Service via DTLS Hello packets during call initiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51443</link><description>FreeSWITCH is a Software Defined Telecom Stack enabling the digital transformation from proprietary telecom switches to a software implementation that runs on any commodity hardware. Prior to version 1.10.11, when handling DTLS-SRTP for media setup, FreeSWITCH is susceptible to Denial of Service due to a race condition in the hello handshake phase of the DTLS protocol. This attack can be done continuously, thus denying new DTLS-SRTP encrypted calls during the attack. If an attacker manages to send a ClientHello DTLS message with an invalid CipherSuite (such as `TLS_NULL_WITH_NULL_NULL`) to the port on the FreeSWITCH server that is expecting packets from the caller, a DTLS error is generated. This results in the media session being torn down, which is followed by teardown at signaling (SIP) level too. Abuse of this vulnerability may lead to a massive Denial of Service on vulnerable FreeSWITCH servers for calls that rely on DTLS-SRTP. To address this vulnerability, upgrade FreeSWITCH to 1.10.11 which includes the security fix. The solution implemented is to drop all packets from addresses that have not been validated by an ICE check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50255 | Zip Path Traversal in Deepin-Compressor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50255</link><description>Deepin-Compressor is the default archive manager of Deepin Linux OS. Prior to 5.12.21, there's a path traversal vulnerability in deepin-compressor that can be exploited to achieve Remote Command Execution on the target system upon opening crafted archives. Users are advised to update to version 5.12.21 which addresses the issue. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3171 | Heap exhaustion via deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3171</link><description>A flaw was found in EAP-7 during deserialization of certain classes, which permits instantiation of HashMap and HashTable with no checks on resources consumed. This issue could allow an attacker to submit malicious requests using these classes, which could eventually exhaust the heap and result in a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 15:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4641 | Shadow-utils: possible password leak during passwd(1) change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4641</link><description>A flaw was found in shadow-utils. When asking for a new password, shadow-utils asks the password twice. If the password fails on the second attempt, shadow-utils fails in cleaning the buffer used to store the first entry. This may allow an attacker with enough access to retrieve the password from the memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 15:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7116 | WeiYe-Jing datax-web HTTP POST Request killJob os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7116</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in WeiYe-Jing datax-web 2.1.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/log/killJob of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument processId leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249086 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 15:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6190 | Authenicated Path Traversal in İzmir Katip Çelebi University</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6190</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in İzmir Katip Çelebi University University Information Management System allows Absolute Path Traversal.This issue affects University Information Management System: before 30.11.2023.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 14:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52096 | SteVe Community ocpp-jaxb before 0.0.8 generates invalid timestamps such as ones with month 00 in certain situations (such as when an applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52096</link><description>SteVe Community ocpp-jaxb before 0.0.8 generates invalid timestamps such as ones with month 00 in certain situations (such as when an application receives a StartTransaction Open Charge Point Protocol message with a timestamp parameter of 1000000). This may lead to a SQL exception in applications, and may undermine the integrity of transaction records.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 22:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48003 | An open redirect through HTML injection in user messages in Asp.Net Zero before 12.3.0 allows remote attackers to redirect targeted victims ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48003</link><description>An open redirect through HTML injection in user messages in Asp.Net Zero before 12.3.0 allows remote attackers to redirect targeted victims to any URL via the '&lt;meta http-equiv="refresh"' in the WebSocket messages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 21:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49438 | An open redirect vulnerability in the python package Flask-Security-Too &lt;=5.3.2 allows attackers to redirect unsuspecting users to malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49438</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability in the python package Flask-Security-Too &lt;=5.3.2 allows attackers to redirect unsuspecting users to malicious sites via a crafted URL by abusing the ?next parameter on the /login and /register routes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 21:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5203 | WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic &amp;lt; 1.0.9 - Unauthenticated SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5203</link><description>The WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic WordPress plugin before 1.0.9 does not sanitize the request URL or query parameters before using them in an SQL query, allowing unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from the database via blind time based SQL injection techniques, or in some cases an error/union based technique.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5644 | WP Mail Log &amp;lt; 1.1.3 – Incorrect Authorization in REST API Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5644</link><description>The WP Mail Log WordPress plugin before 1.1.3 does not correctly authorize its REST API endpoints, allowing users with the Contributor role to view and delete data that should only be accessible to Admin users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5645 | WP Mail Log &amp;lt; 1.1.3 – Contributor+ SQL Injection in wml_logs endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5645</link><description>The WP Mail Log WordPress plugin before 1.1.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by users with a role as low as Contributor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5672 | WP Mail Log &amp;lt; 1.1.3 – Contributor+ LFI in wml_logs/send_mail endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5672</link><description>The WP Mail Log WordPress plugin before 1.1.3 does not properly validate file path parameters when attaching files to emails, leading to local file inclusion, and allowing an attacker to leak the contents of arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5673 | WP Mail Log &amp;lt; 1.1.3 – Contributor+ Arbitrary File Upload to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5673</link><description>The WP Mail Log WordPress plugin before 1.1.3 does not properly validate file extensions uploading files to attach to emails, allowing attackers to upload PHP files, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5674 | WP Mail Log &amp;lt; 1.1.3 – Contributor+ SQL Injection in wml_logs/send_mail endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5674</link><description>The WP Mail Log WordPress plugin before 1.1.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by users with a role as low as Contributor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5931 | rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress &amp;lt; 4.6.16 - Subscriber+ RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5931</link><description>The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress WordPress plugin before 4.6.16 does not validate files to be uploaded, which could allow attackers with a low-privilege account (e.g. subscribers) to upload arbitrary files such as PHP on the server</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5939 | rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress &amp;lt; 4.6.16 - Admin+ RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5939</link><description>The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress WordPress plugin before 4.6.16 loads the contents of the import file in an unsafe manner, leading to remote code execution by privileged users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5980 | BSK Forms Blacklist &amp;lt; 3.7 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5980</link><description>The BSK Forms Blacklist WordPress plugin before 3.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5991 | Hotel Booking Lite &amp;lt; 4.8.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download &amp;amp; Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5991</link><description>The Hotel Booking Lite WordPress plugin before 4.8.5 does not validate file paths provided via user input, as well as does not have proper CSRF and authorisation checks, allowing unauthenticated users to download and delete arbitrary files on the server</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6114 | Duplicator &amp;lt; 1.5.7.1; Duplicator Pro &amp;lt; 4.5.14.2 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6114</link><description>The Duplicator WordPress plugin before 1.5.7.1, Duplicator Pro WordPress plugin before 4.5.14.2 does not disallow listing the `backups-dup-lite/tmp` directory (or the `backups-dup-pro/tmp` directory in the Pro version), which temporarily stores files containing sensitive data. When directory listing is enabled in the web server, this allows unauthenticated attackers to discover and access these sensitive files, which include a full database dump and a zip archive of the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6155 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt; 6.4.9.5 - Unauthenticated Email Address Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6155</link><description>The Quiz Maker WordPress plugin before 6.4.9.5 does not adequately authorize the `ays_quiz_author_user_search` AJAX action, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to perform a search for users of the system, ultimately leaking user email addresses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6166 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt; 6.4.9.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6166</link><description>The Quiz Maker WordPress plugin before 6.4.9.5 does not escape generated URLs before outputting them in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6250 | BestWebSoft&amp;#x27;s Like &amp;amp; Share &amp;lt; 2.74 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Post Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6250</link><description>The BestWebSoft's Like &amp; Share WordPress plugin before 2.74 discloses the content of password protected posts to unauthenticated users via a meta tag</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6268 | JSON Content Importer &amp;lt; 1.5.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6268</link><description>The JSON Content Importer WordPress plugin before 1.5.4 does not sanitise and escape the tab parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52086 | resumable.php (aka PHP backend for resumable.js) 0.1.4 before 3c6dbf5 allows arbitrary file upload anywhere in the filesystem via ../ in mul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52086</link><description>resumable.php (aka PHP backend for resumable.js) 0.1.4 before 3c6dbf5 allows arbitrary file upload anywhere in the filesystem via ../ in multipart/form-data content to upload.php. (File overwrite hasn't been possible with the code available in GitHub in recent years, however.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51097 | Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSetAutoPing.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51097</link><description>Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSetAutoPing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51090 | Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formGetWeiXinConfig.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51090</link><description>Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formGetWeiXinConfig.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51098 | Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function formSetDiagnoseInfo .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51098</link><description>Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function formSetDiagnoseInfo .</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51099 | Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function formexeCommand .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51099</link><description>Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function formexeCommand .</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51100 | Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function formGetDiagnoseInfo .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51100</link><description>Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function formGetDiagnoseInfo .</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51101 | Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSetUplinkInfo.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51101</link><description>Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSetUplinkInfo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51102 | Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWifiMacFilterSet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51102</link><description>Tenda W9 V1.0.0.7(4456)_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWifiMacFilterSet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51091 | Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function R7WebsSecurityHandler.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51091</link><description>Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function R7WebsSecurityHandler.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51092 | Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function upgrade.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51092</link><description>Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function upgrade.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51093 | Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function fromSetLocalVlanInfo.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51093</link><description>Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function fromSetLocalVlanInfo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51094 | Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a Command Execution vulnerability via the function TendaTelnet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51094</link><description>Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a Command Execution vulnerability via the function TendaTelnet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51095 | Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formDelWlRfPolicy.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51095</link><description>Tenda M3 V1.0.0.12(4856) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formDelWlRfPolicy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10127 | PlusCaptcha Plugin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10127</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PlusCaptcha Plugin up to 2.0.6 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.14 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 1274afc635170daafd38306487b6bb8a01f78ecd. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248954 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 17:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125109 | BestWebSoft Portfolio Plugin bws_menu.php bws_add_menu_render cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125109</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BestWebSoft Portfolio Plugin up to 2.27. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function bws_add_menu_render of the file bws_menu/bws_menu.php. The manipulation of the argument bwsmn_form_email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 2.28 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is d2ede580474665af56ff262a05783fbabe4529b8. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248956.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 15:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51467 | Apache OFBiz: Pre-authentication Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51467</link><description>The vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication to achieve a simple Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51103 | A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon fz_new_pixmap_from_float_data() of pixma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51103</link><description>A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon fz_new_pixmap_from_float_data() of pixmap.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51104 | A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon pnm_binary_read_image() of load-pnm.c li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51104</link><description>A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon pnm_binary_read_image() of load-pnm.c line 527.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51106 | A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon pnm_binary_read_image() of load-pnm.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51106</link><description>A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon pnm_binary_read_image() of load-pnm.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51105 | A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in function bmp_decompress_rle4() of load-bmp.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51105</link><description>A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in function bmp_decompress_rle4() of load-bmp.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51107 | A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon compute_color() of jquant2.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51107</link><description>A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in mupdf 1.23.4 in functon compute_color() of jquant2.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49949 | Passwork before 6.2.0 allows remote authenticated users to bypass 2FA by sending all one million of the possible 6-digit codes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49949</link><description>Passwork before 6.2.0 allows remote authenticated users to bypass 2FA by sending all one million of the possible 6-digit codes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50968 | Apache OFBiz: Arbitrary file properties reading and SSRF attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50968</link><description>Arbitrary file properties reading vulnerability in Apache Software Foundation Apache OFBiz when user operates an uri call without authorizations.

The same uri can be operated to realize a SSRF attack also  without  authorizations.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.11, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 12:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10017 | BestWebSoft Portfolio Plugin cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10017</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BestWebSoft Portfolio Plugin up to 2.04 on WordPress. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.06 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 68af950330c3202a706f0ae9bbb52ceaa17dda9d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248955.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 10:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5180 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability exists in ODA Drawings SDK before 2024.12</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5180</link><description>An issue was discovered in Open Design Alliance
Drawings SDK before 2024.12. A corrupted value of number
of sectors used by the Fat structure in a crafted DGN file leads to an
out-of-bounds write. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute
code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45741 | VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier allows an attacker with access to the product's web management page to execute arbitrary OS commands...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45741</link><description>VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier allows an attacker with access to the product's web management page to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46681 | Improper neutralization of argument delimiters in a command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability in VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46681</link><description>Improper neutralization of argument delimiters in a command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability in VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier allows an authenticated attacker who can access to the product's command line interface to execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46711 | VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier uses a hard-coded cryptographic key which may allow an attacker to analyze the password of a specifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46711</link><description>VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier uses a hard-coded cryptographic key which may allow an attacker to analyze the password of a specific product user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51363 | VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker who can access the product's web management page ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51363</link><description>VR-S1000 firmware Ver. 2.37 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker who can access the product's web management page to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42436 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the presentation feature of GROWI versions prior to v3.4.0. If this vulnerability is exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42436</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the presentation feature of GROWI versions prior to v3.4.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45737 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the App Settings (/admin/app) page and the Markdown Settings (/admin/markdown) page of G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45737</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the App Settings (/admin/app) page and the Markdown Settings (/admin/markdown) page of GROWI versions prior to v3.5.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45740 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability when processing profile images exists in GROWI versions prior to v4.1.3. If this vulnerability is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45740</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability when processing profile images exists in GROWI versions prior to v4.1.3. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46699 | Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the User settings (/me) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If a user views a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46699</link><description>Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the User settings (/me) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If a user views a malicious page while logging in, settings may be changed without the user's intention.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47215 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability which is exploiting a behavior of the XSS Filter exists in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47215</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability which is exploiting a behavior of the XSS Filter exists in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49119 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability via the img tags exists in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49119</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability via the img tags exists in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49598 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the event handlers of the pre tags in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49598</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the event handlers of the pre tags in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49779 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the anchor tag of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49779</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the anchor tag of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49807 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability when processing the MathJax exists in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49807</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability when processing the MathJax exists in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50175 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the App Settings (/admin/app) page, the Markdown Settings (/admin/markdown) page, and th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50175</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the App Settings (/admin/app) page, the Markdown Settings (/admin/markdown) page, and the Customize (/admin/customize) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50294 | The App Settings (/admin/app) page in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.6 stores sensitive information in cleartext form. As a result, the Secret...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50294</link><description>The App Settings (/admin/app) page in GROWI versions prior to v6.0.6 stores sensitive information in cleartext form. As a result, the Secret access key for external service may be obtained by an attacker who can access the App Settings page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50332 | Improper authorization vulnerability exists in the User Management (/admin/users) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.6. If this vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50332</link><description>Improper authorization vulnerability exists in the User Management (/admin/users) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.0.6. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user may delete or suspend its own account without the user's intention.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50339 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the User Management (/admin/users) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.1.11. If this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50339</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the User Management (/admin/users) page of GROWI versions prior to v6.1.11. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the site using the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49117 | PowerCMS (6 Series, 5 Series, and 4 Series) contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49117</link><description>PowerCMS (6 Series, 5 Series, and 4 Series) contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on a logged-in user's web browser. Note that all versions of PowerCMS 3 Series and earlier which are unsupported (End-of-Life, EOL) are also affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 05:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50297 | Open redirect vulnerability in PowerCMS (6 Series, 5 Series, and 4 Series) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50297</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in PowerCMS (6 Series, 5 Series, and 4 Series) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arbitrary web sites via a specially crafted URL. Note that all versions of PowerCMS 3 Series and earlier which are unsupported (End-of-Life, EOL) are also affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 05:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51654 | Improper link resolution before file access ('Link Following') issue exists in iPrint&amp;Scan Desktop for Windows versions 11.0.0 and earlier. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51654</link><description>Improper link resolution before file access ('Link Following') issue exists in iPrint&amp;Scan Desktop for Windows versions 11.0.0 and earlier. A symlink attack by a malicious user may cause a Denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the PC.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 05:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28616 | An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) before 4.3.17, 4.4.x through 4.6.x before 4.6.4, and 4.7.x before 4.7.1. It af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28616</link><description>An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) before 4.3.17, 4.4.x through 4.6.x before 4.6.4, and 4.7.x before 4.7.1. It affects user accounts for which the password has an equals sign or space character. The serverd process logs such passwords in cleartext, and potentially sends these logs to the Syslog component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 04:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27150 | openCRX 5.2.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Name field after creation of a Tracker in Manage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27150</link><description>openCRX 5.2.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Name field after creation of a Tracker in Manage Activity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7111 | code-projects Library Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7111</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Library Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249006 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 02:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7110 | code-projects Library Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7110</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Library Management System 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument student leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249005 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 02:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7109 | code-projects Library Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7109</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Library Management System 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249004.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7108 | code-projects E-Commerce Website user_signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7108</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file user_signup.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname with the input &lt;video/src=x onerror=alert(document.domain)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249003.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:06:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>