<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12979 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php cn_update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12979</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function cn_update of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument cname leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56519 | An issue was discovered in TCPDF before 6.8.0. setSVGStyles does not sanitize the SVG font-family attribute.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56519</link><description>An issue was discovered in TCPDF before 6.8.0. setSVGStyles does not sanitize the SVG font-family attribute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56520 | An issue was discovered in tc-lib-pdf-font before 2.6.4, as used in TCPDF before 6.8.0 and other products. Fonts are mishandled, e.g., FontB...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56520</link><description>An issue was discovered in tc-lib-pdf-font before 2.6.4, as used in TCPDF before 6.8.0 and other products. Fonts are mishandled, e.g., FontBBox for Type 1 and TrueType fonts is misparsed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56521 | An issue was discovered in TCPDF before 6.8.0. If libcurl is used, CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYHOST and CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER are set unsafely.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56521</link><description>An issue was discovered in TCPDF before 6.8.0. If libcurl is used, CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYHOST and CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER are set unsafely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56522 | An issue was discovered in TCPDF before 6.8.0. unserializeTCPDFtag uses != (aka loose comparison) and does not use a constant-time function ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56522</link><description>An issue was discovered in TCPDF before 6.8.0. unserializeTCPDFtag uses != (aka loose comparison) and does not use a constant-time function to compare TCPDF tag hashes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12978 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php add_req sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12978</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function add_req of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument jid/limit leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 04:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12977 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12977</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/state.php. The manipulation of the argument state leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9774 | Python-sql: python-sql unary operators does not escape non-expression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9774</link><description>A vulnerability was found in python-sql where unary operators do not escape non-Expression.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12976 | CodeZips Hospital Management System staff.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12976</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CodeZips Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /staff.php. The manipulation of the argument tel leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12969 | code-projects Hospital Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12969</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12968 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php edit_jobpost sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12968</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function edit_jobpost of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument jobtype leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56361 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in lgsl v7.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56361</link><description>LGSL (Live Game Server List) provides online status for games. Before 7.0.0, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in lgsl. The function lgsl_query_40 in lgsl_protocol.php has implemented an HTTP crawler. This function makes a request to the registered game server, and upon crawling the malicious /info endpoint with our payload, will render our javascript on the info page. This information is being displayed via lgsl_details.php. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55950 | Tabby has a TCC Bypass via Unnecessary Permissive Entitlements in Tabby</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55950</link><description>Tabby (formerly Terminus) is a highly configurable terminal emulator. Prior to 1.0.216, Tabby terminal emulator contains overly permissive entitlements that are unnecessary for its core functionality and plugin system, creating potential security vulnerabilities. The application currently holds powerful permissions including camera, microphone access, and the ability to access personal folders (Downloads, Documents, etc.) through Apple Events, while also maintaining dangerous entitlements that enable code injection. The concerning entitlements are com.apple.security.cs.allow-dyld-environment-variables and com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation. Since Tabby's plugins and themes are NodeJS-based without native libraries or frameworks, and no environment variables are used in the codebase, it is recommended to review and remove at least one of the entitlements (com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation or com.apple.security.cs.allow-dyld-environment-variables) to prevent DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES injection while maintaining full application functionality. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.216.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53850 | The Addressing GLPI plugin allows data enumeration through uncontrolled object instantiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53850</link><description>The Addressing GLPI plugin enables you to create IP reports for visualize IP addresses used and free on a given network.. Starting with 3.0.0 and before 3.0.3, a poor security check allows an unauthenticated attacker to determine whether data exists (by name) in GLPI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45805 | OpenCTI leaks support information due to inadequate access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45805</link><description>OpenCTI is an open-source cyber threat intelligence platform. Before 6.3.0, general users can access information that can only be accessed by users with access privileges to admin and support information (SETTINGS_SUPPORT). This is due to inadequate access control for support information (http:///storage/get/support/UUID/UUID.zip), and that the UUID is available to general users using an attached query (logs query). This vulnerability is fixed in 6.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12967 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php fln_update sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12967</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. Affected is the function fln_update of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument fname/lname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45600 | Fields GLPI plugin has an Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45600</link><description>Fields is a GLPI plugin that allows users to add custom fields on GLPI items forms. Prior to 1.21.13, an authenticated user can perform a SQL injection when the plugin is active. The vulnerability is fixed in 1.21.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12966 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php cn_update sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function cn_update of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument cname/url leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56510 | Marp Core allows XSS by improper neutralization of HTML sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56510</link><description>@marp-team/marp-core is the core for Marp, which is the ecosystem to write your presentation with plain Markdown. Marp Core from v3.0.2 to v3.9.0 and v4.0.0, are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) due to improper neutralization of HTML sanitization. Marp Core v3.9.1 and v4.0.1 have been patched to fix that. If you are unable to update the package immediately, disable all HTML tags by setting html: false option in the Marp class constructor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12965 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_ex_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12965</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /update_ex_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12964 | 1000 Projects Daily College Class Work Report Book login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12964</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Daily College Class Work Report Book 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 20:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12963 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php add_xp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12963</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function add_xp of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument job_company leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 19:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12962 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12962</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument skillset leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 19:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54907 | TOTOLINK A3002R V4.0.0-B20230531.1404 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in /bin/boa via formWsc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54907</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R V4.0.0-B20230531.1404 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in /bin/boa via formWsc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 19:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12961 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_ach_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12961</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /update_ach_details.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 18:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12960 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_edu_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12960</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /update_edu_details.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12959 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_personal_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12959</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /update_personal_details.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 16:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51540 | Dell ECS, versions prior to 3.8.1.3 contains an arithmetic overflow vulnerability exists in retention period handling of ECS. An authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51540</link><description>Dell ECS, versions prior to 3.8.1.3 contains an arithmetic overflow vulnerability exists in retention period handling of ECS. An authenticated user with bucket or object-level access and the necessary privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass retention policies and delete objects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 16:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12908 | Delinea addressed a reported case on Secret Server v11.7.31 (protocol handler version 6.0.3.26) where, within the protocol handler function,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12908</link><description>Delinea addressed a reported case on Secret Server v11.7.31 (protocol handler version 6.0.3.26) where, within the protocol handler function, URI's were compared before normalization and canonicalization, potentially leading to over matching against the approved list. If this attack were successfully exploited, a remote attacker may be able to convince a user to visit a malicious web-page, or open a
malicious document which could trigger the vulnerable handler, allowing them to execute
arbitrary code on the user's machine. Delinea added additional validation that the downloaded installer's batch file was in the expected format.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 15:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12958 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_pro_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12958</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /update_pro_details.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12956 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA add_achievement_details.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12956</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add_achievement_details.php. The manipulation of the argument ach_certy leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 15:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12955 | PHPGurukul Blood Bank &amp;amp; Donor Management System logout.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12955</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Blood Bank &amp; Donor Management System 2.4 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /logout.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 14:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12954 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_ach.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12954</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /update_ach.php. The manipulation of the argument ach_certy leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 14:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12953 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA update_pd_process.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12953</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /update_pd_process.php. The manipulation of the argument profile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 13:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12952 | melMass comfy_mtb Dependency endpoint.py run_command code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12952</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in melMass comfy_mtb up to 0.1.4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function run_command of the file comfy_mtb/endpoint.py of the component Dependency Handler. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named d6e004cce2c32f8e48b868e66b89f82da4887dc3. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 13:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12951 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA add_personal_details.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12951</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add_personal_details.php. The manipulation of the argument profile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47149 | Some Honor products are affected by incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause device service excepti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47149</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause device service exceptions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47150 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47150</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12950 | code-projects Travel Management System subcat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12950</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Travel Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /subcat.php. The manipulation of the argument catid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47148 | Some Honor products are affected by incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause device service excepti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47148</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause device service exceptions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47157 | Some Honor products are affected by incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause device service excepti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47157</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause device service exceptions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47155 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47155</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47154 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47154</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12949 | code-projects Travel Management System package.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12949</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Travel Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /package.php. The manipulation of the argument subcatid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47153 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47153</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8992 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8992</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8993 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8993</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8994 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8994</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47151 | Some Honor products are affected by file writing vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47151</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by file writing vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause code execution</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47156 | Information Leak Vulnerability in Honor Product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47156</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation could cause the information leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12948 | code-projects Travel Management System detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12948</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Travel Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /detail.php. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12947 | Codezips Hospital Management System invo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12947</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /invo.php. The manipulation of the argument dname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 10:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12946 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System admin_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12946</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/admin_action.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_user_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 10:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12945 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12945</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /account.php. The manipulation of the argument email/pass leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7300 | Huawei Home Music System has a path traversal vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause the music host file to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7300</link><description>Huawei Home Music System has a path traversal vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause the music host file to be deleted or the file permission to be changed.(Vulnerability ID:HWPSIRT-2023-60613)</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 09:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12944 | CodeAstro House Rental Management System signin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12944</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /signin.php. The manipulation of the argument u/p leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 09:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56433 | shadow-utils (aka shadow) 4.4 through 4.17.0 establishes a default /etc/subuid behavior (e.g., uid 100000 through 165535 for the first user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56433</link><description>shadow-utils (aka shadow) 4.4 through 4.17.0 establishes a default /etc/subuid behavior (e.g., uid 100000 through 165535 for the first user account) that can realistically conflict with the uids of users defined on locally administered networks, potentially leading to account takeover, e.g., by leveraging newuidmap for access to an NFS home directory (or same-host resources in the case of remote logins by these local network users). NOTE: it may also be argued that system administrators should not have assigned uids, within local networks, that are within the range that can occur in /etc/subuid.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12943 | CodeAstro House Rental Management System ownersignup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12943</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ownersignup.php. The manipulation of the argument f/e/p/m/o/n/c/s/ci/a leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "m" to be affected. But it must be assumed that many other parameters are affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12942 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA admin_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12942</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin_login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12941 | CodeAstro Blood Donor Management System deletedannounce.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12941</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Blood Donor Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/deletedannounce.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12940 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System student_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12940</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/student_action.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12939 | code-projects Job Recruitment _all_edits.php add_edu sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12939</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function add_edu of the file /_parse/_all_edits.php. The manipulation of the argument degree leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 06:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10903 | Broken Link Checker &amp;lt; 2.4.2 - Admin+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10903</link><description>The Broken Link Checker WordPress plugin before 2.4.2 does not validate a the link URLs before making a request to them, which could allow admin users to perform SSRF attack, for example on a multisite installation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 06:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11223 | WPForms &amp;lt; 1.9.2.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11223</link><description>The WPForms  WordPress plugin before 1.9.2.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 06:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12938 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel updateOrderStatus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12938</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file updateOrderStatus.php. The manipulation of the argument record leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 06:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12937 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel addVariationController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12937</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file addVariationController.php. The manipulation of the argument qty leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 05:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12936 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel catDeleteController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12936</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file catDeleteController.php. The manipulation of the argument record leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 05:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12935 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel editItemForm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12935</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file editItemForm.php. The manipulation of the argument record leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 04:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12652 | Intumit SmartRobot′s Conversational AI Platform - Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12652</link><description>A Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in groovy script function in SmartRobot′s Conversational AI Platform before v7.2.0 allows remote authenticated users to perform arbitrary system commands via Groovy code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 04:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12934 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel updateItemController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12934</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file updateItemController.php. The manipulation of the argument p_desk leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 04:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12933 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel updateItemController.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12933</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file updateItemController.php. The manipulation of the argument p_name/p_desc leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 03:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12932 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel addSizeController.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12932</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file addSizeController.php. The manipulation of the argument size leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 03:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12931 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel addCatController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12931</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addCatController.php. The manipulation of the argument size leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12930 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel addCatController.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12930</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file addCatController.php. The manipulation of the argument c_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12929 | code-projects Student Management System addCatController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12929</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Student Management System 1.0.00 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /addCatController.php. The manipulation of the argument size leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 01:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12928 | code-projects Simple Admin Panel sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12928</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Simple Admin Panel 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation of the argument c_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 23:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12927 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System check_faculty_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12927</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /faculty/check_faculty_login.php. The manipulation of the argument faculty_emailid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 23:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12926 | Codezips Project Management System advanced.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12926</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips Project Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/forms/advanced.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56430 | OpenFHE through 1.2.3 has a NULL pointer dereference in BinFHEContext::EvalFloor in lib/binfhe-base-scheme.cpp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56430</link><description>OpenFHE through 1.2.3 has a NULL pointer dereference in BinFHEContext::EvalFloor in lib/binfhe-base-scheme.cpp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56431 | oc_huff_tree_unpack in huffdec.c in libtheora in Theora through 1.0 7180717 has an invalid negative left shift.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56431</link><description>oc_huff_tree_unpack in huffdec.c in libtheora in Theora through 1.0 7180717 has an invalid negative left shift.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 17:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52534 | Dell ECS, version(s) prior to ECS 3.8.1.3, contain(s) an Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability. A low privileged attacker wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52534</link><description>Dell ECS, version(s) prior to ECS 3.8.1.3, contain(s) an Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Session theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 16:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52543 | Dell NativeEdge, version(s) 2.1.0.0, contain(s) a Creation of Temporary File With Insecure Permissions vulnerability. A high privileged atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52543</link><description>Dell NativeEdge, version(s) 2.1.0.0, contain(s) a Creation of Temporary File With Insecure Permissions vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 15:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53291 | Dell NativeEdge, version(s) 2.1.0.0, contain(s) an Exposure of Sensitive Information Through Metadata vulnerability. An unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53291</link><description>Dell NativeEdge, version(s) 2.1.0.0, contain(s) an Exposure of Sensitive Information Through Metadata vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 15:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47978 | Dell NativeEdge, version(s) 2.1.0.0, contain(s) an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47978</link><description>Dell NativeEdge, version(s) 2.1.0.0, contain(s) an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 15:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52906 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52906</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, VIOS 3.1, and 4.1



could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the TCP/IP kernel extension to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 15:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5117 | Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5117</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.6.0 in which users were unaware that files uploaded to comments on confidential issues and epics of public projects could be accessed without authentication via a direct link to the uploaded file URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47102 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47102</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, VIOS 3.1, and 4.1

could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the AIX perfstat kernel extension to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52535 | Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.6.1 and prior and Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.0 and prior, contain a symboli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52535</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.6.1 and prior and Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.0 and prior, contain a symbolic link (symlink) attack vulnerability in the software remediation component. A low-privileged authenticated user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, gaining privileges escalation, leading to arbitrary deletion of files and folders from the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39725 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39725</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39727 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights tabnabbing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39727</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 uses a web link with untrusted references to an external site. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or perform unauthorized actions on the victims’ web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8950 | SQLi in Arne Informatics&amp;#x27; Piramit Automation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8950</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Arne Informatics Piramit Automation allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Piramit Automation: before 27.09.2024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 12:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52046 | Apache MINA: MINA applications using unbounded deserialization may allow RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52046</link><description>The ObjectSerializationDecoder in Apache MINA uses Java’s native deserialization protocol to process
incoming serialized data but lacks the necessary security checks and defenses. This vulnerability allows
attackers to exploit the deserialization process by sending specially crafted malicious serialized data,
potentially leading to remote code execution (RCE) attacks.



					


				


			


		


	
This issue affects MINA core versions 2.0.X, 2.1.X and 2.2.X, and will be fixed by the releases 2.0.27, 2.1.10 and 2.2.4.





It's also important to note that an application using MINA core library will only be affected if the IoBuffer#getObject() method is called, and this specific method is potentially called when adding a ProtocolCodecFilter instance using the ObjectSerializationCodecFactory class in the filter chain. If your application is specifically using those classes, you have to upgrade to the latest version of MINA core library.




Upgrading will  not be enough: you also need to explicitly allow the classes the decoder will accept in the ObjectSerializationDecoder instance, using one of the three new methods:




    /**

     * Accept class names where the supplied ClassNameMatcher matches for

     * deserialization, unless they are otherwise rejected.

     *

     * @param classNameMatcher the matcher to use

     */

    public void accept(ClassNameMatcher classNameMatcher)




    /**

     * Accept class names that match the supplied pattern for

     * deserialization, unless they are otherwise rejected.

     *

     * @param pattern standard Java regexp

     */

    public void accept(Pattern pattern) 





    /**

     * Accept the wildcard specified classes for deserialization,

     * unless they are otherwise rejected.

     *

     * @param patterns Wildcard file name patterns as defined by

     *                  {@link org.apache.commons.io.FilenameUtils#wildcardMatch(String, String) FilenameUtils.wildcardMatch}

     */

    public void accept(String... patterns)







By default, the decoder will reject *all* classes that will be present in the incoming data.







Note: The FtpServer, SSHd and Vysper sub-project are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10862 | NEX-Forms &amp;lt;= 8.7.13 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10862</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search_params' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.13 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This can be exploited via CSRF due to a lack of nonce validation on the get_table_records AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11281 | WooCommerce Point of Sale &amp;lt;= 6.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Privilege Escalation via Arbitrary User Email Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11281</link><description>The WooCommerce Point of Sale plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.0. This is due to insufficient validation on the 'logged_in_user_id' value when option values are empty and the ability for attackers to change the email of arbitrary user accounts. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the email of arbitrary user accounts, including administrators, and reset their password to gain access to the account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12335 | Avada Builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12335</link><description>The Avada (Fusion) Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.12 via the handle_clone_post() function and the 'fusion_blog' shortcode and due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10858 | Jetpack 13.0-14.0 - Unauthenticated DOM-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10858</link><description>The Jetpack  WordPress plugin before 14.1 does not properly checks the postmessage origin in its 13.x versions, allowing it to be bypassed and leading to DOM-XSS. The issue only affects websites hosted on WordPress.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12428 | WP Data Access – App, Table, Form and Chart Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.22 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12428</link><description>The WP Data Access – App, Table, Form and Chart Builder plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order[user_login][dir]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.22 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 04:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12636 | Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp;amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12636</link><description>The Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'create_popup_delete_process' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete popups via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12032 | Tourfic – Ultimate Hotel Booking, Travel Booking &amp;amp; Apartment Booking WordPress Plugin | WooCommerce Booking &amp;lt;= 2.15.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12032</link><description>The Tourfic – Ultimate Hotel Booking, Travel Booking &amp; Apartment Booking WordPress Plugin | WooCommerce Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'enquiry_id' parameter of the 'tf_enquiry_reply_email_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12190 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder &amp;lt;=  2.17.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Form Submission Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12190</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the bitform-form-entry-edit endpoint in all versions up to, and including,  2.17.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view all form submissions from other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12272 | WP Travel Engine – Elementor Widgets | Create Travel Booking Website Using WordPress and Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12272</link><description>The WP Travel Engine – Elementor Widgets | Create Travel Booking Website Using WordPress and Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 via several widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12413 | MarketKing — Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 2.0.00 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12413</link><description>The MarketKing — Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several functions like 'marketking_delete_team_member', 'marketkingrejectuser', 'marketking_save_profile_settings', and many more in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.00. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete users, update settings, approve users, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1609 | OPPO Store APP has a WebView component privilege escalation vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1609</link><description>In OPPOStore iOS App, there's a possible escalation of privilege due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>