<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-7114 | Tianchoy Blog so.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7114</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tianchoy Blog up to 1.8.8. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /so.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272445 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41468 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the cmdinput parameter at /goform/exeCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41468</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the cmdinput parameter at /goform/exeCommand</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41473 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the mac parameter at ip/goform/WriteFacMac</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41473</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the mac parameter at ip/goform/WriteFacMac</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 22:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24621 | Softaculous Webuzo Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24621</link><description>Softaculous Webuzo contains an authentication bypass vulnerability through the password reset functionality. Remote, anonymous attackers can exploit this vulnerability to gain full server access as the root user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24622 | Softaculous Webuzo Password Reset Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24622</link><description>Softaculous Webuzo contains a command injection in the password reset functionality. A remote, authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24623 | Softaculous Webuzo FTP Management Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24623</link><description>Softaculous Webuzo contains a command injection vulnerability in the FTP management functionality. A remote, authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38103 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38103</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3938 | The "reset password" login page accepted an HTML injection via URL parameters.

This has already been rectified via patch, and as such it ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3938</link><description>The "reset password" login page accepted an HTML injection via URL parameters.

This has already been rectified via patch, and as such it cannot be demonstrated via Demo site link. Those interested to see the vulnerability may spin up a  http://localhost:8082/dotAdmin/#/public/login?resetEmailSent=true&amp;amp;resetEmail=%3Ch1%3E%3Ca%20href%3D%22https:%2F%2Fgoogle.com%22%3ECLICK%20ME%3C%2Fa%3E%3C%2Fh1%3E 

This will result in a view along these lines:





  *  OWASP Top 10 - A03: Injection
  *  CVSS Score: 5.4
  *   AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator 
  *   https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator?vector=AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N&amp;... https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7106 | Spina CMS media_folders cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7106</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Spina CMS 2.18.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/media_folders. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272431. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7105 | ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX Lista Ura Page detalheIdUra sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7105</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX 1.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file /detalheIdUra of the component Lista Ura Page. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272430 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41809 | OpenObserve Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in `openobserve/web/src/views/MemberSubscription.vue`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41809</link><description>OpenObserve is an open-source observability platform. Starting in version 0.4.4 and prior to version 0.10.0, OpenObserve contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in line 32 of `openobserve/web/src/views/MemberSubscription.vue`. Version 0.10.0 sanitizes incoming html.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41808 | OpenObserve stored XSS vulnerability may lead to complete account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41808</link><description>The OpenObserve open-source observability platform provides the ability to filter logs in a dashboard by the values uploaded in a given log. However, all versions of the platform through 0.9.1 do not sanitize user input in the filter selection menu, which may result in complete account takeover. It has been noted that the front-end uses `DOMPurify` or Vue templating to escape cross-site scripting (XSS) extensively, however certain areas of the front end lack this XSS protection. When combining the missing protection with the insecure authentication handling that the front-end uses, a malicious user may be able to take over any victim's account provided they meet the exploitation steps. As of time of publication, no patched version is available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6558 | HMS Industrial Networks Anybus-CompactCom 30 Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6558</link><description>HMS Industrial Networks

Anybus-CompactCom 30 products are vulnerable to a XSS attack caused by the lack of input sanitation checks. As a consequence, it is possible to insert HTML code into input fields and store the HTML code. The stored HTML code will be embedded in the page and executed by host browser the next time the page is loaded, enabling social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29069 | snapd will follow archived symlinks when unpacking a filesystem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29069</link><description>In snapd versions prior to 2.62, snapd failed to properly check the
destination of symbolic links when extracting a snap. The snap format 
is a squashfs file-system image and so can contain symbolic links and
other file types. Various file entries within the snap squashfs image
(such as icons and desktop files etc) are directly read by snapd when
it is extracted. An attacker who could convince a user to install a
malicious snap which contained symbolic links at these paths could then 
cause snapd to write out the contents of the symbolic link destination
into a world-readable directory. This in-turn could allow an unprivileged
user to gain access to privileged information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38287 | The password-reset mechanism in the Forgot Password functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated remote attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38287</link><description>The password-reset mechanism in the Forgot Password functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated remote attackers to force the application into resetting the administrator's password to a random insecure 8-digit value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38288 | A command-injection issue in the Certificate Signing Request (CSR) functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows authenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38288</link><description>A command-injection issue in the Certificate Signing Request (CSR) functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows authenticated attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying server as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38289 | A boolean-based SQL injection issue in the Virtual Meeting Password (VMP) endpoint in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38289</link><description>A boolean-based SQL injection issue in the Virtual Meeting Password (VMP) endpoint in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated remote attackers to extract hashed passwords from the database, and authenticate to the application, via crafted SQL input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40324 | A CRLF injection vulnerability in E-Staff v5.1 allows attackers to insert Carriage Return (CR) and Line Feed (LF) characters into input fiel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40324</link><description>A CRLF injection vulnerability in E-Staff v5.1 allows attackers to insert Carriage Return (CR) and Line Feed (LF) characters into input fields, leading to HTTP response splitting and header manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29068 | snapd non-regular file indefinite blocking read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29068</link><description>In snapd versions prior to 2.62, snapd failed to properly check the file
type when extracting a snap. The snap format is a squashfs file-system
image and so can contain files that are non-regular files (such as pipes 
or sockets etc). Various file entries within the snap squashfs image
(such as icons etc) are directly read by snapd when it is extracted. An 
attacker who could convince a user to install a malicious snap which
contained non-regular files at these paths could then cause snapd to block
indefinitely trying to read from such files and cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1724 | snapd allows $HOME/bin symlink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1724</link><description>In snapd versions prior to 2.62, when using AppArmor for enforcement of 
sandbox permissions, snapd failed to restrict writes to the $HOME/bin
path. In Ubuntu, when this path exists, it is automatically added to
the users PATH. An attacker who could convince a user to install a
malicious snap which used the 'home' plug could use this vulnerability
to install arbitrary scripts into the users PATH which may then be run
by the user outside of the expected snap sandbox and hence allow them
to escape confinement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40318 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Webkul Qloapps v1.6.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40318</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Webkul Qloapps v1.6.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 18:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28772 | IBM Security Directory Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28772</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  285645.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40873 | XSS in Secure Access administrative console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40873</link><description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.07.
Attackers with system administrator permissions can interfere with another
system administrator’s use of the publishing UI when the administrators are
editing the same management object. The scope is unchanged, there is no loss of
confidentiality. Impact to system availability is none, impact to system
integrity is high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32759 | IBM Security Directory Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32759</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 uses insufficient session expiration which could allow an unauthorized user to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  228565.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40872 | Elevation of privilege in Absolute Secure Access clients and servers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40872</link><description>There is an elevation of privilege vulnerability in server
and client components of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.07.
Attackers with local access and valid desktop user credentials can elevate
their privilege to system level by passing invalid address data to the vulnerable
component. This could be used to
manipulate process tokens to elevate the privilege of a normal process to
System. The scope is changed, the impact to system confidentiality and
integrity is high, the impact to the availability of the effected component is
none.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41801 | OpenProject packaged installation has Open Redirect Vulnerability in Sign-In in default configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41801</link><description>OpenProject is open source project management software. Prior to version 14.3.0, using a forged HOST header in the default configuration of packaged installations and using the "Login required" setting, an attacker could redirect to a remote host to initiate a phishing attack against an OpenProject user's account. This vulnerability affects default packaged installation of OpenProject without any additional configuration or modules on Apache (such as mod_security, manually setting a host name, having a fallthrough VirtualHost). It might also affect other installations that did not take care to fix the HOST/X-Forwarded-Host headers. Version 14.3.0 includes stronger protections for the hostname from within the application using the HostAuthorization middleware of Rails to reject any requests with a host name that does not match the configured one. Also, all generated links by the application are now ensured to use the built-in hostname. Users who aren't able to upgrade immediately may use mod_security for Apache2 or manually fix the Host and X-Forwarded-Host headers in their proxying application before reaching the application server of OpenProject. Alternatively, they can manually apply the patch to opt-in to host header protections in previous versions of OpenProject.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36542 | Insecure permissions in kuma v2.7.0 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's tok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36542</link><description>Insecure permissions in kuma v2.7.0 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7007 | Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel in Positron Broadcast Signal Processor TRA7005</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7007</link><description>Positron Broadcast Signal Processor TRA7005 v1.20 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass exploit that could allow an attacker to have unauthorized access to protected areas of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41800 | Craft CMS Allows TOTP Token To Stay Valid After Use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41800</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). Craft CMS 5 allows reuse of TOTP tokens multiple times within the validity period. An attacker is able to re-submit a valid TOTP token to establish an authenticated session. This requires that the attacker has knowledge of the victim's credentials. This has been patched in Craft 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7101 | ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX Authentication Form login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7101</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX 1.x. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login of the component Authentication Form. The manipulation of the argument usuario leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272423. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41806 | Open edX Platform&amp;#x27;s instructor upload CSV for cohort creation not Private by Default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41806</link><description>The Open edX Platform is a learning management platform. Instructors can upload csv files containing learner information to create cohorts in the instructor dashboard. These files are uploaded using the django default storage. With certain storage backends, uploads may become publicly available when the uploader uses versions master, palm, olive, nutmeg, maple, lilac, koa, or juniper. The patch in commit cb729a3ced0404736dfa0ae768526c82b608657b ensures that cohorts data uploaded to AWS S3 buckets is written with a private ACL. Beyond patching, deployers should also ensure that existing cohorts uploads have a private ACL, or that other precautions are taken to avoid public access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36111 | KubePi&amp;#x27;s JWT token validation has a defect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36111</link><description>KubePi is a K8s panel. Starting in version 1.6.3 and prior to version 1.8.0, there is a defect in the KubePi JWT token verification. The JWT key in the default configuration file is empty. Although a random 32-bit string will be generated to overwrite the key in the configuration file when the key is detected to be empty in the configuration file reading logic, the key is empty during actual verification. Using an empty key to generate a JWT token can bypass the login verification and directly take over the back end. Version 1.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39671 | Access control vulnerability in the security verification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39671</link><description>Access control vulnerability in the security verification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39672 | Memory request logic vulnerability in the memory module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and ava...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39672</link><description>Memory request logic vulnerability in the memory module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7271 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the NMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7271</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the NMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39670 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the account synchronisation module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39670</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the account synchronisation module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39673 | Vulnerability of serialisation/deserialisation mismatch in the iAware module. Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39673</link><description>Vulnerability of serialisation/deserialisation mismatch in the iAware module. Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39674 | Plaintext vulnerability in the Gallery search module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39674</link><description>Plaintext vulnerability in the Gallery search module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6589 | LearnPress &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6589</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8.2 via the 'render_content_block_template' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37084 | CVE-2024-37084: Remote code execution in Spring Cloud Data Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37084</link><description>In Spring Cloud Data Flow versions prior to 2.11.4,  a malicious user who has access to the Skipper server api can use a crafted upload request to write an arbitrary file to any location on the file system which could lead to compromising the server</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41705 | A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6.8 before 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially expl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41705</link><description>A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6.8 before 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.14.P4 (6.14.0.4) and 6.13 P4 (6.13.0.4) are also fixed releases. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-30639.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41706 | A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before version 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41706</link><description>A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before version 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.14 P4 (6.14.0.4) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41707 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.06. Authenticated users can achieve HTML content injection. A remote authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41707</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.06. Authenticated users can achieve HTML content injection. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6972 | In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain circumstances it is possible for sensitive variables to be printed in the task log in c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6972</link><description>In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain circumstances it is possible for sensitive variables to be printed in the task log in clear-text.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4811 | In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain conditions, a user with specific role assignments can access restricted project artifac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4811</link><description>In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain conditions, a user with specific role assignments can access restricted project artifacts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 05:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7047 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7047</link><description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts under the context of the current logged in user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 01:03:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7057 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7057</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where job artifacts can be inappropriately exposed to users lacking the proper authorization level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 01:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0231 | Improper Control of Resource Identifiers (&amp;#x27;Resource Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link><description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5067 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7060 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7091 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7081 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System expcatadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7081</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file expcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41461 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the list1 parameter at ip/goform/DhcpListCl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41461</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the list1 parameter at ip/goform/DhcpListClient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41462 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter at ip/goform/DhcpListCli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41462</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter at ip/goform/DhcpListClient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41463 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter at ip/goform/addressNa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41463</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter at ip/goform/addressNat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41464 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/goform/Rou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41464</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/goform/RouteStatic</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41459 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PPPOEPassword parameter at ip/goform/Qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41459</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PPPOEPassword parameter at ip/goform/QuickIndex.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41460 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter at ip/goform/RouteStat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41460</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter at ip/goform/RouteStatic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41465 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the funcpara1 parameter at ip/goform/setcfm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41465</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the funcpara1 parameter at ip/goform/setcfm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41466 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter at ip/goform/NatStaticSe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41466</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter at ip/goform/NatStaticSetting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41136 | Authenticated Command Injection in HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN Command Line Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41136</link><description>An authenticated command injection vulnerability exists in the HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN gateways Command Line Interface. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in the ability to execute arbitrary commands as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33519 | Authenticated Server-Side prototype pollution Leading to Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33519</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN gateway could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a server-side prototype pollution attack. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41133 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN Command Line Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41133</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN gateway's Command Line Interface that allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary commands on the underlying host. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will result in the ability to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41134 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN Command Line Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41134</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN gateway's Command Line Interface that allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary commands on the underlying host. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will result in the ability to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41135 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN Command Line Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41135</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN gateway's Command Line Interface that allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary commands on the underlying host. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will result in the ability to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7080 | SourceCodester Insurance Management System direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7080</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /E-Insurance/. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272365 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36533 | Insecure permissions in volcano v1.8.2 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36533</link><description>Insecure permissions in volcano v1.8.2 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36534 | Insecure permissions in hwameistor v0.14.3 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service accoun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36534</link><description>Insecure permissions in hwameistor v0.14.3 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41551 | CampCodes Supplier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via Supply_Management_System/admin/view_order_items.php?id= .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41551</link><description>CampCodes Supplier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via Supply_Management_System/admin/view_order_items.php?id= .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36535 | Insecure permissions in meshery v0.7.51 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36535</link><description>Insecure permissions in meshery v0.7.51 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41550 | CampCodes Supplier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via Supply_Management_System/admin/view_invoice_items.php?id= .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41550</link><description>CampCodes Supplier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via Supply_Management_System/admin/view_invoice_items.php?id= .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36536 | Insecure permissions in fabedge v0.8.1 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36536</link><description>Insecure permissions in fabedge v0.8.1 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36537 | Insecure permissions in cert-manager v1.14.4 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36537</link><description>Insecure permissions in cert-manager v1.14.4 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36538 | Insecure permissions in chaos-mesh v2.6.3 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36538</link><description>Insecure permissions in chaos-mesh v2.6.3 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40137 | Dolibarr ERP CRM before 19.0.2-php8.2 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Computed field parameter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40137</link><description>Dolibarr ERP CRM before 19.0.2-php8.2 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Computed field parameter under the Users Module Setup function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40495 | A vulnerability was discovered in Linksys Router E2500 with firmware 2.0.00, allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40495</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in Linksys Router E2500 with firmware 2.0.00, allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via the hnd_parentalctrl_unblock function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21684 | There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link><description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41672 | DuckDB: sniff_csv provides filesystem access even when enable_external_access is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41672</link><description>DuckDB is a SQL database management system. In versions 1.0.0 and prior, content in filesystem is accessible for reading using `sniff_csv`, even with `enable_external_access=false`. This vulnerability provides an attacker with access to filesystem even when access is expected to be disabled and other similar functions do NOT provide access. There seem to be two vectors to this vulnerability. First, access to files that should otherwise not be allowed. Second, the content from a file can be read (e.g. `/etc/hosts`, `proc/self/environ`, etc) even though that doesn't seem to be the intent of the sniff_csv function. A fix for this issue is available in commit c9b7c98aa0e1cd7363fe8bb8543a95f38e980d8a and is expected to be part of version 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41667 | OpenAM FreeMarker template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41667</link><description>OpenAM is an open access management solution. In versions 15.0.3 and prior, the `getCustomLoginUrlTemplate` method in RealmOAuth2ProviderSettings.java is vulnerable to template injection due to its usage of user input. Although the developer intended to implement a custom URL for handling login to override the default PingOne Advanced Identity Cloud login page,they did not restrict the `CustomLoginUrlTemplate`, allowing it to be set freely. Commit fcb8432aa77d5b2e147624fe954cb150c568e0b8 introduces `TemplateClassResolver.SAFER_RESOLVER` to disable the resolution of commonly exploited classes in FreeMarker template injection. As of time of publication, this fix is expected to be part of version 15.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41666 | The Argo CD web terminal session does not handle the revocation of user permissions properly.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41666</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. Argo CD has a Web-based terminal that allows users to get a shell inside a running pod, just as they would with kubectl exec. Starting in version 2.6.0, when the administrator enables this function and grants permission to the user `p, role:myrole, exec, create, */*, allow`, even if the user revokes this permission, the user can still perform operations in the container, as long as the user keeps the terminal view open for a long time. Although the token expiration and revocation of the user are fixed, however, the fix does not address the situation of revocation of only user `p, role:myrole, exec, create, */*, allow` permissions, which may still lead to the leakage of sensitive information. A patch for this vulnerability has been released in Argo CD versions 2.11.7, 2.10.16, and 2.9.21.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37533 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37533</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could disclose sensitive user information to another user with physical access to the machine.  IBM X-Force ID:  294727.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41110 | Moby authz zero length regression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41110</link><description>Moby is an open-source project created by Docker for software containerization. A security vulnerability has been detected in certain versions of Docker Engine, which could allow an attacker to bypass authorization plugins (AuthZ) under specific circumstances. The base likelihood of this being exploited is low.

Using a specially-crafted API request, an Engine API client could make the daemon forward the request or response to an authorization plugin without the body. In certain circumstances, the authorization plugin may allow a request which it would have otherwise denied if the body had been forwarded to it.

A security issue was discovered In 2018, where an attacker could bypass AuthZ plugins using a specially crafted API request. This could lead to unauthorized actions, including privilege escalation. Although this issue was fixed in Docker Engine v18.09.1 in January 2019, the fix was not carried forward to later major versions, resulting in a regression. Anyone who depends on authorization plugins that introspect the request and/or response body to make access control decisions is potentially impacted.

Docker EE v19.03.x and all versions of Mirantis Container Runtime are not vulnerable.

docker-ce v27.1.1 containes patches to fix the vulnerability. Patches have also been merged into the master, 19.0, 20.0, 23.0, 24.0, 25.0, 26.0, and 26.1 release branches. If one is unable to upgrade immediately, avoid using AuthZ plugins and/or restrict access to the Docker API to trusted parties, following the principle of least privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41662 | VNote vulnerable to Markdown XSS, which leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41662</link><description>VNote is a note-taking platform. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Markdown rendering functionality of versions 3.18.1 and prior of the VNote note-taking application. This vulnerability allows the injection and execution of arbitrary JavaScript code through which remote code execution can be achieved. A patch for this issue is available at commit f1af78573a0ef51d6ef6a0bc4080cddc8f30a545. Other mitigation strategies include implementing rigorous input sanitization for all Markdown content and utilizing a secure Markdown parser that appropriately escapes or strips potentially dangerous content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36539 | Insecure permissions in contour v1.28.3 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36539</link><description>Insecure permissions in contour v1.28.3 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36540 | Insecure permissions in external-secrets v0.9.16 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36540</link><description>Insecure permissions in external-secrets v0.9.16 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36541 | Insecure permissions in logging-operator v4.6.0 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36541</link><description>Insecure permissions in logging-operator v4.6.0 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40422 | The snapshot_path parameter in the /api/get-browser-snapshot endpoint in stitionai devika v1 is susceptible to a path traversal attack. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40422</link><description>The snapshot_path parameter in the /api/get-browser-snapshot endpoint in stitionai devika v1 is susceptible to a path traversal attack. An attacker can manipulate the snapshot_path parameter to traverse directories and access sensitive files on the server. This can potentially lead to unauthorized access to critical system files and compromise the confidentiality and integrity of the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7079 | Openshift-console: unauthenticated installation of helm charts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7079</link><description>A flaw was found in the Openshift console. The /API/helm/verify endpoint is tasked to fetch and verify the installation of a Helm chart from a URI that is remote HTTP/HTTPS or local. Access to this endpoint is gated by the authHandlerWithUser() middleware function. Contrary to its name, this middleware function does not verify the validity of the user's credentials. As a result, unauthenticated users can access this endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40575 | An issue in Huawei Technologies opengauss (openGauss 5.0.0 build) v.7.3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the modif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40575</link><description>An issue in Huawei Technologies opengauss (openGauss 5.0.0 build) v.7.3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the modification of table attributes</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31970 | AdTran SRG 834-5 HDC17600021F1 devices (with SmartOS 11.1.1.1 and fixed in Version 12.1.3.1) have SSH enabled by default, accessible both ov...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31970</link><description>AdTran SRG 834-5 HDC17600021F1 devices (with SmartOS 11.1.1.1 and fixed in Version 12.1.3.1) have SSH enabled by default, accessible both over the LAN and the Internet. During a window of time when the device is being set up, it uses a default username and password combination of admin/admin with root-level privileges. An attacker can exploit this window to gain unauthorized root access by either modifying the existing admin account or creating a new account with equivalent privileges. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7069 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7069</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /employee_gatepass/classes/Master.php?f=delete_department. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272351.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22444 | A vulnerability within the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow a remote attacker to conduct a refl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22444</link><description>A vulnerability within the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow a remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in a victims browser in the context of the affected interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22443 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22443</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a server-side prototype pollution attack. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31971 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities on AdTran NetVanta 3120 18.01.01.00.E devices allow remote attackers to inject ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31971</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities on AdTran NetVanta 3120 18.01.01.00.E devices allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript, as demonstrated by /mainPassword.html, /processIdentity.html, /public.html, /dhcp.html, /private.html, /hostname.html, /connectivity.html, /NetworkMonitor.html, /trafficMonitoringConfig.html, and /wizardMain.html.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31977 | Adtran 834-5 11.1.0.101-202106231430, and fixed as of SmartOS Version 12.5.5.1, devices allow OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31977</link><description>Adtran 834-5 11.1.0.101-202106231430, and fixed as of SmartOS Version 12.5.5.1, devices allow OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters to the Ping or Traceroute utility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39345 | AdTran 834-5 HDC17600021F1 (SmartOS 11.1.1.1) devices enable the SSH service by default and have a hidden, undocumented, hard-coded support ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39345</link><description>AdTran 834-5 HDC17600021F1 (SmartOS 11.1.1.1) devices enable the SSH service by default and have a hidden, undocumented, hard-coded support account whose password is based on the devices MAC address. All of the devices internet interfaces share a similar MAC address that only varies in their final octet. This allows network-adjacent attackers to derive the support user's SSH password by decrementing the final octet of the connected gateway address or via the BSSID. An attacker can then execute arbitrary OS commands with root-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41914 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41914</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an administrative user of the interface. A successful exploit allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in a victim's browser in the context of the affected interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7068 | SourceCodester Insurance Management System update_sub_category cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7068</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Insurance Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Script/admin/core/update_sub_category. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272349 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45249 | Remote command execution due to use of default passwords. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45249</link><description>Remote command execution due to use of default passwords. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.0.1-61, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.1.1-71, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.2.1-69, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.3.1-53, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.4.4-132.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6096 | Unsafe Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6096</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Reporting versions prior to 18.1.24.709, a code execution attack is possible through object injection via an insecure type resolution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7067 | kirilkirkov Ecommerce-Laravel-Bootstrap Cart.php getCartProductsIds deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7067</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kirilkirkov Ecommerce-Laravel-Bootstrap up to 1f1097a3448ce8ec53e034ea0f70b8e2a0e64a87. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function getCartProductsIds of the file app/Cart.php. The manipulation of the argument laraCart leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is a02111a674ab49f65018b31da3011b1e396f59b1. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272348.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6327 | Progress Telerik Report Server Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6327</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q2 (10.1.24.709), a remote code execution attack is possible through an insecure deserialization vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3896 | Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 3.2.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Gallery Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3896</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the the Gallery title field in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5818 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.980 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Magazine Grid/Slider Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5818</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Magazine Grid/Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.980 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6896 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.0.96.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6896</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.96.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7066 | F-logic DataCube3 HTTP POST Request config_time_sync.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7066</link><description>A vulnerability was found in F-logic DataCube3 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/config_time_sync.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ntp_server leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272347.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7065 | Spina CMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7065</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Spina CMS up to 2.18.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/pages/. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272346 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3297 | Session establishment lock-up during replay of CASE Sigma1 messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3297</link><description>An issue in the Certificate Authenticated Session Establishment (CASE) protocol for establishing secure sessions between two devices, as implemented in the Matter protocol versions before Matter 1.1 allows an attacker to replay manipulated CASE Sigma1 messages to make the device unresponsive until the device is power-cycled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3454 | In-Fabric Matter Cluster Attribute Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3454</link><description>An implementation issue in the Connectivity Standards Alliance Matter 1.2 protocol as used in the connectedhomeip SDK allows a third party to disclose information about devices part of the same fabric (footprinting), even though the protocol is designed to prevent access to such information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48362 | Apache Drill: XXE Vulnerability in XML Format Reader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48362</link><description>XXE in the XML Format Plugin in Apache Drill version 1.19.0 and greater allows a user to read any file on a remote file system or execute commands via a malicious XML file.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.21.2, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39676 | Apache Pinot: Unauthorized endpoint exposed sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39676</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Pinot.

This issue affects Apache Pinot: from 0.1 before 1.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.0.0 and configure RBAC, which fixes the issue.

Details: 

When using a request to path “/appconfigs” to the controller, it can lead to the disclosure of sensitive information such as system information (e.g. arch, os version), environment information (e.g. maxHeapSize) and Pinot configurations (e.g. zookeeper path). This issue was addressed by the  Role-based Access Control https://docs.pinot.apache.org/operators/tutorials/authentication/basic-auth-access-control , so that /appConfigs` and all other APIs can be access controlled. Only authorized users have access to it. Note the user needs to add the admin role accordingly to the RBAC guide to control access to this endpoint, and in the future version of Pinot, a default admin role is planned to be added.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6874 | macidn punycode buffer overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6874</link><description>libcurl's URL API function
[curl_url_get()](https://curl.se/libcurl/c/curl_url_get.html) offers punycode
conversions, to and from IDN. Asking to convert a name that is exactly 256
bytes, libcurl ends up reading outside of a stack based buffer when built to
use the *macidn* IDN backend. The conversion function then fills up the
provided buffer exactly - but does not null terminate the string.

This flaw can lead to stack contents accidently getting returned as part of
the converted string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6197 | freeing stack buffer in utf8asn1str</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6197</link><description>libcurl's ASN1 parser has this utf8asn1str() function used for parsing an ASN.1 UTF-8 string. Itcan detect an invalid field and return error. Unfortunately, when doing so it also invokes `free()` on a 4 byte localstack buffer.  Most modern malloc implementations detect this error and immediately abort. Some however accept the input pointer and add that memory to its list of available chunks. This leads to the overwriting of nearby stack memory. The content of the overwrite is decided by the `free()` implementation; likely to be memory pointers and a set of flags.  The most likely outcome of exploting this flaw is a crash, although it cannot be ruled out that more serious results can be had in special circumstances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6930 | WP Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bookingform Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6930</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'type' attribute within the plugin's bookingform shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 10.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32471 | Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32471</link><description>Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read contents of stack memory and use this information for further exploits.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32466 | Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with hig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32466</link><description>Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to exposure of some UEFI code, leading to arbitrary code execution or escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6553 | WP Meteor Website Speed Optimization Addon &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6553</link><description>The WP Meteor Website Speed Optimization Addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3.This is due to the plugin utilizing wpdesk and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6571 | Optimize Images ALT Text (alt tag) &amp;amp; names for SEO using AI &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6571</link><description>The Optimize Images ALT Text (alt tag) &amp; names for SEO using AI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1. This is due the plugin utilizing cocur and not preventing direct access to the generate-default.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6629 | All-in-One Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 3.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6629</link><description>The All-in-One Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Video shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6094 | WP ULike &amp;lt; 4.7.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6094</link><description>The WP ULike  WordPress plugin before 4.7.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6836 | Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp;amp; One Click Upsells &amp;lt;= 3.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6836</link><description>The Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp; One Click Upsells plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update multiple settings, including templates, designs, checkouts, and other plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 05:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40767 | In OpenStack Nova before 27.4.1, 28 before 28.2.1, and 29 before 29.1.1, by supplying a raw format image that is actually a crafted QCOW2 im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40767</link><description>In OpenStack Nova before 27.4.1, 28 before 28.2.1, and 29 before 29.1.1, by supplying a raw format image that is actually a crafted QCOW2 image with a backing file path or VMDK flat image with a descriptor file path, an authenticated user may convince systems to return a copy of the referenced file's contents from the server, resulting in unauthorized access to potentially sensitive data. All Nova deployments are affected. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-47951 and CVE-2024-32498.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3246 | LiteSpeed Cache &amp;lt;= 6.2.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3246</link><description>The LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the token setting and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 03:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5861 | WP Easy Pay (Free) &amp;lt;= 4.2.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Service Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5861</link><description>The WP EasyPay – Square for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of datadue to a missing capability check on the wpep_square_disconnect() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disconnect square.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6750 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6750</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete post meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6751 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6751</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete post meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6752 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6752</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wp_name’ parameter in the 'wpw_auto_poster_map_wordpress_post_type' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6753 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6753</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘mapTypes’ parameter in the 'wpw_auto_poster_map_wordpress_post_type' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6754 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Meta Update via wpw_auto_poster_update_tweet_template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6754</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data to a missing capability check on the ‘wpw_auto_poster_update_tweet_template’ function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary post metadata.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6755 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6755</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the ‘wpw_auto_poster_quick_delete_multiple’ function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6756 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6756</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'wpw_auto_poster_get_image_path' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. An attacker can use CVE-2024-6754 to exploit with subscriber-level access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7027 | WooCommerce - PDF Vouchers &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Authentication Bypass to Voucher Vendor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7027</link><description>The WooCommerce - PDF Vouchers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 4.9.3. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during a QR code login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing Voucher Vendor user on the site, if they have access to the user id.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>