<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-7090 | Sudo: improper handling of ipa_hostname leads to privilege mismanagement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7090</link><description>A flaw was found in sudo in the handling of ipa_hostname, where ipa_hostname from /etc/sssd/sssd.conf was not propagated in sudo. Therefore, it leads to privilege mismanagement vulnerability in applications, where client hosts retain privileges even after retracting them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49594 | An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the challenge functionality of instipod DuoUniversalKeycloakAuthenticator 1.0.7 plugin. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49594</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the challenge functionality of instipod DuoUniversalKeycloakAuthenticator 1.0.7 plugin. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An user login to Keycloak using  DuoUniversalKeycloakAuthenticator plugin triggers this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15036 | Deis Workflow Manager race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15036</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Deis Workflow Manager up to 2.3.2. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to race condition. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. Upgrading to version 2.3.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 31fe3bccbdde134a185752e53380330d16053f7f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248847. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 20:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125108 | w3c online-spellchecker-py spellchecker cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in w3c online-spellchecker-py up to 20140130. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file spellchecker. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The identifier of the patch is d6c21fd8187c5db2a50425ff80694149e75d722e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-248849 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7008 | Systemd-resolved: unsigned name response in signed zone is not refused when dnssec=yes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7008</link><description>A vulnerability was found in systemd-resolved. This issue may allow systemd-resolved to accept records of DNSSEC-signed domains even when they have no signature, allowing man-in-the-middles (or the upstream DNS resolver) to manipulate records.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36769 | The Widget Settings Importer/Exporter Plugin  for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wp_ajax_import_widget_datap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36769</link><description>The Widget Settings Importer/Exporter Plugin  for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wp_ajax_import_widget_dataparameter AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6744 | The Divi theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'et_pb_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6744</link><description>The Divi theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'et_pb_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied custom field data. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5962 | ioLogik E1200 Series: Weak Cryptographic Algorithm Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5962</link><description>A weak cryptographic algorithm vulnerability has been identified in ioLogik E1200 Series firmware versions v3.3 and prior. This vulnerability can help an attacker compromise the confidentiality of sensitive data. This vulnerability may lead an attacker to get unexpected authorization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5961 | ioLogik E1200 Series: Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5961</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been identified in ioLogik E1200 Series firmware versions v3.3 and prior. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to trick a client into making an unintentional request to the web server, which will be treated as an authentic request. This vulnerability may lead an attacker to perform operations on behalf of the victimized user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6971 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in versions 1.0.8 to 1.3.9 via the 'content-dir' HTTP heade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6971</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in versions 1.0.8 to 1.3.9 via the 'content-dir' HTTP header. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include remote files on the server, resulting in code execution. NOTE: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that the target server's php.ini is configured with 'allow_url_include' set to 'on'. This feature is deprecated as of PHP 7.4 and is disabled by default, but can still be explicitly enabled in later versions of PHP.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6972 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 via the 'content-backu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6972</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 via the 'content-backups' and 'content-name', 'content-manifest', or 'content-bmitmp' and 'content-identy' HTTP headers. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, including the wp-config.php file, which can make site takeover and remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7002 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to OS Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9  via the 'url' p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7002</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to OS Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9  via the 'url' parameter. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to execute arbitrary commands on the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51386 | Sandbox Accounts for Events vulnerable to privilege escalation to read running events data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51386</link><description>Sandbox Accounts for Events provides multiple, temporary AWS accounts to a number of authenticated users simultaneously via a browser-based GUI. Authenticated users could potentially read data from the events table by sending request payloads to the events API, collecting information on planned events, timeframes, budgets and owner email addresses. This data access may allow users to get insights into upcoming events and join events which they have not been invited to. This issue has been patched in version 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 22:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50928 |  sandbox-accounts-for-events security misconfiguration leads to budget exceed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50928</link><description>"Sandbox Accounts for Events" provides multiple, temporary AWS accounts to a number of authenticated users simultaneously via a browser-based GUI. Authenticated users could potentially claim and access empty AWS accounts by sending request payloads to the account API containing non-existent event ids and self-defined budget &amp; duration. This issue only affects cleaned AWS accounts, it is not possible to access AWS accounts in use or existing data/infrastructure. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51449 | Make the `/file` secure against file traversal attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51449</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package that allows you to quickly build a demo or web application for your machine learning model, API, or any arbitary Python function. Versions of `gradio` prior to 4.11.0 contained a vulnerability in the `/file` route which made them susceptible to file traversal attacks in which an attacker could access arbitrary files on a machine running a Gradio app with a public URL (e.g. if the demo was created with `share=True`, or on Hugging Face Spaces) if they knew the path of files to look for. This issue has been patched in version 4.11.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51451 | SSRF in symbolicator via invalid protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51451</link><description>Symbolicator is a service used in Sentry. Starting in Symbolicator version 0.3.3 and prior to version 21.12.1, an attacker could make Symbolicator send GET HTTP requests to arbitrary URLs with internal IP addresses by using an invalid protocol. The responses of those requests could be exposed via Symbolicator's API. In affected Sentry instances, the data could be exposed through the Sentry API and user interface if the attacker has a registered account. The issue has been fixed in Symbolicator release 23.12.1, Sentry self-hosted release 23.12.1, and has already been mitigated on sentry.io on December 18, 2023. If updating is not possible, some other mitigations are available. One may disable JS processing by toggling the option `Allow JavaScript Source Fetching` in `Organization Settings &gt; Security &amp; Privacy` and/or disable all untrusted public repositories under `Project Settings &gt; Debug Files`. Alternatively, if JavaScript and native symbolication are not required, disable Symbolicator completely in `config.yml`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 21:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51651 | Potential URI resolution path traversal in the AWS SDK for PHP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51651</link><description>AWS SDK for PHP is the Amazon Web Services software development kit for PHP. Within the scope of requests to S3 object keys and/or prefixes containing a Unix double-dot, a URI path traversal is possible. The issue exists in the `buildEndpoint` method in the RestSerializer component of the AWS SDK for PHP v3 prior to 3.288.1. The `buildEndpoint` method relies on the Guzzle Psr7 UriResolver utility, which strips dot segments from the request path in accordance with RFC 3986. Under certain conditions, this could lead to an arbitrary object being accessed. This issue has been patched in version 3.288.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 21:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51650 | Unauthorized access vulnerability on three interfaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51650</link><description>Hertzbeat is an open source, real-time monitoring system. Prior to version 1.4.1, Spring Boot permission configuration issues caused unauthorized access vulnerabilities to three interfaces. This could result in disclosure of sensitive server information. Version 1.4.1 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51387 | Expression Injection Vulnerability in Hertzbeat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51387</link><description>Hertzbeat is an open source, real-time monitoring system. Hertzbeat uses aviatorscript to evaluate alert expressions. The alert expressions are supposed to be some simple expressions. However, due to improper sanitization for alert expressions in version prior to 1.4.1, a malicious user can use a crafted alert expression to execute any command on hertzbeat server. A malicious user who has access to alert define function can execute any command in hertzbeat instance. This issue is fixed in version 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50731 | MindsDB has arbitrary file write in file.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50731</link><description>MindsDB is a SQL Server for artificial intelligence. Prior to version 23.11.4.1, the `put` method in `mindsdb/mindsdb/api/http/namespaces/file.py` does not validate the user-controlled name value, which is used in a temporary file name, which is afterwards opened for writing on lines 122-125, which leads to path injection. Later in the method, the temporary directory is deleted on line 151, but since we can write outside of the directory using the path injection vulnerability, the potentially dangerous file is not deleted. Arbitrary file contents can be written due to `f.write(chunk)` on line 125. Mindsdb does check later on line 149 in the `save_file` method in `file-controller.py` which calls the `_handle_source` method in `file_handler.py` if a file is of one of the types `csv`, `json`, `parquet`, `xls`, or `xlsx`. However, since the check happens after the file has already been written, the files will still exist (and will not be removed due to the path injection described earlier), just the `_handle_source` method will return an error. The same user-controlled source source is used also in another path injection sink on line 138. This leads to another path injection, which allows an attacker to delete any `zip` or `tar.gz` files on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50730 | Grackle has StackOverflowError in GraphQL query processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50730</link><description>Grackle is a GraphQL server written in functional Scala, built on the Typelevel stack. The GraphQL specification requires that GraphQL fragments must not form cycles, either directly or indirectly. Prior to Grackle version 0.18.0, that requirement wasn't checked, and queries with cyclic fragments would have been accepted for type checking and compilation. The attempted compilation of such fragments would result in a JVM `StackOverflowError` being thrown. Some knowledge of an applications GraphQL schema would be required to construct such a query, however no knowledge of any application-specific performance or other behavioural characteristics would be needed.

Grackle uses the cats-parse library for parsing GraphQL queries. Prior to version 0.18.0, Grackle made use of the cats-parse `recursive` operator. However, `recursive` is not currently stack safe. `recursive` was used in three places in the parser: nested selection sets, nested input values (lists and objects), and nested list type declarations. Consequently, queries with deeply nested selection sets, input values or list types could be constructed which exploited this, causing a JVM `StackOverflowException` to be thrown during parsing. Because this happens very early in query processing, no specific knowledge of an applications GraphQL schema would be required to construct such a query.

The possibility of small queries resulting in stack overflow is a potential denial of service vulnerability. This potentially affects all applications using Grackle which have untrusted users. Both stack overflow issues have been resolved in the v0.18.0 release of Grackle. As a workaround, users could interpose a sanitizing layer in between untrusted input and Grackle query processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50924 | Stored XSS in Overview and Output fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50924</link><description>Englesystem is a shift planning system for chaos events. Engelsystem prior to v3.4.1 performed insufficient validation of user supplied data for the DECT number, mobile number, and work-log comment fields. The values of those fields would be displayed in corresponding log overviews, allowing the injection and execution of Javascript code in another user's context. This vulnerability enables an authenticated user to inject Javascript into other user's sessions. The injected JS will be executed during normal usage of the system when viewing, e.g., overview pages. This issue has been fixed in version 3.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50727 | Resque vulnerable to reflected XSS in Queue Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50727</link><description>Resque is a Redis-backed Ruby library for creating background jobs, placing them on multiple queues, and processing them later. Reflected XSS issue occurs when /queues is appended with /"&gt;&lt;svg%20onload=alert(domain)&gt;. This issue has been patched in version 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50725 | Resque vulnerable to reflected XSS in resque-web failed and queues lists</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50725</link><description>Resque is a Redis-backed Ruby library for creating background jobs, placing them on multiple queues, and processing them later. The following paths in resque-web have been found to be vulnerable to reflected XSS: "/failed/?class=&lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt;" and "/queues/&gt;&lt;img src=a onerror=alert(document.cookie)&gt;". This issue has been patched in version 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50712 | Improper Neutralization of Alternate XSS Syntax in iris-web </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50712</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform aiming to help incident responders sharing technical details during investigations. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in iris-web, affecting multiple locations in versions prior to v2.3.7. The vulnerability may allow an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the application, which could then be executed when a user visits the affected locations. This could lead to unauthorized access, data theft, or other related malicious activities. An attacker need to be authenticated on the application to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version v2.3.7 of iris-web. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 19:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50147 | There is an arbitrary command execution vulnerability in the setDiagnosisCfg function of the cstecgi .cgi of the TOTOlink A3700R router devi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50147</link><description>There is an arbitrary command execution vulnerability in the setDiagnosisCfg function of the cstecgi .cgi of the TOTOlink A3700R router device in its firmware version V9.1.2u.5822_B20200513.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 19:06:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51033 | TOTOlink EX1200L V9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution via the cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51033</link><description>TOTOlink EX1200L V9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution via the cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51034 | TOTOlink EX1200L V9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution via the cstecgi.cgi UploadFirmwareFile interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51034</link><description>TOTOlink EX1200L V9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution via the cstecgi.cgi UploadFirmwareFile interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51035 | TOTOLINK EX1200L V9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution on the cstecgi.cgi NTPSyncWithHost interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51035</link><description>TOTOLINK EX1200L V9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution on the cstecgi.cgi NTPSyncWithHost interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51011 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanPriDns parameter’ of the setLan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51011</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanPriDns parameter’ of the setLanConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51012 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanGateway parameter’ of the setLa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51012</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanGateway parameter’ of the setLanConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51013 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanNetmask parameter’ of the setLa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51013</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanNetmask parameter’ of the setLanConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50708 | yii2-authclient vulnerable to possible timing attack on string comparison in OAuth1, OAuth2 and OpenID Connect implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50708</link><description>yii2-authclient is an extension that adds OpenID, OAuth, OAuth2 and OpenId Connect consumers for the Yii framework 2.0. In yii2-authclient prior to version 2.2.15, the Oauth1/2 `state` and OpenID Connect `nonce` is vulnerable for a `timing attack` since it is compared via regular string comparison (instead of `Yii::$app-&gt;getSecurity()-&gt;compareString()`). Version 2.2.15 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50714 | The Oauth2 PKCE implementation is vulnerable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50714</link><description>yii2-authclient is an extension that adds OpenID, OAuth, OAuth2 and OpenId Connect consumers for the Yii framework 2.0. In yii2-authclient prior to version 2.2.15, the Oauth2 PKCE implementation is vulnerable in 2 ways. First, the `authCodeVerifier` should be removed after usage (similar to `authState`). Second, there is a risk for a `downgrade attack` if PKCE is being relied on for CSRF protection. Version 2.2.15 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51014 | TOTOLINK EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanSecDns parameter’ of the setLan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51014</link><description>TOTOLINK EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanSecDns parameter’ of the setLanConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51015 | TOTOLINX EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution in the ‘enable parameter’ of the setDmzCfg interface o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51015</link><description>TOTOLINX EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution in the ‘enable parameter’ of the setDmzCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51016 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the setRebootScheCfg interface of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51016</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the setRebootScheCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51017 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanIp parameter’ of the setLanConf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51017</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the lanIp parameter’ of the setLanConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51018 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘opmode’ parameter of the setWiFiA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51018</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘opmode’ parameter of the setWiFiApConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51019 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘key5g’ parameter of the setWiFiEx...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51019</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘key5g’ parameter of the setWiFiExtenderConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51020 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘langType’ parameter of the setLan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51020</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘langType’ parameter of the setLanguageCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51021 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘merge’ parameter of the setRptWiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51021</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘merge’ parameter of the setRptWizardCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51022 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘langFlag’ parameter of the setLan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51022</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘langFlag’ parameter of the setLanguageCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51023 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution in the ‘host_time’ parameter of the NTPSyncWithHost in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51023</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution in the ‘host_time’ parameter of the NTPSyncWithHost interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51024 | TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘tz’ parameter of the setNtpCfg in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51024</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T v9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘tz’ parameter of the setNtpCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43088 | Dell Client BIOS contains a pre-boot direct memory access (DMA) vulnerability. An authenticated attacker with physical access to the system ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43088</link><description>Dell Client BIOS contains a pre-boot direct memory access (DMA) vulnerability. An authenticated attacker with physical access to the system may potentially exploit this vulnerability in order to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51025 | TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to an unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘admuser’ parameter of the setP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51025</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to an unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘admuser’ parameter of the setPasswordCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51026 | TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘hour’ parameter of the setRebootS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51026</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘hour’ parameter of the setRebootScheCfg interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51027 | TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘apcliAuthMode’ parameter of the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51027</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the ‘apcliAuthMode’ parameter of the setWiFiExtenderConfig interface of the cstecgi .cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 18:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39251 | Dell BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A local malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39251</link><description>Dell BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A local malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability in order to corrupt memory on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 17:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51028 | TOTOLINK EX1800T 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the apcliChannel parameter of the setWi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51028</link><description>TOTOLINK EX1800T 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary command execution in the apcliChannel parameter of the setWiFiExtenderConfig interface of the cstecgi.cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 17:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50259 | Blind SSRF in /home/testslack endpoint </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50259</link><description>Medusa is an automatic video library manager for TV shows. Versions prior to 1.0.19 are vulnerable to unauthenticated blind server-side request forgery (SSRF). The `testslack` request handler in `medusa/server/web/home/handler.py` does not validate the user-controlled `slack_webhook` variable and passes it to the `notifiers.slack_notifier.test_notify` method, then `_notify_slack` and finally `_send_slack` method,  which sends a POST request to the user-controlled URL on line 103 in `/medusa/notifiers/slack.py`, which leads to a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF). This issue allows for crafting POST requests on behalf of the Medusa server. Version 1.0.19 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 17:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50258 | Blind SSRF in `/home/testdiscord` endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50258</link><description>Medusa is an automatic video library manager for TV shows. Versions prior to 1.0.19 are vulnerable to unauthenticated blind server-side request forgery (SSRF). The `testDiscord` request handler in `medusa/server/web/home/handler.py` does not validate the user-controlled `discord_webhook` variable and passes it to the `notifiers.discord_notifier.test_notify` method, then `_notify_discord` and finally `_send_discord_msg` method,  which sends a POST request to the user-controlled URL on line 64 in `/medusa/notifiers/discord.py`, which leads to a blind server-side request forgery. This issue allows for crafting POST requests on behalf of the Medusa server. Version 1.0.19 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 17:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50254 | Deepin Reader RCE vulnerability due to a design flaw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50254</link><description>Deepin Linux's default document reader `deepin-reader` software suffers from a serious vulnerability in versions prior to 6.0.7 due to a design flaw that leads to remote command execution via crafted docx document. This is a file overwrite vulnerability. Remote code execution (RCE) can be achieved by overwriting files like .bash_rc, .bash_login, etc. RCE will be triggered when the user opens the terminal. Version 6.0.7 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51649 | Nautobot missing object-level permissions enforcement when running Job Buttons</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51649</link><description>Nautobot is a Network Source of Truth and Network Automation Platform built as a web application atop the Django Python framework with a PostgreSQL or MySQL database. When submitting a Job to run via a Job Button, only the model-level `extras.run_job` permission is checked (i.e., does the user have permission to run Jobs in general). Object-level permissions (i.e., does the user have permission to run this specific Job?) are not enforced by the URL/view used in this case. A user with permissions to run even a single Job can actually run all configured JobButton Jobs. Fix will be available in Nautobot 1.6.8 and 2.1.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51448 | SQL Injection vulnerability when managing SNMP Notification Receivers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51448</link><description>Cacti provides an operational monitoring and fault management framework. Version 1.2.25 has a Blind SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability within the SNMP Notification Receivers feature in the file `‘managers.php’`. An authenticated attacker with the “Settings/Utilities” permission can send a crafted HTTP GET request to the endpoint `‘/cacti/managers.php’` with an SQLi payload in the `‘selected_graphs_array’` HTTP GET parameter. As of time of publication, no patched versions exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50250 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability when Import xml template file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50250</link><description>Cacti is an open source operational monitoring and fault management framework. A reflection cross-site scripting vulnerability was discovered in version 1.2.25. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to perform actions on behalf of other users. The vulnerability is found in `templates_import.php.` When uploading an xml template file, if the XML file does not pass the check, the server will give a JavaScript pop-up prompt, which contains unfiltered xml template file name, resulting in XSS. An attacker exploiting this vulnerability could execute actions on behalf of other users. This ability to impersonate users could lead to unauthorized changes to settings. As of time of publication, no patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49792 | Bruteforce protection can be bypassed with misconfigured proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49792</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. In Nextcloud Server prior to versions 26.0.9 and 27.1.4; as well as Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to versions 23.0.12.13, 24.0.12.9, 25.0.13.4, 26.0.9, and 27.1.4; when a (reverse) proxy is configured as trusted proxy the server could be tricked into reading a wrong remote address for an attacker, allowing them executing authentication attempts than intended. Nextcloud Server versions 26.0.9 and 27.1.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 23.0.12.13, 24.0.12.9, 25.0.13.4, 26.0.9, and 27.1.4 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49790 | App PIN code can be bypassed in Nextcloud Files iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49790</link><description>The Nextcloud iOS Files app allows users of iOS to interact with Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to version 4.9.2, the application can be used without providing the 4 digit PIN code. Nextcloud iOS Files app should be upgraded to 4.9.2 to receive the patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49791 | Workflows do not require password confirmation on API level</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49791</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. In Nextcloud Server prior to versions 26.0.9 and 27.1.4; as well as Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to versions 23.0.12.13, 24.0.12.9, 25.0.13.4, 26.0.9, and 27.1.4; when an attacker manages to get access to an active session of another user via another way, they could delete and modify workflows by sending calls directly to the API bypassing the password confirmation shown in the UI. Nextcloud Server versions 26.0.9 and 27.1.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 23.0.12.13, 24.0.12.9, 25.0.13.4, 26.0.9, and 27.1.4 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51662 | Snowflake Connector .NET does not properly check the Certificate Revocation List (CRL)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51662</link><description>The Snowflake .NET driver provides an interface to the Microsoft .NET open source software framework for developing applications. Snowflake recently received a report about a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector .NET where the checks against the Certificate Revocation List (CRL) were not performed where the insecureMode flag was set to false, which is the default setting. The vulnerability affects versions between 2.0.25 and 2.1.4 (inclusive). Snowflake fixed the issue in version 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49085 | Cacti SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49085</link><description>Cacti provides an operational monitoring and fault management framework. In versions 1.2.25 and prior, it is possible to execute arbitrary SQL code through the `pollers.php` script. An authorized user may be able to execute arbitrary SQL code. The vulnerable component is the `pollers.php`. Impact of the vulnerability - arbitrary SQL code execution. As of time of publication, a patch does not appear to exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49088 | Cacti has incomplete fix for CVE-2023-39515</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49088</link><description>Cacti is an open source operational monitoring and fault management framework. The fix applied for CVE-2023-39515 in version 1.2.25 is incomplete as it enables an adversary to have a victim browser execute malicious code when a victim user hovers their mouse over the malicious data source path in `data_debug.php`. To perform the cross-site scripting attack, the adversary needs to be an authorized cacti user with the following permissions: `General Administration&gt;Sites/Devices/Data`. The victim of this attack could be any account with permissions to view `http://&lt;HOST&gt;/cacti/data_debug.php`. As of time of publication, no complete fix has been included in Cacti.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42017 | IBM Planning Analytics file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42017</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 could allow a remote attacker to upload arbitrary files, caused by the improper validation of file extensions.  By sending a specially crafted HTTP request, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to upload a malicious script, which could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the vulnerable system.  IBM X-Force ID:  265567.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42465 | Sudo before 1.9.15 might allow row hammer attacks (for authentication bypass or privilege escalation) because application logic sometimes is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42465</link><description>Sudo before 1.9.15 might allow row hammer attacks (for authentication bypass or privilege escalation) because application logic sometimes is based on not equaling an error value (instead of equaling a success value), and because the values do not resist flips of a single bit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48670 | Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs version 3.14.1 and prior versions contain a privilege escalation vulnerability in the installer. A local low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48670</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs version 3.14.1 and prior versions contain a privilege escalation vulnerability in the installer. A local low privileged authenticated attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary executable on the operating system with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45165 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45165</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2 and 7.3 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the AIX SMB client to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267963.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45957 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin/AdminRequestSqlController.php of thirty bees before 1.5.0 allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45957</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin/AdminRequestSqlController.php of thirty bees before 1.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web script or HTML via $e-&gt;getMessage() error mishandling.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48704 | Unauthenticated heap buffer overflow in Gorrila codec decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48704</link><description>ClickHouse is an open-source column-oriented database management system that allows generating analytical data reports in real-time. A heap buffer overflow issue was discovered in ClickHouse server. An attacker could send a specially crafted payload to the native interface exposed by default on port 9000/tcp, triggering a bug in the decompression logic of Gorilla codec that crashes the ClickHouse server process. This attack does not require authentication. This issue has been addressed in ClickHouse Cloud version 23.9.2.47551 and ClickHouse versions 23.10.5.20, 23.3.18.15, 23.8.8.20, and 23.9.6.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39337 | Permission bypass due to incorrect configuration in github.com/dromara/hertzbeat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39337</link><description>Hertzbeat is an open source, real-time monitoring system with custom-monitoring, high performance cluster, prometheus-like and agentless. Hertzbeat versions 1.20 and prior have a permission bypass vulnerability. System authentication can be bypassed and invoke interfaces without authorization. Version 1.2.1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51661 | Filesystem sandbox not enforced in wasmer-cli</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51661</link><description>Wasmer is a WebAssembly runtime that enables containers to run anywhere: from Desktop to the Cloud, Edge and even the browser. Wasm programs can access the filesystem outside of the sandbox. Service providers running untrusted Wasm code on Wasmer can unexpectedly expose the host filesystem. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7076 | slawkens MyAAC bugtracker.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in slawkens MyAAC up to 0.8.13. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file system/pages/bugtracker.php. The manipulation of the argument bug[2]['subject']/bug[2]['text']/report['subject'] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 0.8.14 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 83a91ec540072d319dd338abff45f8d5ebf48190. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248848.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 14:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7075 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System checkout.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7075</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /main/checkout.php. The manipulation of the argument pt leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248846 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 12:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49391 | An issue was discovered in free5GC version 3.3.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) on A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49391</link><description>An issue was discovered in free5GC version 3.3.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) on AMF component via crafted NGAP message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 10:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50569 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cacti v1.2.25, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges when uploading an xml te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50569</link><description>Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cacti v1.2.25, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges when uploading an xml template file via templates_import.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 10:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49356 | A stack buffer overflow vulnerability in MP3Gain v1.6.2 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via the WriteMP3GainAPETag function ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49356</link><description>A stack buffer overflow vulnerability in MP3Gain v1.6.2 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via the WriteMP3GainAPETag function at apetag.c:592.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43116 | A symbolic link following vulnerability in Buildkite Elastic CI for AWS versions prior to 6.7.1 and 5.22.5 allows the buildkite-agent user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43116</link><description>A symbolic link following vulnerability in Buildkite Elastic CI for AWS versions prior to 6.7.1 and 5.22.5 allows the buildkite-agent user to change ownership of arbitrary directories via the PIPELINE_PATH variable in the fix-buildkite-agent-builds-permissions script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43741 | A time-of-check-time-of-use race condition vulnerability in Buildkite Elastic CI for AWS versions prior to 6.7.1 and 5.22.5 allows the build...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43741</link><description>A time-of-check-time-of-use race condition vulnerability in Buildkite Elastic CI for AWS versions prior to 6.7.1 and 5.22.5 allows the buildkite-agent user to bypass a symbolic link check for the PIPELINE_PATH variable in the fix-buildkite-agent-builds-permissions script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7059 | SourceCodester School Visitor Log e-Book log-book.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7059</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Visitor Log e-Book 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file log-book.php. The manipulation of the argument Full Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248750 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 05:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7058 | SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7058</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument page leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248749 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24609 | Matrix SSL 4.x through 4.6.0 and Rambus TLS Toolkit have a length-subtraction integer overflow for Client Hello Pre-Shared Key extension par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24609</link><description>Matrix SSL 4.x through 4.6.0 and Rambus TLS Toolkit have a length-subtraction integer overflow for Client Hello Pre-Shared Key extension parsing in the TLS 1.3 server. An attacked device calculates an SHA-2 hash over at least 65 KB (in RAM). With a large number of crafted TLS messages, the CPU becomes heavily loaded. This occurs in tls13VerifyBinder and tls13TranscriptHashUpdate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 03:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7057 | code-projects Faculty Management System yearlevel.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7057</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Faculty Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/pages/yearlevel.php. The manipulation of the argument Year Level/Section leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248744.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 03:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47532 | FileRun 20220519 allows SQL Injection via the "dir" parameter in a /?module=users&amp;section=cpanel&amp;page=list request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47532</link><description>FileRun 20220519 allows SQL Injection via the "dir" parameter in a /?module=users&amp;section=cpanel&amp;page=list request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 03:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7056 | code-projects Faculty Management System subjects.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7056</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Faculty Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/pages/subjects.php. The manipulation of the argument Description/Units leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248743.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 03:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51713 | make_ftp_cmd in main.c in ProFTPD before 1.3.8a has a one-byte out-of-bounds read, and daemon crash, because of mishandling of quote/backsla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51713</link><description>make_ftp_cmd in main.c in ProFTPD before 1.3.8a has a one-byte out-of-bounds read, and daemon crash, because of mishandling of quote/backslash semantics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7055 | PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System Contact Information profile.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7055</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/profile.php of the component Contact Information Handler. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248742 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7054 | PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System add-notes.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7054</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/add-notes.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248741 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51707 | MotionPro in Array ArrayOS AG before 9.4.0.505 on AG and vxAG allows remote command execution via crafted packets. AG and vxAG 9.3.0.259.x a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51707</link><description>MotionPro in Array ArrayOS AG before 9.4.0.505 on AG and vxAG allows remote command execution via crafted packets. AG and vxAG 9.3.0.259.x are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51708 | Bentley eB System Management Console applications within Assetwise Integrity Information Server allow an unauthenticated user to view config...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51708</link><description>Bentley eB System Management Console applications within Assetwise Integrity Information Server allow an unauthenticated user to view configuration options via a crafted request, leading to information disclosure. This affects eB System management Console before 23.00.02.03 and Assetwise ALIM For Transportation before 23.00.01.25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51704 | An issue was discovered in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. In includes/logging/Righ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51704</link><description>An issue was discovered in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. In includes/logging/RightsLogFormatter.php, group-*-member messages can result in XSS on Special:log/rights.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7053 | PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System signup.php weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7053</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/signup.php. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248740.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7052 | PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System profile.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7052</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248739.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 01:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49086 | Cacti is vulnerable to cross-Site scripting (XSS) DOM </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49086</link><description>Cacti is a robust performance and fault management framework and a frontend to RRDTool - a Time Series Database (TSDB). Bypassing an earlier fix (CVE-2023-39360) that leads to a DOM XSS attack.
Exploitation of the vulnerability is possible for an authorized user. The vulnerable component is
the `graphs_new.php`. Impact of the vulnerability - execution of arbitrary javascript code in
the attacked user's browser. This issue has been patched in version 1.2.26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49689 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49689</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'JobId' parameter of the Employer/DeleteJob.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49690 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49690</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'WalkinId' parameter of the Employer/DeleteJob.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49687 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49687</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtPass' parameter of the login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49688 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49688</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtUser' parameter of the login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48308 | Calendar app returns full stacktrace when an error happens while editing appointment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48308</link><description>Nextcloud/Cloud is a calendar app for Nextcloud. An attacker can gain access to stacktrace and internal paths of the server when generating an exception while editing a calendar appointment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar app is upgraded to 4.5.3</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49684 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49684</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtTitle' parameter of the Employer/InsertWalkin.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49685 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49685</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtTime' parameter of the Employer/InsertWalkin.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49686 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49686</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtTotal' parameter of the Employer/InsertWalkin.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48298 | Integer underflow leading to stack overflow in FPC codec decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48298</link><description>ClickHouse® is an open-source column-oriented database management system that allows generating analytical data reports in real-time. This vulnerability is an integer underflow resulting in crash due to stack buffer overflow in decompression of FPC codec. It can be triggered and exploited by an unauthenticated attacker. The vulnerability is very similar to CVE-2023-47118 with how the vulnerable function can be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49084 | Local File Inclusion (RCE) in Cacti</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49084</link><description>Cacti is a robust performance and fault management framework and a frontend to RRDTool - a Time Series Database (TSDB). While using the detected SQL Injection and insufficient processing of the include file path, it is possible to execute arbitrary code on the server. Exploitation of the vulnerability is possible for an authorized user. The vulnerable component is the `link.php`. Impact of the vulnerability execution of arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49681 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49681</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'cmbQual' parameter of the Employer/InsertWalkin.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49682 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49682</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtDate' parameter of the Employer/InsertWalkin.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49683 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49683</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtDesc' parameter of the Employer/InsertWalkin.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49677 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49677</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'cmbQual' parameter of the Employer/InsertJob.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49678 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49678</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtDesc' parameter of the Employer/InsertJob.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49679 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49679</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtTitle' parameter of the Employer/InsertJob.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49680 | Job Portal v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49680</link><description>Job Portal v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'txtTotal' parameter of the Employer/InsertJob.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7024 | Heap buffer overflow in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.129 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7024</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.129 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37520 | HCL BigFix Platform is affected by Unathenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37520</link><description>Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability identified in BigFix Server version 9.5.12.68, allowing for potential data exfiltration. This XSS vulnerability is in the Gather Status Report, which is served by the BigFix Relay.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7051 | PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System manage-notes.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7051</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/manage-notes.php of the component Notes Handler. The manipulation of the argument delid leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248738 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37519 | HCL BigFix Platform is affected by Unathenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37519</link><description>Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This XSS vulnerability is in the Download Status Report, which is served by the BigFix Server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7050 | PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7050</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file user/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248737 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27319 |  CVE-2023-27319 Information Disclosure Vulnerability in ONTAP Mediator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27319</link><description>ONTAP Mediator versions prior to 1.7 are susceptible to a 
vulnerability that can allow an unauthenticated attacker to enumerate 
URLs via REST API.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48723 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48723</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'rno' parameter of the add_results.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48719 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48719</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'roll_no' parameter of the add_students.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48720 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48720</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'password' parameter of the login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48722 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48722</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'class_name' parameter of the add_results.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48717 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48717</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'class_name' parameter of the add_classes.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48718 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48718</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'class_name' parameter of the add_students.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 21:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48716 | Student Result Management System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48716</link><description>Student Result Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'class_id' parameter of the add_classes.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46645 | Path traversal in GitHub Enterprise Server leading to arbitrary file reading when building a GitHub Pages site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46645</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed arbitrary file reading when building a GitHub Pages site. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.7.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46646 | Improper access control in all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server allows unauthorized users to view private repository names via the "Get ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46646</link><description>Improper access control in all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server allows unauthorized users to view private repository names via the "Get a check run" API endpoint. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.7.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.17.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7 3.10.4, and 3.11.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46647 | Improper Privilege Management in GitHub Enterprise Server management console leads to privilege escalation </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46647</link><description>Improper privilege management in all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server allows users with authorized access to the management console with an editor role to escalate their privileges by making requests to the endpoint used for bootstrapping the instance. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.6, 3.10.3, and 3.11.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46648 | Insufficient Entropy in GitHub Enterprise Server Management Console Invitation Token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46648</link><description>An insufficient entropy vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server (GHES) that allowed an attacker to brute force a user invitation to the GHES Management Console. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need knowledge that a user invitation was pending. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46649 | Race Condition allows Administrative Access on Organization Repositories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46649</link><description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server was identified that could allow an attacker administrator access. To exploit this, an organization needs to be converted from a user. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.7.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48687 | Railway Reservation System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48687</link><description>Railway Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'from' parameter of the reservation.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48688 | Railway Reservation System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48688</link><description>Railway Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'to' parameter of the reservation.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48689 | Railway Reservation System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48689</link><description>Railway Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'byname' parameter of the train.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48690 | Railway Reservation System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48690</link><description>Railway Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'bynum' parameter of the train.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51379 | Incorrect Authorization for Issue Comments in GitHub Enterprise Server </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51379</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed issue comments to be updated with an improperly scoped token. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content as it also required contents:write and issues:read permissions. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.17.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51380 | Incorrect Authorization allows Read Access to Issue Comments in GitHub Enterprise Server </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51380</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed issue comments to be read with an improperly scoped token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.17.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6690 | A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on transferred repositories by making a Graph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6690</link><description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on transferred repositories by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions during the transfer. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6746 | Sensitive Information in Log File in GitHub Enterprise Server </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6746</link><description>An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerability was identified in the log files for a GitHub Enterprise Server back-end service that could permit an `adversary in the middle attack` when combined with other phishing techniques. To exploit this, an attacker would need access to the log files for the GitHub Enterprise Server appliance, a backup archive created with GitHub Enterprise Server Backup Utilities, or a service which received streamed logs. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.17.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6802 | Sensitive Information in Log File in GitHub Enterprise Server </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6802</link><description>An insertion of sensitive information into the log file in the audit log in GitHub Enterprise Server was identified that could allow an attacker to gain access to the management console. To exploit this, an attacker would need access to the log files for the GitHub Enterprise Server appliance, a backup archive created with GitHub Enterprise Server Backup Utilities, or a service which received streamed logs. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6803 | Race Condition allows Unauthorized Outside Collaborator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6803</link><description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allows an outside collaborator to be added while a repository is being transferred. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6804 | Improper Privilege Management allows for arbitrary workflows to be run</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6804</link><description>Improper privilege management allowed arbitrary workflows to be committed and run using an improperly scoped PAT. To exploit this, a workflow must have already existed in the target repo. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6847 | Improper Authentication in GitHub Enterprise Server leading to Authentication Bypass for Public Repository Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6847</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a bypass of Private Mode by using a specially crafted API request. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need network access to the Enterprise Server appliance configured in Private Mode. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.9 and was fixed in version 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48686 | Railway Reservation System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48686</link><description>Railway Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'user' parameter of the login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41097 | Potential Timing vulnerability in CBC PKCS7 padding calculations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41097</link><description>An Observable Timing Discrepancy, Covert Timing Channel vulnerability in Silabs GSDK on ARM potentially allows Padding Oracle Crypto Attack on CBC PKCS7.This issue affects GSDK: through 4.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48685 | Railway Reservation System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48685</link><description>Railway Reservation System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'psd' parameter of the login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46791 | Online Matrimonial Project v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46791</link><description>Online Matrimonial Project v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'filename' attribute of the 'pic3' multipart parameter of the functions.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7042 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in ath10k_wmi_tlv_op_pull_mgmt_tx_compl_ev()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7042</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability was found in ath10k_wmi_tlv_op_pull_mgmt_tx_compl_ev() in drivers/net/wireless/ath/ath10k/wmi-tlv.c in the Linux kernel. This issue could be exploited to trigger a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6546 | Kernel: gsm multiplexing race condition leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6546</link><description>A race condition was found in the GSM 0710 tty multiplexor in the Linux kernel. This issue occurs when two threads execute the GSMIOC_SETCONF ioctl on the same tty file descriptor with the gsm line discipline enabled, and can lead to a use-after-free problem on a struct gsm_dlci while restarting the gsm mux. This could allow a local unprivileged user to escalate their privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7041 | codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS rename.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7041</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS up to 1.2.4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /file-manager/rename.php. The manipulation of the argument newName leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248690 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50732 | Velocity execution without script right through tree macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50732</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. It's possible to execute a Velocity script without script right through the document tree. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.7 and 15.2RC1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7040 | codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS rename.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7040</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS up to 1.2.4. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /file-manager/rename.php. The manipulation of the argument oldName leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248689 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44481 | Leave Management System Project v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44481</link><description>Leave Management System Project v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'setearnleave' parameter of the admin/setleaves.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44482 | Leave Management System Project v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44482</link><description>Leave Management System Project v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'setsickleave' parameter of the admin/setleaves.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45124 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45124</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'tag' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45125 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45125</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'time' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45126 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45126</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'total' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45127 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45127</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'wrong' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47191 | WordPress Youzify Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47191</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in KaineLabs Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress.This issue affects Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49765 | WordPress Rate my Post – WP Rating System Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.1 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49765</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Blaz K. Rate my Post – WP Rating System.This issue affects Rate my Post – WP Rating System: from n/a through 3.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7039 | Beijing Baichuo S210 importexport.php injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7039</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Beijing Baichuo S210 up to 20231210. Affected is an unknown function of the file /importexport.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248688.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32747 | WordPress WooCommerce Bookings Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.78 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32747</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WooCommerce WooCommerce Bookings.This issue affects WooCommerce Bookings: from n/a through 1.15.78.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32799 | WordPress WooCommerce Ship to Multiple Addresses Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32799</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WooCommerce Shipping Multiple Addresses.This issue affects Shipping Multiple Addresses: from n/a through 3.8.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50834 | WordPress WooCommerce Menu Extension Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in August Infotech WooCommerce Menu Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Menu Extension: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50833 | WordPress Colibri Page Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.239 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50833</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ExtendThemes Colibri Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Colibri Page Builder: from n/a through 1.0.239.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 18:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7038 | automad User Creation cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7038</link><description>A vulnerability was found in automad up to 1.10.9. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dashboard?controller=UserCollection::createUser of the component User Creation Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248687. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 17:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50831 | WordPress CURCY Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50831</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VillaTheme CURCY – Multi Currency for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CURCY – Multi Currency for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 17:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50832 | WordPress Multi Step Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50832</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mondula GmbH Multi Step Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Multi Step Form: from n/a through 1.7.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 17:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50829 | WordPress Loan Repayment Calculator and Application Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50829</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aerin Loan Repayment Calculator and Application Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Loan Repayment Calculator and Application Form: from n/a through 2.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50830 | WordPress Seos Contact Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50830</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Seosbg Seos Contact Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Seos Contact Form: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7037 | automad FileController.php import server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7037</link><description>A vulnerability was found in automad up to 1.10.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function import of the file FileController.php. The manipulation of the argument importUrl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248686 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 17:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45123 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45123</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'right' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45122 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45122</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'name' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45120 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45120</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'qid' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45121 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45121</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'desc' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40058 | Sensitive Information Disclosure Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40058</link><description>Sensitive data was added to our public-facing knowledgebase that, if exploited, could be used to access components of Access Rights Manager (ARM) if the threat actor is in the same environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45119 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45119</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'n' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4255 | W3m: out-of-bounds write in function checktype() in etc.c (incomplete fix for cve-2022-38223)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4255</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue has been discovered in the backspace handling of the checkType() function in etc.c within the W3M application. This vulnerability is triggered by supplying a specially crafted HTML file to the w3m binary. Exploitation of this flaw could lead to application crashes, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4256 | Tcpreplay: tcprewrite: double free in tcpedit_dlt_cleanup() in plugins/dlt_plugins.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4256</link><description>Within tcpreplay's tcprewrite, a double free vulnerability has been identified in the tcpedit_dlt_cleanup() function within plugins/dlt_plugins.c. This vulnerability can be exploited by supplying a specifically crafted file to the tcprewrite binary. This flaw enables a local attacker to initiate a Denial of Service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7036 | automad Content Type FileCollectionController.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7036</link><description>A vulnerability was found in automad up to 1.10.9. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function upload of the file FileCollectionController.php of the component Content Type Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248685 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45118 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45118</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'fdid' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45117 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45117</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'eid' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45116 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45116</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'demail' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45115 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45115</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'ch' parameter of the update.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51048 | S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_newsauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51048</link><description>S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_newsauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51049 | S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_bbsauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51049</link><description>S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_bbsauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51050 | S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_productauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51050</link><description>S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_productauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51051 | S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_textauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51051</link><description>S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_textauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51052 | S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_formauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51052</link><description>S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the A_formauth parameter at /admin/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48115 | SmarterTools SmarterMail 8495 through 8664 before 8747 allows stored DOM XSS because an XSS protection mechanism is skipped when messageHTML...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48115</link><description>SmarterTools SmarterMail 8495 through 8664 before 8747 allows stored DOM XSS because an XSS protection mechanism is skipped when messageHTML and messagePlainText are set in the same request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51442 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in navidrome&amp;#x27;s subsonic endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51442</link><description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. A security vulnerability has been identified in navidrome's subsonic endpoint, allowing for authentication bypass. This exploit enables unauthorized access to any known account by utilizing a JSON Web Token (JWT) signed with the key "not so secret". The vulnerability can only be exploited on instances that have never been restarted. Navidrome supports an extension to the subsonic authentication scheme, where a JWT can be provided using a `jwt` query parameter instead of the traditional password or token and salt (corresponding to resp. the `p` or `t` and `s` query parameters). This authentication bypass vulnerability potentially affects all instances that don't protect the subsonic endpoint `/rest/`, which is expected to be most instances in a standard deployment, and most instances in the reverse proxy setup too (as the documentation mentions to leave that endpoint unprotected). This issue has been patched in version 0.50.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48116 | SmarterTools SmarterMail 8495 through 8664 before 8747 allows stored XSS via a crafted description of a Calendar appointment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48116</link><description>SmarterTools SmarterMail 8495 through 8664 before 8747 allows stored XSS via a crafted description of a Calendar appointment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50724 | Resque vulnerable to reflected cross site scripting through pathname </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50724</link><description>Resque (pronounced like "rescue") is a Redis-backed library for creating background jobs, placing those jobs on multiple queues, and processing them later. resque-web in resque versions before 2.1.0 are vulnerable to reflected XSS through the current_queue parameter in the path of the queues endpoint. This issue has been patched in version 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50826 | WordPress Menu Image, Icons made easy Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50826</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Freshlight Lab Menu Image, Icons made easy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Menu Image, Icons made easy: from n/a through 3.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50827 | WordPress Accredible Certificates &amp;amp; Open Badges Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50827</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Accredible Accredible Certificates &amp; Open Badges allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accredible Certificates &amp; Open Badges: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50828 | WordPress Ultimate Dashboard Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50828</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in David Vongries Ultimate Dashboard – Custom WordPress Dashboard allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Dashboard – Custom WordPress Dashboard: from n/a through 3.7.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50824 | WordPress Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3000000021 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50824</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brian Batt Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress: from n/a through 4.3000000021.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50825 | WordPress iframe Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50825</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Terrier Tenacity iframe Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects iframe Shortcode: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7047 | Inadequate validation of permissions when employing remote tools and 
macros via the context menu within Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7047</link><description>Inadequate validation of permissions when employing remote tools and 
macros via the context menu within Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager versions 2023.3.31 and 
earlier permits a user to initiate a connection without proper execution
 rights via the remote tools feature. This affects only SQL data sources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50823 | WordPress CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript Toolbox Plugin &amp;lt;= 11.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50823</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wipeout Media CSS &amp; JavaScript Toolbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CSS &amp; JavaScript Toolbox: from n/a through 11.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50377 | WordPress Simple Counter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50377</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AB-WP Simple Counter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Counter: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50822 | WordPress Currency Converter Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50822</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Currency.Wiki Currency Converter Widget – Exchange Rates allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Currency Converter Widget – Exchange Rates: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7035 | automad Setting post.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7035</link><description>A vulnerability was found in automad up to 1.10.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file packages\standard\templates\post.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument sitename leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248684. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47525 | WordPress Event Management Tickets Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47525</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in A WP Life Event Monster – Event Management, Tickets Booking, Upcoming Event allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Event Monster – Event Management, Tickets Booking, Upcoming Event: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47527 | WordPress WP Edit Username Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47527</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sajjad Hossain Sagor WP Edit Username allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Edit Username: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48114 | SmarterTools SmarterMail 8495 through 8664 before 8747 allows stored XSS by using image/svg+xml and an uploaded SVG document. This occurs be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48114</link><description>SmarterTools SmarterMail 8495 through 8664 before 8747 allows stored XSS by using image/svg+xml and an uploaded SVG document. This occurs because the application tries to allow youtube.com URLs, but actually allows youtube.com followed by an @ character and an attacker-controlled domain name.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22674 | WordPress Dashicons + Custom Post Types Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22674</link><description>Missing Authorization, Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hal Gatewood Dashicons + Custom Post Types.This issue affects Dashicons + Custom Post Types: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28421 | WordPress WordPress Email Marketing Plugin – WP Email Capture Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28421</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Winwar Media WordPress Email Marketing Plugin – WP Email Capture.This issue affects WordPress Email Marketing Plugin – WP Email Capture: from n/a through 3.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2487 | WordPress WP Ultimate Exporter Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2487</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Smackcoders Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users.This issue affects Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48288 | WordPress WordPress Job Board and Recruitment Plugin – JobWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48288</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HM Plugin WordPress Job Board and Recruitment Plugin – JobWP.This issue affects WordPress Job Board and Recruitment Plugin – JobWP: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6145 | SQLi in Softomi E-commerce Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6145</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in İstanbul Soft Informatics and Consultancy Limited Company Softomi Advanced C2C Marketplace Software allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Softomi Advanced C2C Marketplace Software: before 12122023.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49162 | WordPress BigCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.6 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49162</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in BigCommerce BigCommerce For WordPress.This issue affects BigCommerce For WordPress: from n/a through 5.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6122 | Reflected XSS in Softomi E-commerce Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in İstanbul Soft Informatics and Consultancy Limited Company Softomi Gelişmiş C2C Pazaryeri Yazılımı allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Softomi Gelişmiş C2C Pazaryeri Yazılımı: before 12122023.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45377 | WordPress Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 is vulnerable to Multiple Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45377</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Glen Don L. Mongaya Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce.This issue affects Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32242 | WordPress Woodmart Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.36 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32242</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in xtemos WoodMart - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme.This issue affects WoodMart - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme: from n/a through 1.0.36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49762 | WordPress AppMySite Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.11.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49762</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in AppMySite AppMySite – Create an app with the Best Mobile App Builder.This issue affects AppMySite – Create an app with the Best Mobile App Builder: from n/a through 3.11.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49778 | WordPress Sayfa Sayaç Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49778</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Hakan Demiray Sayfa Sayac.This issue affects Sayfa Sayac: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49826 | WordPress Soledad Theme &amp;lt;= 8.4.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49826</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PenciDesign Soledad – Multipurpose, Newspaper, Blog &amp; WooCommerce WordPress Theme.This issue affects Soledad – Multipurpose, Newspaper, Blog &amp; WooCommerce WordPress Theme: from n/a through 8.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51656 | Apache IoTDB: Unsafe deserialize map in Sync Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51656</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache IoTDB.This issue affects Apache IoTDB: from 0.13.0 through 0.13.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.2.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5594 | Improper following of a certificate&amp;#x27;s chain of trust in ESET security products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5594</link><description>Improper validation of the server’s certificate chain in secure traffic scanning feature considered intermediate certificate signed using the MD5 or SHA1 algorithm as trusted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50481 | An issue was discovered in blinksocks version 3.3.8, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via weak encryption algorithms ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50481</link><description>An issue was discovered in blinksocks version 3.3.8, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via weak encryption algorithms in the component /presets/ssr-auth-chain.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50473 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in bill-ahmed qbit-matUI version 1.16.4, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50473</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in bill-ahmed qbit-matUI version 1.16.4, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via fixed session identifiers (SID) in index.js file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50475 | An issue was discovered in bcoin-org bcoin version 2.2.0, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via weak hashing algorithm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50475</link><description>An issue was discovered in bcoin-org bcoin version 2.2.0, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via weak hashing algorithms in the component \vendor\faye-websocket.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50477 | An issue was discovered in nos client version 0.6.6, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges via getRPCEndpoint.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50477</link><description>An issue was discovered in nos client version 0.6.6, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges via getRPCEndpoint.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51655 | In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2023.3.2 code execution was possible in Untrusted Project mode via a malicious plugin repository specified...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51655</link><description>In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2023.3.2 code execution was possible in Untrusted Project mode via a malicious plugin repository specified in the project configuration</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5989 | Stored XSS in Uyumsoft ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uyumsoft Information System and Technologies LioXERP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LioXERP: before v.146.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5988 | Reflected XSS in Uyumsoft ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5988</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uyumsoft Information System and Technologies LioXERP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LioXERP: before v.146.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47265 | Apache Airflow: DAG Params alllow to embed unchecked Javascript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47265</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions 2.6.0 through 2.7.3 has a stored XSS vulnerability that allows a DAG author to add an unbounded and not-sanitized javascript in the parameter description field of the DAG. This Javascript can be executed on the client side of any of the user who looks at the tasks in the browser sandbox. While this issue does not allow to exit the browser sandbox or manipulation of the server-side data - more than the DAG author already has, it allows to modify what the user looking at the DAG details sees in the browser - which opens up all kinds of possibilities of misleading other users.

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.0 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48291 | Apache Airflow: Improper access control to DAG resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48291</link><description>Apache Airflow, in versions prior to 2.8.0, contains a security vulnerability that allows an authenticated user with limited access to some DAGs, to craft a request that could give the user write access to various DAG resources for DAGs that the user had no access to, thus, enabling the user to clear DAGs they shouldn't.

This is a missing fix for CVE-2023-42792 in Apache Airflow 2.7.2 

Users of Apache Airflow are strongly advised to upgrade to version 2.8.0 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49920 | Apache Airflow: Missing CSRF protection on DAG/trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49920</link><description>Apache Airflow, version 2.7.0 through 2.7.3, has a vulnerability that allows an attacker to trigger a DAG in a GET request without CSRF validation. As a result, it was possible for a malicious website opened in the same browser - by the user who also had Airflow UI opened - to trigger the execution of DAGs without the user's consent.
Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.8.0 or later which is not affected</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50783 | Apache Airflow: Improper access control vulnerability on the &amp;quot;varimport&amp;quot; endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50783</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.0, is affected by a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user without the variable edit permission, to update a variable.
This flaw compromises the integrity of variable management, potentially leading to unauthorized data modification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to 2.8.0, which fixes this issue</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2585 | Client access via device auth request spoof</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2585</link><description>Keycloak's device authorization grant does not correctly validate the device code and client ID. An attacker client could abuse the missing validation to spoof a client consent request and trick an authorization admin into granting consent to a malicious OAuth client or possible unauthorized access to an existing OAuth client.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7026 | Lightxun IPTV Gateway web_upload_template.html unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7026</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Lightxun IPTV Gateway up to 20231208. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ZHGXTV/index.php/admin/index/web_upload_template.html. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248579.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 04:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7025 | KylinSoft hedron-domain-hook DBus init_kcm access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7025</link><description>A vulnerability was found in KylinSoft hedron-domain-hook up to 3.8.0.12-0k0.5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function init_kcm of the component DBus Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7023 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7023</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file general/vehicle/query/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument VU_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 02:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7022 | Tongda OA 2017 delete_all.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7022</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/work_plan/manage/delete_all.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29485 | An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to bypass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29485</link><description>An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to bypass network filtering, execute arbitrary code, and obtain sensitive information via DarkLayer Guard threat prevention module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29486 | An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before 3.7.0 on Windows, allows attackers to bypass USB access restrictions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29486</link><description>An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before 3.7.0 on Windows, allows attackers to bypass USB access restrictions, execute arbitrary code, and obtain sensitive information via Next-Gen Antivirus component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29487 | An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29487</link><description>An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the Threat To Process Correlation threat prevention module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28025 | An HTML injection vulnerability can affect HCL BigFix Mobile / Modern Client Management </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28025</link><description>Due to this vulnerability, the Master operator could potentially incorporate an SVG tag into HTML, leading to an alert pop-up displaying a cookie. To mitigate stored XSS vulnerabilities, a preventive measure involves thoroughly sanitizing and validating all user inputs before they are processed and stored in the server storage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7021 | Tongda OA 2017 delete_search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7021</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file general/vehicle/checkup/delete_search.php. The manipulation of the argument VU_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45700 | HCL Launch is susceptible to an HTML injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45700</link><description>HCL Launch is vulnerable to HTML injection. This vulnerability may allow a user to embed arbitrary HTML tags in the Web UI potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7020 | Tongda OA 2017 view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7020</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file general/wiki/cp/ct/view.php. The manipulation of the argument TEMP_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248567. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>