<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11137 | Gstarsoft GstarCAD File Renaming cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Gstarsoft GstarCAD up to 9.4.0. This affects an unknown function of the component File Renaming Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11136 | YiFang CMS Backend File.php webUploader unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11136</link><description>A flaw has been found in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.2. The impacted element is the function webUploader of the file app/app/controller/File.php of the component Backend. Executing manipulation of the argument uploadpath can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11135 | pmTicket Project-Management-Software Cookie class.database.php loadLanguage deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in pmTicket Project-Management-Software up to 2ef379da2075f4761a2c9029cf91d073474e7486. The affected element is the function loadLanguage of the file classes/class.database.php of the component Cookie Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument user_id results in deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11134 | Cudy TR1200 Wireless Settings config cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Cudy TR1200 1.16.3-20230804-164635. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/luci/admin/network/wireless/config/ of the component Wireless Settings Page. Such manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7698 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7698</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9903 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9903</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9904 | Unallocated memory access vulnerability in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Gener...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9904</link><description>Unallocated memory access vulnerability in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11130 | iHongRen pptp-vpn XPC Service HelperTool.m shouldAcceptNewConnection missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11130</link><description>A weakness has been identified in iHongRen pptp-vpn 1.0/1.0.1 on macOS. This issue affects the function shouldAcceptNewConnection of the file HelpTool/HelperTool.m of the component XPC Service. This manipulation causes missing authentication. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11126 | Apeman ID71 system.ini hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11126</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Apeman ID71 218.53.203.117. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/www/system.ini. The manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11125 | langleyfcu Online Banking System Error Message connection_error.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11125</link><description>A vulnerability was found in langleyfcu Online Banking System up to 57437e6400ce0ae240e692c24e6346b8d0c17d7a. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /connection_error.php of the component Error Message Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument Error results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11124 | code-projects Project Monitoring System postjob.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11124</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Project Monitoring System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /onlineJobSearchEngine/postjob.php. Such manipulation of the argument txtapplyto leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11123 | Tenda AC18 saveAutoQos stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11123</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/saveAutoQos. This manipulation of the argument enable causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11122 | Tenda AC18 WizardHandle stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11122</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/WizardHandle. The manipulation of the argument WANT/mtuvalue results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11121 | Tenda AC18 AdvSetLanip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11121</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanIp leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11120 | Tenda AC8 SetServerConfig formSetServerConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11120</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. The affected element is the function formSetServerConfig of the file /goform/SetServerConfig. Executing manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11119 | itsourcecode Hostel Management System POST Request index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11119</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Hostel Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /justines/index.php of the component POST Request Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument from results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11118 | CodeAstro Student Grading System adminLogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11118</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CodeAstro Student Grading System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adminLogin.php. Such manipulation of the argument staffId leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11117 | Tenda CH22 GstDhcpSetSer formWrlExtraGet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11117</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formWrlExtraGet of the file /goform/GstDhcpSetSer. This manipulation of the argument dips causes buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11116 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System add.home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11116</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add.home.php. The manipulation of the argument faculty results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11115 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addtime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11115</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addtime.php. The manipulation of the argument starttime/endtime leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11114 | CodeAstro Online Leave Application leaveAplicationForm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11114</link><description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Online Leave Application 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /leaveAplicationForm.php. Executing manipulation of the argument absence[] can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11113 | CodeAstro Online Leave Application signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11113</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Online Leave Application 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument city results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11112 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System myprofile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11112</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /myprofile.php. Such manipulation of the argument First name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11111 | Campcodes Advanced Online Voting Management System candidates_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11111</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Advanced Online Voting Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/candidates_edit.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11110 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System school_year.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11110</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/school_year.php. The manipulation of the argument school_year results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11109 | Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System us_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11109</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pages/us_edit.php?action=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11108 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11108</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /schedulingsystem/addroom.php. Executing manipulation of the argument room can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11107 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addcourse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /schedulingsystem/addcourse.php. Performing manipulation of the argument corcode results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11106 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addfaculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /schedulingsystem/addfaculty.php. Such manipulation of the argument falname leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11105 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addsubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11105</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /schedulingsystem/addsubject.php. This manipulation of the argument subcode causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11104 | CodeAstro Electricity Billing System bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11104</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Electricity Billing System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bill.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 12:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11103 | Projectworlds Online Tours and Travels change-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11103</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Projectworlds Online Tours and Travels 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/change-image.php. The manipulation of the argument packageimage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 11:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11102 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_content.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11102</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_content.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Title can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 07:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11101 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11101</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /jobportal/admin/company/index.php?view=edit. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11100 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifi_blacklists uci_set command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11100</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function uci_set of the file /goform/set_wifi_blacklists. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11099 | D-Link DIR-823X delete_prohibiting uci_del command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11099</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The impacted element is the function uci_del of the file /goform/delete_prohibiting. This manipulation of the argument delvalue causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11098 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifi_blacklists command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11098</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_wifi_blacklists. The manipulation of the argument macList results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11097 | D-Link DIR-823X set_device_name command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11097</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_device_name. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11096 | D-Link DIR-823X diag_traceroute command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11096</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/diag_traceroute. Executing manipulation of the argument target_addr can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 04:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11095 | D-Link DIR-823X delete_offline_device command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11095</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/delete_offline_device. Performing manipulation of the argument delvalue results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 04:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11094 | code-projects E-Commerce Website admin_product_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11094</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/admin_product_details.php. Such manipulation of the argument prod_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11092 | D-Link DIR-823X set_switch_settings sub_412E7C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11092</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is the function sub_412E7C of the file /goform/set_switch_settings. This manipulation of the argument port causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11091 | Tenda AC21 SetStaticRouteCfg sscanf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11091</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda AC21 up to 16.03.08.16. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sscanf of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 02:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11090 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11090</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/employee/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 02:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11089 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem COUNT3s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11089</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem up to 42cd892b40a18d50bd4ed1905fa89f939173a464. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Profilers/PriProfile/COUNT3s4.php. Executing manipulation of the argument cbranch can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11088 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11088</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/vacancy/index.php?view=edit. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11083 | GNU Binutils Linker elfcode.h elf_swap_shdr heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11083</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU Binutils 2.45. The affected element is the function elf_swap_shdr in the library bfd/elfcode.h of the component Linker. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 9ca499644a21ceb3f946d1c179c38a83be084490. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The code maintainer replied with "[f]ixed for 2.46".</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11082 | GNU Binutils Linker elf-eh-frame.c _bfd_elf_parse_eh_frame heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11082</link><description>A flaw has been found in GNU Binutils 2.45. Impacted is the function _bfd_elf_parse_eh_frame of the file bfd/elf-eh-frame.c of the component Linker. Executing manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called ea1a0737c7692737a644af0486b71e4a392cbca8. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue. The code maintainer replied with "[f]ixed for 2.46".</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11081 | GNU Binutils objdump.c dump_dwarf_section out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11081</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in GNU Binutils 2.45. This issue affects the function dump_dwarf_section of the file binutils/objdump.c. Performing manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit is now public and may be used. The patch is named f87a66db645caf8cc0e6fc87b0c28c78a38af59b. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11080 | zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education ExamInfoController.java selectStudentExamInfoList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11080</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education up to 1.0.4. This vulnerability affects the function selectStudentExamInfoList of the file src/main/java/com/education/api/controller/student/ExamInfoController.java. Such manipulation of the argument subjectId leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11079 | Campcodes Farm Management System file information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11079</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation results in file and directory information exposure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11078 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal controller.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11078</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/user/controller.php?action=photos. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11077 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System add_content.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11077</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add_content.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Title can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11076 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_teacher.php. Performing manipulation of the argument department results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11075 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System de_activate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11075</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/de_activate.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11074 | code-projects Project Monitoring System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11074</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Project Monitoring System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /login.php. This manipulation of the argument username/password causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11073 | Keyfactor RG-EW5100BE HTTP POST Request cmd command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11073</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Keyfactor RG-EW5100BE EW_3.0B11P280_EW5100BE-PRO_12183019. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/luci/api/cmd of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11071 | SeaCMS Cron Task Management admin_cron.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11071</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SeaCMS 13.3.20250820. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin_cron.php of the component Cron Task Management Module. The manipulation of the argument resourcefrom/collectID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11070 | Projectworlds Online Shopping System cart_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11070</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Projectworlds Online Shopping System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /store/cart_add.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11069 | westboy CicadasCMS Add Department save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11069</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/org/save of the component Add Department Handler. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7647 | Insecure Temporary File Handling in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7647</link><description>The llama-index-core package, up to version 0.12.44, contains a vulnerability in the `get_cache_dir()` function where a predictable, hardcoded directory path `/tmp/llama_index` is used on Linux systems without proper security controls. This vulnerability allows attackers on multi-user systems to steal proprietary models, poison cached embeddings, or conduct symlink attacks. The issue affects all Linux deployments where multiple users share the same system. The vulnerability is classified under CWE-379, CWE-377, and CWE-367, indicating insecure temporary file creation and potential race conditions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8014 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8014</link><description>Denial of Service issue in GraphQL endpoints in Gitlab EE/CE affecting all versions from 11.10 prior to 18.2.7, 18.3 prior to 18.3.3, and 18.4 prior to 18.4.1 allows unauthenticated users to potentially bypass query complexity limits leading to resource exhaustion and service disruption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11068 | westboy CicadasCMS save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11068</link><description>A vulnerability was found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/cms/category/save. The manipulation of the argument categoryName results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11067 | Projectworlds Visitor Management System Add Visitor myform.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11067</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Projectworlds Visitor Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /myform.php of the component Add Visitor Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11066 | code-projects Online Bidding System bidlist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11066</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Bidding System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /administrator/bidlist.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11064 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System teachers.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11064</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/teachers.php. The manipulation of the argument department results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11063 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11063</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit_department.php. The manipulation of the argument d leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11062 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System save_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11062</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/save_student.php. Executing manipulation of the argument class_id can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11061 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11061</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit_student.php. Performing manipulation of the argument cys results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11057 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software print_inv.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11057</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/print_inv.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11056 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System select-students.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11056</link><description>A flaw has been found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file owner_panel/fetch-data/select-students.php. This manipulation of the argument select causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 10:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11055 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System updateaddress.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11055</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/updateaddress.php. The manipulation of the argument address results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 10:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11054 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11054</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /jobportal/admin/category/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11053 | PHPGurukul Small CRM forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11053</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /forgot-password.php. Executing manipulation of the argument email can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 08:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11052 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem COUNT3s5.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11052</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem 1.0/5.php. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Profilers/PriProfile/COUNT3s5.php. Performing manipulation of the argument csslc results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 07:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9893 | VM Menu Reorder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9893</link><description>The VM Menu Reorder plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the vm_set_to_default function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset all menu reordering settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9894 | Sync Feedly &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Sync Trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9894</link><description>The Sync Feedly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the crsf_cron_job_func function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger content synchronization from Feedly, potentially creating multiple posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9896 | HidePost &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9896</link><description>The HidePost plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the options.php settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9898 | cForms – Light speed fast Form Builder &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9898</link><description>The cForms – Light speed fast Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cforms_api function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify forms and their settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9899 | Trust Reviews plugin for Google, Tripadvisor, Yelp, Airbnb and other platforms &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9899</link><description>The Trust Reviews plugin for Google, Tripadvisor, Yelp, Airbnb and other platforms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the feed_save function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create or modify feed entries via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9944 | Professional Contact Form &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Test Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9944</link><description>The Professional Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the watch_for_contact_form_submit function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger test email sending via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11051 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11051</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10954 | Versions of the package github.com/nyaruka/phonenumbers before 1.2.2 are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10954</link><description>Versions of the package github.com/nyaruka/phonenumbers before 1.2.2 are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input in the phonenumbers.Parse() function. An attacker can cause a panic by providing crafted input causing a "runtime error: slice bounds out of range".</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 05:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3193 | Versions of the package algoliasearch-helper from 2.0.0-rc1 and before 3.11.2 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the _merge() function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3193</link><description>Versions of the package algoliasearch-helper from 2.0.0-rc1 and before 3.11.2 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the _merge() function in merge.js, which allows constructor.prototype to be written even though doing so throws an error. In the "extreme edge-case" that the resulting error is caught, code injected into the user-supplied search parameter may be exeucted.&#13;&#13;This is related to but distinct from the issue reported in [CVE-2021-23433](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-ALGOLIASEARCHHELPER-1570421).&#13;&#13;**NOTE:** This vulnerability is not exploitable in the default configuration of InstantSearch since searchParameters are not modifiable by users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 05:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11050 | Portabilis i-Educar periodo-lancamento improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11050</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /periodo-lancamento. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9816 | WP Statistics &amp;lt;= 14.5.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via User-Agent Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9816</link><description>The WP Statistics – The Most Popular Privacy-Friendly Analytics Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the User-Agent Header in all versions up to, and including, 14.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11049 | Portabilis i-Educar unificacao-aluno improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11049</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /unificacao-aluno. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 04:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10498 | Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10498</link><description>The Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.12.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation when exporting CSV files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete those files granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10499 | Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10499</link><description>The Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the maybe_opt_in() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to opt an affected site into usage statistics collection via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43192 | IBM Storage TS4500 Library cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43192</link><description>IBM Storage TS4500 Library 1.11.0.0 and 2.11.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36239 | IBM Storage TS4500 Library cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36239</link><description>IBM Storage TS4500 Library 1.11.0.0 and 2.11.0.0 

is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8440 | Team Members &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8440</link><description>The Team Members plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the first and last name fields in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59932 | FlagForgeCTF Unauthenticated Resource Modification/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59932</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. From versions 2.0.0 to before 2.3.1, the /api/resources endpoint previously allowed POST and DELETE requests without proper authentication or authorization. This could have enabled unauthorized users to create, modify, or delete resources on the platform. The issue has been fixed in FlagForge version 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59945 | SysReptor Susceptible to Privilege Escalation by Authenticated Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59945</link><description>SysReptor is a fully customizable pentest reporting platform. In versions from 2024.74 to before 2025.83, authenticated and unprivileged (non-admin) users can assign the is_project_admin permission to their own user. This allows users to read, modify and delete pentesting projects they are not members of and are therefore not supposed to access. This issue has been patched in version 2025.83.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59936 | get-jwks poisoned JWKS cache allows post-fetch issuer validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59936</link><description>get-jwks contains fetch utils for JWKS keys. In versions prior to 11.0.2, a vulnerability in get-jwks can lead to cache poisoning in the JWKS key-fetching mechanism. When the iss (issuer) claim is validated only after keys are retrieved from the cache, it is possible for cached keys from an unexpected issuer to be reused, resulting in a bypass of issuer validation. This design flaw enables a potential attack where a malicious actor crafts a pair of JWTs, the first one ensuring that a chosen public key is fetched and stored in the shared JWKS cache, and the second one leveraging that cached key to pass signature validation for a targeted iss value. The vulnerability will work only if the iss validation is done after the use of get-jwks for keys retrieval. This issue has been patched in version 11.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59938 | Heap buffer overflow in wazuh-analysisd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59938</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. In versions starting from 3.8.0 to before 4.11.0, wazuh-analysisd is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow when parsing XML elements from Windows EventChannel messages. This issue has been patched in version 4.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59939 | WeGIA vulnerable to SQL Injection into method `excluir` of  the `ProdutoControle` class in the parameter `id_produto`.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59939</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to version 3.5.0, WeGIA is vulnerable to SQL Injection attacks in the control.php endpoint with the following parameters: nomeClasse=ProdutoControle&amp;amp;metodo=excluir&amp;amp;id_produto=[malicious command]. It is necessary to apply prepared statements methods, sanitization, and validations on theid_produto parameter. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36144 | IBM watsonx.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36144</link><description>IBM Lakehouse (watsonx.data 2.2) stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>