<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:37:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2015-10132 | Thimo Grauerholz WP-Spreadplugin spreadplugin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10132</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Thimo Grauerholz WP-Spreadplugin up to 3.8.6.1 on WordPress. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file spreadplugin.php. The manipulation of the argument Spreadplugin leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.8.6.6 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is a9b9afc641854698e80aa5dd9ababfc8e0e57d69. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261676.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29733 | Apache Airflow FTP Provider: FTP_TLS instance with unverified SSL context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29733</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in Apache Airflow FTP Provider.

The FTP hook lacks complete certificate validation in FTP_TLS connections, which can potentially be leveraged. Implementing proper certificate validation by passing context=ssl.create_default_context() during FTP_TLS instantiation is used as mitigation to validate the certificates properly.

This issue affects Apache Airflow FTP Provider: before 3.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29217 | Apache Answer: XSS vulnerability when changing personal website</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29217</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: before 1.3.0.

XSS attack when user changes personal website. A logged-in user, when modifying their personal website, can input malicious code in the website to create such an attack.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.3.0], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4022 | Keenetic KN-1010/KN-1410/KN-1711/KN-1810/KN-1910 Version Data version.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4022</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keenetic KN-1010, KN-1410, KN-1711, KN-1810 and KN-1910 up to 4.1.2.15. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /version.js of the component Version Data Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 10:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4021 | Keenetic KN-1010/KN-1410/KN-1711/KN-1810/KN-1910 Configuration Setting ndmComponents.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4021</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keenetic KN-1010, KN-1410, KN-1711, KN-1810 and KN-1910 up to 4.1.2.15. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ndmComponents.js of the component Configuration Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261673 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 10:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4020 | Tenda FH1206 addressNat fromAddressNat buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4020</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 1.2.0.8(8155) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function fromAddressNat of the file /goform/addressNat. The manipulation of the argument entrys leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261671. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4019 | Byzoro Smart S80 Management Platform importhtml.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4019</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Byzoro Smart S80 Management Platform up to 20240411. Affected is an unknown function of the file /importhtml.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4014 | The hCaptcha for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cf7-hcaptcha shortcode in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4014</link><description>The hCaptcha for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cf7-hcaptcha shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 09:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1730 | The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Media Slider, Drag Drop Slider, Video Slider, Product Slider, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1730</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Media Slider, Drag Drop Slider, Video Slider, Product Slider, Ecommerce Slider) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via urls in link fields, images from URLs, and html tags used in widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 03:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1057 | The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +10 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1057</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +10 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'button_class'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1480 | Unitronics Vision Standard Unauthenticated Password Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1480</link><description>Unitronics Vision Standard line of controllers allow the Information Mode password to be retrieved without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31994 | Mealie vulnerable to a DoS in recipe image importer (GHSL-2023-228)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31994</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, an attacker can point the image request to an arbitrarily large file. Mealie will attempt to retrieve this file in whole. If it can be retrieved, it may be stored on the file system in whole (leading to possible disk consumption), however the more likely scenario given resource limitations is that the container will OOM during file retrieval if the target file size is greater than the allocated memory of the container. At best this can be used to force the container to infinitely restart due to OOM (if so configured in `docker-compose.yml), or at worst this can be used to force the Mealie container to crash and remain offline. In the event that the file can be retrieved, the lack of rate limiting on this endpoint also permits an attacker to generate ongoing requests to any target of their choice, potentially contributing to an external-facing DoS attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30974 | SQL Injection vulnerability in autoexpress v.1.3.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the carId parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30974</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in autoexpress v.1.3.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the carId parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31993 | Mealie vulnerable to a GET-based SSRF in recipe image importer (GHSL-2023-227)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31993</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, the scrape_image function will retrieve an image based on a user-provided URL, however the provided URL is not validated to point to an external location and does not have any enforced rate limiting. The response from the Mealie server will also vary depending on whether or not the target file is an image, is not an image, or does not exist. Additionally, when a file is retrieved the file may remain stored on Mealie’s file system as original.jpg under the UUID of the recipe it was requested for. If the attacker has access to an admin account (e.g. the default changeme@example.com), this file can then be retrieved. Note that if Mealie is running in a development setting this could be leveraged by an attacker to retrieve any file that the Mealie server had downloaded in this fashion without the need for administrator access. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22905 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ARM mbed-os v.6.17.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the hciTrSe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22905</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ARM mbed-os v.6.17.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the hciTrSerialRxIncoming function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32391 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MacCMS v.10 v.2024.1000.3000 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32391</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MacCMS v.10 v.2024.1000.3000 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32392 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CmSimple v.5.15 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the functions.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32392</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CmSimple v.5.15 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the functions.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31584 | Pytorch before v2.2.0 has an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability via the component torch/csrc/jit/mobile/flatbuffer_loader.cpp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31584</link><description>Pytorch before v2.2.0 has an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability via the component torch/csrc/jit/mobile/flatbuffer_loader.cpp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31992 | Mealie contains a DoS vulnerability in recipe importer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31992</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, The safe_scrape_html function utilizes a user-controlled URL to issue a request to a remote server, however these requests are not rate-limited. While there are efforts to prevent DDoS by implementing a timeout on requests, it is possible for an attacker to issue a large number of requests to the server which will be handled in batches based on the configuration of the Mealie server. The chunking of responses is helpful for mitigating memory exhaustion on the Mealie server, however a single request to an arbitrarily large external file (e.g. a Debian ISO) is often sufficient to completely saturate a CPU core assigned to the Mealie container. Without rate limiting in place, it is possible to not only sustain traffic against an external target indefinitely, but also to exhaust the CPU resources assigned to the Mealie container. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31991 | Mealie vulnerable to a GET-based SSRF in recipe importer (GHSL-2023-225)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31991</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, the safe_scrape_html function utilizes a user-controlled URL to issue a request to a remote server. Based on the content of the response, it will either parse the content or disregard it. This function, nor those that call it, add any restrictions on the URL that can be provided, nor is it restricted to being an FQDN (i.e., an IP address can be provided). As this function’s return will be handled differently by its caller depending on the response, it is possible for an attacker to use this functionality to positively identify HTTP(s) servers on the local network with any IP/port combination. This issue can result in any authenticated user being able to map HTTP servers on a local network that the Mealie service has access to. Note that by default any user can create an account on a Mealie server, and that the default changeme@example.com user is available with its hard-coded password. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4017 | Privilege Escalation in U-Series Appliance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4017</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in BeyondTrust U-Series Appliance on Windows, 64 bit (filesystem modules) allows DLL Side-Loading.This issue affects U-Series Appliance: from 3.4 before 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4018 | Privilege Escalation in U-Series Appliance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4018</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in BeyondTrust U-Series Appliance on Windows, 64 bit (local appliance api modules) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects U-Series Appliance: before 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1681 | Log Injection Vulnerability in corydolphin/flask-cors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1681</link><description>corydolphin/flask-cors is vulnerable to log injection when the log level is set to debug. An attacker can inject fake log entries into the log file by sending a specially crafted GET request containing a CRLF sequence in the request path. This vulnerability allows attackers to corrupt log files, potentially covering tracks of other attacks, confusing log post-processing tools, and forging log entries. The issue is due to improper output neutralization for logs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31450 | Owncast vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in emoji.go (GHSL-2023-277)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31450</link><description>Owncast is an open source, self-hosted, decentralized, single user live video streaming and chat server. The Owncast application exposes an administrator API at the URL /api/admin. The emoji/delete endpoint of said API allows administrators to delete custom emojis, which are saved on disk. The parameter name is taken from the JSON request and directly appended to the filepath that points to the emoji to delete. By using path traversal sequences (../), attackers with administrative privileges can exploit this endpoint to delete arbitrary files on the system, outside of the emoji directory. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32652 | @hono/node-server contains Denial of Service risk when receiving Host header that cannot be parsed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32652</link><description>The adapter @hono/node-server allows you to run your Hono application on Node.js. Prior to 1.10.1, the application hangs when receiving a Host header with a value that `@hono/node-server` can't handle well. Invalid values are those that cannot be parsed by the `URL` as a hostname such as an empty string, slashes `/`, and other strings. The version 1.10.1 includes the fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47435 | An issue in the verifyPassword function of hexo-theme-matery v2.0.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication and access password protected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47435</link><description>An issue in the verifyPassword function of hexo-theme-matery v2.0.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication and access password protected pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3979 | COVESA vsomeip race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3979</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in COVESA vsomeip up to 3.4.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to race condition. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261596.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31546 | Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/damage/view_damage.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31546</link><description>Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/damage/view_damage.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31547 | Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/item/view_item.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31547</link><description>Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/item/view_item.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2440 | Race Condition was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed maintaining admin permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2440</link><description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40745 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40745</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information due to weaker than expected security.  IBM X-Force ID:  236452.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37397 | IBM Aspera Faspex data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37397</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to obtain or modify sensitive information due to improper encryption of certain data.  IBM X-Force ID:  259672.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51795 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_show...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51795</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_showspectrum.c:1789:52 component in showspectrumpic_request_frame</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51796 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/f_revers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51796</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/f_reverse.c:269:26 in areverse_request_frame.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51797 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_show...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51797</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_showwaves.c:722:24 in showwaves_filter_frame</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51798 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a floating point excepti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51798</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a floating point exception (FPE) error at libavfilter/vf_minterpolate.c:1078:60 in interpolate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31552 | CuteHttpFileServer v.3.1 version has an arbitrary file download vulnerability, which allows attackers to download arbitrary files on the ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31552</link><description>CuteHttpFileServer v.3.1 version has an arbitrary file download vulnerability, which allows attackers to download arbitrary files on the server and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51793 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavutil/imgutils.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51793</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavutil/imgutils.c:353:9 in image_copy_plane.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29991 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29991</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27279 | IBM Aspera Faspex denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27279</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a user to cause a denial of service due to missing API rate limiting.  IBM X-Force ID:  248533.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50007 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via theav_samples_set_silence...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50007</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via theav_samples_set_silence function in thelibavutil/samplefmt.c:260:9 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50008 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the av_malloc function in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50008</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the av_malloc function in libavutil/mem.c:105:9 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50009 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_gaussian_blur_8 fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50009</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_gaussian_blur_8 function in libavfilter/edge_template.c:116:5 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50010 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the set_encoder_id functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50010</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the set_encoder_id function in /fftools/ffmpeg_enc.c component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51791 | Buffer Overflow vulenrability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavcodec/jpegxl_pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51791</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulenrability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavcodec/jpegxl_parser.c in gen_alias_map.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51792 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libde265 v1.0.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the allocation size exceeding the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51792</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libde265 v1.0.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the allocation size exceeding the maximum supported size of 0x10000000000.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49501 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the config_eq_output func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49501</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the config_eq_output function in the libavfilter/asrc_afirsrc.c:495:30 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49502 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_bwdif_filter_intra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49502</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_bwdif_filter_intra_c function in the libavfilter/bwdifdsp.c:125:5 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49963 | DYMO LabelWriter Print Server through 2.366 contains a backdoor hard-coded password that could allow an attacker to take control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49963</link><description>DYMO LabelWriter Print Server through 2.366 contains a backdoor hard-coded password that could allow an attacker to take control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37396 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37396</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information due to improper encryption of certain data.  IBM X-Force ID:  259671.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31841 | An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web server fails to sanitize input data, allowing remote unauthenticated attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31841</link><description>An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web server fails to sanitize input data, allowing remote unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32650 | Rustls vulnerable to an infinite loop in rustls::conn::ConnectionCommon::complete_io() with proper client input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32650</link><description>Rustls is a modern TLS library written in Rust. `rustls::ConnectionCommon::complete_io` could fall into an infinite loop based on network input. When using a blocking rustls server, if a client send a `close_notify` message immediately after `client_hello`, the server's `complete_io` will get in an infinite loop. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.23.5, 0.22.4, and 0.21.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22640 | TCPDF version &lt;=6.6.5 is vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) if parsing an untrusted HTML page with a crafted color.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22640</link><description>TCPDF version &lt;=6.6.5 is vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) if parsing an untrusted HTML page with a crafted color.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29183 | OpenRASP vulnerable to a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack in /login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29183</link><description>OpenRASP is a RASP solution that directly integrates its protection engine into the application server by instrumentation. There exists a reflected XSS in the /login page due to a reflection of the redirect parameter. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary javascript with the permissions of a user after the user logins with their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22869 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22869</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  244119.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31846 | An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web application does not restrict or incorrectly restricts access to a resource from a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31846</link><description>An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web application does not restrict or incorrectly restricts access to a resource from an unauthorized actor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31587 | SecuSTATION Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and lower allows an unauthenticated attacker to download device configuration files via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31587</link><description>SecuSTATION Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and lower allows an unauthenticated attacker to download device configuration files via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32206 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component \affiche\admin\index.php of WUZHICMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32206</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component \affiche\admin\index.php of WUZHICMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the $formdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27752 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CSZ CMS v.1.3.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Default Keyword field in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27752</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CSZ CMS v.1.3.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Default Keyword field in the settings function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29029 | memos vulnerable to an SSRF in /o/get/image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29029</link><description>memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service. In memos 0.13.2, an SSRF vulnerability exists at the /o/get/image that allows unauthenticated users to enumerate the internal network and retrieve images. The response from the image request is then copied into the response of the current server request, causing a reflected XSS vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32409 | An issue in SEMCMS v.4.8 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32409</link><description>An issue in SEMCMS v.4.8 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29028 | memos vulnerable to an SSRF in /o/get/httpmeta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29028</link><description>memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service. In memos 0.13.2, an SSRF vulnerability exists at the /o/get/httpmeta that allows unauthenticated users to enumerate the internal network and receive limited html values in json form.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29030 | memos vulnerable to an SSRF in /api/resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29030</link><description>memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service. In memos 0.13.2, an SSRF vulnerability exists at the /api/resource that allows authenticated users to enumerate the internal network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32644 | Evmos&amp;#x27; transaction execution not accounting for all state transition after interaction with precompiles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32644</link><description>Evmos is a scalable, high-throughput Proof-of-Stake EVM blockchain that is fully compatible and interoperable with Ethereum. Prior to 17.0.0, there is a way to mint arbitrary tokens due to the possibility to have two different states not in sync during the execution of a transaction. The exploit is based on the fact that to sync the Cosmos SDK state and the EVM one, we rely on the `stateDB.Commit()` method. When we call this method, we iterate though all the `dirtyStorage` and, **if and only if** it is different than the `originStorage`, we set the new state. Setting the new state means we update the Cosmos SDK KVStore.  If a contract storage state that is the same before and after a transaction, but is changed during the transaction and can call an external contract after the change, it can be exploited to make the transaction similar to non-atomic. The vulnerability is **critical** since this could lead to drain of funds through creative SC interactions.  The issue has been patched in versions &gt;=V17.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32478 | Git Credential Manager (GCM)&amp;#x27;s Debian package does not set root ownership on installed files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32478</link><description>Git Credential Manager (GCM) is a secure Git credential helper. Prior to 2.5.0, the Debian package does not set root ownership on installed files. This allows user 1001 on a multi-user system can replace binary and gain other users' privileges. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32038 | Wazuh Analysis Engine Event Decoder Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32038</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. There is a buffer overflow hazard in wazuh-analysisd when handling Unicode characters from Windows Eventchannel messages. It impacts Wazuh Manager 3.8.0 and above. This vulnerability is fixed in Wazuh Manager 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49275 | Wazuh vulnerable to  NULL Pointer Dereference in wazuh-analysisd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49275</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. A NULL pointer dereference was detected during fuzzing of the analysis engine, allowing malicious clients to DoS the analysis engine. The bug occurs when `analysisd` receives a syscollector message with the `hotfix` `msg_type` but lacking a `timestamp`. It uses `cJSON_GetObjectItem()` to get the `timestamp` object item and dereferences it without checking for a `NULL` value. A malicious client can DoS the analysis engine. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50260 | Wazuh&amp;#x27;s vulnerability in host_deny AR script allows arbitrary command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50260</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. A wrong validation in the `host_deny` script allows to write any string in the `hosts.deny` file, which can end in an arbitrary command execution on the target system. This vulnerability is part of the active response feature, which can automatically triggers actions in response to alerts. By default, active responses are limited to a set of pre defined executables. This is enforced by only allowing executables stored under `/var/ossec/active-response/bin` to be run as an active response. However, the `/var/ossec/active-response/bin/host_deny` can be exploited. `host_deny` is used to add IP address to the `/etc/hosts.deny` file to block incoming connections on a service level by using TCP wrappers. Attacker can inject arbitrary command into the `/etc/hosts.deny` file and execute arbitrary command by using the spawn directive. The active response can be triggered by writing events either to the local `execd` queue on server or to the `ar` queue which forwards the events to agents. So, it can leads to LPE on server as root and RCE on agent as root. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3646 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3646</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3684 | Improper Privilege Management was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3684</link><description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin access to the appliance when configuring the Artifacts &amp; Logs and Migrations Storage. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3470 | Repository administrator can bypass organization&amp;#x27;s ruleset using deploy keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3470</link><description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use a deploy key pertaining to an organization to bypass an organization ruleset. An attacker would require access to a valid deploy key for a repository in the organization as well as repository administrator access. This vulnerability affected versions of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.8 and 3.12.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37400 | IBM Aspera Faspex privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37400</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to insecure credential storage.  IBM X-Force ID:  259677.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32166 | Webid v1.2.1 suffers from an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) - Broken Access Control vulnerability, allowing attackers to buy now an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32166</link><description>Webid v1.2.1 suffers from an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) - Broken Access Control vulnerability, allowing attackers to buy now an auction that is suspended (horizontal privilege escalation).</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31744 | In Jasper 4.2.2, the jpc_streamlist_remove function in src/libjasper/jpc/jpc_dec.c:2407 has an assertion failure vulnerability, allowing att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31744</link><description>In Jasper 4.2.2, the jpc_streamlist_remove function in src/libjasper/jpc/jpc_dec.c:2407 has an assertion failure vulnerability, allowing attackers to cause a denial of service attack through a specific image file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3654 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Teixo by Teimas Global</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3654</link><description>An XSS vulnerability has been found in Teimas Global's Teixo, version 1.42.42-stable. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload via the "seconds" parameter in the program's URL, resulting in a possible takeover of a registered user's session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31745 | Libdwarf v0.9.1 was discovered to contain a heap use-after-free via the dw_empty_errlist_item function at /libdwarf/dwarf_alloc.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31745</link><description>Libdwarf v0.9.1 was discovered to contain a heap use-after-free via the dw_empty_errlist_item function at /libdwarf/dwarf_alloc.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32683 | WordPress WP Ultimate Review plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32683</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Wpmet Wp Ultimate Review.This issue affects Wp Ultimate Review: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0671 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0671</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Midgard GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Midgard GPU Kernel Driver: from r19p0 through r32p0; Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r7p0 through r48p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r19p0 through r48p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r48p0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1065 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1065</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r45p0 through r48p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r45p0 through r48p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r45p0 through r48p0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29968 | SQL Table names, column names, and SQL queries are collected in DR standby Supportsave</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29968</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a when Brocade SANnav instances are configured in disaster recovery mode. SQL Table names, column names, and SQL queries are collected in DR standby Supportsave. This could allow authenticated users to access the database structure and its contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29969 | TLS/SSL weak message authentication code ciphers are added by default for port 18082</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29969</link><description>When a Brocade SANnav installation is upgraded from Brocade SANnav v2.2.2 to Brocade SANnav 2.3.0, TLS/SSL weak message authentication code ciphers are added by default for port 18082.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29967 | In Brocade SANnav before v2.31 and v2.3.0a, it was observed that Docker instances inside the appliance have insecure mount points</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29967</link><description>In Brocade SANnav before Brocade SANnav v2.31 and v2.3.0a, it was observed that Docker instances inside the appliance have insecure mount points, allowing reading and writing access to sensitive files. The vulnerability could allow a sudo privileged user on the host OS to read and write access to these files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2761 | Genesis Blocks &amp;lt; 3.1.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2761</link><description>The Genesis Blocks WordPress plugin before 3.1.3 does not properly escape data input provided to some of its blocks, allowing using with at least contributor privileges to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29966 | hard-coded credentials in the documentation that appear as the appliance root password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29966</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a contain hard-coded credentials in the documentation that appear as the appliance's root password. The vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker full access to the Brocade SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29965 | Insecure backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29965</link><description>In Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1, and v2.3.0a, it is possible to back up the appliance from the web interface or the command line interface ("SSH"). The resulting backups are world-readable. A local attacker can recover backup files, restore them to a new malicious appliance, and retrieve the passwords of all the switches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29964 | Docker instances in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a have an insecure architecture and configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29964</link><description>Docker instances in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a have an insecure architecture and configuration that leads to multiple vulnerabilities. Docker daemons are exposed to the WAN interface, and other vulnerabilities allow total control over the Ova appliance. A Docker instance could access any other instances, and a few could access sensitive files. The vulnerability could allow a sudo privileged user on the underlying OS to access and modify these files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29962 | Insecure file permission setting that makes files world-readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29962</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a have an insecure file permission setting that makes files world-readable. This could allow a local user without the required privileges to access sensitive information or a Java binary.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29963 | Brocade SANnav contains hardcoded keys used by Docker to reach remote registries over TLS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29963</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before v2.3.1, and v2.3.0a, contain hardcoded keys used by Docker to reach remote registries over TLS. TLS connections with an exposed key allow an attacker to MITM the traffic. 
Note: Brocade SANnav doesn't have access to remote Docker registries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29961 | supply-chain attack risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29961</link><description>A vulnerability affects Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a. It allows a Brocade SANnav service to send ping commands in the background at regular intervals to gridgain.com to check if updates are available for the Component. This could make an unauthenticated, remote attacker aware of the behavior and launch a supply-chain attack against a Brocade SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29960 | In the Brocade SANnav server versions before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a, the SSH keys inside the OVA image are hardcoded and identical in the VM eve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29960</link><description>In the Brocade SANnav server versions before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a, the SSH keys inside the OVA image are hardcoded and identical in the VM every time SANnav is installed. Any Brocade SANnav VM based on the official OVA images is vulnerable to MITM over SSH. An attacker can decrypt and compromise the SSH traffic to the SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29959 | Brocade Fabric OS switch encrypted passwords in the Brocade SANnav Standby node&amp;#x27;s support save</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29959</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a prints Brocade Fabric OS switch encrypted passwords in the Brocade SANnav Standby node's support save.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29957 | Encryption key is stored in the DR log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29957</link><description>When Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a servers are configured in Disaster Recovery mode, the encryption key is stored in the DR log files. This could provide attackers with an additional, less-protected path to acquiring the encryption key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29958 | Encryption key in the console when a privileged user executes the script to replace the Brocade SANnav Management Portal standby node.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29958</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a prints the encryption key in the console when a privileged user executes the script to replace the Brocade SANnav Management Portal standby node. This could provide attackers an additional, less protected path to acquiring the encryption key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3600 | The Poll Maker – Best WordPress Poll Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to a missing capability ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3600</link><description>The Poll Maker – Best WordPress Poll Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to a missing capability check on the ays_poll_maker_quick_start AJAX action in addition to insufficient escaping and sanitization in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create quizzes and inject malicious web scripts into them that execute when a user visits the page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3615 | The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3615</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3731 | The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3731</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.47.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3818 | The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3818</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "Social Icons" block in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3560 | The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the _id value in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3560</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the _id value in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3598 | The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Creative Button widget in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3598</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Creative Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22061 | A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22061</link><description>A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23526 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23526</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23528 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23528</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23529 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23529</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23530 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23530</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23531 | An Integer Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23531</link><description>An Integer Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks. In certain rare conditions this could also lead to reading content from memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23532 | An out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23532</link><description>An out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks. In certain conditions this could also lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23533 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23533</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an authenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23534 | An Unrestricted File-upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23534</link><description>An Unrestricted File-upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23535 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23535</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24991 | A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24991</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24992 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24992</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24993 | A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24993</link><description>A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24994 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24994</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24995 | A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24995</link><description>A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24996 | A Heap overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24996</link><description>A Heap overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24997 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24997</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24998 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24998</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24999 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24999</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25000 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25000</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27975 | An Use-after-free vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27975</link><description>An Use-after-free vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27976 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27976</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27977 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27977</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete arbitrary files, thereby leading to Denial-of-Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27978 | A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27978</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27984 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete specific t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27984</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete specific type of files and/or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29204 | A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29204</link><description>A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>