<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-31798 | Identical Hardcoded Root Password for All Devices in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to retr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31798</link><description>Identical Hardcoded Root Password for All Devices in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to retrieve the root password for all similar devices</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31799 | Information Disclosure in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to read the WiFi passphrase via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31799</link><description>Information Disclosure in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to read the WiFi passphrase via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31800 | Authentication Bypass in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to gain a privileged command shell ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31800</link><description>Authentication Bypass in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to gain a privileged command shell via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40704 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40704</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a privileged user to obtain sensitive information from authentication request headers.   IBM X-Force ID:  298277.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42843 | Projectworlds Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the subject parameter in feed.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42843</link><description>Projectworlds Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the subject parameter in feed.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42940 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42940</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42941 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanmode parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42941</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanmode parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42942 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42942</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42943 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42943</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42944 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42944</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42945 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromAddressNat function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42945</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromAddressNat function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42946 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42946</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42947 | An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42947</link><description>An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42948 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42948</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42949 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42949</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42950 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42950</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42951 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the mit_pptpusrpw parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42951</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the mit_pptpusrpw parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42952 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42952</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42953 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPW parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42953</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPW parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42954 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42954</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42955 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42955</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42966 | Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK N350RT V9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42966</link><description>Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK N350RT V9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains the username and the password, via a crafted request to /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42967 | Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42967</link><description>Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains the username and the password, via a crafted request to /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42968 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42968</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42969 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42969</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42973 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSetlpBind function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42973</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSetlpBind function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42974 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42974</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42976 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42976</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42977 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42977</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42978 | An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42978</link><description>An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42979 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ProtForm function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42979</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ProtForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42980 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42980</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42981 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42981</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42982 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42982</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42983 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the pptpPPW parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42983</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the pptpPPW parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42984 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42984</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42985 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42985</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42986 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42986</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42987 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the modino parameter in the fromPptpUserAdd function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42987</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the modino parameter in the fromPptpUserAdd function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42681 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in xxl-job v.2.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sub-Task ID component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42681</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in xxl-job v.2.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sub-Task ID component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43373 | webcrack has an Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability on Windows when Parsing and Saving a Malicious Bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43373</link><description>webcrack is a tool for reverse engineering javascript. An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists in the webcrack module when processing specifically crafted malicious code on Windows systems. This vulnerability is triggered when using the unpack bundles feature in conjunction with the saving feature. If a module name includes a path traversal sequence with Windows path separators, an attacker can exploit this to overwrite files on the host system. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write arbitrary `.js` files to the host system, which can be leveraged to hijack legitimate Node.js modules to gain arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6347 | Unauthorized access to ECU functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6347</link><description>*  Unprotected privileged mode access through UDS session in the Blind Spot Detection Sensor ECU firmware in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) by unauthorized access to the ECU's programming session.
  *  No preconditions implemented for ECU management functionality through UDS session in the Blind Spot Detection Sensor ECU in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to disrupt normal ECU operations by triggering a control command without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7262 | Arbitrary Code Execution in WPS Office</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7262</link><description>Improper path validation in promecefpluginhost.exe in Kingsoft WPS Office version ranging from 12.2.0.13110 to 12.2.0.13489 on Windows allows an attacker to load an arbitrary Windows library.
Using the MHTML format allows an attacker to automatically deliver a malicious library on opening the document and a single user click on a crafted hyperlink leads to the execution of the library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7263 | Arbitrary Code Execution in WPS Office</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7263</link><description>Improper path validation in promecefpluginhost.exe in Kingsoft WPS Office version ranging from 12.2.0.13110 to 12.2.0.13489 on Windows allows an attacker to load an arbitrary Windows library.
The patch released in version 12.2.0.16909 to mitigate CVE-2024-7262 was not restrictive enough. Another hyperlink parameter was not properly sanitized which leads to the execution of an arbitrary Windows library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7833 | D-Link DI-8100 upgrade_filter.asp upgrade_filter_asp command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7833</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function upgrade_filter_asp of the file upgrade_filter.asp. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42679 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42679</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the/ajax/Login.ashx component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42680 | An issue in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain the server absolute path by enterin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42680</link><description>An issue in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain the server absolute path by entering a single quotation mark.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42676 | File Upload vulnerability in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42676</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /nssys/common/Upload. Aspx? Action=DNPageAjaxPostBack component</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42677 | An issue in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42677</link><description>An issue in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /nssys/common/filehandle. Aspx component</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7832 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_get_fullscreen_photos buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7832</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_get_fullscreen_photos of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument user leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42678 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42678</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the /WebSet/DlgGridSet.html component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7830 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_move_photo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7830</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_move_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument photo_name leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7831 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_get_cooliris buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7831</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_get_cooliris of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument path leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7828 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_set_cover buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7829 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_del_photo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43275 | WordPress Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43275</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Xyzscripts Insert PHP Code Snippet.This issue affects Insert PHP Code Snippet: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 08:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7411 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7411</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the /vendor/mobiledetect/mobiledetectlib/export/exportToJSON.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7063 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.6.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7063</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.6 via the 'render_raw' function. This can allow authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level permissions and above, to extract sensitive data including private, future, and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7064 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7064</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7815 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Update Employee Page admin-update-employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7815</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-update-employee.php of the component Update Employee Page. The manipulation of the argument emp_fname /emp_lname /emp_nat_idno/emp_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 04:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7814 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Add Employee Page admin-add-employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7814</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin-add-employee.php of the component Add Employee Page. The manipulation of the argument emp_fname /emp_lname /emp_nat_idno/emp_addr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6534 | Directus 10.13.0 - Insecure object reference via PATH presets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6534</link><description>Directus v10.13.0 allows an authenticated external attacker to modify presets created by the same user to assign them to another user. This is possible because the application only validates the user parameter in the 'POST /presets' request but not in the PATCH request. When chained with CVE-2024-6533, it could result in account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6533 | Directus 10.13.0 - DOM-Based cross-site scripting (XSS) via layout_options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6533</link><description>Directus v10.13.0 allows an authenticated external attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript on the client. This is possible because the application injects an attacker-controlled parameter that will be stored in the server and used by the client into an unsanitized DOM element. When chained with CVE-2024-6534, it could result in account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7812 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System POST Parameter ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7812</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /rental_0/rental/ajax.php?action=save_tenant of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument lastname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7813 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Profile Image insufficiently protected credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7813</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /uploadImage/Profile/ of the component Profile Image Handler. The manipulation leads to insufficiently protected credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25024 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25024</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  281430.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7420 | Insert PHP Code Snippet &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Code Snippet Activate/Deactivate/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7420</link><description>The Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the /admin/snippets.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to activate/deactivate and delete code snippets via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7624 | Zephyr Project Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.101 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7624</link><description>The Zephyr Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.101. This is due to the plugin not properly checking a users capabilities before allowing them to enable access to the plugin's settings through the update_user_access() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to grant themselves full access to the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7628 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.15.2 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7628</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 4.15.2. This is due to the use of loose comparison in the 'verify_id_token' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to an @flutter.io email address or phone number. This also requires firebase to be configured on the website and the user to have set up firebase for their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7811 | SourceCodester Daily Expenses Monitoring App delete-expense.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7811</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Daily Expenses Monitoring App 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/delete-expense.php. The manipulation of the argument expense leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7810 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System view_itprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/view_itprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7809 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System nbproject exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tracking/nbproject/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7808 | code-projects Job Portal logindbc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file logindbc.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7625 | Nomad Vulnerable to Allocation Directory Escape On Non-Existing File Paths Through Archive Unpacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7625</link><description>In HashiCorp Nomad and Nomad Enterprise from 0.6.1 up to 1.16.13, 1.7.10, and 1.8.2, the archive unpacking process is vulnerable to writes outside the allocation directory during migration of allocation directories when multiple archive headers target the same file. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-7625, is fixed in Nomad 1.6.14, 1.7.11, and 1.8.3. Access or compromise of the Nomad client agent at the source allocation first is a prerequisite for leveraging this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7799 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System users.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7799</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/users.php. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7800 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7800</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/ajax.php?action=delete_product. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7797 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7798 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7798</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/ajax.php?action=login2. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43368 | Trix has a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on copy &amp;amp; paste</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43368</link><description>The Trix editor, versions prior to 2.1.4, is vulnerable to XSS when pasting malicious code. This vulnerability is a bypass of the fix put in place for GHSA-qjqp-xr96-cj99. In pull request 1149, sanitation was added for Trix attachments with a `text/html` content type. However, Trix only checks the content type on the paste event's `dataTransfer` object. As long as the `dataTransfer` has a content type of `text/html`, Trix parses its contents and creates an `Attachment` with them, even if the attachment itself doesn't have a `text/html` content type. Trix then uses the attachment content to set the attachment element's `innerHTML`. An attacker could trick a user to copy and paste malicious code that would execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's session, potentially leading to unauthorized actions being performed or sensitive information being disclosed. This vulnerability was fixed in version 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7793 | SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker add-task.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7793</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7794 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System mybill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file mybill.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42353 | WebOb&amp;#x27;s location header normalization during redirect leads to open redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42353</link><description>WebOb provides objects for HTTP requests and responses. When WebOb normalizes the HTTP Location header to include the request hostname, it does so by parsing the URL that the user is to be redirected to with Python's urlparse, and joining it to the base URL. `urlparse` however treats a `//` at the start of a string as a URI without a scheme, and then treats the next part as the hostname. `urljoin` will then use that hostname from the second part as the hostname replacing the original one from the request. This vulnerability is patched in WebOb version 1.8.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27120 | Local File Inclusion in ComfortKey before version 24.1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27120</link><description>A Local File Inclusion vulnerability has been found in ComfortKey, a product of Celsius Benelux. Using this vulnerability, an unauthenticated attacker may retrieve sensitive information about the underlying system. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 24.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40620 | Rockwell Automation Pavilion8® Unencrypted Data Vulnerability via HTTP protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40620</link><description>CVE-2024-40620 IMPACT

A vulnerability exists in the affected product due to lack of encryption of sensitive information. The vulnerability results in data being sent between the Console and the Dashboard without encryption, which can be seen in the logs of proxy servers, potentially impacting the data's confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40619 | Rockwell Automation GuardLogix/ControlLogix 5580 Controller denial-of-service Vulnerability via Malformed Packet Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40619</link><description>CVE-2024-40619 IMPACT

A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability occurs when a malformed CIP packet is sent over the network to the device and results in a major nonrecoverable fault causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42360 | Command Injection in sequenceserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42360</link><description>SequenceServer lets you rapidly set up a BLAST+ server with an intuitive user interface for personal or group use. Several HTTP endpoints did not properly sanitize user input and/or query parameters. This could be exploited to inject and run unwanted shell commands. This vulnerability has been fixed in 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7513 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View Site Edition Code Execution Vulnerability via File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7513</link><description>CVE-2024-7513 IMPACT

A code execution vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability occurs due to improper default file permissions allowing any user to edit or replace files, which are executed by account with elevated permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6078 | Rockwell Automation Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in DataMosaix™</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6078</link><description>CVE-2024-6078 IMPACT

An improper authentication vulnerability exists in the affected product, which could allow a malicious user to generate cookies for any user ID without the use of a username or password. If exploited, a malicious user could take over the account of a legitimate user. The malicious user would be able to view and modify data stored in the cloud.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7507 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix/GuardLogix 5580 and CompactLogix/Compact GuardLogix® 5380 Controller Denial-of-Service Vulnerability via Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7507</link><description>CVE-2024-7507 IMPACT

A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products.  This vulnerability occurs when a malformed PCCC message is received, causing a fault in the controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7515 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix/GuardLogix 5580 and CompactLogix/Compact GuardLogix® 5380 Controller Denial-of-Service Vulnerability via Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7515</link><description>CVE-2024-7515 IMPACT

A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. A malformed PTP management packet can cause a major nonrecoverable fault in the controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7792 | SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker delete-task.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7792</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/delete-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31882 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31882</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.1 and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service, under specific configurations, as the server may crash when using a specially crafted SQL statement by an authenticated user.  IBM X-Force ID:  287614.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37529 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37529</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.1 and 11.5 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service with a specially crafted query due to improper memory allocation.  IBM X-Force ID:  294295.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35136 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35136</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) federated server 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted query under certain conditions.  IBM X-Force ID:  291307.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35152 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35152</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.5 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service with a specially crafted query due to improper memory allocation. IBM X-Force ID:  292639.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50314 | IBM WebSphere Application Server Libery information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50314</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 24.0.0.8 could allow an attacker with access to the network to conduct spoofing attacks.  An attacker could exploit this vulnerability using a certificate issued by a trusted authority to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  274713.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50315 | IBM WebSphere Application Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50315</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 could allow an attacker with access to the network to conduct spoofing attacks.  An attacker could exploit this vulnerability using a certificate issued by a trusted authority to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  274714.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42436 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42436</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42437 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42437</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42438 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42438</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42439 | Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS and Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS - Untrusted Search Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42439</link><description>Untrusted search path in the installer for Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS and Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS before 6.1.0 may allow a privileged user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42440 | Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS, Zoom Rooms Client for macOS -  Improper Privilege Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42440</link><description>Improper privilege management in the installer for Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS and Zoom Rooms Client for macOS before 6.1.5 may allow a privileged user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42441 | Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS, Zoom Rooms Client for macOS -  Improper Privilege Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42441</link><description>Improper privilege management in the installer for Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS and Zoom Rooms Client for macOS before 6.1.5 may allow a privileged user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5915 | GlobalProtect App: Local Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5915</link><description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5916 | PAN-OS: Cleartext Exposure of External System Secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5916</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a local system administrator to unintentionally disclose secrets, passwords, and tokens of external systems. A read-only administrator who has access to the config log, can read secrets, passwords, and tokens to external systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39818 | Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs - Protection Mechanism Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39818</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs may allow an authenticated user to conduct information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39822 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39822</link><description>Sensitive information exposure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39823 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39823</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39824 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39824</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39825 | Zoom Workplace Apps and Rooms Clients - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39825</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps and Rooms Clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42434 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42434</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42435 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42435</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5914 | Cortex XSOAR: Command Injection in CommonScripts Pack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5914</link><description>A command injection issue in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR CommonScripts Pack allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of an integration container.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27267 | IBM SDK, Java Technology Edition denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27267</link><description>The Object Request Broker (ORB) in IBM SDK, Java Technology Edition 7.1.0.0 through 7.1.5.18 and 8.0.0.0 through 8.0.8.26 is vulnerable to remote denial of service, caused by a race condition in the management of ORB listener threads.  IBM X-Force ID:  284573.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28799 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28799</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 displays sensitive data improperly during back-end commands which may result in the unexpected disclosure of this information.  IBM X-Force ID:  287173.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25157 | Authentication bypass in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25157</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.6.0 allows Admin Users with access to the Agent Console to circumvent some permission checks when attempting to visit other pages. This could lead to unauthorized information disclosure or modification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34127 | Adobe Indesign TIF File Parsing Out Of Bound Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34127</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39383 | PoC sample of unknown vulnerability detected by EXPMON system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39383</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39386 | ZDI-CAN-24057: Adobe Bridge AVI FIle Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39386</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.8, 14.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39387 | ZDI-CAN-24047: Adobe Bridge AVI FIle Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39387</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.8, 14.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39388 | ZDI-CAN-24055: Adobe Substance 3D Stager SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39388</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.2 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39389 | Adobe Indesign PDF File Parsing Stack Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39389</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39390 | Adobe Indesign 2024 DOC File Parsing Memory Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39390</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39391 | Adobe Indesign XLS File Parsing Out Of Bound Write Remote Code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39391</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39393 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PCT File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39393</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39394 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PDF File Parsing Out Of Bound Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39394</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39395 | Adobe Indesign 2024 DOC File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39395</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39420 | Talos Security Advisory for Adobe (TALOS-2024-2011)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39420</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. This issue occurs when the state of a resource changes between its check-time and use-time, allowing an attacker to manipulate the resource. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39422 | ZDI-CAN-24090: New Vulnerability Report - Use-after-free remote code execution vulnerability in Adobe Acrobat Reader DC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39422</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39423 | ZDI-CAN-24182: New Vulnerability Report - Adobe Acrobat Reader DC AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39423</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39424 | ZDI-CAN-24309: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39424</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39425 | Security vulnerability in AdobeARMHelper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39425</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability that could lead to privilege escalation. Exploitation of this issue require local low-privilege access to the affected system and attack complexity is high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39426 | ZDI-CAN-24312: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39426</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41830 | Talos Security Advisory for Adobe (TALOS-2024-2009)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41830</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41831 | ZDI-CAN-24569: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41831</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41832 | TALOS-2024-2002 | Adobe Acrobat Reader Font gvar TupleVariation Data Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41832</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41833 | ZDI-CAN-24310: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41833</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41834 | ZDI-CAN-24311: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41834</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41835 | TALOS-2024-2003 | Adobe Acrobat Reader Font Packed Point Numbers Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41835</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41840 | ZDI-CAN-24607: Adobe Bridge JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41840</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.8, 14.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41850 | Adobe Indesign 2024 TIF File Parsing Heap Memory Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41850</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41851 | Adobe InDesign (Beta) has an integer overflow vulnerability when parsing SVG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41851</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41852 | Adobe Indesign 2024 AVI File Parsing Stack Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41852</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41853 | Indesign 2024 EPS File Parsing Heap Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41853</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41854 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PDF File parsing memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41854</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41866 | Adobe Indesign 2024 DOC File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41866</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20789 | ZDI-CAN-24030: Adobe Dimension SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20789</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20790 | Adobe Dimension Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability I, when parsing FBX file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20790</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34117 | Adobe Photoshop 2024 MPO File Parsing Use-After-Free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34117</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 24.7.3, 25.9.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34118 | Adobe illustrator 2024 TIF File parsing Division by zero denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34118</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to render the application unresponsive or terminate its execution. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34124 | ZDI-CAN-24031: Adobe Dimension SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34124</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34125 | ZDI-CAN-24027: Adobe Dimension GLB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34125</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34126 | ZDI-CAN-24028: Adobe Dimension USD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34126</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34133 | Adobe Illustrator CC 2023 v27.9 Vulnerability I</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34133</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34134 | Adobe Illustrator 2023 CC 27.7 Memory Corruption Out-Of-Bounds-Read Vulnerability II.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34134</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34135 | Adobe Illustrator CC 2023 v27.9 Vulnerability II</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34135</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34136 | Adobe Illustrator PSD File Parsing Null Pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34136</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34137 | Adobe Illustrator 2024 CGM File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34137</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS) condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34138 | Adobe Illustrator CGM File Parsing Division By zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34138</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41856 | Adobe Illustrator 2024 GIF File Parsing Memory Corruption vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41856</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41865 | Adobe Dimension Untrusted Search Path lead to load malicious DLL swift.dll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41865</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an Untrusted Search Path vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting a malicious file into the search path, which the application might execute instead of the legitimate file. This could occur if the application uses a search path to locate executables or libraries. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42259 | drm/i915/gem: Fix Virtual Memory mapping boundaries calculation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42259</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/i915/gem: Fix Virtual Memory mapping boundaries calculation

Calculating the size of the mapped area as the lesser value
between the requested size and the actual size does not consider
the partial mapping offset. This can cause page fault access.

Fix the calculation of the starting and ending addresses, the
total size is now deduced from the difference between the end and
start addresses.

Additionally, the calculations have been rewritten in a clearer
and more understandable form.

[Joonas: Add Requires: tag]
Requires: 60a2066c5005 ("drm/i915/gem: Adjust vma offset for framebuffer mmap offset")
(cherry picked from commit 97b6784753da06d9d40232328efc5c5367e53417)</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37028 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37028</link><description>BIG-IP Next Central Manager may allow an attacker to lock out an account that has never been logged in.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39778 | BIG-IP HSB vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39778</link><description>When a stateless virtual server is configured on BIG-IP system with a High-Speed Bridge (HSB), undisclosed requests can cause TMM to terminate.

  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39792 | NGINX Plus MQTT vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39792</link><description>When the NGINX Plus is configured to use the MQTT pre-read module, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39809 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39809</link><description>The Central Manager user session refresh token does not expire when a user logs out.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41164 | BIG-IP MPTCP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41164</link><description>When TCP profile with Multipath TCP enabled (MPTCP) is configured on a Virtual Server, undisclosed traffic along with conditions beyond the attackers control can cause TMM to terminate.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41719 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41719</link><description>When generating QKView of BIG-IP Next instance from the BIG-IP Next Central Manager (CM),  F5 iHealth credentials will be logged in the BIG-IP Central Manager logs.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41723 | BIG-IP iControl REST vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41723</link><description>Undisclosed requests to BIG-IP iControl REST can lead to information leak of user account names.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41727 | BIG-IP TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41727</link><description>In BIG-IP tenants running on r2000 and r4000 series hardware, or BIG-IP Virtual Edition (VEs) using Intel E810 SR-IOV NIC, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7347 | NGINX MP4 module vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7347</link><description>NGINX Open Source and NGINX Plus have a vulnerability in the ngx_http_mp4_module, which might allow an attacker to over-read NGINX worker memory resulting in its termination, using a specially crafted mp4 file. The issue only affects NGINX if it is built with the ngx_http_mp4_module and the mp4 directive is used in the configuration file. Additionally, the attack is possible only if an attacker can trigger the processing of a specially crafted mp4 file with the ngx_http_mp4_module.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34424 | Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34424</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35123 | Uncaught exception in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.14-0, bhs-0.27 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35123</link><description>Uncaught exception in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.14-0, bhs-0.27 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38655 | Improper buffer restrictions in firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow a privileged user to potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38655</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40067 | Unchecked return value in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40067</link><description>Unchecked return value in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via physical access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42667 | Improper isolation in the Intel(R) Core(TM) Ultra Processor stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42667</link><description>Improper isolation in the Intel(R) Core(TM) Ultra Processor stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43489 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10717 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43489</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10717 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43747 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Connectivity Performance Suite software installers before version 2.0 may allow an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43747</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Connectivity Performance Suite software installers before version 2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48361 | Improper initialization in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48361</link><description>Improper initialization in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49141 | Improper isolation in some Intel(R) Processors stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49141</link><description>Improper isolation in some Intel(R) Processors stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49144 | Out of bounds read in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.15-0, bhs-0.27 may allow a privileged user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49144</link><description>Out of bounds read in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.15-0, bhs-0.27 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21766 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Math Kernel Library software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21766</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Math Kernel Library software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21769 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219-LM install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21769</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219-LM install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21784 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21784</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21787 | Inadequate encryption strength for some BMRA software before version 22.08 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21787</link><description>Inadequate encryption strength for some BMRA software before version 22.08 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21801 | Insufficient control flow management in some Intel(R) TDX module software before version 1.5.05.46.698 may allow a privileged user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21801</link><description>Insufficient control flow management in some Intel(R) TDX module software before version 1.5.05.46.698 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21806 | Improper conditions check in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21806</link><description>Improper conditions check in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21807 | Improper initialization in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21807</link><description>Improper initialization in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21810 | Improper input validation in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21810</link><description>Improper input validation in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21844 | Integer overflow in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21844</link><description>Integer overflow in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21857 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Compiler software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21857</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Compiler software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22184 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Quartus(R) Prime Pro Edition Design Software before version 24.1 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22184</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Quartus(R) Prime Pro Edition Design Software before version 24.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22374 | Insufficient control flow management for some Intel(R) Xeon Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22374</link><description>Insufficient control flow management for some Intel(R) Xeon Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22376 | Uncontrolled search path element in some installation software for Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Driver Pack before version 28.3 may allow an au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22376</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some installation software for Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Driver Pack before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22378 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Unite(R) Client Extended Display Plugin software installers before version 1.1.352.157 may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22378</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Unite(R) Client Extended Display Plugin software installers before version 1.1.352.157 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23489 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.6.0.1191 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23489</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.6.0.1191 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23491 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23491</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23495 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23495</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23497 | Out-of-bounds write in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23497</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23499 | Protection mechanism failure in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23499</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 28.3 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23907 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) High Level Synthesis Compiler software before version 23.4 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23907</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) High Level Synthesis Compiler software before version 23.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23908 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Flexlm License Daemons for Intel(R) FPGA software before version v11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23908</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Flexlm License Daemons for Intel(R) FPGA software before version v11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23909 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) FPGA SDK for OpenCL(TM) software technology may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23909</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) FPGA SDK for OpenCL(TM) software technology may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23974 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) ISH software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23974</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) ISH software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23981 | Wrap-around error in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23981</link><description>Wrap-around error in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24580 | Improper conditions check in some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Max Series 1100 and 1550 products may allow a privileged user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24580</link><description>Improper conditions check in some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Max Series 1100 and 1550 products may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24853 | Incorrect behavior order in transition between executive monitor and SMI transfer monitor (STM) in some Intel(R) Processor may allow a privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24853</link><description>Incorrect behavior order in transition between executive monitor and SMI transfer monitor (STM) in some Intel(R) Processor may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24973 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24973</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24977 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) License Manager for FLEXlm product software before version 11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24977</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) License Manager for FLEXlm product software before version 11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24980 | Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd, 4th, and 5th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24980</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd, 4th, and 5th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24983 | Protection mechanism failure in firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 4.4 may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24983</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 4.4 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24986 | Improper access control in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24986</link><description>Improper access control in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25561 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) HID Event Filter software installers before version 2.2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25561</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) HID Event Filter software installers before version 2.2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25562 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25562</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25576 | improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) FPGA products before version 24.1 may allow a privileged user to enable escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25576</link><description>improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) FPGA products before version 24.1 may allow a privileged user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25939 | Mirrored regions with different values in 3rd Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Scalable Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25939</link><description>Mirrored regions with different values in 3rd Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Scalable Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26022 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) UEFI Integrator Tools on Aptio V for Intel(R) NUC may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26022</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) UEFI Integrator Tools on Aptio V for Intel(R) NUC may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26025 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Advisor software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26025</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Advisor software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26027 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Simics Package Manager software before version 1.8.3 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26027</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Simics Package Manager software before version 1.8.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27461 | Incorrect default permissions in software installer for Intel(R) MAS (GUI) may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27461</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in software installer for Intel(R) MAS (GUI) may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28046 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) GPA software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28046</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) GPA software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28050 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics software before version 31.0.101.4824 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28050</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics software before version 31.0.101.4824 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28172 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Trace Analyzer and Collector software before version 2022.1 may allow an authenticated user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28172</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Trace Analyzer and Collector software before version 2022.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28876 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library software before version 2021.12 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28876</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library software before version 2021.12 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28887 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) IPP software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28887</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) IPP software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28947 | Improper input validation in kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST Family firmware before version 02.01.0017 may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28947</link><description>Improper input validation in kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST Family firmware before version 02.01.0017 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28953 | Uncontrolled search path in some EMON software before version 11.44 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28953</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some EMON software before version 11.44 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29015 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) VTune(TM) Profiler software before versions 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29015</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) VTune(TM) Profiler software before versions 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34163 | Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) NUC may allow a privileged user to potentially enableescalation of privilege via loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34163</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) NUC may allow a privileged user to potentially enableescalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39283 | Incomplete filtering of special elements in Intel(R) TDX module software before version TDX_1.5.01.00.592 may allow an authenticated user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39283</link><description>Incomplete filtering of special elements in Intel(R) TDX module software before version TDX_1.5.01.00.592 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7790 | DevikaAI Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7790</link><description>A stored cross site scripting vulnerabilities exists in DevikaAI from commit 6acce21fb08c3d1123ef05df6a33912bf0ee77c2 onwards via improperly decoded user input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39397 | Remote code execution vulnerability in product custom options via file upload and POST /checkout/cart/updateItemOptions/id/{id}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39397</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution by an attacker. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which can then be executed on the server. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction, but attack complexity is high and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39398 | OTP 2FA can be bruteforced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39398</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to perform brute force attacks and potentially gain unauthorized access to accounts. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction, but attack complexity is high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39399 | [Paris] Path Traversal lead to local file read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39399</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. A low-privileged attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to files and directories that are outside the restricted directory. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39400 | DOM XSS through integrations can impact other admins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39400</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow an admin attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's browser session. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, such as convincing a victim to click on a malicious link. Confidentiality and integrity impact is high as it affects other admin accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39401 | Blind RCE in Adobe Commerce support module through a malicious AC Cloud Console config for support/backup_items/code/params/output_file_extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39401</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that could lead in arbitrary code execution by an admin attacker. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39402 | Blind RCE in Adobe Commerce support module through a malicious AC Cloud Console config for `support/backup_items/db/params/output_file_extension`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39402</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that could lead in arbitrary code execution by an admin attacker. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39403 | Stored XSS through Webhook module public key configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39403</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. Confidentiality impact is high due to the attacker being able to exfiltrate sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39404 | A user without Shop Policy Parameters section privilege can alter the shop policy parameters section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39404</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39405 | A user without Send Sales Emails permission can send sales email of order to the customers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39405</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39406 | [Magento Commerce] Limited path traversal allows reading files in var/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39406</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to files and directories that are outside the restricted directory. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39407 | A user without  Credit Memos privilege can create/access credit memos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39407</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39408 | [Spain] CSRF to delete user roles at Adobe Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39408</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could allow an attacker to bypass security features and perform minor unauthorised actions on behalf of a user. The vulnerability could be exploited by tricking a victim into clicking a link or loading a page that submits a malicious request. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39409 | [Spain] CSRF to delete Gift Registry at Adobe Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39409</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could allow an attacker to bypass security features and perform minor unauthorised actions on behalf of a user. The vulnerability could be exploited by tricking a victim into clicking a link or loading a page that submits a malicious request. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39410 | [Magento B2B] CSRF allows attackers to force remove negotiation from a quote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39410</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could allow an attacker to bypass security features and perform minor unauthorised actions on behalf of a user. The vulnerability could be exploited by tricking a victim into clicking a link or loading a page that submits a malicious request. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39411 | A user without Reviews &amp;gt; By Products  permission can export the Reviews Product Report via GET /admin/reports/report_review/exportProductCsv/key/{key}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39411</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39412 | Being able to queue/create newsletter templates without appropriate permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39412</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39413 | An unauthorized user can export the Invoiced Sales Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39413</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39414 | Being able to import/export tax rates without proper privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39414</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39415 | An unauthorized user can export the Tax Sales Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39415</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39416 | Unauthorized user can export Orders Sale Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39416</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39417 | An unauthorized user can export the Shipping Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39417</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39418 | User without `Customers` permission can view/delete customer shopping cart, View Wishlist, Last Ordered Items, Comparison List, etc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39418</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures to view and edit low-sensitivity information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39419 | A user without ship permissions can ship the orders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39419</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6532 | Sheet to Table Live Sync for Google Sheet &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via STWT_Sheet_Table Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6532</link><description>The Sheet to Table Live Sync for Google Sheet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's STWT_Sheet_Table shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6532 | Sheet to Table Live Sync for Google Sheet &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via STWT_Sheet_Table Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6532</link><description>The Sheet to Table Live Sync for Google Sheet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's STWT_Sheet_Table shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38483 | Dell BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker with local ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38483</link><description>Dell BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41864 | Adobe Substance 3D Designer ICO Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41864</link><description>Substance3D - Designer versions 13.1.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4389 | Slider &amp;amp; Popup Builder by Depicter – Add Image Slider, Carousel Slider, Exit Intent Popup, Popup Modal, Coupon Popup, Post Slider Carousel &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4389</link><description>The Slider and Carousel slider by Depicter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the uploadFile function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41858 | Adobe InCopy has an integer overflow vulnerability when parsing SVG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41858</link><description>InCopy versions 18.5.2, 19.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41860 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Vulnerability I, when parsing PSD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41860</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41861 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability I, when parsing PSD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41861</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41862 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability II, when parsing PSD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41862</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41863 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability III, when parsing DNG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41863</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7732 | SECOM Dr.ID Attendance system - Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7732</link><description>Dr.ID Access Control System from SECOM does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 07:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7731 | SECOM Dr.ID Access control  system - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7731</link><description>Dr.ID Access Control System from SECOM does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7588 | Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.87 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Accordion Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7588</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion block in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.87 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7729 | CAYIN Technology CMS - Sensitive File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7729</link><description>The CAYIN Technology CMS lacks proper access control, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to download arbitrary CGI files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7728 | CAYIN Technology CMS - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7728</link><description>The specific CGI of the CAYIN Technology CMS does not properly validate user input, allowing a remote attacker with administrator privileges to inject OS commands into the specific parameter and execute them on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20082 | In Modem, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20082</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01182594; Issue ID: MSV-1529.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20083 | In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20083</link><description>In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08810810 / ALPS08805789; Issue ID: MSV-1502.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36136 | An off-by-one error in WLInfoRailService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36136</link><description>An off-by-one error in WLInfoRailService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting in a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37373 | Improper input validation in the Central Filestore in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin rights to ach...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37373</link><description>Improper input validation in the Central Filestore in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin rights to achieve RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37399 | A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37399</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting in a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38652 | Path traversal in the skin management component of Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38652</link><description>Path traversal in the skin management component of Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve denial of service via arbitrary file deletion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38653 | XXE in SmartDeviceServer in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38653</link><description>XXE in SmartDeviceServer in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7753 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System user_images direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user_images/. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7754 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System check_medicine_name.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7754</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax/check_medicine_name.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7752 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System update_medicine.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7752</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /update_medicine.php. The manipulation of the argument medicine_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38163 | Windows Update Stack Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38163</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7751 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System update_medicine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7751</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /update_medicine.php. The manipulation of the argument hidden_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7750 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System medicines.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7750</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /medicines.php. The manipulation of the argument medicine_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28986 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Java Deserialization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28986</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was susceptible to a Java Deserialization  Remote Code Execution that would allow access to run commands on the host machine.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7749 | SourceCodester Accounts Manager App add-account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7749</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Accounts Manager App 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/add-account.php. The manipulation of the argument account_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7748 | SourceCodester Accounts Manager App delete-account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7748</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Accounts Manager App 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-account.php. The manipulation of the argument account leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7742 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint multiDownload server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7742</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function multiDownload of the file /api/file/multiDownload of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument file leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7743 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint downloadUrl server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7743</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function downloadUrl of the file /api/file/downloadUrl of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument file leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7740 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint download server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7740</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function download of the file /api/test/download of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7741 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint downloadfile downloadFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7741</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function downloadFile of the file /api/file/downloadfile of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42368 | open-telemetry has an Observable Timing Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42368</link><description>OpenTelemetry, also known as OTel, is a vendor-neutral open source Observability framework for instrumenting, generating, collecting, and exporting telemetry data such as traces, metrics, and logs. The bearertokenauth extension's server authenticator performs a simple, non-constant time string comparison of the received &amp; configured bearer tokens. This impacts anyone using the `bearertokenauth` server authenticator. Malicious clients with network access to the collector may perform a timing attack against a collector with this authenticator to guess the configured token, by iteratively sending tokens and comparing the response time. This would allow an attacker to introduce fabricated or bad data into the collector's telemetry pipeline. The observable timing vulnerability was fixed by using constant-time comparison in  0.107.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7738 | yzane vscode-markdown-pdf Markdown File pathname traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7738</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in yzane vscode-markdown-pdf 1.5.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Markdown File Handler. The manipulation leads to pathname traversal. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7739 | yzane vscode-markdown-pdf cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7739</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in yzane vscode-markdown-pdf 1.5.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7569 | An information disclosure vulnerability in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM versions 2023.4 and earlier allows an unauthenticated at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7569</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM versions 2023.4 and earlier allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the OIDC client secret via debug information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7570 | Improper certificate validation in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM Versions 2023.4 and earlier allows a remote attacker in a MITM p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7570</link><description>Improper certificate validation in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM Versions 2023.4 and earlier allows a remote attacker in a MITM position to craft a token that would allow access to ITSM as any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7593 | Incorrect implementation of an authentication algorithm in Ivanti vTM other than versions 22.2R1 or 22.7R2 allows a remote unauthenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7593</link><description>Incorrect implementation of an authentication algorithm in Ivanti vTM other than versions 22.2R1 or 22.7R2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication of the admin panel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7733 | FastCMS New Article Category Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7733</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in FastCMS up to 0.1.5. Affected is an unknown function of the component New Article Category Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7567 | Rockwell Automation Micro850/870 Vulnerable to denial-of-service Vulnerability via CIP/Modbus Port</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7567</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists via the CIP/Modbus port in the Rockwell Automation Micro850/870 (2080 -L50E/2080 -L70E). If exploited, the CIP/Modbus communication may be disrupted for short duration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6079 | DLL Hijacking Vulnerability Exists in Rockwell Automation Emulate3D™</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6079</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Emulate3D™, which could be leveraged to execute a DLL Hijacking attack. The application loads shared libraries, which are readable and writable by any user. If exploited, a malicious user could leverage a malicious dll and perform a remote code execution attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29995 | Windows Kerberos Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29995</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37968 | Windows DNS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37968</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38063 | Windows TCP/IP Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38063</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38084 | Microsoft OfficePlus Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38084</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38098 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38098</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38106 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38106</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38107 | Windows Power Dependency Coordinator Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38107</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38108 | Azure Stack Hub Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38108</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38109 | Azure Health Bot Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38109</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38114 | Windows IP Routing Management Snapin Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38114</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38115 | Windows IP Routing Management Snapin Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38115</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38116 | Windows IP Routing Management Snapin Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38116</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38117 | NTFS Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38117</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38118 | Microsoft Local Security Authority (LSA) Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38118</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38120 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38120</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38121 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38121</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38122 | Microsoft Local Security Authority (LSA) Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38122</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38123 | Windows Bluetooth Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38123</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38125 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38125</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38126 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38126</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38127 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38127</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38128 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38128</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38130 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38130</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38131 | Clipboard Virtual Channel Extension Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38131</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38132 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38132</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38133 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38133</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38134 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38134</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38135 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38135</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38136 | Windows Resource Manager PSM Service Extension Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38136</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38137 | Windows Resource Manager PSM Service Extension Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38137</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38138 | Windows Deployment Services Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38138</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38140 | Windows Reliable Multicast Transport Driver (RMCAST) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38140</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38141 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38141</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38142 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38142</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38143 | Windows WLAN AutoConfig Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38143</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38144 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38144</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38145 | Windows Layer-2 Bridge Network Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38145</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38146 | Windows Layer-2 Bridge Network Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38146</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38147 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38147</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38148 | Windows Secure Channel Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38148</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38150 | Windows DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38150</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38151 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38151</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38152 | Windows OLE Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38152</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38153 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38153</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38154 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38154</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38155 | Security Center Broker Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38155</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38157 | Azure IoT SDK Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38157</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38158 | Azure IoT SDK Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38158</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38159 | Windows Network Virtualization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38159</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38160 | Windows Network Virtualization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38160</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38161 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38161</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38162 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38162</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38165 | Windows Compressed Folder Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38165</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38167 | .NET and Visual Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38167</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38168 | .NET and Visual Studio Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38168</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38169 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38169</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38170 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38170</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38171 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38171</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38172 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38172</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38173 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38173</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38177 | Windows App Installer Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38177</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38178 | Scripting Engine Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38178</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38180 | Windows SmartScreen Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38180</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38184 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38184</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38185 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38185</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38186 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38186</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38187 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38187</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38189 | Microsoft Project Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38189</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38191 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38191</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38193 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38193</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38195 | Azure CycleCloud Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38195</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38196 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38196</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38197 | Microsoft Teams for iOS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38197</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38198 | Windows Print Spooler Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38198</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38199 | Windows Line Printer Daemon (LPD) Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38199</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38201 | Azure Stack Hub Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38201</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38211 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38211</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38213 | Windows Mark of the Web Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38213</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38214 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38214</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38215 | Windows Cloud Files Mini Filter Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38215</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38223 | Windows Initial Machine Configuration Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37015 | An issue was discovered in Ada Web Server 20.0. When configured to use SSL (which is not the default setting), the SSL/TLS used to establish...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37015</link><description>An issue was discovered in Ada Web Server 20.0. When configured to use SSL (which is not the default setting), the SSL/TLS used to establish connections to external services is done without proper hostname validation. This is exploitable by man-in-the-middle attackers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31339 | Improper input validation in ARM® Trusted Firmware used in AMD’s Zynq™ UltraScale+™) MPSoC/RFSoC may allow a privileged attacker to perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31339</link><description>Improper input validation in ARM® Trusted Firmware used in AMD’s Zynq™ UltraScale+™) MPSoC/RFSoC may allow a privileged attacker to perform out of bound reads, potentially resulting in data leakage and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31341 | Insufficient
validation of the Input Output Control (IOCTL) input buffer in AMD μProf may
allow an authenticated attacker to cause an out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31341</link><description>Insufficient
validation of the Input Output Control (IOCTL) input buffer in AMD μProf may
allow an authenticated attacker to cause an out-of-bounds write, potentially
causing a Windows® OS crash, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31348 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31348</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31349 | Incorrect default permissions in the AMD μProf installation directory could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31349</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in the AMD μProf installation directory could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31366 | Improper input validation in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to perform a write to an invalid address, potentially resulting in denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31366</link><description>Improper input validation in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to perform a write to an invalid address, potentially resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21981 | Improper key usage control in AMD Secure Processor
(ASP) may allow an attacker with local access who has gained arbitrary code
execution pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21981</link><description>Improper key usage control in AMD Secure Processor
(ASP) may allow an attacker with local access who has gained arbitrary code
execution privilege in ASP to
extract ASP cryptographic keys, potentially resulting in loss of
confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41613 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Symphony CMS 2.7.10 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML by editing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41613</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Symphony CMS 2.7.10 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML by editing note.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41614 | symphonycms &lt;=2.7.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Comment component for articles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41614</link><description>symphonycms &lt;=2.7.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Comment component for articles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26344 | An out of bounds memory write when processing the AMD
PSP1 Configuration Block (APCB) could allow an attacker with access the ability
to mod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26344</link><description>An out of bounds memory write when processing the AMD
PSP1 Configuration Block (APCB) could allow an attacker with access the ability
to modify the BIOS image, and the ability to sign the resulting image, to
potentially modify the APCB block resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26367 | A malicious attacker in x86 can misconfigure the Trusted Memory Regions (TMRs), which may allow the attacker to set an arbitrary address ran...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26367</link><description>A malicious attacker in x86 can misconfigure the Trusted Memory Regions (TMRs), which may allow the attacker to set an arbitrary address range for the TMR, potentially leading to a loss of integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26387 | Insufficient access controls in ASP kernel may allow a
privileged attacker with access to AMD signing keys and the BIOS menu or UEFI
shell t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26387</link><description>Insufficient access controls in ASP kernel may allow a
privileged attacker with access to AMD signing keys and the BIOS menu or UEFI
shell to map DRAM regions in protected areas, potentially leading to a loss of platform integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46746 | Lack of stack protection exploit mechanisms in ASP Secure OS Trusted Execution Environment (TEE) may allow a privileged attacker with access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46746</link><description>Lack of stack protection exploit mechanisms in ASP Secure OS Trusted Execution Environment (TEE) may allow a privileged attacker with access to AMD signing
keys to c006Frrupt the return address, causing a
stack-based buffer overrun, potentially leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46772 | Insufficient input validation in the ABL may allow a privileged
attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell to tamper with the
struc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46772</link><description>Insufficient input validation in the ABL may allow a privileged
attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell to tamper with the
structure headers in SPI ROM causing an out of bounds memory read and write,
potentially resulting in memory corruption or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23815 | Improper bounds checking in APCB firmware may allow an attacker to perform an out of bounds write, corrupting the APCB entry, potentially le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23815</link><description>Improper bounds checking in APCB firmware may allow an attacker to perform an out of bounds write, corrupting the APCB entry, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23817 | Insufficient checking of memory buffer in ASP Secure OS may allow an attacker with a malicious TA to read/write to the ASP Secure OS kernel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23817</link><description>Insufficient checking of memory buffer in ASP Secure OS may allow an attacker with a malicious TA to read/write to the ASP Secure OS kernel virtual address space, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20509 | An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to perform a DMA read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20509</link><description>An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to perform a DMA read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, potentially resulting in loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20510 | An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, potentially re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20510</link><description>An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, potentially resulting in data corruption or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20512 | A hardcoded AES   key in PMFW may result in a privileged attacker gaining access to the key, potentially resulting in internal debug informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20512</link><description>A hardcoded AES   key in PMFW may result in a privileged attacker gaining access to the key, potentially resulting in internal debug information leakage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20513 | An insufficient bounds check in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker to utilize a malicious VF (virtualization function) t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20513</link><description>An insufficient bounds check in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker to utilize a malicious VF (virtualization function) to send a malformed message, potentially resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20518 | Incomplete cleanup in the ASP may expose the Master Encryption Key (MEK) to a privileged attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20518</link><description>Incomplete cleanup in the ASP may expose the Master Encryption Key (MEK) to a privileged attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell and a memory exfiltration vulnerability, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20578 | A TOCTOU (Time-Of-Check-Time-Of-Use) in SMM may allow
an attacker with ring0 privileges and access to the
BIOS menu or UEFI shell to modify ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20578</link><description>A TOCTOU (Time-Of-Check-Time-Of-Use) in SMM may allow
an attacker with ring0 privileges and access to the
BIOS menu or UEFI shell to modify the communications buffer potentially
resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20584 | IOMMU improperly handles certain special address
ranges with invalid device table entries (DTEs), which may allow an attacker
with privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20584</link><description>IOMMU improperly handles certain special address
ranges with invalid device table entries (DTEs), which may allow an attacker
with privileges and a compromised Hypervisor to
induce DTE faults to bypass RMP checks in SEV-SNP, potentially leading to a
loss of guest integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20591 | Improper re-initialization of IOMMU during the DRTM event
may permit an untrusted platform configuration to persist, allowing an attacker
to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20591</link><description>Improper re-initialization of IOMMU during the DRTM event
may permit an untrusted platform configuration to persist, allowing an attacker
to read or modify hypervisor memory, potentially resulting in loss of
confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31304 | Improper input validation in SMU may allow an attacker with privileges and a compromised physical function (PF)      to modify the PCIe® lan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31304</link><description>Improper input validation in SMU may allow an attacker with privileges and a compromised physical function (PF)      to modify the PCIe® lane count and speed, potentially leading to a loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31305 | Generation of weak and predictable Initialization Vector (IV) in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker with privileges to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31305</link><description>Generation of weak and predictable Initialization Vector (IV) in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker with privileges to reuse IV values to reverse-engineer debug data, potentially resulting in information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31307 | Improper validation of array index in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow a privileged attacker to cause an out-of-bounds memory read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31307</link><description>Improper validation of array index in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow a privileged attacker to cause an out-of-bounds memory read within PMFW, potentially leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31310 | Improper input validation in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow an attacker with privileges to send a malformed input for the "set t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31310</link><description>Improper input validation in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow an attacker with privileges to send a malformed input for the "set temperature input selection" command, potentially resulting in a loss of integrity and/or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31356 | Incomplete system memory cleanup in SEV firmware could
allow a privileged attacker to corrupt guest private memory, potentially
resulting in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31356</link><description>Incomplete system memory cleanup in SEV firmware could
allow a privileged attacker to corrupt guest private memory, potentially
resulting in a loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41711 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41711</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (R6.4.0.136) could allow an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to the phone to conduct an argument injection attack, due to insufficient parameter sanitization. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6619 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource in Ocean Data Systems Dream Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6619</link><description>In Ocean Data Systems Dream Report, an incorrect permission vulnerability could allow a local unprivileged attacker to escalate their privileges and could cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36446 | The provisioning manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE through 7.6 SP1 could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct an authenticatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36446</link><description>The provisioning manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE through 7.6 SP1 could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct an authentication bypass attack due to improper access control. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to bypass the authorization schema.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6618 | Path Traversal in Ocean Data Systems Dream Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6618</link><description>In Ocean Data Systems Dream Report, a path traversal vulnerability could allow an attacker to perform remote code execution through the injection of a malicious dynamic-link library (DLL).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7113 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in AVEVA SuiteLink Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7113</link><description>If exploited, this vulnerability could cause a SuiteLink server to consume excessive system resources and slow down processing of Data I/O for the duration of the attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27486 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiDDoS version 5.5.0 through 5.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27486</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiDDoS version 5.5.0 through 5.5.1, 5.4.2 through 5.4.0, 5.3.0 through 5.3.1, 5.2.0, 5.1.0, 5.0.0, 4.7.0, 4.6.0 and 4.5.0 and FortiDDoS-F version 6.3.0 through 6.3.1, 6.2.0 through 6.2.2, 6.1.0 through 6.1.4 allows an authenticated attacker to execute shell code as `root` via `execute` CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45862 | An insufficient session expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] vulnerability in FortiOS 7.2.5 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45862</link><description>An insufficient session expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] vulnerability in FortiOS 7.2.5 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; FortiProxy 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions; FortiPAM 1.3 all versions, 1.2 all versions, 1.1 all versions, 1.0 all versions; FortiSwitchManager 7.2.1 and below, 7.0 all versions GUI may allow attackers to re-use websessions after GUI logout, should they manage to acquire the required credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26211 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('cross-site scripting') in Fortinet FortiSOAR 7.3.0 through 7.3.2 allows an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26211</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('cross-site scripting') in Fortinet FortiSOAR 7.3.0 through 7.3.2 allows an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Communications module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21757 | A unverified password change in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, and versions 7.4.0 throug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21757</link><description>A unverified password change in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, and versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.1, as well as Fortinet FortiAnalyzer versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, and versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.1, allows an attacker to modify admin passwords via the device configuration backup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36505 | An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.5 through 7.2.7, 7.0.12 through 7.0.14 and 6.4.x may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36505</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.5 through 7.2.7, 7.0.12 through 7.0.14 and 6.4.x may allow an attacker who has already successfully obtained write access to the underlying system (via another hypothetical exploit) to bypass the file integrity checking system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7746 | Use of default credentials at Traccar fleet management solution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7746</link><description>Use of Default Credentials vulnerability in Tananaev Solutions Traccar Server on Administrator Panel modules allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects the privileged transactions implemented by the Traccar solution that should otherwise be protected by the authentication mechanism. 
These transactions could have an impact on any sensitive aspect of the platform, including Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6384 | Backup files may be downloaded by underprivileged users in MongoDB Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6384</link><description>"Hot" backup files may be downloaded by underprivileged users, if they are capable of acquiring a unique backup identifier. This issue affects MongoDB Enterprise Server v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.16, MongoDB Enterprise Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.11 and MongoDB Enterprise Server v7.3 versions prior to 7.3.3</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42736 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in addBlacklist. Au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42736</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in addBlacklist. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42737 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in delBlacklist. Au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42737</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in delBlacklist. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42738 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setDmzCfg. Authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42738</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setDmzCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42739 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setAccessDeviceC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42739</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setAccessDeviceCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42740 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setLedCfg. Authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42740</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setLedCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41623 | An issue in D3D Security D3D IP Camera (D8801) v.V9.1.17.1.4-20180428 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41623</link><description>An issue in D3D Security D3D IP Camera (D8801) v.V9.1.17.1.4-20180428 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6788 | Phoenix Contact: update feature from CHARX controller can be used to reset a low privilege user password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6788</link><description>A remote unauthenticated attacker can use the firmware update feature on the LAN interface of the device to reset the password for the predefined, low-privileged user “user-app” to the default password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38501 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Device Master ICDM-RX/* XSS vulnerability allows HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38501</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a HTML injection vulnerability with limited length to inject malicious HTML code and gain low-privileged access on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38502 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Device Master ICDM-RX/* XSS vulnerability allows stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38502</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use stored XSS vulnerability to obtain information from a user or reboot the affected device once.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3913 | Phoenix Contact: Start sequence allows attack during the boot process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3913</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use this vulnerability to change the device configuration due to a file writeable for short time after system startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5849 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Device Master ICDM-RX/* XSS vulnerability allows reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5849</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a reflected XSS vulnerability to obtain information from a user or reboot the affected device once.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43160 | WordPress BerqWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43160</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in BerqWP allows Code Injection.This issue affects BerqWP: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43165 | WordPress WPSection plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Contributor+ Limited Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43165</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Rashid87 WPSection allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WPSection: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37287 | Kibana arbitrary code execution via prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37287</link><description>A flaw allowing arbitrary code execution was discovered in Kibana. An attacker with access to ML and Alerting connector features, as well as write access to internal ML indices can trigger a prototype pollution vulnerability, ultimately leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43138 | WordPress Event Manager and Tickets Selling Plugin for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43138</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in MagePeople Team Event Manager for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Event Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43140 | WordPress  Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43140</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in G5Theme Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43141 | WordPress Participants Database plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.9.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43141</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Roland Barker, xnau webdesign Participants Database allows Object Injection.This issue affects Participants Database: from n/a through 2.5.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43153 | WordPress Woffice theme &amp;lt;= 5.4.10 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43153</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Woffice: from n/a through 5.4.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35124 | IBM OpenBMC authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35124</link><description>A vulnerability in the combination of the OpenBMC's FW1050.00 through FW1050.10, FW1030.00 through FW1030.50, and FW1020.00 through FW1020.60 default password and session management allow an attacker to gain administrative access to the BMC.  IBM X-Force ID:  290674.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40697 | IBM Common Licensing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40697</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  297895.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41774 | IBM Common Licensing cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41774</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  350348.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43131 | WordPress Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist) plugin &amp;lt; 1.7.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post/Page Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43131</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in WPWeb Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist) allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist): from n/a before 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43135 | WordPress WPCafe plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.28 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43135</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Themewinter WPCafe allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WPCafe: from n/a through 2.2.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39651 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Vouchers plugin &amp;lt; 4.9.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39651</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WPWeb WooCommerce PDF Vouchers allows File Manipulation.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Vouchers: from n/a before 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43121 | WordPress HUSKY plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43121</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in realmag777 HUSKY allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects HUSKY: from n/a through 1.3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43128 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Table Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43128</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WC Product Table WooCommerce Product Table Lite allows Code Injection.This issue affects WooCommerce Product Table Lite: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43129 | WordPress BetterDocs plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43129</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WPDeveloper BetterDocs allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects BetterDocs: from n/a through 3.5.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39642 | WordPress LearnPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.2 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39642</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects LearnPress: from n/a through 4.2.6.8.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38760 | WordPress Send Users Email plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38760</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in David Maucher Send Users Email allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Send Users Email: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38787 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26.8 - Sensitive Information via Imported File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38787</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Codection Import and export users and customers allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.26.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38747 | WordPress HitPay Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38747</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HitPay Payment Solutions Pte Ltd HitPay Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects HitPay Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38749 | WordPress Olive One Click Demo Import plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38749</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Olive Themes Olive One Click Demo Import allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Olive One Click Demo Import: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38752 | WordPress Zoho Campaigns plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zoho Campaigns allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Zoho Campaigns: from n/a through 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38756 | WordPress Coming Soon Page – Responsive Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38756</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Weblizar Coming Soon allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Coming Soon: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2259 | Reflected XXS Vulnerability in InstaRISPACS Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2259</link><description>This vulnerability exists in InstaRISPACS software due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the loginTo parameter in user login module of the web interface of the application. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted input to the vulnerable parameter to perform reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attacks on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38699 | WordPress Wallet System for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.13 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Exported File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38699</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Swings Wallet System for WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Wallet System for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.5.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38724 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Summary and Print plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38724</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Muhammad Rehman Contact Form 7 Summary and Print allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Summary and Print: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38742 | WordPress MBE eShip plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38742</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in MBE Worldwide S.P.A. MBE eShip allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects MBE eShip: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37935 | WordPress Woocommerce OpenPos plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.4 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37935</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in anhvnit Woocommerce OpenPos allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Woocommerce OpenPos: from n/a through 6.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38688 | WordPress Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Igor Benić Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes: from n/a through 8.2.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36398 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application executes a subset of its services as `NT AU...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36398</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application executes a subset of its services as `NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM`. This could allow a local attacker to execute operating system commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39922 | A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA1) (All version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39922</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCE (6ED1052-1FB08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCEo (6ED1052-2FB08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24CE (6ED1052-1CC08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24CEo (6ED1052-2CC08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCE (6ED1052-1HB08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCEo (6ED1052-2HB08-0BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCE (6AG1052-1MD08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6AG1052-2MD08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCE (6AG1052-1FB08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCEo (6AG1052-2FB08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CE (6AG1052-1CC08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CEo (6AG1052-2CC08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCE (6AG1052-1HB08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCEo (6AG1052-2HB08-7BA1) (All versions). Affected devices store user passwords in plaintext without proper protection. This could allow a physical attacker to retrieve them from the embedded storage ICs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41681 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). The web server of affected products is configured...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41681</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). The web server of affected products is configured to support weak ciphers  by default. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker in an on-path position to to read and modify any data passed over the connection between legitimate clients and the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41682 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce restric...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41682</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce restriction of  excessive authentication attempts. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to conduct brute force attacks against legitimate user passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41683 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce a stron...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41683</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce a strong user password policy. This could facilitate a brute force attack against legitimate user passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41903 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application mounts th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41903</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application mounts the container's root filesystem with read and write privileges. This could allow an attacker to alter the container's filesystem leading to unauthorized modifications and data corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41904 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41904</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not properly enforce restriction of  excessive authentication attempts. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct brute force attacks against legitimate user credentials or keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41905 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41905</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not have access control for accessing the files. This could allow an authenticated attacker with low privilege's to get access to sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41906 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application does not ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41906</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application does not properly handle cacheable HTTP responses in the web service. This could allow an attacker to read and modify data stored in the local cache.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41907 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application is missin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41907</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application is missing general HTTP security headers in the web server. This could allow an attacker to make the servers more prone to clickjacking attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41908 | A vulnerability has been identified in NX (All versions &lt; V2406.3000). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41908</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in NX (All versions &lt; V2406.3000). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PRT files. This could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41938 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The importCertificate function of the SINEC NMS Control web applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41938</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The importCertificate function of the SINEC NMS Control web application contains a path traversal vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated attacker it to delete arbitrary certificate files on the drive SINEC NMS is installed on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41939 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41939</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization checks. This could allow an authenticated attacker to bypass the checks and elevate their privileges on the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41940 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly validate user input to a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41940</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly validate user input to a privileged command queue. This could allow an authenticated attacker to execute OS commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41941 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41941</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization checks. This could allow an authenticated attacker to bypass the checks and modify settings in the application without authorization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41976 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41976</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1). Affected devices do not properly validate input in specific VPN configuration fields. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41977 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41977</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1). Affected devices do not properly enforce isolation between user sessions in their web server component. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to escalate their privileges on the devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41978 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41978</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1). Affected devices insert sensitive information about the generation of 2FA tokens into log files. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to forge 2FA tokens of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7715 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi sprintf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6724 | Generate Images – Magic Post Thumbnail &amp;lt; 5.2.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6724</link><description>The Generate Images  WordPress plugin before 5.2.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6823 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.18 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via mla-inline-edit-upload-scripts AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6823</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation involving the mla-inline-edit-upload-scripts AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.18. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7247 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Gallery and Countdown Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7247</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Custom Gallery and Countdown widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39591 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Document Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39591</link><description>SAP Document Builder does not perform necessary authorization checks for one of the function modules resulting in escalation of privileges causing low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42373 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42373</link><description>SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM) fails to conduct proper authorization checks for authenticated users, leading to the potential escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation it could allow an attacker to delete non-sensitive report variants that are typically restricted, causing minimal impact on the integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7092 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 5.9.27 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via no_more_items_text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7092</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘no_more_items_text’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41734 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41734</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform, an authenticated attacker could call an underlying transaction, which leads to disclosure of user related information. There is no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28166 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28166</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
  Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
  network, that could be executed by the application. On successful
  exploitation, the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the
  application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41731 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41731</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
network, that could be executed by the application. On successful exploitation,
the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41736 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Permit to Work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41736</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP Permit to Work
allows an authenticated attacker to access information which would otherwise be
restricted causing low impact on the confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42375 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42375</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
  Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
  network, that could be executed by the application. On successful exploitation,
  the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41732 | Improper Access Control in SAP Netweaver Application Server ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41732</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP allows
  an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link that could bypass allowlist
  controls. Depending on the web applications provided by this server, the
  attacker might inject CSS code or links into the web application that could
  allow the attacker to read or modify information. There is no impact on
  availability of application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41737 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in SAP CRM ABAP (Insights Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41737</link><description>SAP CRM ABAP (Insights
Management) allows an authenticated attacker to enumerate HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33005 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP and Java),SAP Web Dispatcher and SAP Content Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33005</link><description>Due to the missing authorization checks in the
local systems, the admin users of SAP Web Dispatcher, SAP NetWeaver Application
Server (ABAP and Java), and SAP Content Server can impersonate other users and
may perform some unintended actions. This could lead to a low impact on
confidentiality and a high impact on the integrity and availability of the
applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41733 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41733</link><description>In SAP Commerce, valid user accounts can be
identified during the customer registration and login processes. This allows a
potential attacker to learn if a given e-mail is used for an account, but does
not grant access to any customer data beyond this knowledge. The attacker must
already know the e-mail that they wish to test for. The impact on
confidentiality therefore is low and no impact to integrity or availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41735 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Commerce Backoffice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41735</link><description>SAP Commerce Backoffice does not sufficiently
encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)
vulnerability causing low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42377 | Multiple Missing Authorization Check vulnerabilities in SAP Shared Service Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42377</link><description>SAP shared service framework allows an
authenticated non-administrative user to call a remote-enabled function, which
will allow them to insert value entries into a non-sensitive table, causing low
impact on integrity of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33003 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Commerce Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33003</link><description>Some OCC API endpoints in SAP Commerce Cloud
allows Personally Identifiable Information (PII) data, such as passwords, email
addresses, mobile numbers, coupon codes, and voucher codes, to be included in
the request URL as query or path parameters. On successful exploitation, this
could lead to a High impact on confidentiality and integrity of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41730 | Missing Authentication check in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41730</link><description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
Platform, if Single Signed On is enabled on Enterprise authentication, an
unauthorized user can get a logon token using a REST endpoint. The attacker can
fully compromise the system resulting in High impact on confidentiality,
integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42374 | XML injection in SAP BEx Web Java Runtime Export Web Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42374</link><description>BEx Web Java Runtime Export Web Service does not
sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source. An
attacker can retrieve information from the SAP ADS system and exhaust the
number of XMLForm service which makes the SAP ADS rendering (PDF creation)
unavailable. This affects the confidentiality and availability of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42376 | Multiple Missing Authorization Check vulnerabilities in SAP Shared Service Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42376</link><description>SAP Shared Service Framework does not perform necessary
authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges. On successful exploitation, an attacker can cause a high impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7094 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Code Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7094</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection leading to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.6 via the 'storeTheme' function. This is due to a lack of sanitization on user-supplied values, which replace values in the style.php file, along with missing capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. This issue was partially patched in 2.8.6 when the code injection issue was resolved, and fully patched in 2.8.7 when the missing authorization and cross-site request forgery protection was added.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7388 | WP Bannerize Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7388</link><description>The WP Bannerize Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via banner alt data in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38382 | IBM Cloud Pak for Security session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38382</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security (CP4S) 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow another user to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  233672.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7709 | OcoMon URL require_access_recovery.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7709</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in OcoMon 4.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /includes/common/require_access_recovery.php of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.0.1 and 5.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7707 | Tenda FH1206 HTTP POST Request SafeEmailFilter formSafeEmailFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 02.03.01.35 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSafeEmailFilter of the file /goform/SafeEmailFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>