<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:51:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-52108 | Vulnerability of process priorities being raised in the ActivityManagerService module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52108</link><description>Vulnerability of process priorities being raised in the ActivityManagerService module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52107 | Vulnerability of permissions being not strictly verified in the WMS module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52107</link><description>Vulnerability of permissions being not strictly verified in the WMS module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52114 | Data confidentiality vulnerability in the ScreenReader module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52114</link><description>Data confidentiality vulnerability in the ScreenReader module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52115 | The iaware module has a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the system functions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52115</link><description>The iaware module has a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the system functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52116 | Permission management vulnerability in the multi-screen interaction module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52116</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the multi-screen interaction module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause service exceptions of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10005 | EasyFTP MKD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10005</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in EasyFTP 1.7.0.2. Affected is an unknown function of the component MKD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250716.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44112 | Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the device authentication module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44112</link><description>Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the device authentication module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52113 | launchAnyWhere vulnerability in the ActivityManagerService module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52113</link><description>launchAnyWhere vulnerability in the ActivityManagerService module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52109 | Vulnerability of trust relationships being inaccurate in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52109</link><description>Vulnerability of trust relationships being inaccurate in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52110 | The sensor module has an out-of-bounds access vulnerability.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52110</link><description>The sensor module has an out-of-bounds access vulnerability.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52111 | Authorization vulnerability in the BootLoader module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52111</link><description>Authorization vulnerability in the BootLoader module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52112 | Unauthorized file access vulnerability in the wallpaper service module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52112</link><description>Unauthorized file access vulnerability in the wallpaper service module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44117 | Vulnerability of trust relationships being inaccurate in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44117</link><description>Vulnerability of trust relationships being inaccurate in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 07:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4566 | Vulnerability of trust relationships being inaccurate in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4566</link><description>Vulnerability of trust relationships being inaccurate in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 07:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22526 | This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.19.0 of Confluence Data Center.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22526</link><description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.19.0 of Confluence Data Center.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release 7.19.17, or any higher 7.19.x release&#13;
 Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release 8.5.5 or any higher 8.5.x release&#13;
 Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release 8.7.2 or any higher release&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by m1sn0w and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22527 | Summary of Vulnerability
A template injection vulnerability on older versions of Confluence Data Center and Server allows an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22527</link><description>Summary of Vulnerability
A template injection vulnerability on older versions of Confluence Data Center and Server allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve RCE on an affected instance. Customers using an affected version must take immediate action.

Most recent supported versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are not affected by this vulnerability as it was ultimately mitigated during regular version updates. However, Atlassian recommends that customers take care to install the latest version to protect their instances from non-critical vulnerabilities outlined in Atlassian’s January Security Bulletin.

See “What You Need to Do” for detailed instructions.

{panel:bgColor=#deebff}
Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.
{panel}

Affected Versions

||Product||Affected Versions||
|Confluence Data Center and Server|8.0.x
8.1.x
8.2.x
8.3.x
8.4.x
8.5.0
8.5.1
8.5.2
8.5.3|

Fixed Versions

||Product||Fixed Versions||
|Confluence Data Center and Server|8.5.4 (LTS)|
|Confluence Data Center|8.6.0 or later (Data Center Only)
8.7.1 or later (Data Center Only)|

What You Need To Do
Immediately patch to a fixed version

Atlassian recommends that you patch each of your affected installations to the latest version. The listed Fixed Versions are no longer the most up-to-date versions and do not protect your instance from other non-critical vulnerabilities as outlined in Atlassian’s January Security Bulletin.

||Product||Fixed Versions||Latest Versions||
|Confluence Data Center and Server|8.5.4 (LTS)|8.5.5 (LTS)|
|Confluence Data Center|8.6.0 or later (Data Center Only)
8.7.1 or later (Data Center Only)|8.7.2 or later (Data Center Only)|

For additional details, please see full advisory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21672 | This High severity Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was introduced in version 2.1.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

Remote C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21672</link><description>This High severity Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was introduced in version 2.1.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H allows an unauthenticated attacker to remotely expose assets in your environment susceptible to exploitation which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release 7.19.18, or any higher 7.19.x release
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release 8.5.5 or any higher 8.5.x release
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release 8.7.2 or any higher release

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html ). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21673 | This High severity Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

Remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21673</link><description>This High severity Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.0 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H allows an authenticated attacker to expose assets in your environment susceptible to exploitation which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and does not require user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release 7.19.18, or any higher 7.19.x release
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release 8.5.5 or any higher 8.5.x release
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release 8.7.2 or any higher release

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html ). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives ).</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21674 | This High severity Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.13.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

Remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21674</link><description>This High severity Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.13.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.6 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N allows an unauthenticated attacker to expose assets in your environment susceptible to exploitation which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and does not require user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release 7.19.18, or any higher 7.19.x release
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release 8.5.5 or any higher 8.5.x release
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release 8.7.2 or any higher release

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html ). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives ).</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22428 | Dell iDRAC Service Module, versions 5.2.0.0 and prior, contain an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. It may allow a local unprivil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22428</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module, versions 5.2.0.0 and prior, contain an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. It may allow a local unprivileged user to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code on the affected system. Dell recommends customers upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 04:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22362 | Drupal contains a vulnerability with improper handling of structural elements. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22362</link><description>Drupal contains a vulnerability with improper handling of structural elements. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 03:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43449 | An issue in HummerRisk HummerRisk v.1.10 thru 1.4.1 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43449</link><description>An issue in HummerRisk HummerRisk v.1.10 thru 1.4.1 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the service/LicenseService component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51059 | An issue in MOKO TECHNOLOGY LTD MOKOSmart MKGW1 BLE Gateway v.1.1.1 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sessi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51059</link><description>An issue in MOKO TECHNOLOGY LTD MOKOSmart MKGW1 BLE Gateway v.1.1.1 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the session management component of the administrative web interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51257 | An invalid memory write issue in Jasper-Software Jasper v.4.1.1 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51257</link><description>An invalid memory write issue in Jasper-Software Jasper v.4.1.1 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51282 | An issue in mingSoft MCMS v.5.2.4 allows a a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the password parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51282</link><description>An issue in mingSoft MCMS v.5.2.4 allows a a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the password parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41619 | Emlog Pro v2.1.14 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin/article.php?action=write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41619</link><description>Emlog Pro v2.1.14 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin/article.php?action=write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47459 | An issue in Knovos Discovery v.22.67.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /DiscoveryReview/Service/CaseManagem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47459</link><description>An issue in Knovos Discovery v.22.67.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /DiscoveryReview/Service/CaseManagement.svc/GetProductSiteName component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47460 | SQL injection vulnerability in Knovos Discovery v.22.67.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /DiscoveryProcess/Servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47460</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Knovos Discovery v.22.67.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /DiscoveryProcess/Service/Admin.svc/getGridColumnStructure component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49106 | Missing Password Field Masking Vulnerability in Hitachi Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49106</link><description>Missing Password Field Masking vulnerability in Hitachi Device Manager on Windows, Linux (Device Manager Agent component).This issue affects Hitachi Device Manager: before 8.8.5-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49107 | Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information Vulnerability in Hitachi Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49107</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Hitachi Device Manager on Windows, Linux (Device Manager Agent modules).This issue affects Hitachi Device Manager: before 8.8.5-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51810 | SQL injection vulnerability in StackIdeas EasyDiscuss v.5.0.5 and fixed in v.5.0.10 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51810</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in StackIdeas EasyDiscuss v.5.0.5 and fixed in v.5.0.10 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the search parameter in the Users module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6457 | File and Directory Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Tuning Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6457</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Tuning Manager on Windows (Hitachi Tuning Manager server component) allows local users to read and write specific files.This issue affects Hitachi Tuning Manager: before 8.8.5-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48104 | Alinto SOGo 5.8.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48104</link><description>Alinto SOGo 5.8.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7206 | Horner Automation Cscape Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7206</link><description>In Horner Automation Cscape versions 9.90 SP10 and prior, local attackers are able to exploit this vulnerability if a user opens a malicious CSP file, which would result in execution of arbitrary code on affected installations of Cscape.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0565 | Kernel: cifs filesystem decryption improper input validation remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0565</link><description>An out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in receive_encrypted_standard in fs/smb/client/smb2ops.c in the SMB Client sub-component in the Linux Kernel. This issue occurs due to integer underflow on the memcpy length, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 20:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0562 | Kernel: use-after-free after removing device in wb_inode_writeback_end in mm/page-writeback.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0562</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux Kernel. When a disk is removed, bdi_unregister is called to stop further write-back and waits for associated delayed work to complete. However, wb_inode_writeback_end() may schedule bandwidth estimation work after this has completed, which can result in the timer attempting to access the recently freed bdi_writeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 19:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0558 | DedeBIZ makehtml_freelist_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0558</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DedeBIZ 6.3.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/makehtml_freelist_action.php. The manipulation of the argument startid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250726 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 17:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0320 | Cross-Site Scripting in FireEye Malware Analysis (AX)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0320</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting in FireEye Malware Analysis (AX) affecting version 9.0.3.936530. This vulnerability allows an attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload in the application URL to retrieve the session details of a legitimate user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0557 | DedeBIZ Website Copyright Setting cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0557</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DedeBIZ 6.3.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Website Copyright Setting. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250725 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0317 | Cross-Site Scripting in FireEye EX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0317</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting in FireEye EX, affecting version 9.0.3.936727. Exploitation of this vulnerability allows an attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload via the 'type' and 's_f_name' parameters to an authenticated user to retrieve their session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0318 | Cross-Site Scripting in FireEye HXTool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0318</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting in FireEye HXTool affecting version 4.6. This vulnerability allows an attacker to store a specially crafted JavaScript payload in the 'Profile Name' and 'Hostname/IP' parameters that will be triggered when items are loaded.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0319 | Open Redirect vulnerability in FireEye HXTool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0319</link><description>Open Redirect vulnerability in FireEye HXTool affecting version 4.6, the exploitation of which could allow an attacker to redirect a legitimate user to a malicious page by changing the 'redirect_uri' parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0314 | XSS vulnerability in FireEye Central Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0314</link><description>XSS vulnerability in FireEye Central Management affecting version 9.1.1.956704, which could allow an attacker to modify special HTML elements in the application and cause a reflected XSS, leading to a session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0315 | Remote file inclusion vulnerability in FireEye Central Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0315</link><description>Remote file inclusion vulnerability in FireEye Central Management affecting version 9.1.1.956704. This vulnerability allows an attacker to upload a malicious PDF file to the system during the report creation process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0316 | Improper cleanup vulnerability in FireEye Endpoint Security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0316</link><description>Improper cleanup vulnerability in exceptions thrown in FireEye Endpoint Security, affecting version 5.2.0.958244. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send multiple request packets to the containment_notify/preview parameter, which could lead to a service outage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50729 | An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in traccar leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50729</link><description>Traccar is an open source GPS tracking system. Prior to 5.11, Traccar is affected by an unrestricted file upload vulnerability in File feature allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server. This vulnerability is more prevalent because Traccar is recommended to run web servers as root user. It is also more dangerous because it can write or overwrite files in arbitrary locations.  Version 5.11 was published to fix this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22207 | Default swagger-ui configuration exposes all files in the module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22207</link><description>fastify-swagger-ui is a Fastify plugin for serving Swagger UI.  Prior to 2.1.0, the default configuration of `@fastify/swagger-ui` without `baseDir` set will lead to all files in the module's directory being exposed via http routes served by the module.  The vulnerability is fixed in v2.1.0. Setting the `baseDir` option can also work around this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4925 | Easy Forms for Mailchimp &amp;lt;= 6.8.10 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4925</link><description>The Easy Forms for Mailchimp WordPress plugin through 6.8.10 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5905 | DeMomentSomTres WordPress Export Posts With Images &amp;lt;= 20220825 - Subscriber+ unauthorized data export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5905</link><description>The DeMomentSomTres WordPress Export Posts With Images WordPress plugin through 20220825 does not check authorization of requests to export the blog data, allowing any logged in user, such as subscribers to export the contents of the blog, including restricted and unpublished posts, as well as passwords of protected posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6029 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.3.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Posts Deletion and Document Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6029</link><description>The EazyDocs WordPress plugin before 2.3.6 does not have authorization and CSRF checks when handling documents and does not ensure that they are documents from the plugin, allowing unauthenticated users to delete arbitrary posts, as well as add and delete documents/sections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6048 | Estatik Real Estate Plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.1 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6048</link><description>The Estatik Real Estate Plugin WordPress plugin before 4.1.1 does not prevent user with low privileges on the site, like subscribers, from setting any of the site's options to 1, which could be used to break sites and lead to DoS when certain options are reset</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6049 | Estatik Real Estate Plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6049</link><description>The Estatik Real Estate Plugin WordPress plugin before 4.1.1 unserializes user input via some of its cookies, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform PHP Object Injection when a suitable gadget chain is present on the blog</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6050 | Estatik Real Estate Plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6050</link><description>The Estatik Real Estate Plugin WordPress plugin before 4.1.1 does not sanitise and escape various parameters and generated URLs before outputting them back in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6066 | WP Custom Widget Area &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Subscriber+ Menus Creation/Deletion/Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6066</link><description>The WP Custom Widget area WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not properly apply capability and nonce checks on any of its AJAX action callback functions, which could allow attackers with subscriber+ privilege to create, delete or modify menus on the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6163 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt; 2.1.10 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6163</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding WordPress plugin before 2.1.10 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6620 | Post SMTP &amp;lt; 2.8.7 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6620</link><description>The POST SMTP Mailer WordPress plugin before 2.8.7 does not properly sanitise and escape several parameters before using them in SQL statements, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6623 | Essential Blocks &amp;lt; 4.4.3 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6623</link><description>The Essential Blocks WordPress plugin before 4.4.3 does not prevent unauthenticated attackers from overwriting local variables when rendering templates over the REST API, which may lead to Local File Inclusion attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6843 | easy.jobs &amp;lt; 2.4.7 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6843</link><description>The easy.jobs- Best Recruitment Plugin for Job Board Listing, Manager, Career Page for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg WordPress plugin before 2.4.7 does not properly secure some of its AJAX actions, allowing any logged-in users to modify its settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6941 | Keap Official Opt-in Forms &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6941</link><description>The Keap Official Opt-in Forms WordPress plugin through 1.0.11 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example, in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6991 | JSM file_get_contents() Shortcode &amp;lt; 2.7.1 - Contributor+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6991</link><description>The JSM file_get_contents() Shortcode WordPress plugin before 2.7.1 does not validate one of its shortcode's parameters before making a request to it, which could allow users with contributor role and above to perform SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42134 | PAX Android based POS devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.45_20230314 or earlier can allow the signed partition overwrite and subs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42134</link><description>PAX Android based POS devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.45_20230314 or earlier can allow the signed partition overwrite and subsequently local code execution via hidden command.





The attacker must have physical USB access to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42135 | PAX A920Pro/A50 devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.50_20230614 or earlier can allow local code execution via parameter injection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42135</link><description>PAX A920Pro/A50 devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.50_20230614 or earlier can allow local code execution via parameter injection by bypassing the input validation when flashing a specific partition. 





The attacker must have physical USB access to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42136 | PAX Android based POS devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.50_20230614 or earlier can allow the execution of arbitrary commands wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42136</link><description>PAX Android based POS devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.50_20230614 or earlier can allow the execution of arbitrary commands with system account privilege by shell injection starting with a specific word.




The attacker must have shell access to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 13:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42137 | PAX Android based POS devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.50_20230614 or earlier can allow for command execution with high privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42137</link><description>PAX Android based POS devices with PayDroid_8.1.0_Sagittarius_V11.1.50_20230614 or earlier can allow for command execution with high privileges by using malicious symlinks.




The attacker must have shell access to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 13:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4818 | PAX A920 device allows to downgrade bootloader due to a bug in its version check. The signature is correctly checked and only bootloader sig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4818</link><description>PAX A920 device allows to downgrade bootloader due to a bug in its version check. The signature is correctly checked and only bootloader signed by PAX can be used. 




The attacker must have physical USB access to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 13:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20709 | New Edge T5 MSRC Case [DCMSFT-1081]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20709</link><description>Acrobat Reader T5 (MSFT Edge) versions 120.0.2210.91 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 12:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20721 | T5 Acrobat JS vulnerability - Exploitable crash via t5::javascript::get_page_num_words</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20721</link><description>Acrobat Reader T5 (MSFT Edge) versions 120.0.2210.91 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 12:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4001 | Grub2: bypass the grub password protection feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4001</link><description>An authentication bypass flaw was found in GRUB due to the way that GRUB uses the UUID of a device to search for the configuration file that contains the password hash for the GRUB password protection feature. An attacker capable of attaching an external drive such as a USB stick containing a file system with a duplicate UUID (the same as in the "/boot/" file system) can bypass the GRUB password protection feature on UEFI systems, which enumerate removable drives before non-removable ones. This issue was introduced in a downstream patch in Red Hat's version of grub2 and does not affect the upstream package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 11:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5253 | Check Point IoT integration: WebSocket returns assets data without authentication in Guardian/CMC before 23.3.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5253</link><description>A missing authentication check in the WebSocket channel used for the Check Point IoT integration in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, may allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain assets data without authentication.



Malicious unauthenticated users with knowledge on the underlying system may be able to extract asset information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 11:07:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46226 | Apache IoTDB: Remote Code Execution (RCE) risk via the UDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46226</link><description>Remote Code Execution vulnerability in Apache IoTDB.This issue affects Apache IoTDB: from 1.0.0 through 1.2.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 10:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46749 | Apache Shiro before 1.130 or 2.0.0-alpha-4, may be susceptible to a path traversal attack that results in an authentication bypass when used together with path rewriting </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46749</link><description>Apache Shiro before 1.130 or 2.0.0-alpha-4, may be susceptible to a path traversal attack that results in an authentication bypass when used together with path rewriting 

Mitigation: Update to Apache Shiro 1.13.0+ or 2.0.0-alpha-4+, or ensure `blockSemicolon` is enabled (this is the default).</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50290 | Apache Solr: Host environment variables are published via the Metrics API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50290</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Solr.
The Solr Metrics API publishes all unprotected environment variables available to each Apache Solr instance. Users are able to specify which environment variables to hide, however, the default list is designed to work for known secret Java system properties. Environment variables cannot be strictly defined in Solr, like Java system properties can be, and may be set for the entire host, unlike Java system properties which are set per-Java-proccess.

The Solr Metrics API is protected by the "metrics-read" permission.
Therefore, Solr Clouds with Authorization setup will only be vulnerable via users with the "metrics-read" permission.
This issue affects Apache Solr: from 9.0.0 before 9.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.3.0 or later, in which environment variables are not published via the Metrics API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6915 | Kernel: null pointer dereference vulnerability in ida_free in lib/idr.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6915</link><description>A Null pointer dereference problem was found in ida_free in lib/idr.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow an attacker using this library to cause a denial of service problem due to a missing check at a function return.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36770 | pkg_postinst in the Gentoo ebuild for Slurm through 22.05.3 unnecessarily calls chown to assign root's ownership on files in the live root f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36770</link><description>pkg_postinst in the Gentoo ebuild for Slurm through 22.05.3 unnecessarily calls chown to assign root's ownership on files in the live root filesystem. This could be exploited by the slurm user to become the owner of root-owned files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 07:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22028 | Insufficient technical documentation issue exists in thermal camera TMC series all firmware versions. The user of the affected product is no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22028</link><description>Insufficient technical documentation issue exists in thermal camera TMC series all firmware versions. The user of the affected product is not aware of the internally saved data. By accessing the affected product physically, an attacker may retrieve the internal data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0547 | Ability FTP Server APPE Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0547</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Ability FTP Server 2.34 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component APPE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0548 | FreeFloat FTP Server SIZE Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0548</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component SIZE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250718 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0545 | CodeCanyon RISE Rise Ultimate Project Manager signin redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0545</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CodeCanyon RISE Rise Ultimate Project Manager 3.5.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php/signin. The manipulation of the argument redirect with the input http://evil.com leads to open redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250714 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0546 | EasyFTP LIST Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0546</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in EasyFTP 1.7.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component LIST Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250715.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0543 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System propertydetail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0543</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file propertydetail.php. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250713 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0541 | Tenda W9 httpd formAddSysLogRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0541</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formAddSysLogRule of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument sysRulenEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250711. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0542 | Tenda W9 httpd formWifiMacFilterGet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0542</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formWifiMacFilterGet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250712. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0539 | Tenda W9 httpd formQosManage_user stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0539</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formQosManage_user of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250709 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0540 | Tenda W9 httpd formOfflineSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0540</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formOfflineSet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250710 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0537 | Tenda W9 httpd setWrlBasicInfo stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0537</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). This affects the function setWrlBasicInfo of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250707. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0538 | Tenda W9 httpd formQosManage_auto stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0538</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formQosManage_auto of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250708. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0552 | Intumit inc. SmartRobot - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0552</link><description>Intumit inc. SmartRobot's web framwork has a remote code execution vulnerability. An unauthorized remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0536 | Tenda W9 httpd setWrlAccessList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0536</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). Affected by this issue is the function setWrlAccessList of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250706 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 03:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0535 | Tenda PA6 httpd portmap cgiPortMapAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0535</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda PA6 1.0.1.21. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgiPortMapAdd of the file /portmap of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument groupName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250705 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 03:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48383 | NetVision Information airPASS - Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48383</link><description>NetVision

Information 

 airPASS has a path traversal vulnerability within its parameter in a specific URL. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0533 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface SetOnlineDevName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0533</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250703. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0534 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface SetOnlineDevName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0534</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250704. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0531 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface setBlackRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0531</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250701 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0532 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface WifiExtraSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0532</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto2_4g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250702 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0530 | CXBSoft Post-Office HTTP POST Request reg_go.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0530</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CXBSoft Post-Office up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /apps/reg_go.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username_reg leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250700. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0529 | CXBSoft Post-Office HTTP POST Request login_auth.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0529</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CXBSoft Post-Office up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /apps/login_auth.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username_login leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250699. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0527 | CXBSoft Url-shorting HTTP POST Request update_go.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0527</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/pages/update_go.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument version leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250697 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0528 | CXBSoft Post-Office HTTP POST Request update_go.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0528</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CXBSoft Post-Office 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/pages/update_go.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument version leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0526 | CXBSoft Url-shorting HTTP POST Request short_to_long.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0526</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pages/short_to_long.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument shorturl leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250696. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0524 | CXBSoft Url-shorting index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0524</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250694 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0525 | CXBSoft Url-shorting HTTP POST Request long_s_short.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0525</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/long_s_short.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument longurl leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250695. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0522 | Allegro RomPager HTTP POST Request cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0522</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Allegro RomPager 4.01. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file usertable.htm?action=delete of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 4.30 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250692. NOTE: The vendor explains that this is a very old issue that got fixed 20 years ago but without a public disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0523 | CmsEasy language_admin.php getslide_child_action sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0523</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CmsEasy up to 7.7.7. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getslide_child_action in the library lib/admin/language_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250693 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>