<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 06:32:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-13239 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution submit_checkout behavioral workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13239</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Bdtask/CodeCanyon Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution 5. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /submit_checkout. Such manipulation of the argument order_total_amount/cart_total_amount leads to enforcement of behavioral workflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 06:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13238 | Bdtask Flight Booking Software Edit Profile edit unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13238</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Bdtask Flight Booking Software 4. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /agent/profile/edit of the component Edit Profile Page. This manipulation causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13237 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System LogSignModal.PHP sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13237</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /LogSignModal.PHP. The manipulation of the argument U_USERNAME results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 05:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12482 | Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia &amp;lt;= 1.2.35 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12482</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘search’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.35 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 04:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13236 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13236</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/products/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 04:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13235 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13235</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/login.php. Executing manipulation of the argument user_email can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13233 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13233</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /index.php?q=single-item. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13234 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13234</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /index.php?q=product. Performing manipulation of the argument PROID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13232 | projectsend File Editor/Custom Download Aliases cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13232</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectsend up to r1720. Impacted is an unknown function of the component File Editor/Custom Download Aliases. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version r1945 is recommended to address this issue. Patch name: 334da1ea39cb12f6b6e98dd2f80bb033e0c7b845. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 02:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13221 | Intelbras UnniTI usuarios.xml credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13221</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Intelbras UnniTI 24.07.11. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /xml/sistema/usuarios.xml. Executing manipulation of the argument Usuario/Senha can lead to unprotected storage of credentials. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13210 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13210</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/products/index.php?view=add. Such manipulation of the argument PROMODEL leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13209 | bestfeng oa_git_free WorkflowPredefineController.java updateWriteBack xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13209</link><description>A weakness has been identified in bestfeng oa_git_free up to 9.5. This affects the function updateWriteBack of the file yimioa-oa9.5\server\c-flow\src\main\java\com\cloudweb\oa\controller\WorkflowPredefineController.java. This manipulation of the argument writeProp causes xml external entity reference. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13208 | FantasticLBP Hotels Server hotelList.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13208</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FantasticLBP Hotels Server up to 67b44df162fab26df209bd5d5d542875fcbec1d0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file controller/api/hotelList.php. The manipulation of the argument subjectId/cityName results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13203 | code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System addmem.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13203</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /addmem.php. Executing manipulation of the argument studentnum can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13202 | code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System add_to_cart cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13202</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add_to_cart. Performing manipulation of the argument product_name results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13201 | code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13201</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13200 | SourceCodester Farm Management System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13200</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. This manipulation causes exposure of information through directory listing. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13199 | code-projects Email Logging Interface signup.cpp path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13199</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Email Logging Interface 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file signup.cpp. The manipulation of the argument Username results in path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 10:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13198 | DouPHP file.class.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13198</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DouPHP up to 1.8 Release 20251022. This impacts an unknown function of the file upload/include/file.class.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 09:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12983 | Memory Allocation with Excessive Size Value in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12983</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.9 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition by submitting specially crafted markdown content with nested formatting patterns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11865 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11865</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.1 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that, under certain circumstances, could have allowed an attacker to remove Duo flows of another user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11990 | Improper Handling of URL Encoding (Hex Encoding) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11990</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated user to gain CSRF tokens by exploiting improper input validation in repository references combined with redirect handling weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2615 | Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2615</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.7  before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2, that could have allowed a blocked user to access sensitive information by establishing GraphQL subscriptions through WebSocket connections.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6171 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6171</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker with reporter access to view branch names and pipeline details by accessing the packages API endpoint even when repository access was disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6945 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (&amp;#x27;Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6945</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.8 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to leak sensitive information from confidential issues by injecting hidden prompts into merge request comments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7000 | Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7000</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions  from 17.6  before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2, that, under specific conditions, could have allowed unauthorized users to view confidential branch names by accessing project issues with related merge requests.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7736 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7736</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.9 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to bypass access control restrictions and view GitLab Pages content intended only for project members by authenticating through OAuth providers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13191 | D-Link DIR-816L soap.cgi soapcgi_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13191</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. This issue affects the function soapcgi_main of the file /soap.cgi. This manipulation causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 07:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12849 | Contest Gallery &amp;lt;= 28.0.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12849</link><description>The Contest Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 28.0.2. This is due to the plugin registering the `cg_check_wp_admin_upload_v10` AJAX action for both authenticated and unauthenticated users without implementing capability checks or nonce verification. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary WordPress media attachments into galleries and manipulate gallery metadata via the `cg_check_wp_admin_upload_v10` action. It does not enable an attacker to move or upload files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13190 | D-Link DIR-816L __ajax_exporer.sgi scandir_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13190</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. This vulnerability affects the function scandir_main of the file /portal/__ajax_exporer.sgi. The manipulation of the argument en results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13189 | D-Link DIR-816L gena.cgi genacgi_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13189</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. This affects the function genacgi_main of the file gena.cgi. The manipulation of the argument SERVER_ID/HTTP_SID leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12494 | Image Gallery – Photo Grid &amp;amp; Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.12.28 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Image File Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12494</link><description>The Image Gallery – Photo Grid &amp; Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the ajax_import_file function in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.28. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to move arbitrary image files on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12847 | All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp;amp; Increase Traffic &amp;lt;= 4.8.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Media Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12847</link><description>The All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp; Increase Traffic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary media attachment deletion due to a missing authorization check in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.9. This is due to the REST API endpoint `/wp-json/aioseo/v1/ai/image-generator` only verifying that users have the `edit_posts` capability (Contributors and above) without checking if they own or have permission to delete the specific media attachments. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to permanently delete arbitrary media attachments by ID via the REST API, granted they can determine valid attachment IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8994 | WP Project Manager &amp;lt;= 2.6.26 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;completed_at_operator&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8994</link><description>The Project Management, Team Collaboration, Kanban Board, Gantt Charts, Task Manager and More – WP Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘completed_at_operator’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.26 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12182 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Attachment Resize</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12182</link><description>The Qi Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the `resize_image_callback()` function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user has permission to resize a specific attachment. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to resize arbitrary media library images belonging to other users, which can result in unintended file writes, disk consumption, and server resource abuse through processing of large images.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 03:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8386 | AVEVA Application Server IDE Basic Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8386</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(with privilege of "aaConfigTools") to tamper with App Objects' help 
files and persist a cross-site scripting (XSS) injection that when 
executed by a victim user, can result in horizontal or vertical 
escalation of privileges. The vulnerability can only be exploited during
 config-time operations within the IDE component of Application Server. 
Run-time components and operations are not affected.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9317 | AVEVA Edge Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9317</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow a miscreant with read 
access to Edge Project files or Edge Offline Cache files to reverse 
engineer Edge users' app-native or Active Directory passwords through 
computational brute-forcing of weak hashes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64308 | Brightpick Mission Control / Internal Logic Control Unprotected Transport of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64308</link><description>The Brightpick Mission Control web application exposes hardcoded credentials in its client-side JavaScript bundle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64309 | Brightpick Mission Control / Internal Logic Control Unprotected Transport of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64309</link><description>Brightpick Mission Control 
discloses device telemetry, configuration, and credential information 
via WebSocket traffic to unauthenticated users when they connect to a 
specific URL. The unauthenticated URL can be discovered through basic 
network scanning techniques.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64307 | Brightpick Mission Control / Internal Logic Control Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64307</link><description>The Brightpick Internal Logic Control web interface is accessible 
without requiring user authentication. An unauthorized user could 
exploit this interface to manipulate robot control functions, including 
initiating or halting runners, assigning jobs, clearing stations, and 
deploying storage totes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55034 | General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway Weak Password Requirements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55034</link><description>General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway is vulnerable to a weak password requirement vulnerability, which may 
allow an attacker to execute a brute-force attack resulting in 
unauthorized access and login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58083 | General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58083</link><description>General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway 
 is missing critical authentication in the embedded web server which could allow an attacker to remotely reset the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59780 | General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59780</link><description>General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway is missing critical authentication in the embedded web server which 
could allow an attacker to send GET requests to obtain sensitive device 
information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62765 | General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62765</link><description>General Industrial Controls Lynx+ Gateway is vulnerable to a cleartext transmission vulnerability that could allow
 an attacker to observe network traffic to obtain sensitive information,
 including plaintext credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15056 | Ubee EVW3226 Unauthenticated Backup File Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15056</link><description>Ubee EVW3226 cable modem/routers firmware versions up to and including 1.0.20 store configuration backup files in the web root after they are generated for download. These backup files remain accessible without authentication until the next reboot. A remote attacker on the local network can request 'Configuration_file.cfg' directly to obtain the backup archive. Because backup files are not encrypted, they expose sensitive information including the plaintext admin password, allowing full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25125 | Netis DL4322D RTK 2.1.1 FTP Service DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25125</link><description>Netis ADSL Router DL4322D firmware RTK 2.1.1 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the embedded FTP service that allows an authenticated remote user to trigger a denial of service. After logging in to the FTP service, sending an FTP command such as ABOR with an excessively long argument causes the service, and in practice the router, to crash or become unresponsive, resulting in a loss of availability for the device and connected users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4465 | ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Server &amp;lt;= 7.0.3 Remote DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4465</link><description>ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Server versions 7.0.3.4968 (Pro), 7.0.2.4954, 6.5.2.4954, 6.4.2.4681, 6.3.2.4203, and 2.0.1.823 contain a remote denial-of-service vulnerability. The device can be shut down or rebooted by an unauthenticated attacker through a single crafted HTTP GET request, allowing remote interruption of service availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4466 | IPCop &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 Authenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4466</link><description>IPCop versions up to and including 2.1.9 contain an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability within the web-based administration interface. The email configuration component inserts user-controlled values, including the EMAIL_PW parameter, directly into system-level operations without proper input sanitation. By modifying the email password field to include shell metacharacters and issuing a save-and-test-mail action, an authenticated attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands with the privileges of the web interface, resulting in full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4467 | Positive Technologies MaxPatrol 8 &amp;amp; XSpider Remote DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4467</link><description>Positive Technologies MaxPatrol 8 and XSpider contain a remote denial-of-service vulnerability in the client communication service on TCP port 2002. The service generates a new session identifier for each incoming connection without adequately limiting concurrent requests. An unauthenticated remote attacker can repeatedly issue HTTPS requests to the service, causing excessive allocation of session identifiers. Under load, session identifier collisions may occur, forcing active client sessions to disconnect and resulting in service disruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4468 | PLANEX CS-QP50F-ING2 Smart Camera Remote Configuration Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4468</link><description>PLANEX CS-QP50F-ING2 smart cameras expose a configuration backup interface over HTTP that does not require authentication. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can directly retrieve a compressed configuration backup file from the device. The backup contains sensitive configuration information, including credentials, allowing an attacker to obtain administrative access to the camera and compromise the confidentiality of the monitored environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4469 | Denver SHO-110 IP Camera Unauthenticated Snapshot Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4469</link><description>Denver SHO-110 IP cameras expose a secondary HTTP service on TCP port 8001 that provides access to a '/snapshot' endpoint without authentication. While the primary web interface on port 80 enforces authentication, the backdoor service allows any remote attacker to retrieve image snapshots by directly requesting the 'snapshot' endpoint. An attacker can repeatedly collect snapshots and reconstruct the camera stream, compromising the confidentiality of the monitored environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4470 | TG8 Firewall Unauthenticated RCE via runphpcmd.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4470</link><description>TG8 Firewall contains a pre-authentication remote code execution vulnerability in the runphpcmd.php endpoint. The syscmd POST parameter is passed directly to a system command without validation and executed with root privileges. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can supply crafted values to execute arbitrary operating system commands as root, resulting in full device compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4471 | TG8 Firewall Unauthenticated User Password Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4471</link><description>TG8 Firewall exposes a directory such as /data/ over HTTP without authentication. This directory stores credential files for previously logged-in users. A remote unauthenticated attacker can enumerate and download files within the directory to obtain valid account usernames and passwords, leading to loss of confidentiality and further unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4985 | Vodafone H500s WiFi Password Disclosure via activation.json</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4985</link><description>Vodafone H500s devices running firmware v3.5.10 (hardware model Sercomm VFH500) expose the WiFi access point password via an unauthenticated HTTP endpoint. By sending a crafted GET request to /data/activation.json with specific headers and cookies, a remote attacker can retrieve a JSON document that contains the wifi_password field. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the WiFi credentials and gain unauthorized access to the wireless network, compromising confidentiality of network traffic and attached systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7328 | Screen SFT DAB 600/C &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 Unauthenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7328</link><description>Screen SFT DAB 600/C firmware versions up to and including 1.9.3 contain an improper access control on the user management API allows unauthenticated requests to retrieve structured user data, including account names and connection metadata such as client IP and timeout values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13188 | D-Link DIR-816L authentication.cgi authenticationcgi_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13188</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. Affected by this vulnerability is the function authenticationcgi_main of the file /authentication.cgi. Performing manipulation of the argument Password results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13187 | Intelbras ICIP acessodeusuario.xml credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13187</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Intelbras ICIP 2.0.20. Affected is an unknown function of the file /xml/sistema/acessodeusuario.xml. Such manipulation of the argument NomeUsuario/SenhaAcess leads to unprotected storage of credentials. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13186 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution manage_customer cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13186</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Bdtask/CodeCanyon Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution up to 4.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /dashboard/Ccustomer/manage_customer. This manipulation of the argument Search causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13185 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon News365 profile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13185</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Bdtask/CodeCanyon News365 up to 7.0.3. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/dashboard/profile. The manipulation of the argument profile_image/banner_image results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63745 | A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability was discovered in radare2 6.0.5 and earlier within the info() function of bin_ne.c. A crafted binar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63745</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability was discovered in radare2 6.0.5 and earlier within the info() function of bin_ne.c. A crafted binary input can trigger a segmentation fault, leading to a denial of service when the tool processes malformed data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13182 | pojoin h3blog addtitle cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13182</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in pojoin h3blog 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/cms/category/addtitle. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63744 | A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability was discovered in radare2 6.0.5 and earlier within the load() function of bin_dyldcache.c. Processi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63744</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability was discovered in radare2 6.0.5 and earlier within the load() function of bin_dyldcache.c. Processing a crafted file can cause a segmentation fault and crash the program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64084 | An authenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in Cloudlog 2.7.5 and earlier. The vucc_details_ajax function in application/controllers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64084</link><description>An authenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in Cloudlog 2.7.5 and earlier. The vucc_details_ajax function in application/controllers/Awards.php does not properly sanitize the user-supplied Gridsquare POST parameter. This allows a remote, authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands by injecting a malicious payload, which is then concatenated directly into a raw SQL query in the vucc_qso_details function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63891 | Information Disclosure in web-accessible backup file in SourceCodester Simple Online Book Store System allows a remote unauthenticated attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63891</link><description>Information Disclosure in web-accessible backup file in SourceCodester Simple Online Book Store System allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to disclose full database contents (including schema and credential hashes) via an unauthenticated HTTP GET request to /obs/database/obs_db.sql.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13181 | pojoin h3blog add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13181</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in pojoin h3blog 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/cms/material/add. Executing manipulation of the argument Name can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63701 | A heap corruption vulnerability exists in the Advantech TP-3250 printer driver's DrvUI_x64_ADVANTECH.dll (v0.3.9200.20789) when DocumentProp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63701</link><description>A heap corruption vulnerability exists in the Advantech TP-3250 printer driver's DrvUI_x64_ADVANTECH.dll (v0.3.9200.20789) when DocumentPropertiesW() is called with a valid dmDriverExtra value but an undersized output buffer. The driver incorrectly assumes the output buffer size matches the input buffer size, leading to invalid memory operations and heap corruption. This vulnerability can cause denial of service through application crashes and potentially lead to code execution in user space. Local access is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13033 | Nodemailer: nodemailer: email to an unintended domain can occur due to interpretation conflict</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13033</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the email parsing library due to improper handling of specially formatted recipient email addresses. An attacker can exploit this flaw by crafting a recipient address that embeds an external address within quotes. This causes the application to misdirect the email to the attacker's external address instead of the intended internal recipient. This could lead to a significant data leak of sensitive information and allow an attacker to bypass security filters and access controls.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13179 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon Wholesale Inventory Control and Inventory Management System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13179</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask/CodeCanyon Wholesale Inventory Control and Inventory Management System up to 20250320. This issue affects some unknown processing. Such manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13180 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon Wholesale Inventory Control and Inventory Management System edit_profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13180</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask/CodeCanyon Wholesale Inventory Control and Inventory Management System up to 20250320. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /edit_profile. Performing manipulation of the argument first_name/last_name results in basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13177 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon SalesERP cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13177</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Bdtask/CodeCanyon SalesERP up to 20250728. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation results in cross-site request forgery. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13178 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon SalesERP User Profile edit_profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13178</link><description>A flaw has been found in Bdtask/CodeCanyon SalesERP up to 20250728. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit_profile of the component User Profile Handler. This manipulation of the argument first_name/last_name causes basic cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63291 | When processing API requests, the Alteryx server 2022.1.1.42654 and 2024.1 used MongoDB object IDs to uniquely identify the data being reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63291</link><description>When processing API requests, the Alteryx server 2022.1.1.42654 and 2024.1 used MongoDB object IDs to uniquely identify the data being requested by the caller. The Alteryx server did not check whether the authenticated user had permission to access the specified MongoDB object ID. By specifying particlar MongoDB object IDs, callers could obtain records for other users without proper authorization. Records retrievable using this attack included administrative API keys and private studio api keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13174 | rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss Webhook mps.py do_job server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13174</link><description>A weakness has been identified in rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss up to 1.4.7. Affected by this vulnerability is the function do_job of the file /rachelos/we-mp-rss/blob/main/jobs/mps.py of the component Webhook Module. Executing manipulation of the argument web_hook_url can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63680 | Nero BackItUp in the Nero Productline is vulnerable to a path parsing/UI rendering flaw (CWE-22) that, in combination with Windows ShellExec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63680</link><description>Nero BackItUp in the Nero Productline is vulnerable to a path parsing/UI rendering flaw (CWE-22) that, in combination with Windows ShellExecuteW fallback extension resolution, leads to arbitrary code execution when a user clicks a crafted entry. By creating a trailing-dot folder and placing a same-basename script, Nero BackItUp renders the file as a folder icon and then invokes ShellExecuteW, which executes the script via PATHEXT fallback (.COM/.EXE/.BAT/.CMD). The issue affects recent Nero BackItUp product lines (2019-2025 and earlier) and has been acknowledged by the vendor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13172 | CodeAstro Gym Management System view-member-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13172</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/view-member-report.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63724 | SQL injection (SQL-i) vulnerability in SVX Portal 2.7A via crafted POST request to admin/update_setings.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63724</link><description>SQL injection (SQL-i) vulnerability in SVX Portal 2.7A via crafted POST request to admin/update_setings.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4617 | Prisma Browser: Insufficient Policy Enforcement Vulnerability in Prisma Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4617</link><description>An insufficient policy enforcement vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma® Browser on Windows allows a locally authenticated non-admin user to bypass the screenshot control feature of the browser.


Browser self-protection should be enabled to mitigate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4618 | Prisma Browser: Sensitive Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Prisma Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4618</link><description>A sensitive information disclosure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma® Browser allows a locally authenticated non-admin user to retrieve sensitive data from Prisma Browser.

Browser self-protection should be enabled to mitigate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54345 | An issue was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. Sensitive Information is exposed to an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54345</link><description>An issue was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. Sensitive Information is exposed to an Unauthorized Actor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54560 | A Server-side Request Forgery vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54560</link><description>A Server-side Request Forgery vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows Probing of internal infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54342 | A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There is Exposure of Sensitive I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54342</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There is Exposure of Sensitive Information because of Incompatible Policies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54559 | An issue was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows remote Path Traversal for l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54559</link><description>An issue was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows remote Path Traversal for loading arbitrary external content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63725 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SVX Portal 2.7A via the id parameter to Recivers.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63725</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SVX Portal 2.7A via the id parameter to Recivers.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54348 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54348</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows an attacker to hijack user’s browser, capturing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54561 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54561</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows remote access to content despite lack of the correct permission through a Broken Authorization Schema.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54562 | A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows Technical Informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows Technical Information to be Disclosed through stack trace.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13171 | ZZCMS wangkan_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13171</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ZZCMS 2023. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/wangkan_list.php. Such manipulation of the argument keyword leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4616 | Prisma Browser: Insufficient Validation of Untrusted Input Vulnerability in Prisma Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4616</link><description>An insufficient validation of an untrusted input vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma® Browser allows a locally authenticated non-admin user to revert the browser’s security controls.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54340 | A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There is a Broken or Risky Crypt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54340</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There is a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54343 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54343</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 exploitable remotely for Escalation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54346 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54346</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows an attacker to hijack user’s browser, capturing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54339 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54339</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 exploitable remotely for Escalation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63830 | CKFinder 1.4.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the File Upload function. An attacker can upload a crafted SVG containing acti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63830</link><description>CKFinder 1.4.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the File Upload function. An attacker can upload a crafted SVG containing active content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13204 | CVE-2025-13204</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13204</link><description>npm package `expr-eval` is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution. An attacker with access to express eval interface can use JavaScript prototype-based inheritance model to achieve arbitrary code execution. The npm expr-eval-fork package resolves this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44639 | PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the sub1, sub2, sub3, sub4, and course-short parameters in add-subj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44639</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the sub1, sub2, sub3, sub4, and course-short parameters in add-subject.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44640 | PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the course-short, course-full, and cdate parameters in add-course.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44640</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the course-short, course-full, and cdate parameters in add-course.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55016 | PHPGurukul Student Record Management System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the id and password parameters in login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55016</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record Management System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the id and password parameters in login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13170 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System edit_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13170</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit_account.php. Performing manipulation of the argument admin_id results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8870 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS, certain serial console input might result in an unexpected reload of the device.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8870</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS, certain serial console input might result in an unexpected reload of the device.153</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44630 | Multiple parameters in register.php in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 are vulnerable to SQL injection. These include: c-full, fname, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44630</link><description>Multiple parameters in register.php in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 are vulnerable to SQL injection. These include: c-full, fname, mname,lname, gname, ocp, nation, mobno, email, board1, roll1, pyear1, board2, roll2, pyear2, sub1,marks1, sub2, course-short, income, category, ph, country, state, city, padd, cadd, and gender.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64446 | A relative path traversal vulnerability in Fortinet FortiWeb 8.0.0 through 8.0.1, FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, FortiWeb 7.4.0 through 7.4.9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64446</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability in Fortinet FortiWeb 8.0.0 through 8.0.1, FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, FortiWeb 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiWeb 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, FortiWeb 7.0.0 through 7.0.11 may allow an attacker to execute administrative commands on the system via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44636 | PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the adminname and aemailid parameters in /admin-profile.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44636</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the adminname and aemailid parameters in /admin-profile.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44632 | PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the id and emailid parameters in password-recovery.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44632</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the id and emailid parameters in password-recovery.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44635 | PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via adminname and aemailid parameters in /admin-profile.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44635</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via adminname and aemailid parameters in /admin-profile.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42749 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Alto CMS v.1.1.13 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42749</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Alto CMS v.1.1.13 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44633 | PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the currentpassword parameter in change-password.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44633</link><description>PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the currentpassword parameter in change-password.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13169 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System add_query_reserve.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13169</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add_query_reserve.php. Such manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13168 | ury-erp ury pos_extend.py overrided_past_order_list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13168</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ury-erp ury up to 0.2.0. This affects the function overrided_past_order_list of the file ury/ury/api/pos_extend.py. This manipulation of the argument search_term causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Upgrading to version 0.2.1 is able to mitigate this issue. Patch name: 063384e0dddfd191847cd2d6524c342cc380b058. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. The vendor replied and reacted very professional.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21635 | Memos Access Tokens Stay Valid after User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21635</link><description>Memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service that uses Access Tokens to authenticate application access. When a user changes their password, the existing list of Access Tokens stay valid instead of expiring. If a user finds that their account has been compromised, they can update their password. In versions up to and including 0.18.1, though, the bad actor will still have access to their account because the bad actor's Access Token stays on the list as a valid token. The user will have to manually delete the bad actor's Access Token to secure their account. The list of Access Tokens has a generic Description which makes it hard to pinpoint a bad actor in a list of Access Tokens. A known patched version of Memos isn't available. To improve Memos security, all Access Tokens will need to be revoked when a user changes their password. This removes the session for all the user's devices and prompts the user to log in again. One can treat the old Access Tokens as "invalid" because those Access Tokens were created with the older password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 14:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12149 | Unauthorized access to documents protected by Document-Level Security (DLS), when Signal&amp;#x27;s watches include a search query involving protected documents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12149</link><description>In Search Guard FLX versions 3.1.2 and earlier, while Document-Level Security (DLS) is correctly enforced elsewhere, when the search is trigged from a Signal's watch, the DLS rule is not enforced, allowing access to all documents in the queried indices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 14:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11918 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Simulation Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11918</link><description>Rockwell Automation Arena® suffers from a
stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the
parsing of DOE files. Local attackers are able to exploit this issue to
potentially execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Arena®. Exploiting
the vulnerability requires opening a malicious DOE file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10018 | Multiple Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10018</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to multiple Stored XSS in language editor functionality (languages). Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed on every page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9982 | Hard-coded admin credentials in Quick.CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9982</link><description>A vulnerability exists in QuickCMS version 6.8 where sensitive admin credentials are hardcoded in a configuration file and stored in plaintext. This flaw allows attackers with access to the source code or the server file system to retrieve authentication details, potentially leading to privilege escalation.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8855 | 2FA Expiry Bypass in Optimus Software&amp;#x27;s Brokerage Automation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8855</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key, Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password, Authentication Bypass by Assumed-Immutable Data vulnerability in Optimus Software Brokerage Automation allows Exploiting Trust in Client, Authentication Bypass, Manipulate Registry Information.This issue affects Brokerage Automation: before 1.1.71.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:06:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11981 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.23 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11981</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'SCodes' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.23 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 11:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11794 | Password hash and MFA secret returned in user email verification endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11794</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.3, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.11, 10.12.x &lt;= 10.12.0 fail to sanitize user data which allows system administrators to access password hashes and MFA secrets via the POST /api/v4/users/{user_id}/email/verify/member endpoint</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 10:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11776 | Guest user can discover archived public channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11776</link><description>Mattermost versions &lt;11 fail to properly restrict access to archived channel search API which allows guest users to discover archived public channels via the `/api/v4/teams/{team_id}/channels/search_archived` endpoint</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 08:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41436 | Unauthorized access to archived channel content via threads interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41436</link><description>Mattermost versions &lt;11.0 fail to properly enforce the "Allow users to view archived channels" setting which allows regular users to access archived channel content and files via the "Open in Channel" functionality from followed threads</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 08:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55070 | Lack of MFA enforcement in WebSocket connections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55070</link><description>Mattermost versions &lt;11 fail to enforce multi-factor authentication on WebSocket connections which allows unauthenticated users to access sensitive information via WebSocket events</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 08:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55073 | MS Teams plugin OAuth allows editing arbitrary posts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55073</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.3, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.11, 10.12.x &lt;= 10.12.0 fail to validate the relationship between the post being updated and the MSTeams plugin OAuth flow which allows an attacker to edit arbitrary posts via a crafted MSTeams plugin OAuth redirect URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 08:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10686 | Creta Testimonial Showcase &amp;lt; 1.2.4 - Editor+ Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10686</link><description>The Creta Testimonial Showcase WordPress plugin before 1.2.4 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 06:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64444 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in NCP-HG100 1.4.48.16 and earlier. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64444</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in NCP-HG100 1.4.48.16 and earlier. If exploited, a remote attacker who has obtained the authentication information to log in to the management page of the product may execute an arbitrary OS command with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 05:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13160 | IQ Service International｜IQ-Support - Exposure of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13160</link><description>IQ-Support developed by IQ Service International has a Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access specific APIs to obtain sensitive information from the internal network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13161 | IQ Service International｜IQ-Support - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13161</link><description>IQ-Support developed by IQ Service International has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11919 | Inappropriate implementation in Intents in Google Chrome on Android prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11919</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Intents in Google Chrome on Android prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11920 | Inappropriate implementation in Dawn in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 130.0.6723.92 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11920</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Dawn in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 130.0.6723.92 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13178 | Inappropriate implementation in Fullscreen in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.84 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13178</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Fullscreen in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.84 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13983 | Inappropriate implementation in Lens in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13983</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Lens in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted QR code. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7017 | Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.182 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7017</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.182 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7021 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 124.0.6367.60 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7021</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 124.0.6367.60 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9126 | Use after free in Internals in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9126</link><description>Use after free in Internals in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a series of curated UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12904 | SNORDIAN&amp;#x27;s H5PxAPIkatchu &amp;lt;= 0.4.17 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via insert_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12904</link><description>The SNORDIAN's H5PxAPIkatchu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'insert_data' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13097 | Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13097</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13102 | Inappropriate implementation in WebApp Installs in Google Chrome on Android prior to 134.0.6998.35 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13102</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in WebApp Installs in Google Chrome on Android prior to 134.0.6998.35 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13107 | Inappropriate implementation in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13107</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9479 | Out of bounds read in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.141 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9479</link><description>Out of bounds read in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.141 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>