<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-25891 | Fiber has an Arbitrary File Read in Static Middleware on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25891</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. A Path Traversal (CWE-22) vulnerability in Fiber allows a remote attacker to bypass the static middleware sanitizer and read arbitrary files on the server file system on Windows. This affects Fiber v3 through version 3.0.0. This has been patched in Fiber v3 version 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25899 | Fiber is Vulnerable to Denial of Service via Flash Cookie Unbounded Allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25899</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. In versions on the v3 branch prior to 3.1.0, the use of the `fiber_flash` cookie can force an unbounded allocation on any server. A crafted 10-character cookie value triggers an attempt to allocate up to 85GB of memory via unvalidated msgpack deserialization. No authentication is required. Every GoFiber v3 endpoint is affected regardless of whether the application uses flash messages. Version 3.1.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27195 | Wasmtime is vulnerable to panic when dropping a `[Typed]Func::call_async` future</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27195</link><description>Wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. Starting with Wasmtime 39.0.0, the `component-model-async` feature became the default, which brought with it a new implementation of `[Typed]Func::call_async` which made it capable of calling async-typed guest export functions.  However, that implementation had a bug leading to a panic under certain circumstances: First, the host embedding calls `[Typed]Func::call_async` on a function exported by a component, polling the returned `Future` once. Second, the component function yields control to the async runtime (e.g. Tokio), e.g. due to a call to host function registered using `LinkerInstance::func_wrap_async` which yields, or due an epoch interruption. Third, the host embedding drops the `Future` after polling it once.  This leaves the component instance in a non-reenterable state since the call never had a chance to complete. Fourth, the host embedding calls `[Typed]Func::call_async` again, polling the returned `Future`.  Since the component instance cannot be entered at this point, the call traps, but not before allocating a task and thread for the call. Fifth, the host embedding ignores the trap and drops the `Future`.  This panics due to the runtime attempting to dispose of the task created above, which panics since the thread has not yet exited. When a host embedder using the affected versions of Wasmtime calls `wasmtime::component::[Typed]Func::call_async` on a guest export and then drops the returned future without waiting for it to resolve, and then does so again with the same component instance, Wasmtime will panic. Embeddings that have the `component-model-async` compile-time feature disabled are unaffected. Wasmtime 40.0.4 and 41.0.4 have been patched to fix this issue. Versions 42.0.0 and later are not affected. If an embedding is not actually using any component-model-async features then disabling the `component-model-async` Cargo feature can work around this issue. This issue can also be worked around by either ensuring every `call_async` future is awaited until it completes or refraining from using the `Store` again after dropping a not-yet-resolved `call_async` future.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21410 | InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21410</link><description>InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS is susceptible to SQL Injection through its main web interface. Malicious users that use the vulnerable endpoint are potentially able to cause remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22553 | InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22553</link><description>All versions of InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS are susceptible to OS command injection through a field in its MMadmServ web interface. Malicious users that use the vulnerable endpoint are potentially able to cause remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25882 | Fiber has a Denial of Service Vulnerability via Route Parameter Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25882</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. A denial of service vulnerability exists in Fiber v2 and v3 that allows remote attackers to crash the application by sending requests to routes with more than 30 parameters. The vulnerability results from missing validation during route registration combined with an unbounded array write during request matching. Version 2.52.12 patches the issue in the v2 branch and 3.1.0 patches the issue in the v3 branch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46320 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in a FileMaker WebDirect custom homepage could lead to unauthorized access and remote code execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46320</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in a FileMaker WebDirect custom homepage could lead to unauthorized access and remote code execution. This vulnerability has been fully addressed in FileMaker Server 22.0.4 and FileMaker Server 21.1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24443 | EventSentry &amp;lt; 6.0.1.20 Web Reports Unverified Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24443</link><description>EventSentry versions prior to 6.0.1.20 contain an unverified password change vulnerability in the account management functionality of the Web Reports interface. The password change mechanism does not require validation of the current password before allowing a new password to be set. An attacker who gains temporary access to an authenticated user session can change the account password without knowledge of the original credentials. This enables persistent account takeover and, if administrative accounts are affected, may result in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10010 | Integrity Validation Bypass in CryptoPro Secure Disk for BitLocker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10010</link><description>The CPSD CryptoPro Secure Disk application boots a small Linux operating system to perform user authentication before using BitLocker to decrypt the Windows partition. The system is located on a separate unencrypted partition which can be reached by anyone with access to the hard disk.

Multiple checks are performed to validate the integrity of the Linux operating system and the CryptoPro Secure Disk application files. When files are changed an error is shown on system start. One of the checks is the Linux kernel's Integrity Measurement Architecture (IMA). It was identified that configuration files are not validated by the IMA and can then (if not checked by other measures) be changed. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the root user and enables an attacker to e.g., plant a backdoor and access data during execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27208 | api-gateway-deploy Affected by Exploitable Command Injection via Unprivileged Root Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27208</link><description>bleon-ethical/api-gateway-deploy provides API gateway deployment. Version 1.0.0 is vulnerable to an attack chain involving OS Command Injection and Privilege Escalation. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges within the container, potentially leading to a container escape and unauthorized infrastructure modifications. This is fixed in version 1.0.1 by implementing strict input sanitization and secure delimiters in entrypoint.sh, enforcing a non-root user (appuser) in the Dockerfile, and establishing mandatory security quality gates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27483 | MindsDB has Path Traversal in /api/files Leading to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27483</link><description>MindsDB is a platform for building artificial intelligence from enterprise data. Prior to version 25.9.1.1, there is a path traversal vulnerability in Mindsdb's /api/files interface, which an authenticated attacker can exploit to achieve remote command execution. The vulnerability exists in the "Upload File" module, which corresponds to the API endpoint /api/files. Since the multipart file upload does not perform security checks on the uploaded file path, an attacker can perform path traversal by using `../` sequences in the filename field. The file write operation occurs before calling clear_filename and save_file, meaning there is no filtering of filenames or file types, allowing arbitrary content to be written to any path on the server. Version 25.9.1.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14577 | PHP Function Injection in Slican NPC/IPL/IPM/IPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14577</link><description>Slican NCP/IPL/IPM/IPU devices are vulnerable to PHP Function Injection. An unauthenticated remote attacker is able to execute arbitrary PHP commands by sending specially crafted requests to /webcti/session_ajax.php endpoint.


This issue was fixed in version 1.24.0190 (Slican NCP) and 6.61.0010 (Slican IPL/IPM/IPU).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2459 | A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with Installer role to access and alter the contents of directories that the role...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2459</link><description>A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with Installer role to access and alter the contents of directories that the role is not authorized to do so.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2460 | A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with low-level privileges to access and alter the content of directories by using...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2460</link><description>A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with low-level privileges to access and alter the content of directories by using the DAC protocol that the user is not authorized to do so.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2634 | Spoofed web content presented under trusted domains using scripted navigation on Firefox iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2634</link><description>Malicious scripts could cause desynchronization between the address bar and web content before a response is received in Firefox iOS, allowing attacker-controlled pages to be presented under spoofed domains. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 147.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2757 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the WebRTC: Audio/Video component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2757</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the WebRTC: Audio/Video component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2758 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2758</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2759 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: ImageLib component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2759</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: ImageLib component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2760 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebRender component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2760</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebRender component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2761 | Sandbox escape in the Graphics: WebRender component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2761</link><description>Sandbox escape in the Graphics: WebRender component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2762 | Integer overflow in the JavaScript: Standard Library component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2762</link><description>Integer overflow in the JavaScript: Standard Library component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2763 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2763</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2764 | JIT miscompilation, use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2764</link><description>JIT miscompilation, use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2765 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2765</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2766 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2766</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2767 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2767</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2768 | Sandbox escape in the Storage: IndexedDB component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2768</link><description>Sandbox escape in the Storage: IndexedDB component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2769 | Use-after-free in the Storage: IndexedDB component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2769</link><description>Use-after-free in the Storage: IndexedDB component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2770 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Bindings (WebIDL) component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2770</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Bindings (WebIDL) component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2771 | Undefined behavior in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2771</link><description>Undefined behavior in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2772 | Use-after-free in the Audio/Video: Playback component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2772</link><description>Use-after-free in the Audio/Video: Playback component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2773 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Web Audio component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2773</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Web Audio component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2774 | Integer overflow in the Audio/Video component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2774</link><description>Integer overflow in the Audio/Video component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2775 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: HTML Parser component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2775</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: HTML Parser component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2776 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Telemetry component in External Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2776</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Telemetry component in External Software. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2777 | Privilege escalation in the Messaging System component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2777</link><description>Privilege escalation in the Messaging System component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2778 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2778</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2779 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Networking: JAR component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2779</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Networking: JAR component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2780 | Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2780</link><description>Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2781 | Integer overflow in the Libraries component in NSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2781</link><description>Integer overflow in the Libraries component in NSS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2782 | Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2782</link><description>Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2783 | Information disclosure due to JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2783</link><description>Information disclosure due to JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2784 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2784</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2785 | Invalid pointer in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2785</link><description>Invalid pointer in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2786 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2786</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2787 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Window and Location component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2787</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Window and Location component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2788 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Audio/Video: GMP component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2788</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Audio/Video: GMP component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2789 | Use-after-free in the Graphics: ImageLib component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2789</link><description>Use-after-free in the Graphics: ImageLib component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2790 | Same-origin policy bypass in the Networking: JAR component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2790</link><description>Same-origin policy bypass in the Networking: JAR component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2791 | Mitigation bypass in the Networking: Cache component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2791</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the Networking: Cache component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2792 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox ESR 140.8, Thunderbird ESR 140.8, Firefox 148 and Thunderbird 148</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2792</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.7, Thunderbird ESR 140.7, Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2793 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox ESR 115.33, Firefox ESR 140.8, Thunderbird ESR 140.8, Firefox 148 and Thunderbird 148</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2793</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 115.32, Firefox ESR 140.7, Thunderbird ESR 140.7, Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2794 | Information disclosure due to uninitialized memory in Firefox and Firefox Focus for Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2794</link><description>Information disclosure due to uninitialized memory in Firefox and Firefox Focus for Android. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2795 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2795</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2796 | JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2796</link><description>JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2797 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2797</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2798 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2798</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2799 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2799</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2800 | Spoofing issue in the WebAuthn component in Firefox for Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2800</link><description>Spoofing issue in the WebAuthn component in Firefox for Android. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2801 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2801</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2802 | Race condition in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2802</link><description>Race condition in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2803 | Information disclosure, mitigation bypass in the Settings UI component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2803</link><description>Information disclosure, mitigation bypass in the Settings UI component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2804 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2804</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2805 | Invalid pointer in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2805</link><description>Invalid pointer in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2806 | Uninitialized memory in the Graphics: Text component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2806</link><description>Uninitialized memory in the Graphics: Text component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2807 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox 148 and Thunderbird 148</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2807</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1772 | RTU500 web interface: An unprivileged user can read user management information. The information cannot be accessed via the RTU500 web user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1772</link><description>RTU500 web interface: An unprivileged user can read user management information. The information cannot be accessed via the RTU500 web user interface but requires further tools like browser development utilities to access them without required privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1773 | IEC 60870-5-104: Potential Denial of Service impact on reception of invalid U-format frame. Product is only affected if IEC 60870-5-104 bi-d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1773</link><description>IEC 60870-5-104: Potential Denial of Service impact on reception of invalid U-format frame. Product is only affected if IEC 60870-5-104 bi-directional functionality is configured. Enabling secure communication following IEC 62351-3 does not remediate the vulnerability but mitigates the risk of exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23969 | Apache Superset: Exposure of Sensitive Information via Incomplete ClickHouse Function Filtering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23969</link><description>Apache Superset utilizes a configurable dictionary, DISALLOWED_SQL_FUNCTIONS, to restrict the execution of potentially sensitive SQL functions within SQL Lab and charts. While this feature included restrictions for engines like PostgreSQL, a vulnerability was reported where the default list for the ClickHouse engine was incomplete.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.1.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.1.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23980 | Apache Superset: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a SQL Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23980</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Superset allows an authenticated user with read access to conduct error-based SQL injection via the sqlExpression or where parameters.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23982 | Apache Superset: Improper Authorization in Dataset Creation Allows Access Control Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23982</link><description>An Improper Authorization vulnerability exists in Apache Superset that allows a low-privileged user to bypass data access controls. When creating a dataset, Superset enforces permission checks to prevent users from querying unauthorized data. However, an authenticated attacker with permissions to write datasets and read charts can bypass these checks by overwriting the SQL query of an existing dataset.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23983 | Apache Superset: Sensitive Data Exposure via REST API (disabled by default)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23983</link><description>A Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability exists in Apache Superset allowing authenticated users to retrieve sensitive user information. The Tag endpoint (disabled by default) allows users to retrieve a list of objects associated with a specific tag.
When these associated objects include Users, the API response improperly serializes and returns sensitive fields, including password hashes (pbkdf2), email addresses, and login statistics. This vulnerability allows authenticated users with low privileges (e.g., Gamma role) to view sensitive authentication data 

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue or make sure TAGGING_SYSTEM is False (Apache Superset current default)</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23984 | Apache Superset: SQLLab Read-Only Bypass on PostgreSQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23984</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists in Apache Superset that allows an authenticated user with SQLLab access to bypass the read-only verification check when using a PostgreSQL database connection.
While the system effectively blocks standard Data Manipulation Language (DML) statements (e.g., INSERT, UPDATE, DELETE) on read-only connections, it fails to detect them in specially crafted SQL statements.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56373 | Apache Airflow: SSTI to Code Execution in Airflow through Shared DB Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56373</link><description>DAG Author (who already has quite a lot of permissions) could manipulate database of Airflow 2 in the way to execute arbitrary code in the web-server context, which they should normally not be able to do, leading to potentially remote code execution in the context of web-server (server-side) as a result of a user viewing historical task information.

The functionality responsible for that (log template history) has been disabled by default in 2.11.1 and users should upgrade to Airflow 3 if they want to continue to use log template history. They can also manually modify historical log file names if they want to see historical logs that were generated before the last log template change.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27555 | Apache Airflow: Connection Secrets not masked in UI when Connection are added via Airflow cli</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27555</link><description>Airflow versions before 2.11.1 have a vulnerability that allows authenticated users with audit log access to see sensitive values in audit logs which they should not see. When sensitive connection parameters were set via airflow CLI, values of those variables appeared in the audit log and were stored unencrypted in the Airflow database. While this risk is limited to users with audit log access, it is recommended to upgrade to Airflow 2.11.1 or a later version, which addresses this issue. Users who previously used the CLI to set connections should manually delete entries with those connection sensitive values from the log table. This is similar but not the same issue as CVE-2024-50378</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2664 | Out of bounds read vulnerability in grpcfuse kernel module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2664</link><description>An out of bounds read vulnerability in the grpcfuse kernel module present in the Linux VM in Docker Desktop for Windows, Linux and macOS up to version 4.61.0 could allow a local attacker to cause an unspecified impact by writing to /proc/docker entries. The issue has been fixed in Docker Desktop 4.62.0 .</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1524 | A local user can be impersonated when using federated authentication with Silent JIT Provisioning.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1524</link><description>When the "Silent Just-In-Time Provisioning" feature is enabled for a federated identity provider (IDP)  there is a risk that a local user store user's information may be replaced during the account provisioning process in cases where federated users share the same username as local users. 

 There will be no impact on your deployment if any of the preconditions mentioned below are not met. Only when all the preconditions mentioned below are fulfilled could a malicious actor associate a targeted local user account with a federated IDP user account that they control.

The Deployment should have: 
-An IDP configured for federated authentication with Silent JIT provisioning enabled.

The malicious actor should have:
-A fresh valid user account in the federated IDP that has not been used earlier.
-Knowledge of the username of a valid user in the local IDP. 
-An account at the federated IDP matching the targeted local username.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11165 | A sandbox escape vulnerability exists in dotCMS’s Velocity scripting engine (VTools) that allows authenticated users with scripting privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11165</link><description>A sandbox escape vulnerability exists in dotCMS’s Velocity scripting engine (VTools) that allows authenticated users with scripting privileges to bypass class and package restrictions enforced by SecureUberspectorImpl.

By dynamically modifying the Velocity engine’s runtime configuration and reinitializing its Uberspect, a malicious actor can remove the introspector.restrict.classes and introspector.restrict.packages protections.

Once these restrictions are cleared, the attacker can access arbitrary Java classes, including java.lang.Runtime, and execute arbitrary system commands under the privileges of the application process (e.g. dotCMS or Tomcat user).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40541 | SolarWinds Serv-U Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40541</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in Serv-U, which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to execute native code as a privileged account.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1229 | Incorrect calculation in CIRCL secp384r1 CombinedMult</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1229</link><description>The CombinedMult function in the CIRCL ecc/p384 package (secp384r1 curve) produces an incorrect value for specific inputs. The issue is fixed by using complete addition formulas.
ECDH and ECDSA signing relying on this curve are not affected.

The bug was fixed in  v1.6.3 https://github.com/cloudflare/circl/releases/tag/v1.6.3 .</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40538 | SolarWinds Serv-U Broken Access Control Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40538</link><description>A broken access control vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to create a system admin user and execute arbitrary code as a privileged account via domain admin or group admin privileges.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40539 | SolarWinds Serv-U Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40539</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to execute arbitrary native code as privileged account.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40540 | SolarWinds Serv-U Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40540</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to execute arbitrary native code as privileged account.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15386 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt; 2.6.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15386</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery WordPress plugin before 2.6.1 is vulnerable to an Unauthenticated Stored-XSS attack due to flawed regex replacement rules that can be abused by posting a comment with a malicious link when lightbox for comments are enabled and then approved.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15589 | MuYuCMS Template Management Template.php delete_dir_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15589</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in MuYuCMS 2.7. Affected is the function delete_dir_file of the file application/admin/controller/Template.php of the component Template Management Page. This manipulation of the argument temn/tp causes path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24314 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in S/4HANA (Manage Payment Media)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24314</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP S/4HANA (Manage Payment Media) allows an authenticated attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted. This could cause low impact on confidentiality of the application while integrity and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3070 | SourceCodester Modern Image Gallery App upload.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3070</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Modern Image Gallery App 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file upload.php. The manipulation of the argument filename results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:48:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3069 | itsourcecode Document Management System edtlbls.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3069</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edtlbls.php. The manipulation of the argument field1 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27461 | Pimcore vulnerable to SQL injection via unsanitized filter value in Dependency Dao RLIKE clause</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27461</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. In versions up to and including 11.5.14.1 and 12.3.2, the filter query parameter in the dependency listing endpoints is JSON-decoded and the value field is concatenated directly into RLIKE clauses without sanitization or parameterized queries. Exploiting this issue requires admin authentication. An attacker with admin panel access can extract the full database including password hashes of other admin users. Version 12.3.3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3066 | HummerRisk Cloud Compliance Scanning PlatformUtils.java fixedCommand command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3066</link><description>A flaw has been found in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. This vulnerability affects the function fixedCommand of the file hummer-common/hummer-common-core/src/main/java/com/hummer/common/core/utils/PlatformUtils.java of the component Cloud Compliance Scanning. Executing a manipulation can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3067 | HummerRisk Archive Extraction CommandUtils.java extractZip path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3067</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. This issue affects the function extractTarGZ/extractZip of the file hummer-common/hummer-common-core/src/main/java/com/hummer/common/core/utils/CommandUtils.java of the component Archive Extraction. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3068 | itsourcecode Document Management System deluser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3068</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /deluser.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument user2del can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11847 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the IP settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11847</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the IP settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11848 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Wake-on-LAN CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware version through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11848</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Wake-on-LAN CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware version through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13942 | A command injection vulnerability in the UPnP function of the Zyxel EX3510-B0 firmware versions through 5.17(ABUP.15.1)C0 could allow a remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13942</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the UPnP function of the Zyxel EX3510-B0 firmware versions through 5.17(ABUP.15.1)C0 could allow a remote attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by sending specially crafted UPnP SOAP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13943 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the log file download function of the Zyxel EX3301-T0 firmware versions through 5.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13943</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the log file download function of the Zyxel EX3301-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVY.7)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1459 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the TR-369 certificate download CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1459</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the TR-369 certificate download CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.7)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25989 | ImageMagick has integer overflow or wraparound and incorrect conversion between numeric types in the internal SVG decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25989</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted SVG file can cause a denial of service. An off-by-one boundary check (`&gt;` instead of `&gt;=`) that allows bypass the guard and reach an undefined `(size_t)` cast. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26066 | ImageMagick has infinite loop when writing IPTCTEXT leads to denial of service via crafted profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26066</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted profile contain invalid IPTC data may cause an infinite loop when writing it with `IPTCTEXT`. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26198 | ormar is vulnerable to SQL Injection through aggregate functions min() and max()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26198</link><description>Ormar is a async mini ORM for Python. In versions 0.9.9 through 0.22.0, when performing aggregate queries, Ormar ORM constructs SQL expressions by passing user-supplied column names directly into `sqlalchemy.text()` without any validation or sanitization. The `min()` and `max()` methods in the `QuerySet` class accept arbitrary string input as the column parameter. While `sum()` and `avg()` are partially protected by an `is_numeric` type check that rejects non-existent fields, `min()` and `max()` skip this validation entirely. As a result, an attacker-controlled string is embedded as raw SQL inside the aggregate function call. Any unauthorized user can exploit this vulnerability to read the entire database contents, including tables unrelated to the queried model, by injecting a subquery as the column parameter. Version 0.23.0 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26283 | ImageMagick has possible infinite loop in JPEG encoder when using `jpeg:extent`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26283</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a `continue` statement in the JPEG extent binary search loop in the jpeg encoder causes an infinite loop when writing persistently fails. An attacker can trigger a 100% CPU consumption and process hang (Denial of Service) with a crafted image. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26284 | ImageMagick has heap overflow in pcd decoder that leads to out of bounds read.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26284</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, ImageMagick lacks proper boundary checking when processing Huffman-coded data from PCD (Photo CD) files. The decoder contains an function that has an incorrect initialization that could cause an out of bounds read. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26331 | yt-dlp: Arbitrary Command Injection when using the `--netrc-cmd` option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26331</link><description>yt-dlp is a command-line audio/video downloader. Starting in version 2023.06.21 and prior to version 2026.02.21, when yt-dlp's `--netrc-cmd` command-line option (or `netrc_cmd` Python API parameter) is used, an attacker could achieve arbitrary command injection on the user's system with a maliciously crafted URL. yt-dlp maintainers assume the impact of this vulnerability to be high for anyone who uses `--netrc-cmd` in their command/configuration or `netrc_cmd` in their Python scripts. Even though the maliciously crafted URL itself will look very suspicious to many users, it would be trivial for a maliciously crafted webpage with an inconspicuous URL to covertly exploit this vulnerability via HTTP redirect. Users without `--netrc-cmd` in their arguments or `netrc_cmd` in their scripts are unaffected. No evidence has been found of this exploit being used in the wild. yt-dlp version 2026.02.21 fixes this issue by validating all netrc "machine" values and raising an error upon unexpected input. As a workaround, users who are unable to upgrade should avoid using the `--netrc-cmd` command-line option (or `netrc_cmd` Python API parameter), or they should at least not pass a placeholder (`{}`) in their `--netrc-cmd` argument.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26981 | OpenEXR has heap-buffer-overflow via signed integer underflow in ImfContextInit.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26981</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In versions 3.3.0 through 3.3.6 and 3.4.0 through 3.4.4, a heap-buffer-overflow (OOB read) occurs in the `istream_nonparallel_read` function in `ImfContextInit.cpp` when parsing a malformed EXR file through a memory-mapped `IStream`. A signed integer subtraction produces a negative value that is implicitly converted to `size_t`, resulting in a massive length being passed to `memcpy`. Versions 3.3.7 and 3.4.5 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26983 | ImageMagick: Invalid MSL &amp;lt;map&amp;gt; can result in a use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26983</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, the MSL interpreter crashes when processing a invalid `&lt;map&gt;` element that causes it to use an image after it has been freed. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27126 | Craft CMS has Stored XSS in Table Field via &amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot; Column Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27126</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, a stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the `editableTable.twig` component when using the `html` column type. The application fails to sanitize the input, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript when another user views a page with the malicious table field. In order to exploit the vulnerability, an attacker must have an administrator account, and `allowAdminChanges` must be enabled in production, which is against Craft's security recommendations. Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27127 | Craft CMS has Cloud Metadata SSRF Protection Bypass via DNS Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27127</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, the SSRF validation in Craft CMS’s GraphQL Asset mutation performs DNS resolution separately from the HTTP request. This Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability enables DNS rebinding attacks, where an attacker’s DNS server returns different IP addresses for validation compared to the actual request. This is a bypass of the security fix for CVE-2025-68437 that allows access to all blocked IPs, not just IPv6 endpoints. Exploitation requires GraphQL schema permissions for editing assets in the `` volume and creating assets in the `` volume. These permissions may be granted to authenticated users with appropriate GraphQL schema access and/or Public Schema (if misconfigured with write permissions). Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27128 | Craft CMS&amp;#x27;s race condition in Token Service potentially allows for token usage greater than the token limit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27128</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, a Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition exists in Craft CMS’s token validation service for tokens that explicitly set a limited usage. The `getTokenRoute()` method reads a token’s usage count, checks if it’s within limits, then updates the database in separate non-atomic operations. By sending concurrent requests, an attacker can use a single-use impersonation token multiple times before the database update completes. To make this work, an attacker needs to obtain a valid user account impersonation URL with a non-expired token via some other means and exploit a race condition while bypassing any rate-limiting rules in place. For this to be a privilege escalation, the impersonation URL must include a token for a user account with more permissions than the current user. Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27129 | Cloud Metadata SSRF Protection Bypass via IPv6 Resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27129</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, the SSRF validation in Craft CMS’s GraphQL Asset mutation uses `gethostbyname()`, which only resolves IPv4 addresses. When a hostname has only AAAA (IPv6) records, the function returns the hostname string itself, causing the blocklist comparison to always fail and completely bypassing SSRF protection. This is a bypass of the security fix for CVE-2025-68437. Exploitation requires GraphQL schema permissions for editing assets in the `` volume and creating assets in the `` volume. These permissions may be granted to authenticated users with appropriate GraphQL schema access and/or Public Schema (if misconfigured with write permissions). Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3054 | Alinto SOGo cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3054</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Alinto SOGo 5.12.3/5.12.4. This impacts an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument hint leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3057 | a54552239 pearProjectApi Backend Task.php dateTotalForProject sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3057</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in a54552239 pearProjectApi up to 2.8.10. Affected is the function dateTotalForProject of the file application/common/Model/Task.php of the component Backend Interface. The manipulation of the argument projectCode results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3064 | HummerRisk Cloud Task Scheduler ResourceCreateService.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3064</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ResourceCreateService.java of the component Cloud Task Scheduler. Such manipulation of the argument regionId leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3065 | HummerRisk Cloud Task Dry-run CloudTaskService.java CommandUtils.commonExecCmdWithResult command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3065</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. This affects the function CommandUtils.commonExecCmdWithResult of the file CloudTaskService.java of the component Cloud Task Dry-run. Performing a manipulation of the argument fileName results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3091 | An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Synology Presto Client before 2.1.3-0672 allows local users to read or write arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3091</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Synology Presto Client before 2.1.3-0672 allows local users to read or write arbitrary files during installation by placing a malicious DLL in advance in the same directory as the installer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11845 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the certificate downloader CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11845</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the certificate downloader CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11846 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the account settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11846</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the account settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25897 | ImageMagick has heap overflow in sun decoder on 32-bit systems that can result in out of bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25897</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, an Integer Overflow vulnerability exists in the sun decoder. On 32-bit systems/builds, a carefully crafted image can lead to an out of bounds heap write. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25898 | Imagemagick Has Global Buffer Overflow (OOB Read) via Negative Pixel Index in UIL and XPM Writer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25898</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, the UIL and XPM image encoder do not validate the pixel index value returned by `GetPixelIndex()` before using it as an array subscript. In HDRI builds, `Quantum` is a floating-point type, so pixel index values can be negative. An attacker can craft an image with negative pixel index values to trigger a global buffer overflow read during conversion, leading to information disclosure or a process crash. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25965 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s policy bypass through path traversal allows reading restricted content despite secured policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25965</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, ImageMagick’s path security policy is enforced on the raw filename string before the filesystem resolves it. As a result, a policy rule such as /etc/* can be bypassed by a path traversal. The OS resolves the traversal and opens the sensitive file, but the policy matcher only sees the unnormalized path and therefore allows the read. This enables local file disclosure (LFI) even when policy-secure.xml is applied. Actions to prevent reading from files have been taken in versions .7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 But it make sure writing is also not possible the following should be added to one's policy. This will also be included in ImageMagick's more secure policies by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25966 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s Security Policy Bypass through config/policy-secure.xml via &amp;quot;fd handler&amp;quot; leads to stdin/stdout access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25966</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. The shipped "secure" security policy includes a rule intended to prevent reading/writing from standard streams. However, ImageMagick also supports fd: pseudo-filenames (e.g., fd:0, fd:1). Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, this path form is not blocked by the secure policy templates, and therefore bypasses the protection goal of "no stdin/stdout." Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch by including a change to the more secure policies by default. As a workaround, add the change to one's security policy manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25967 | ImageMagick has stack buffer overflow in FTXT reader via oversized integer field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25967</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, a stack-based buffer overflow exists in the ImageMagick FTXT image reader. A crafted FTXT file can cause out-of-bounds writes on the stack, leading to a crash. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25968 | ImageMagick has MSL attribute stack buffer overflow that leads to out of bounds write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25968</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a stack buffer overflow occurs when processing the an attribute in msl.c. A long value overflows a fixed-size stack buffer, leading to memory corruption. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25969 | ImageMagick has Memory Leak in coders/ashlar.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25969</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, a memory leak exists in `coders/ashlar.c`. The `WriteASHLARImage` allocates a structure.  However, when an exception is thrown, the allocated memory is not properly released, resulting in a potential memory leak. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25970 | ImageMagick SIXEL Decoder Has Signed Integer Overflow, Leading to Memory Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25970</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a signed integer overflow vulnerability in ImageMagick's SIXEL decoder allows an attacker to trigger memory corruption and denial of service when processing a maliciously crafted SIXEL image file. The vulnerability occurs during buffer reallocation operations where pointer arithmetic using signed 32-bit integers overflows. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25971 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s MSL: Stack overflow in ProcessMSLScript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25971</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, Magick fails to check for circular references between two MSLs, leading to a stack overflow. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25982 | ImageMagick Has Heap Out-of-Bounds Read in DCM Decoder (ReadDCMImage)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25982</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the `coders/dcm.c` module. When processing DICOM files with a specific configuration, the decoder loop incorrectly reads bytes per iteration. This causes the function to read past the end of the allocated buffer, potentially leading to a Denial of Service (crash) or Information Disclosure (leaking heap memory into the image). Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25983 | ImageMagick has Use After Free in MSLStartElement in &amp;quot;coders/msl.c&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25983</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted MSL script triggers a heap-use-after-free. The operation element handler replaces and frees the image while the parser continues reading from it, leading to a UAF in ReadBlobString during further parsing. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25985 | Memory allocation with excessive without limits in the internal SVG decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25985</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted SVG file containing an malicious element causes ImageMagick to attempt to allocate ~674 GB of memory, leading to an out-of-memory abort. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25986 | ImageMagick has a heap buffer overflow in YUV 4:2:2 decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25986</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer overflow write vulnerability exists in ReadYUVImage() (coders/yuv.c) when processing malicious YUV 4:2:2 (NoInterlace) images. The pixel-pair loop writes one pixel beyond the allocated row buffer. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25987 | ImageMagick has heap buffer over-read in MAP image decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25987</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in the MAP image decoder when processing crafted MAP files, potentially leading to crashes or unintended memory disclosure during image decoding. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25988 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s MSL image stack index not refreshed, leading to leaked images.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25988</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, sometimes msl.c fails to update the stack index, so an image is stored in the wrong slot and never freed on error, causing leaks. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3052 | DataLinkDC dinky Flink Proxy Controller FlinkProxyController.java proxyUba server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3052</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DataLinkDC dinky up to 1.2.5. The impacted element is the function proxyUba of the file dinky-admin/src/main/java/org/dinky/controller/FlinkProxyController.java of the component Flink Proxy Controller. Performing a manipulation results in server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3053 | DataLinkDC dinky OpenAPI Endpoint AppConfig.java addInterceptors missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3053</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in DataLinkDC dinky up to 1.2.5. This affects the function addInterceptors of the file dinky-admin/src/main/java/org/dinky/configure/AppConfig.java of the component OpenAPI Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25591 | New API has an SQL LIKE Wildcard Injection DoS via Token Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25591</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. Prior to version 0.10.8-alpha.10, a SQL LIKE wildcard injection vulnerability in the `/api/token/search` endpoint allows authenticated users to cause denial of service through resource exhaustion by crafting malicious search patterns. The token search endpoint accepts user-supplied `keyword` and `token` parameters that are directly concatenated into SQL LIKE clauses without escaping wildcard characters (`%`, `_`). This allows attackers to inject patterns that trigger expensive database queries. Version 0.10.8-alpha.10 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25637 | ImageMagick: Possible memory leak in ASHLAR encoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25637</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, a memory leak in the ASHLAR image writer allows an attacker to exhaust process memory by providing a crafted image that results in small objects that are allocated but never freed. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25638 | ImageMagick has memory leak in msl encoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25638</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, memory leak exists in `coders/msl.c`. In the `WriteMSLImage` function of the `msl.c` file, resources are allocated. But the function returns early without releasing these allocated resources. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25794 | ImageMagick has heap-buffer-overflow via signed integer overflow in `WriteUHDRImage` when writing UHDR images with large dimensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25794</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. `WriteUHDRImage` in `coders/uhdr.c` uses `int` arithmetic to compute the pixel buffer size. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, when image dimensions are large, the multiplication overflows 32-bit `int`, causing an undersized heap allocation followed by an out-of-bounds write. This can crash the process or potentially lead to an out of bounds heap write. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25795 | ImageMagick has NULL pointer dereference in ReadSFWImage after DestroyImageInfo (sfw.c)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25795</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, in `ReadSFWImage()` (`coders/sfw.c`), when temporary file creation fails, `read_info` is destroyed before its `filename` member is accessed, causing a NULL pointer dereference and crash. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25796 | ImageMagick has memory leak of watermark Image object in ReadSTEGANOImage on multiple error/early-return paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25796</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, in `ReadSTEGANOImage()` (`coders/stegano.c`), the `watermark` Image object is not freed on three early-return paths, resulting in a definite memory leak (~13.5KB+ per invocation) that can be exploited for denial of service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25797 | ImageMagick vulnerable to Code injection via PostScript header in ps coders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25797</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, the ps coders, responsible for writing PostScript files, fails to sanitize the input before writing it into the PostScript header.  An attacker can provide a malicous file and inject arbitrary PostScript code. When the resulting file is processed by a printer or a viewer (like Ghostscript), the injected code is interpreted and executed. The html encoder does not properly escape strings that are written to in the html document. An attacker can provide a malicious file and injection arbitrary html code. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25798 | ImageMagick has NULL Pointer Dereference in ClonePixelCacheRepository via crafted image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25798</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a NULL pointer dereference in ClonePixelCacheRepository allows a remote attacker to crash any application linked against ImageMagick by supplying a crafted image file, resulting in denial of service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25799 | ImageMagick has Division-by-Zero in YUV sampling factor validation, which leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25799</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a logic error in YUV sampling factor validation allows an invalid sampling factor to bypass checks and trigger a division-by-zero during image loading, resulting in a reliable denial-of-service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25802 | New API has Potential XSS in its MarkdownRenderer component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25802</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. Prior to version 0.10.8-alpha.9, a potential unsafe operation occurs in component `MarkdownRenderer.jsx`, allowing for Cross-Site Scripting(XSS) when the model outputs items containing `</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27729 | Astro has  memory exhaustion DoS due to missing request body size limit in Server Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27729</link><description>Astro is a web framework. In versions 9.0.0 through 9.5.3, Astro server actions have no default request body size limit, which can lead to memory exhaustion DoS. A single large POST to a valid action endpoint can crash the server process on memory-constrained deployments. On-demand rendered sites built with Astro can define server actions, which automatically parse incoming request bodies (JSON or FormData). The body is buffered entirely into memory with no size limit — a single oversized request is sufficient to exhaust the process heap and crash the server. Astro's Node adapter (`mode: 'standalone'`) creates an HTTP server with no body size protection. In containerized environments, the crashed process is automatically restarted, and repeated requests cause a persistent crash-restart loop. Action names are discoverable from HTML form attributes on any public page, so no authentication is required. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated denial of service against SSR standalone deployments using server actions. A single oversized request crashes the server process, and repeated requests cause a persistent crash-restart loop in containerized environments. Version 9.5.4 contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3050 | horilla-opensource horilla Leads global.js cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3050</link><description>A flaw has been found in horilla-opensource horilla up to 1.0.2. Impacted is an unknown function of the file static/assets/js/global.js of the component Leads Module. This manipulation of the argument Notes causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.0.3 is recommended to address this issue. Patch name: fc5c8e55988e89273012491b5f097b762b474546. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3051 | DataLinkDC dinky Project Name GitRepository.java getProjectDir path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3051</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DataLinkDC dinky up to 1.2.5. The affected element is the function getProjectDir of the file dinky-admin/src/main/java/org/dinky/utils/GitRepository.java of the component Project Name Handler. Such manipulation of the argument projectName leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69253 | free5GC vulnerable to improper error handling in NEF with information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69253</link><description>free5GC is an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions up to and including 1.4.1 of the User Data Repository are affected by Improper Error Handling with Information Exposure. The NEF component reliably leaks internal parsing error details (e.g., invalid character 'n' after top-level value) to remote clients, which can aid attackers in service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the Nnef_PfdManagement service may be vulnerable. free5gc/udr pull request 56 contains a patch. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9120 | RCE vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Carbonite Safe Server Backup.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9120</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in OpenText™ Carbonite Safe Server Backup allows Code Injection. 

The vulnerability could be exploited through an open port, potentially allowing unauthorized access.

This issue affects Carbonite Safe Server Backup: through 6.8.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21864 | Remote DoS from malformed RESTORE command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21864</link><description>Valkey-Bloom is a Rust based Valkey module which brings a Bloom Filter (Module) data type into the Valkey distributed key-value database. Prior to commit a68614b6e3845777d383b3a513cedcc08b3b7ccd, a specially crafted `RESTORE` command can cause Valkey to hit an assertion, causes the server to shutdown. Valkey modules are required to handle errors in RDB parsing by using `VALKEYMODULE_OPTIONS_HANDLE_IO_ERRORS` flag. If this flag is not set, errors encountered during parsing result in a system assertion which shuts down the system. Even though the Valkey-bloom module correctly handled the parsing, it did not originally set the flag. Commit a68614b6e3845777d383b3a513cedcc08b3b7ccd contains a patch. One may mitigate this defect by disabling the `RESTORE` command if it is unused by one's application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24481 | ImageMagick has Possible Heap Information Disclosure in PSD ZIP Decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24481</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap information disclosure vulnerability exists in ImageMagick's PSD (Adobe Photoshop) format handler. When processing a maliciously crafted PSD file containing ZIP-compressed layer data that decompresses to less than the expected size, uninitialized heap memory is leaked into the output image. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24484 | ImageMagick: Converting multi-layer nested MVG to SVG can cause DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24484</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, Magick fails to check for multi-layer nested mvg conversions to svg, leading to DoS. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24485 | ImageMagick: Infinite loop vulnerability when parsing a PCD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24485</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, when a PCD file does not contain a valid Sync marker, the DecodeImage() function becomes trapped in an infinite loop while searching for the Sync marker, causing the program to become unresponsive and continuously consume CPU resources, ultimately leading to system resource exhaustion and denial of service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25501 | free5GC SMF crash (nil pointer dereference) on PFCP SessionReportRequest when ReportType.DLDR is set but DownlinkDataReport IE is missing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25501</link><description>free5GC SMF provides Session Management Function for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, SMF panics due to nil pointer dereference and the SMF process terminates. This is triggered by a malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest on the SMF PFCP (UDP/8805) interface. No known upstream fix is available, but some workarounds are available. ACL/firewall the PFCP interface so only trusted UPF IPs can reach SMF (reduce spoofing/abuse surface); drop/inspect malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest messages at the network edge where feasible, and/or add recover() around PFCP handler dispatch to avoid whole-process termination (mitigation only).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25545 | Astro has Full-Read SSRF in error rendering via Host: header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25545</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 9.5.4, Server-Side Rendered pages that return an error with a prerendered custom error page (eg. `404.astro` or `500.astro`) are vulnerable to SSRF. If the `Host:` header is changed to an attacker's server, it will be fetched on `/500.html` and they can redirect this to any internal URL to read the response body through the first request. An attacker who can access the application without `Host:` header validation (eg. through finding the origin IP behind a proxy, or just by default) can fetch their own server to redirect to any internal IP. With this they can fetch cloud metadata IPs and interact with services in the internal network or localhost. For this to be vulnerable, a common feature needs to be used, with direct access to the server (no proxies). Version 9.5.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25576 | ImageMagick: Out of bounds read in multiple coders read raw pixel data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25576</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in multiple raw image format handles. The vulnerability occurs when processing images with -extract dimensions larger than -size dimensions, causing out-of-bounds memory reads from a heap-allocated buffer. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26024 | free5GC SMF crash (nil pointer dereference) on PFCP SessionReportRequest when ReportType.USAR=1 and UsageReport omits mandatory URRID sub-IE ￼</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26024</link><description>free5GC SMF provides Session Management Function for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, SMF panics and terminates when processing a malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest on the PFCP (UDP/8805) interface. ￼No known upstream fix is available, but some workarounds are available. ACL/firewall the PFCP interface so only trusted UPF IPs can reach SMF (reduce spoofing/abuse surface); drop/inspect malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest messages at the network edge where feasible, and/or add recover() around PFCP handler dispatch to avoid whole-process termination (mitigation only).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26025 | free5GC SMF crash (nil pointer dereference) on PFCP SessionReportRequest when ReportType.USAR=1 and UsageReport omits mandatory URRID sub-IE ￼</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26025</link><description>free5GC SMF provides Session Management Function for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, SMF panics and terminates when processing a malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest on the PFCP (UDP/8805) interface. ￼No known upstream fix is available, but some workarounds are available. ACL/firewall the PFCP interface so only trusted UPF IPs can reach SMF (reduce spoofing/abuse surface); drop/inspect malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest messages at the network edge where feasible, and/or add recover() around PFCP handler dispatch to avoid whole-process termination (mitigation only).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27642 | free5GC has Improper Input Validation in UDM UEAU Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27642</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, remote attackers can inject control characters (e.g., %00) into the supi parameter, triggering internal URL parsing errors (net/url: invalid control character). This exposes system-level error details and can be used for service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM Nudm_UEAU service may be affected. free5gc/udm pull request 75 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27643 | free5GC has improper error handling in NEF with information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27643</link><description>free5GC UDR is the user data repository (UDR) for free5GC, an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, the NEF component reliably leaks internal parsing error details (e.g., invalid character 'n' after top-level value) to remote clients, which can aid attackers in service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC  using the Nnef_PfdManagement service may be affected. free5gc/udr pull request 56 contains a patch for the issue. There is no direct workaround at the application level. The recommendation is to apply the provided patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3046 | itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 check_profile_old.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3046</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /check_profile_old.php. The manipulation of the argument profile_id leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3049 | horilla-opensource horilla Query Parameter global_search.py get redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3049</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in horilla-opensource horilla up to 1.0.2. This issue affects the function get of the file horilla_generics/global_search.py of the component Query Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument prev_url results in open redirect. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.0.3 is capable of addressing this issue. The patch is identified as 730b5a44ff060916780c44a4bdbc8ced70a2cd27. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58041 | Smolder versions through 1.51 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58041</link><description>Smolder versions through 1.51 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions.

Smolder 1.51 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Smolder::DB::Developer uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69251 | free5GC has Improper Input Validation in UDM, Leading to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69251</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1,  remote attackers can inject control characters (e.g., %00) into the ueId parameter, triggering internal URL parsing errors (net/url: invalid control character). This exposes system implementation details and can aid in service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM Nudm_UECM service may be affected. free5gc/udm pull request 76 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69252 | free5GC has Null Pointer Dereference in UDM, Leading to Service Panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69252</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions up to and including 1.4.1 have a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability. Remote unauthenticated attackers can trigger a service panic (Denial of Service) by sending a crafted PUT request with an unexpected ueId, crashing the UDM service. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM component may be affected. free5gc/udm pull request 76 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69250 | free5GC has Improper Error Handling in UDM, Leading to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69250</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, the service reliably leaks detailed internal error messages (e.g., strconv.ParseInt parsing errors) to remote clients when processing invalid pduSessionId inputs. This exposes implementation details and can be used for service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM Nudm_UECM DELETE service may be vulnerable. free5gc/udm pull request 76 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3044 | Tenda AC8 Httpd Service UploadCfg webCgiGetUploadFile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3044</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This affects the function webCgiGetUploadFile of the file /cgi-bin/UploadCfg of the component Httpd Service. The manipulation of the argument boundary leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3042 | itsourcecode Event Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3042</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3043 | itsourcecode Event Management System navbar.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3043</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/navbar.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument page can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21665 | The Print Service component of Fiserv Originate Loans Peripherals (formerly Velocity Services) in unsupported version 2021.2.4 (build 4.7.31...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21665</link><description>The Print Service component of Fiserv Originate Loans Peripherals (formerly Velocity Services) in unsupported version 2021.2.4 (build 4.7.3155.0011) uses deprecated .NET Remoting TCP channels that allow unsafe deserialization of untrusted data. When these services are exposed to an untrusted network in a client-managed deployment, an unauthenticated attacker can achieve remote code execution. Version 2021.2.4 is no longer supported by Fiserv. Customers should upgrade to a currently supported release (2025.1 or later) and ensure that .NET Remoting service ports are not exposed beyond trusted network boundaries.

This CVE documents behavior observed in a client-hosted deployment running an unsupported legacy version of Originate Loans Peripherals with .NET Remoting ports exposed to an untrusted network. This is not a default or supported configuration. Customers running legacy versions should upgrade to a currently supported release and ensure .NET Remoting ports are restricted to trusted network segments. The finding does not apply to Fiserv-hosted environments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3061 | Out of bounds read in Media in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3061</link><description>Out of bounds read in Media in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3062 | Out of bounds read and write in Tint in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3062</link><description>Out of bounds read and write in Tint in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3063 | Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3063</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to inject scripts or HTML into a privileged page via DevTools. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27741 | Bludit &amp;lt;= 3.16.1 CSRF in Plugin and Theme Management Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27741</link><description>Bludit version 3.16.1 contains a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /admin/uninstall-plugin/ and /admin/install-theme/ endpoints. The application does not implement anti-CSRF tokens or other request origin validation mechanisms for these administrative actions. An attacker can induce an authenticated administrator to visit a malicious page that silently submits crafted requests, resulting in unauthorized plugin uninstallation or theme installation. This may lead to loss of functionality, execution of untrusted code via malicious themes, and compromise of system integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27742 | Bludit &amp;lt;= 3.16.2 Stored XSS in Post Content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27742</link><description>Bludit version 3.16.2 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the post content functionality. The application performs client-side sanitation of content input but does not enforce equivalent sanitation on the server side. An authenticated user can inject arbitrary JavaScript into the content field of a post, which is stored and later rendered to other users without proper output encoding. When viewed, the injected script executes in the context of the victim’s browser, allowing session hijacking, credential theft, content manipulation, or other actions within the user’s privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3040 | DrayTek Vigor 300B Web Management uploadlangs cgiGetFile os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3040</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in DrayTek Vigor 300B up to 1.5.1.6. This affects the function cgiGetFile of the file /cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi/uploadlangs of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor confirms that "300B is EoL, and this is an authenticated vulnerability. We don't plan to fix it." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3041 | xingfuggz BaykeShop Article Sidebar custom.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3041</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in xingfuggz BaykeShop up to 1.3.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file src/baykeshop/contrib/article/templates/baykeshop/sidebar/custom.html of the component Article Sidebar Module. Such manipulation of the argument sidebar.content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69232 | free5GC hasProtocol Compliance Violation in UPF Leading to SMF Service Disruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69232</link><description>free5GC is an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. free5GC go-upf versions up to and including 1.2.6, corresponding to free5gc smf up to and including 1.4.0, have an Improper Input Validation and Protocol Compliance vulnerability leading to Denial of Service. Remote attackers can disrupt core network functionality by sending a malformed PFCP Association Setup Request. The UPF incorrectly accepts it, entering an inconsistent state that causes subsequent legitimate requests to trigger SMF reconnection loops and service degradation. All deployments of free5GC using the UPF and SMF components may be affected. As of time of publication, a fix is in development but not yet available. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch, once released, is recommended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69247 | free5GC has Heap Buffer Overflow in UPF Leading to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69247</link><description>free5GC go-upf is the User Plane Function (UPF) implementation for 5G networks that is part of the free5GC project. Versions prior to 1.2.8 have a Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122) vulnerability leading to Denial of Service. Remote attackers can crash the UPF network element by sending a specially crafted PFCP Session Modification Request with an invalid SDF Filter length field. This causes a heap buffer overflow, resulting in complete service disruption for all connected UEs and potential cascading failures affecting the SMF. All deployments of free5GC using the UPF component may be affected. Version 1.2.8 of go-upf contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69248 | free5GC has Array Index Out of Bounds in AMF Leading to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69248</link><description>free5GC is an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions up to and including 1.4.1 of free5GC's AMF service have a Buffer Overflow vulnerability leading to Denial of Service. Remote unauthenticated attackers can crash the AMF service by sending a specially crafted NAS Registration Request with a malformed 5GS Mobile Identity, causing complete denial of service for the 5G core network. All deployments of free5GC using the AMF component may be affected. Pull request 43 of the free5gc/nas repo contains a fix. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3028 | erzhongxmu JEEWMS JeecgListDemoController.java doAdd cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3028</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in erzhongxmu JEEWMS up to 3.7. This vulnerability affects the function doAdd of the file src/main/java/com/jeecg/demo/controller/JeecgListDemoController.java. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69208 | free5GC UDR&amp;#x27;s NEF incorrectly returns 500 for missing PFD data (UDR 404) in Nnef_PfdManagement GET request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69208</link><description>free5GC UDR is the user data repository (UDR) for free5GC, an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions prior to 1.4.1 contain an Improper Error Handling vulnerability with Information Exposure. All deployments of free5GC using the Nnef_PfdManagement service may be affected. The NEF component reliably leaks internal parsing errors (e.g., invalid character 'n' after top-level value) to remote clients. This can aid attackers in fingerprinting server software and logic flows. Version 1.4.1 fixes the issue. There is no direct workaround at the application level. The recommended mitigation is to apply the provided patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25649 | Traccar Vulnerable to Authorization Code Theft via Open Redirect in OIDC Provider Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25649</link><description>Versions of the Traccar open-source GPS tracking system up to and including 6.11.1 contain an issue in which authenticated users can steal OAuth 2.0 authorization codes by exploiting an open redirect vulnerability in two OIDC-related endpoints. The `redirect_uri` parameter is not validated against a whitelist, allowing attackers to redirect authorization codes to attacker-controlled URLs, enabling account takeover on any OAuth-integrated application. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23521 | Traccar vulnerable to Path Traversal and External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23521</link><description>Versions of the Traccar open-source GPS tracking system up to and including 6.11.1 contain an issue in which authenticated users who can create or edit devices can set a device `uniqueId` to an absolute path. When uploading a device image, Traccar uses that `uniqueId` to build the filesystem path without enforcing that the resolved path stays under the media root. This allows writing files outside the media directory. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25648 | Traccar Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Malicious SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25648</link><description>Versions of the Traccar open-source GPS tracking system starting with 6.11.1 contain an issue in which authenticated users can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of other users' browsers by uploading malicious SVG files as device images. The application accepts SVG file uploads without sanitization and serves them with the `image/svg+xml` Content-Type, allowing embedded JavaScript to execute when victims view the image. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3027 | erzhongxmu JEEWMS UEditor getContent.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3027</link><description>A vulnerability was found in erzhongxmu JEEWMS up to 3.7. This affects an unknown part of the file src/main/webapp/plug-in/ueditor/jsp/getContent.jsp of the component UEditor. The manipulation of the argument myEditor results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3075 | WordPress Simple Ajax Chat plugin &amp;lt;= 20251121 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3075</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Jeff Starr Simple Ajax Chat simple-ajax-chat allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Simple Ajax Chat: from n/a through &lt;= 20251121.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3025 | ShuoRen Smart Heating Integrated Management Platform ExampleNodeService.asmx unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3025</link><description>A flaw has been found in ShuoRen Smart Heating Integrated Management Platform 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /MP/Service/Webservice/ExampleNodeService.asmx. Executing a manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3026 | erzhongxmu JEEWMS UEditor getRemoteImage.jsp server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3026</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in erzhongxmu JEEWMS 3.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /plug-in/ueditor/jsp/getRemoteImage.jsp of the component UEditor. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22567 | ZIA Admin UI Input Validation Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22567</link><description>Improper validation of user-supplied input in the ZIA Admin UI could allow an authenticated administrator to initiate backend functions through specific input fields in limited scenarios.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22568 | Unauthorized information retrieval in ZIA Admin UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22568</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements in user-supplied input within the ZIA Admin UI could allow an authenticated administrator to access or retrieve unauthorized internal information in rare conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3015 | UTT HiPER 810G formPolicyRouteConf strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3015</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPolicyRouteConf. Executing a manipulation of the argument GroupName can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69700 | Tenda FH1203 V2.0.1.6 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the modify_add_client_prio function, which is reachable via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69700</link><description>Tenda FH1203 V2.0.1.6 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the modify_add_client_prio function, which is reachable via the formSetClientPrio CGI handler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21420 | Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions prior to 3.4.8, contains an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21420</link><description>Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions prior to 3.4.8, contains an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59873 | Session Token Exposure via URL Query Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59873</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in

Vulnerability in HCL Software ZIE for Web.

The application transmits sensitive session tokens and authentication identifiers within the URL query parameters . An attacker who gains access to any network log or operates a site linked from the application can hijack user sessions

This issue affects ZIE for Web: v16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40701 | Reflected Cross-Site scripting (XSS) in SOTE&amp;#x27;s SOTESHOP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40701</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in SOTESHOP, version 8.3.4. THis vulnerability allows an attacker execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser when a malicious URL with the 'id' parameter in '/adsTracker/checkAds' is sent to the victim. The vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user information such as session cookies, or to perform actions on their behalf.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40986 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in PideTuCita</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40986</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PideTuCita. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending him/her a malicious URL using the endpoint 'cookies/indes.php/'. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal confidential user data, such as session cookies or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2985 | Tiandy Video Surveillance System 视频监控平台 CLSBODownLoad.java downloadImage server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2985</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tiandy Video Surveillance System 视频监控平台 7.17.0. This impacts the function downloadImage of the file /com/tiandy/easy7/core/bo/CLSBODownLoad.java. Performing a manipulation of the argument urlPath results in server-side request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2984 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System drop_user.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2984</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/core/drop_user.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to denial of service. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41002 | SQL injection in Infoticketing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41002</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Infoticketing. This vulnerability allows
 an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete the
 database by sending a POST request using the 'code' parameter in '/components/cart/cartApplyDiscount.php'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2983 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Bulk Import import_users.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2983</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/core/import_users.php of the component Bulk Import. This manipulation of the argument File causes improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23552 | Apache Camel: Camel-Keycloak: Cross-Realm Token Acceptance Bypass in KeycloakSecurityPolicy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23552</link><description>Cross-Realm Token Acceptance Bypass in KeycloakSecurityPolicy Apache Camel Keycloak component. 

The Camel-Keycloak KeycloakSecurityPolicy does not validate the iss (issuer) claim of JWT tokens against the configured realm. A token issued by one Keycloak realm is silently accepted by a policy configured for a completely different realm, breaking tenant isolation.
This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.15.0 before 4.18.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25747 | Apache Camel: Deserialization of Untrusted Data in Camel LevelDB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25747</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel LevelDB component.

The Camel-LevelDB DefaultLevelDBSerializer class deserializes data read from the LevelDB aggregation repository using java.io.ObjectInputStream without applying any ObjectInputFilter or class-loading restrictions. An attacker who can write to the LevelDB database files used by a Camel application can inject a crafted serialized Java object that, when deserialized during normal aggregation repository operations, results in arbitrary code execution in the context of the application.
This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.10.0 before 4.10.8, from 4.14.0 before 4.14.5, from 4.15.0 before 4.18.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.0, which fixes the issue. For the 4.10.x LTS releases, users are recommended to upgrade to 4.10.9, while for 4.14.x LTS releases, users are recommended to upgrade to 4.14.5</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2981 | UTT HiPER 810G formTaskEdit_ap strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2981</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-1711. The affected element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formTaskEdit_ap. The manipulation of the argument txtMin2 results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2980 | UTT HiPER 810G setSysAdm strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2980</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-1711. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/setSysAdm. The manipulation of the argument passwd1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26365 | Akamai Ghost on Akamai CDN edge servers before 2026-02-06 mishandles processing of custom hop-by-hop HTTP headers, where an incoming request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26365</link><description>Akamai Ghost on Akamai CDN edge servers before 2026-02-06 mishandles processing of custom hop-by-hop HTTP headers, where an incoming request containing the header "Connection: Transfer-Encoding" could result in a forward request with invalid message framing, depending on the Akamai processing path. This could result in the origin server parsing the request body incorrectly, leading to HTTP request smuggling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2979 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py user_avatar_upload_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2979</link><description>A flaw has been found in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This issue affects the function user_avatar_upload_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_system/user/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Executing a manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2978 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py upload_file_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2978</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function upload_file_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_system/params/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Performing a manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1367 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1367</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus versions 6522 and below are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in the search report option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2977 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py upload_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2977</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This affects the function upload_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_common/file/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2976 | FastApiAdmin Download Endpoint controller.py download_controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2976</link><description>A weakness has been identified in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. Affected by this issue is the function download_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_common/file/controller.py of the component Download Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument file_path causes information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2975 | FastApiAdmin Custom Documentation Endpoint init_app.py reset_api_docs information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2975</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function reset_api_docs of the file /backend/app/plugin/init_app.py of the component Custom Documentation Endpoint. The manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2974 | AliasVault App Backup aliasvault.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2974</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in AliasVault App up to 0.25.3 on Android/iOS. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file shared_prefs/aliasvault.xml of the component Backup Handler. The manipulation of the argument accessToken/refreshToken/metadata/key_derivation_params/auth_methods leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. An attack has to be approached locally. The attack is considered to have high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 0.26.0 is able to resolve this issue. The identifier of the patch is 873ecc03f92238e162f98a068ad56069a922b4f6/0bd662320174d8265dfe3b05a04bc13efc960532. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The creator of the software explains: "Because of AliasVault's zero-knowledge encryption design, the tokens stored in aliasvault.xml are API session tokens that cannot decrypt the vault on their own: the master password is required for that. So while this isn't a direct vault compromise risk, there's no reason to include them in backups either."</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2972 | a466350665 Smart-SSO Role Edit UserController.java save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2972</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in a466350665 Smart-SSO up to 2.1.1. This affects the function Save of the file smart-sso-server/src/main/java/openjoe/smart/sso/server/controller/admin/UserController.java of the component Role Edit Page. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2971 | a466350665 Smart-SSO Login login.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in a466350665 Smart-SSO up to 2.1.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file smart-sso-server/src/main/resources/templates/login.html of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument redirectUri results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2969 | datapizza-labs datapizza-ai Jinja2 Template prompt.py ChatPromptTemplate special elements used in a template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2969</link><description>A flaw has been found in datapizza-labs datapizza-ai 0.0.2. Affected is the function ChatPromptTemplate of the file datapizza-ai-core/datapizza/modules/prompt/prompt.py of the component Jinja2 Template Handler. This manipulation of the argument Prompt causes improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2970 | datapizza-labs datapizza-ai cache.py RedisCache deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2970</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in datapizza-labs datapizza-ai 0.0.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RedisCache of the file datapizza-ai-cache/redis/datapizza/cache/redis/cache.py. Such manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack requires being on the local network. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2967 | Cesanta Mongoose TCP Sequence Number net_builtin.c getpeer verification of source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2967</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. This affects the function getpeer of the file /src/net_builtin.c of the component TCP Sequence Number Handler. The manipulation leads to improper verification of source of a communication channel. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2968 | Cesanta Mongoose Poly1305 Authentication Tag tls_chacha20.c mg_chacha20_poly1305_decrypt signature verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2968</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. This impacts the function mg_chacha20_poly1305_decrypt of the file /src/tls_chacha20.c of the component Poly1305 Authentication Tag Handler. The manipulation results in improper verification of cryptographic signature. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2998 | eAI Technologies｜ERP - DLL Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2998</link><description>ERP developed by eAI Technologies has a DLL Hijacking vulnerability, allowing authenticated local attackers to place a crafted DLL file in the same directory as the program, thereby executing arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2965 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM System Extension edit.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2965</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 1.2.9. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/SysModule/edit.html of the component System Extension Module. Performing a manipulation of the argument Title results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product is published under multiple names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2966 | Cesanta Mongoose DNS Transaction ID dns.c mg_sendnsreq random values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2966</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. The impacted element is the function mg_sendnsreq of the file /src/dns.c of the component DNS Transaction ID Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument random can lead to insufficiently random values. The attack can be launched remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2997 | WisdomGarden｜Tronclass - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2997</link><description>Tronclass developed by WisdomGarden has a Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability. After obtaining a course ID, authenticated remote attackers to modify a specific parameter to obtain a course invitation code, thereby joining any course.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24494 | SQL injection vulnerability in Order Up Online Ordering System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24494</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the /api/integrations/getintegrations endpoint of Order Up Online Ordering System 1.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to access sensitive backend database data via a crafted store_id parameter in a POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2964 | higuma web-audio-recorder-js Dynamic Config Handling WebAudioRecorder.js extend prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2964</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in higuma web-audio-recorder-js 0.1/0.1.1. Impacted is the function extend in the library lib/WebAudioRecorder.js of the component Dynamic Config Handling. Such manipulation leads to improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2962 | D-Link DWR-M960 Scheduled Reboot Configuration Endpoint formDateReboot sub_460F30 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2962</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_460F30 of the file /boafrm/formDateReboot of the component Scheduled Reboot Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2963 | Jinher OA C6 OfficeSupplyTypeRight.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2963</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Jinher OA C6 up to 20260210. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /C6/Jhsoft.Web.officesupply/OfficeSupplyTypeRight.aspx. This manipulation of the argument id/offsnum causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2960 | D-Link DWR-M960 formDhcpv6s sub_468D64 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2960</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this issue is the function sub_468D64 of the file /boafrm/formDhcpv6s. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2961 | D-Link DWR-M960 VPN Configuration Endpoint formVpnConfigSetup sub_4196C4 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2961</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This affects the function sub_4196C4 of the file /boafrm/formVpnConfigSetup of the component VPN Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2588 | Crypt::NaCl::Sodium versions through 2.001 for Perl has an integer overflow flaw on 32-bit systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2588</link><description>Crypt::NaCl::Sodium versions through 2.001 for Perl has an integer overflow flaw on 32-bit systems.

Sodium.xs casts a STRLEN (size_t) to unsigned long long when passing a length pointer to libsodium functions.  On 32-bit systems size_t is typically 32-bits while an unsigned long long is at least 64-bits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2958 | D-Link DWR-M960 formWsc sub_457C5C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2958</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected is the function sub_457C5C of the file /boafrm/formWsc. Such manipulation of the argument save_apply leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2959 | D-Link DWR-M960 formNewSchedule sub_44E0F8 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2959</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_44E0F8 of the file /boafrm/formNewSchedule. Performing a manipulation of the argument url results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2957 | qinming99 dst-admin File BackupController.java deleteBackup denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2957</link><description>A weakness has been identified in qinming99 dst-admin up to 1.5.0. This impacts the function deleteBackup of the file src/main/java/com/tugos/dst/admin/controller/BackupController.java of the component File Handler. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2956 | qinming99 dst-admin restore revertBackup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2956</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in qinming99 dst-admin up to 1.5.0. This affects the function revertBackup of the file /home/restore. The manipulation of the argument Name results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 22:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2954 | Dromara UJCMS ImportDataController import-channel importChanel injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2954</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara UJCMS 10.0.2. Impacted is the function importChanel of the file /api/backend/ext/import-data/import-channel of the component ImportDataController. Performing a manipulation of the argument driverClassName/url results in injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25455 | Web Ofisi E-Ticaret v3 SQL Injection via ara.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25455</link><description>Web Ofisi E-Ticaret v3 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'a' parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to with malicious 'a' parameter values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25456 | Web Ofisi Emlak v2 SQL Injection via ara Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25456</link><description>Web Ofisi Emlak v2 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'ara' GET parameter. Attackers can send requests to with time-based SQL injection payloads to extract sensitive database information or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25457 | Web Ofisi Firma v13 SQL Injection via oz Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25457</link><description>Web Ofisi Firma v13 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'oz' array parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to category pages with malicious 'oz[]' values using time-based blind SQL injection payloads to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25458 | Web Ofisi Firma Rehberi v1 SQL Injection via firmalar.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25458</link><description>Web Ofisi Firma Rehberi v1 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through GET parameters. Attackers can send requests to with malicious payloads in the 'il', 'kat', or 'kelime' parameters to extract sensitive database information or perform time-based blind SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25459 | Web Ofisi Emlak V2 SQL Injection via emlak-ara.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25459</link><description>Web Ofisi Emlak V2 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in the endpoint that allow unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries through GET parameters. Attackers can inject SQL code into parameters like emlak_durumu, emlak_tipi, il, ilce, kelime, and semt to extract sensitive database information or perform time-based blind SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25460 | Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 SQL Injection via q Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25460</link><description>Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'q' GET parameter. Attackers can send requests to the arama endpoint with malicious 'q' values using time-based SQL injection techniques to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25461 | Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 SQL Injection via ajax/productsFilterSearch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25461</link><description>Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'q' parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the ajax/productsFilterSearch endpoint with malicious 'q' values using time-based blind SQL injection techniques to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25462 | Web Ofisi Rent a Car v3 SQL Injection via klima Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25462</link><description>Web Ofisi Rent a Car v3 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'klima' parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to with malicious 'klima' values to extract sensitive database information or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2952 | Vaelsys HTTP POST Request tree_server.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2952</link><description>A flaw has been found in Vaelsys 4.1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /tree/tree_server.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument xajaxargs causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2953 | Dromara UJCMS Template WebFileTemplateController.delete deleteDirectory path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2953</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dromara UJCMS 101.2. This issue affects the function deleteDirectory of the file WebFileTemplateController.delete of the component Template Handler. Such manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25366 | microASP Portal+ CMS SQL Injection via pagina.phtml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25366</link><description>microASP Portal+ CMS contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries by injecting malicious code into the explode_tree parameter. Attackers can send crafted requests to pagina.phtml with SQL injection payloads using extractvalue and concat functions to extract sensitive database information like the current database name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25391 | Ashop Shopping Cart Software Lastest Latest SQL Injection via bannedcustomers.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25391</link><description>Ashop Shopping Cart Software contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the blacklistitemid parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the admin/bannedcustomers.php endpoint with crafted SQL payloads using SLEEP functions to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25433 | XOOPS CMS 2.5.9 SQL Injection via gerar_pdf.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25433</link><description>XOOPS CMS 2.5.9 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the cid parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to the gerar_pdf.php endpoint with malicious cid values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25439 | NoviSmart CMS SQL Injection via Referer HTTP Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25439</link><description>NoviSmart CMS contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries by injecting malicious code through the Referer HTTP header field. Attackers can craft requests with time-based SQL injection payloads in the Referer header to extract sensitive database information or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25440 | WebIncorp ERP Every version SQL Injection via product_detail.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25440</link><description>WebIncorp ERP contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the prod_id parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to product_detail.php with malicious prod_id values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2947 | rymcu forest User Profile UserInfoController.java updateUserInfo cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2947</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in rymcu forest up to 0.0.5. This affects the function updateUserInfo of the file - src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/web/api/user/UserInfoController.java of the component User Profile Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25442 | Web Wiz Forums 12.01 SQL Injection via PF Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25442</link><description>Web Wiz Forums 12.01 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the PF parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to member_profile.asp with malicious PF values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25443 | Inventory Webapp SQL Injection via add-item.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25443</link><description>Inventory Webapp contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through GET parameters. Attackers can supply malicious SQL payloads in the name, description, quantity, or cat_id parameters to add-item.php to execute arbitrary database commands.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25446 | DIGIT CENTRIS ERP Every version SQL Injection via datum1 Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25446</link><description>DIGIT CENTRIS ERP contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the datum1, datum2, KID, and PID parameters. Attackers can send POST requests to /korisnikinfo.php with malicious SQL syntax in these parameters to extract or modify sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25450 | Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 SQL Injection via card.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25450</link><description>Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities that allow authenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through POST parameters. Attackers can inject malicious SQL through parameters like actioncode, demand_reason_id, and availability_id in card.php endpoints to extract sensitive database information using boolean-based blind, error-based, and time-based blind techniques.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25452 | Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 SQL Injection via elemid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25452</link><description>Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 contains an SQL injection vulnerability in the elemid POST parameter of the viewcat.php endpoint that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries. Attackers can submit crafted POST requests with malicious SQL payloads in the elemid parameter to extract sensitive database information using error-based or time-based blind SQL injection techniques.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2945 | JeecgBoot uploadImgByHttp server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2945</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot 3.9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sys/common/uploadImgByHttp. Executing a manipulation of the argument fileUrl can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2946 | rymcu forest Article Content/Comments/Portfolio XssUtils.java XssUtils.replaceHtmlCode cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2946</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in rymcu forest up to 0.0.5. Affected by this issue is the function XssUtils.replaceHtmlCode of the file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/util/XssUtils.java of the component Article Content/Comments/Portfolio. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2944 | Tosei Online Store Management System ネット店舗管理システム HTTP POST Request monitor.php system os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2944</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tosei Online Store Management System ネット店舗管理システム 1.01. Affected is the function system of the file /cgi-bin/monitor.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument DevId results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2943 | SapneshNaik Student Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2943</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SapneshNaik Student Management System up to f4b4f0928f0b5551a28ee81ae7e7fe47d9345318. This impacts an unknown function of the file index.php. Such manipulation of the argument Error leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2940 | Zaher1307 tiny_web_server URL tiny.c out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2940</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Zaher1307 tiny_web_server up to 8d77b1044a0ca3a5297d8726ac8aa2cf944d481b. This affects the function tiny_web_server/tiny.c of the file tiny_web_server/tiny.c of the component URL Handler. This manipulation causes out-of-bounds write. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2939 | itsourcecode Student Management System Add Student add_student cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2939</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /add_student/ of the component Add Student Module. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2938 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System update_smtp.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2938</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /srms/script/admin/core/update_smtp.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2385 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Addons for Elementor, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.4.7 - Unauthenticated Email Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2385</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Addons for Elementor, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.7. This is due to the plugin decrypting and trusting attacker-controlled email_data in an unauthenticated AJAX handler without cryptographic authenticity guarantees. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to tamper with form email routing and redirection values to trigger unauthorized email relay and attacker-controlled redirection via the 'email_data' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2934 | YiFang CMS Extended Management D_friendLinkGroup.php update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2934</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. This impacts the function update of the file app/db/admin/D_friendLinkGroup.php of the component Extended Management Module. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2935 | UTT HiPER 810G ConfigExceptMSN strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2935</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. This issue affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptMSN. Executing a manipulation of the argument remark can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2932 | YiFang CMS Extended Management D_adPosition.php update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2932</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. The impacted element is the function update of the file app/db/admin/D_adPosition.php of the component Extended Management Module. Performing a manipulation of the argument name/index results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2933 | YiFang CMS Extended Management D_adManage.php update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2933</link><description>A weakness has been identified in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. This affects the function update of the file app/db/admin/D_adManage.php of the component Extended Management Module. Executing a manipulation of the argument Name can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2930 | Tenda A18 Httpd Service UploadCfg webCgiGetUploadFile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2930</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda A18 15.13.07.13. The affected element is the function webCgiGetUploadFile of the file /cgi-bin/UploadCfg of the component Httpd Service. Such manipulation of the argument boundary leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1369 | Conditional CAPTCHA &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1369</link><description>The Conditional CAPTCHA WordPress plugin through 4.0.0 does not validate a parameter before redirecting the user to its value, leading to an Open Redirect issue</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2929 | D-Link DWR-M960 Wireless Access Control Endpoint formWlAc sub_453140 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2929</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Impacted is the function sub_453140 of the file /boafrm/formWlAc of the component Wireless Access Control Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument submit-url causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2928 | D-Link DWR-M960 WLAN Encryption Configuration Endpoint formWlEncrypt sub_452CCC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2928</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This issue affects the function sub_452CCC of the file /boafrm/formWlEncrypt of the component WLAN Encryption Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2926 | D-Link DWR-M960 LTE Configuration Endpoint formLteSetup sub_4237AC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2926</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This affects the function sub_4237AC of the file /boafrm/formLteSetup of the component LTE Configuration Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2927 | D-Link DWR-M960 Operation Mode Configuration Endpoint formOpMode sub_462590 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2927</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_462590 of the file /boafrm/formOpMode of the component Operation Mode Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2912 | code-projects Online Reviewer System studentresult-view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2912</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /system/system/students/assessments/results/studentresult-view.php. The manipulation of the argument test_id results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2913 | libvips source.c vips_source_read_to_memory heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2913</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in libvips up to 8.19.0. The affected element is the function vips_source_read_to_memory of the file libvips/iofuncs/source.c. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: a56feecbe9ed66521d9647ec9fbcd2546eccd7ee. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue. The confirmation of the bugfix mentions: "[T]he impact of this is negligible, since this only affects custom seekable sources larger than 4 GiB (and the crash occurs in user code rather than libvips itself)."</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2925 | D-Link DWR-M960 Bridge VLAN Configuration Endpoint formBridgeVlan sub_42B5A0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2925</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this issue is the function sub_42B5A0 of the file /boafrm/formBridgeVlan of the component Bridge VLAN Configuration Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2910 | Tenda HG9 formPing6 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2910</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda HG9 300001138. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boaform/formPing6. Executing a manipulation of the argument pingAddr can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2911 | Tenda FH451 GstDhcpSetSer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2911</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH451 up to 1.0.0.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/GstDhcpSetSer. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2906 | Tenda HG9 Samba Configuration Endpoint formSamba stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2906</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boaform/formSamba of the component Samba Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument sambaCap results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2907 | Tenda HG9 GPON Configuration Endpoint formgponConf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2907</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boaform/formgponConf of the component GPON Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument fmgpon_loid/fmgpon_loid_password causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2908 | Tenda HG9 Loopback Detection Configuration Endpoint formLoopBack stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2908</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boaform/formLoopBack of the component Loopback Detection Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument Ethtype leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2909 | Tenda HG9 Diagnostic Ping Endpoint formPing stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2909</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda HG9 300001138. This affects an unknown part of the file /boaform/formPing of the component Diagnostic Ping Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument pingAddr results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2905 | Tenda HG9 Wireless Configuration Endpoint formWlanSetup stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2905</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda HG9 300001138. This impacts an unknown function of the file /boaform/formWlanSetup of the component Wireless Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2897 | funadmin Backend index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2897</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file app/backend/view/index/index.html of the component Backend Interface. The manipulation of the argument Value leads to cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2898 | funadmin Backend Endpoint AuthCloudService.php getMember deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2898</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This issue affects the function getMember of the file app/common/service/AuthCloudService.php of the component Backend Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument cloud_account results in deserialization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2903 | skvadrik re2c ast.cc check_and_merge_special_rules null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2903</link><description>A flaw has been found in skvadrik re2c up to 4.4. Impacted is the function check_and_merge_special_rules of the file src/parse/ast.cc. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. Patch name: febeb977936f9519a25d9fbd10ff8256358cdb97. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2904 | UTT HiPER 810G ConfigExceptAli strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2904</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810G 1.7.7-171114. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptAli. Executing a manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>