<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:30:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-38268 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38268</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  260585.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26024 | IBM Planning Analytics on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26024</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0 could allow an attacker on a shared network to obtain sensitive information caused by insecure network communication.  IBM X-Force ID:  247898.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42006 | IBM i information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42006</link><description>IBM Administration Runtime Expert for i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information caused by improper authority checks.  IBM X-Force ID:  265266.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48893 | Senayan Library Management Systems SLIMS 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/staff_act.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48893</link><description>Senayan Library Management Systems SLIMS 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/staff_act.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48813 | Senayan Library Management Systems (Slims) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/fines_report.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48813</link><description>Senayan Library Management Systems (Slims) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/fines_report.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48842 | D-Link Go-RT-AC750 revA_v101b03 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the service parameter at hedwig.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48842</link><description>D-Link Go-RT-AC750 revA_v101b03 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the service parameter at hedwig.cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49371 | RuoYi up to v4.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via /system/dept/edit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49371</link><description>RuoYi up to v4.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via /system/dept/edit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4518 | A vulnerability exists in the input validation of the GOOSE 
messages where out of range values received and processed 
by the IED caused a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4518</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the input validation of the GOOSE 
messages where out of range values received and processed 
by the IED caused a reboot of the device. In order for an 
attacker to exploit the vulnerability, goose receiving blocks need 
to be configured.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45168 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45168</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the invscout command to execute arbitrary commands.  IBM X-Force ID:  267966.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28896 | Weak encoding for password in UDS services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28896</link><description>Access to critical Unified Diagnostics Services (UDS) of the Modular Infotainment Platform 3 (MIB3) infotainment is transmitted via Controller Area Network (CAN) bus in a form that can be easily decoded by attackers with physical access to the vehicle.

Vulnerability discovered on Škoda Superb III (3V3) - 2.0 TDI manufactured in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28895 | Hard-coded password for access to power controller chip memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28895</link><description>The password for access to the debugging console of the PoWer Controller chip (PWC) of the MIB3 infotainment is hard-coded in the firmware. The console allows attackers with physical access to the MIB3 unit to gain full control over the PWC chip.

Vulnerability found on Škoda Superb III (3V3) - 2.0 TDI manufactured in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5636 | Malicious File Upload in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5636</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows Command Injection.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5637 | Plaintext Storage of a Password in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5637</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5635 | User Enumeration in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5635</link><description>Improper Protection for Outbound Error Messages and Alert Signals vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows Account Footprinting.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6461 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in viliusle/minipaint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6461</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository viliusle/minipaint prior to 4.14.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5634 | SQLi in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6449 | The Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'validate' f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6449</link><description>The Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'validate' function and insufficient blocklisting on the 'wpcf7_antiscript_file_name' function in versions up to, and including, 5.8.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with editor-level capabilities or above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, but due to the htaccess configuration, remote code cannot be executed in most cases. By default, the file will be deleted from the server immediately. However, in some cases, other plugins may make it possible for the file to live on the server longer. This can make remote code execution possible when combined with another vulnerability, such as local file inclusion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5427 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5427</link><description>A local non-privileged user can make improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3443 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3443</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 12.1 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for a Guest user to add an emoji on confidential work items.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3949 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3949</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for unauthorized users to view a public projects' release descriptions via an atom endpoint when release access on the public was set to only project members.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3964 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3964</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 13.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for users to access composer packages on public projects that have package registry disabled in the project settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4317 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4317</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 9.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for a user with the Developer role to update a pipeline schedule from an unprotected branch to a protected branch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4658 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4658</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 8.13 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to abuse the `Allowed to merge` permission as a guest user, when granted the permission through a group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4912 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4912</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 10.5 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted mermaid diagram input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5226 | Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5226</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. Under certain circumstances, a malicious actor bypass prohibited branch checks using a specially crafted branch name to manipulate repository content in the UI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5995 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5995</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to abuse the policy bot to gain access to internal projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6033 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6033</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Jira integration configuration in GitLab CE/EE, affecting all versions from 15.10 prior to 16.6.1, 16.5 prior to 16.5.3, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.3 allows attacker to execute javascript in victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5915 | A vulnerability of Uncontrolled Resource Consumption has been identified in STARDOM provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5915</link><description>A vulnerability of Uncontrolled Resource Consumption has been identified in STARDOM provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation. This vulnerability may allow to a remote attacker to cause a denial-of-service condition to the FCN/FCJ controller by sending a crafted packet. While sending the packet, the maintenance homepage of the controller could not be accessed. Therefore, functions of the maintenance homepage, changing configuration, viewing logs, etc. are not available. But the controller’s operation is not stopped by the condition.

The affected products and versions are as follows: STARDOM FCN/FCJ R1.01 to R4.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45252 | DLL Hijacking vulnerability in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, due to the installation of the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45252</link><description>DLL Hijacking vulnerability in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, due to the installation of the service in a directory that grants write privileges to standard users, allows attackers to manipulate files, execute arbitrary code, and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45253 | An issue was discovered in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, allows attackers to manipulate files...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45253</link><description>An issue was discovered in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, allows attackers to manipulate files and escalate privileges via RollingFileAppender.DeleteFile method performed by the log4net library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48016 | Restaurant Table Booking System V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rtbs/admin/index.php via the username parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48016</link><description>Restaurant Table Booking System V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rtbs/admin/index.php via the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43089 | Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains insufficient protection for the Policy folder. A local malicious standard user co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43089</link><description>Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains insufficient protection for the Policy folder. A local malicious standard user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify the content of the policy file, leading to unauthorized access to resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43453 | An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the IP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43453</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the IP parameter of the setDiagnosisCfg component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43454 | An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43454</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hostName parameter of the switchOpMode component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43455 | An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43455</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the command parameter of the setting/setTracerouteCfg component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46956 | SQL injection vulnerability in Packers and Movers Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted pay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46956</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Packers and Movers Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted payload to the /mpms/admin/?page=user/manage_user&amp;id file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 23:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46389 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 firmware 6.2.4 and LINX-151 Firmware 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via registry.xml file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46389</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 firmware 6.2.4 and LINX-151 Firmware 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via registry.xml file. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on LINX configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 23:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46386 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 firmware 6.2.4 and LINX-151 firmware 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via registry.xml file. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46386</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 firmware 6.2.4 and LINX-151 firmware 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via registry.xml file. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose smtp client account credentials and bypass email authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46387 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 firmware 6.2.4 and LINX-151 firmware 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via dpal_config.zml f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46387</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 firmware 6.2.4 and LINX-151 firmware 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via dpal_config.zml file. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on Loytec device data point configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46388 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 6.2.4 and LINX-151 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via dpal_config.zml file. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46388</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX-212 6.2.4 and LINX-151 7.2.4 are vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via dpal_config.zml file. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose smtp client account credentials and bypass email authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46326 | ZStack Cloud version 3.10.38 and before allows unauthenticated API access to the list of active job UUIDs and the session ID for each of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46326</link><description>ZStack Cloud version 3.10.38 and before allows unauthenticated API access to the list of active job UUIDs and the session ID for each of these. This leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47307 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in /apply.cgi in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T310 v2.2.2.6 allows attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47307</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in /apply.cgi in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T310 v2.2.2.6 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the ApCliAuthMode parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46383 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX Configurator 7.4.10 uses HTTP Basic Authentication, which transmits usernames and passwords in base64-encoded c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46383</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX Configurator 7.4.10 uses HTTP Basic Authentication, which transmits usernames and passwords in base64-encoded cleartext and allows remote attackers to steal the password and gain full control of Loytec device configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46384 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX Configurator 7.4.10 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. Cleartext storage of credentials allows remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46384</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX Configurator 7.4.10 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. Cleartext storage of credentials allows remote attackers to disclose admin password and bypass an authentication to login Loytec device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46385 | LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX Configurator 7.4.10 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. An admin credential is passed as a value of URL para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46385</link><description>LOYTEC electronics GmbH LINX Configurator 7.4.10 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. An admin credential is passed as a value of URL parameters without encryption, so it allows remote attackers to steal the password and gain full control of Loytec device configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42916 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.1.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42916</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.1.2, Safari 17.1.2. Processing web content may disclose sensitive information. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42917 | A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2, macOS Sonoma 14....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42917</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.1.2, Safari 17.1.2. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47279 | Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47279</link><description>In Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master v.1.0.7, A vulnerability exists that allows an unauthenticated attacker to disclose user information through a single UDP packet, obtain plaintext credentials, or perform NTLM relaying.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39226 | Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master Exposed Dangerous Method Or Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39226</link><description>In Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master v.1.0.7, a vulnerability exists that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code through a single UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46690 | Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46690</link><description>In Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master v.1.0.7, a vulnerability exists that allows an attacker to write to any file to any location of the filesystem, which could lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47207 | Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47207</link><description>In Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master v.1.0.7, a vulnerability exists that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute code with local administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48894 | Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in jshERP V3.3 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doFilter function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48894</link><description>Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in jshERP V3.3 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doFilter function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5908 | Heap Based Buffer Overflow in PTC KEPServerEx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5908</link><description>KEPServerEX is vulnerable to a buffer overflow which may allow an attacker to crash the product being accessed or leak information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5909 | Improper Validation of Certificate with Host Mismatch in PTC KEPServerEx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5909</link><description>KEPServerEX does not properly validate certificates from clients which may allow unauthenticated users to connect.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35975 | Absolute path traversal vulnerability in the Systematica SMTP Adapter component (up to v2.0.1.101) in Systematica Radius (up to v.3.9.256.77...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35975</link><description>Absolute path traversal vulnerability in the Systematica SMTP Adapter component (up to v2.0.1.101) in Systematica Radius (up to v.3.9.256.777) allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a full pathname in GET parameter "file" in URL. Also: affected components in same product - HTTP Adapter (up to v.1.8.0.15), MSSQL MessageBus Proxy (up to v.1.1.06), Financial Calculator (up to v.1.3.05), FIX Adapter (up to v.2.4.0.25)</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 21:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49735 | Apache Tiles: Unvalidated input may lead to path traversal and XXE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49735</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **

The value set as the DefaultLocaleResolver.LOCALE_KEY attribute on the session was not validated while resolving XML definition files, leading to possible path traversal and eventually SSRF/XXE when passing user-controlled data to this key. Passing user-controlled data to this key may be relatively common, as it was also used like that to set the language in the 'tiles-test' application shipped with Tiles.

This issue affects Apache Tiles from version 2 onwards.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 21:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6442 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System add-phlebotomist.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6442</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file add-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument empid/fullname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246445 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 21:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47453 | An Untrusted search path vulnerability in Sohu Video Player 7.0.15.0 allows local users to gain escalated privileges through the version.dll...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47453</link><description>An Untrusted search path vulnerability in Sohu Video Player 7.0.15.0 allows local users to gain escalated privileges through the version.dll file in the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47454 | An Untrusted search path vulnerability in NetEase CloudMusic 2.10.4 for Windows allows local users to gain escalated privileges through the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47454</link><description>An Untrusted search path vulnerability in NetEase CloudMusic 2.10.4 for Windows allows local users to gain escalated privileges through the urlmon.dll file in the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47452 | An Untrusted search path vulnerability in notepad++ 6.5 allows local users to gain escalated privileges through the msimg32.dll file in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47452</link><description>An Untrusted search path vulnerability in notepad++ 6.5 allows local users to gain escalated privileges through the msimg32.dll file in the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6440 | SourceCodester Book Borrower System add-book.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6440</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Book Borrower System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file endpoint/add-book.php. The manipulation of the argument Book Title/Book Author leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246443.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6439 | ZenTao PMS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6439</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ZenTao PMS 18.8. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246439.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48802 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48802</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48803 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48803</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48804 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48804</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48805 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48805</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48806 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48806</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48807 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48807</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48808 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48808</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6352 | Aquaforest TIFF Server default configuration allows access to arbitrary files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6352</link><description>The default configuration of Aquaforest TIFF Server allows access to arbitrary file paths, subject to any restrictions imposed by Internet Information Services (IIS) or Microsoft Windows. Depending on how a web application uses and configures TIFF Server, a remote attacker may be able to enumerate files or directories, traverse directories, bypass authentication, or access restricted files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48810 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48810</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48811 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48811</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file, sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function that when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6353 | Tyler Technologies Civil and Criminal Electronic Filing Upload.aspx allows authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6353</link><description>Tyler Technologies Civil and Criminal Electronic Filing allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload, delete, and view files by manipulating the Upload.aspx 'enky' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6354 | Tyler Technologies Magistrate Court Case Management Plus PDFViewer.aspx allows authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6354</link><description>Tyler Technologies Magistrate Court Case Management Plus allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload, delete, and view files by manipulating the PDFViewer.aspx 'filename' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6375 | Tyler Technologies Magistrate Court Case Management Plus stores backups insecurely</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6375</link><description>Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus may store backups in a location that can be accessed by a remote, unauthenticated attacker. Backups may contain sensitive information such as database credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6376 | Henschen &amp;amp; Associates court document management software cache uses predictable file names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6376</link><description>Henschen &amp; Associates court document management software does not sufficiently randomize file names of cached documents, allowing a remote, unauthenticated attacker to access restricted documents.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48812 | In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48812</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file sub_4119A0 function obtains fields from the front-end through Uci_ Set_ The Str function that when passed to the CsteSystem function creates a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6343 | Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus use of Aquaforest TIFF Server tssp.aspx allows authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6343</link><description>Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to enumerate and access sensitive files using the tiffserver/tssp.aspx 'FN' and 'PN' parameters. This behavior is related to the use of a deprecated version of Aquaforest TIFF Server, possibly 2.x. The vulnerable Aquaforest TIFF Server feature was removed on or around 2023-11-01. Insecure configuration issues in Aquaforest TIFF Server are identified separately as CVE-2023-6352. CVE-2023-6343 is similar to CVE-2020-9323. CVE-2023-6343 is related to or partially caused by CVE-2023-6352.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6344 | Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus use of Aquaforest TIFF Server te003.aspx and te004.aspx allows authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6344</link><description>Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to enumerate directories using the tiffserver/te003.aspx or te004.aspx 'ifolder' parameter. This behavior is related to the use of a deprecated version of Aquaforest TIFF Server, possibly 2.x. The vulnerable Aquaforest TIFF Server feature was removed on or around 2023-11-01. Insecure configuration issues in Aquaforest TIFF Server are identified separately as CVE-2023-6352. CVE-2023-6343 is related to or partially caused by CVE-2023-6352.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6341 | Catalis CM360 allows authentication bypass </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6341</link><description>Catalis (previously Icon Software) CMS360 allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive court documents by modifying document and other identifiers in URLs. The impact varies based on the intention and configuration of a specific CMS360 installation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6342 | Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus &amp;quot;pay for print&amp;quot; allows authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6342</link><description>Tyler Technologies Court Case Management Plus allows a remote attacker to authenticate as any user by manipulating at least the 'CmWebSearchPfp/Login.aspx?xyzldk=' and 
'payforprint_CM/Redirector.ashx?userid=' parameters. The vulnerable "pay for print" feature was removed on or around 2023-11-01.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47870 | WordPress wpForo Forum Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control and Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47870</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), Missing Authorization vulnerability in gVectors Team wpForo Forum wpforo allows Cross Site Request Forgery, Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs leading to forced all users log out.This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through 2.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34018 | WordPress SoundCloud Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34018</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SoundCloud Inc. SoundCloud Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SoundCloud Shortcode: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2265 | Improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames could lead to clickjacking attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2265</link><description>An Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-411L could allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform clickjacking based attacks against an authenticated and authorized user.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2266 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation could lead to cross-site scripting based attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2266</link><description>An Improper neutralization of input during web page generation in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-411L could allow an attacker to generate cross-site scripting based attacks against an authorized and authenticated user.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2267 | Improper input validation could lead to reflection injection attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2267</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-411L could allow an attacker to perform reflection attacks against an authorized and authenticated user.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38400 | WordPress Enfold Theme &amp;lt;= 5.6.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38400</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kriesi Enfold - Responsive Multi-Purpose Theme allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Enfold - Responsive Multi-Purpose Theme: from n/a through 5.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47521 | WordPress Q2W3 Post Order Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47521</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Max Bond, AndreSC Q2W3 Post Order allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Q2W3 Post Order: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6438 | Thecosy IceCMS Like improper enforcement of a single, unique action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6438</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Thecosy IceCMS 2.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /WebArticle/articles/ of the component Like Handler. The manipulation leads to improper enforcement of a single, unique action. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246438 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2264 | Improper input validition could lead to code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2264</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-411L could allow a malicious actor to manipulate authorized users to click on a link that could allow undesired behavior.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31176 | Insufficient entropy vulnerability could lead to authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31176</link><description>An Insufficient Entropy vulnerability in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-451 could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to brute-force session tokens and bypass authentication. 


See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31177 | Improper neutralizataion of input could lead to execution of arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31177</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation  ('Cross-site Scripting') in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-451 could allow an attacker to craft a link that could execute arbitrary code on a victim's system.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34388 | Improper authentication could lead to session hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34388</link><description>An Improper Authentication vulnerability in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-451 could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to potentially perform session hijacking attack and bypass authentication.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34389 | Allocation of resources without limits could lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34389</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-451 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to make the system unavailable for an indefinite amount of time.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34390 |  Improper input validation could lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34390</link><description>An input validation vulnerability in the Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories SEL-451 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to create a denial of service against the system and locking out services.



See product Instruction Manual Appendix A dated 20230830 for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47844 | WordPress Grab &amp;amp; Save Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47844</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lim Kai Yang Grab &amp; Save allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Grab &amp; Save: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47848 | WordPress Tainacan Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.20.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47848</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tainacan.Org Tainacan allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tainacan: from n/a through 0.20.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47853 | WordPress myCred Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47853</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in myCred myCred – Points, Rewards, Gamification, Ranks, Badges &amp; Loyalty Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects myCred – Points, Rewards, Gamification, Ranks, Badges &amp; Loyalty Plugin: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47872 | WordPress wpForo Forum Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47872</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gVectors Team wpForo Forum allows Stored XSS.This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47876 | WordPress Perfmatters Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47876</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Perfmatters allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Perfmatters: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47877 | WordPress Perfmatters Plugin &amp;lt; 2.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47877</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Perfmatters allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Perfmatters: from n/a before 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48272 | WordPress Maspik – Spam blacklist Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48272</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in yonifre Maspik – Spam Blacklist allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Maspik – Spam Blacklist: from n/a through 0.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48317 | WordPress Display Custom Post Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48317</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vikas Vatsa Display Custom Post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Display Custom Post: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48320 | WordPress Video Player Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.22 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48320</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebDorado SpiderVPlayer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SpiderVPlayer: from n/a through 1.5.22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48321 | WordPress Accelerated Mobile Pages Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.88.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48321</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ahmed Kaludi, Mohammed Kaludi AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages: from n/a through 1.0.88.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48746 | WordPress Community by PeepSo Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.6.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48746</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PeepSo Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles: from n/a through 6.2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48748 | WordPress Salient Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48748</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Theme nectar Salient Core allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Salient Core: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48752 | WordPress Happyforms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.25.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Happyforms Form builder to get in touch with visitors, grow your email list and collect payments — Happyforms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Form builder to get in touch with visitors, grow your email list and collect payments — Happyforms: from n/a through 1.25.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47875 | WordPress Perfmatters Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47875</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Perfmatters allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Perfmatters: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48278 | WordPress WP Forms Puzzle Captcha Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48278</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Nitin Rathod WP Forms Puzzle Captcha allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Forms Puzzle Captcha: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48749 | WordPress Salient Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48749</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Theme nectar Salient Core allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Salient Core: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48328 | WordPress NextGEN Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.37 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48328</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Imagely WordPress Gallery Plugin – NextGEN Gallery allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WordPress Gallery Plugin – NextGEN Gallery: from n/a through 3.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48754 | WordPress Delete Post Revisions In WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48754</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wap Nepal Delete Post Revisions In WordPress allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Delete Post Revisions In WordPress: from n/a through 4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44143 | WordPress Bamboo Columns Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44143</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bamboo Mcr Bamboo Columns allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bamboo Columns: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5803 | WordPress Business Directory Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5803</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Business Directory Team Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress allows Cross-Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress: from n/a through 6.3.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45609 | WordPress Powr Pack Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45609</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POWR.Io Contact Form – Custom Builder, Payment Form, and More allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Form – Custom Builder, Payment Form, and More: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46086 | WordPress affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46086</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SERVIT Software Solutions affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin: from n/a through 3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25057 | WordPress Libsyn Publisher Hub Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25057</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Libsyn Libsyn Publisher Hub.This issue affects Libsyn Publisher Hub: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39921 | WordPress Molongui Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.19 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39921</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Molongui Author Box, Guest Author and Co-Authors for Your Posts – Molongui allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Author Box, Guest Author and Co-Authors for Your Posts – Molongui: from n/a through 4.6.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26533 | WordPress Zippy Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26533</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Gesundheit Bewegt GmbH Zippy.This issue affects Zippy: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36507 | WordPress BookingPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.64 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36507</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Repute Infosystems BookingPress – Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Online Scheduling Plugin.This issue affects BookingPress – Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Online Scheduling Plugin: from n/a through 1.0.64.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36523 | WordPress Email download link Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36523</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Gopi Ramasamy Email download link.This issue affects Email download link: from n/a through 3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37868 | WordPress Premium Addons PRO Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37868</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons PRO.This issue affects Premium Addons PRO: from n/a through 2.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6360 | The 'My Calendar' WordPress Plugin, version &lt; 3.4.22 is affected by an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'from' and 'to' pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6360</link><description>The 'My Calendar' WordPress Plugin, version &lt; 3.4.22 is affected by an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'from' and 'to' parameters in the '/my-calendar/v1/events' rest route.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37890 | WordPress KB Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.88 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37890</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPOmnia KB Support – WordPress Help Desk and Knowledge Base allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. Users with a role as low as a subscriber can view other customers.This issue affects KB Support – WordPress Help Desk and Knowledge Base: from n/a through 1.5.88.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37972 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Stock Alert Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37972</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in MultiVendorX Product Stock Manager &amp; Notifier for WooCommerce.This issue affects Product Stock Manager &amp; Notifier for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40211 | WordPress Post Grid Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.50 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40211</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in PickPlugins Post Grid Combo – 36+ Gutenberg Blocks.This issue affects Post Grid Combo – 36+ Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 2.2.50.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40600 | WordPress EWWW Image Optimizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40600</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Exactly WWW EWWW Image Optimizer. It works only when debug.log is turned on.This issue affects EWWW Image Optimizer: from n/a through 7.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40662 | WordPress Cookies and Content Security Policy Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.15 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40662</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Jonk @ Follow me Darling Cookies and Content Security Policy.This issue affects Cookies and Content Security Policy: from n/a through 2.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6402 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System add-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6402</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file add-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument empid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246423.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41735 | WordPress Email posts to subscribers Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41735</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Gopi Ramasamy Email posts to subscribers.This issue affects Email posts to subscribers: from n/a through 6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44150 | WordPress ProfilePress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.13.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44150</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in ProfilePress Membership Team Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress.This issue affects Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress: from n/a through 4.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45066 | WordPress WP Ultimate Exporter Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45066</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Smackcoders Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users.This issue affects Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45834 | WordPress Libsyn Publisher Hub Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45834</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Libsyn Libsyn Publisher Hub.This issue affects Libsyn Publisher Hub: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46820 | WordPress Image Regenerate &amp;amp; Select Crop Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46820</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Iulia Cazan Image Regenerate &amp; Select Crop.This issue affects Image Regenerate &amp; Select Crop: from n/a through 7.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6401 | NotePad++ dbghelp.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6401</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in NotePad++ up to 8.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file dbghelp.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The identifier VDB-246421 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48333 | WordPress Booster for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48333</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Pluggabl LLC Booster for WooCommerce.This issue affects Booster for WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37867 | WordPress Yet Another Stars Rating Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 is vulnerable to Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37867</link><description>Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability in YetAnotherStarsRating.Com YASR – Yet Another Star Rating Plugin for WordPress.This issue affects YASR – Yet Another Star Rating Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 3.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48742 | WordPress License Manager for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.10 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LicenseManager License Manager for WooCommerce license-manager-for-woocommerce allows SQL Injection.This issue affects License Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6136 | WordPress Debug Log Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6136</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Bowo Debug Log Manager.This issue affects Debug Log Manager: from n/a through 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33333 | WordPress Complianz and Complianz Premium plugins - Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33333</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Really Simple Plugins Complianz, Really Simple Plugins Complianz Premium allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Complianz: from n/a through 6.4.4; Complianz Premium: from n/a through 6.4.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48912 | Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/archives/edit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48912</link><description>Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/archives/edit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48913 | Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/archives/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48913</link><description>Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/archives/delete.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48914 | Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/archives/add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48914</link><description>Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/archives/add.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34030 | WordPress Complianz and Complianz Premium plugins - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34030</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Really Simple Plugins Complianz, Really Simple Plugins Complianz Premium allows Cross-Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Complianz: from n/a through 6.4.5; Complianz Premium: from n/a through 6.4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6428 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6428</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /invoicing/app/items_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6429 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6429</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /invoicing/app/clients_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6430 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6430</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /inventory/transactions_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6431 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6431</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /inventory/categories_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6432 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6432</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /inventory/items_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6433 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6433</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /inventory/suppliers_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6434 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6434</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /inventory/sections_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6435 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6435</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /inventory/batches_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36682 | WordPress Schema Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36682</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Brainstorm Force US LLC Schema Pro allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Schema Pro: from n/a through 2.7.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6422 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6422</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Clinic Management System 2.2, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /clinic/patients_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6423 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6423</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Clinic Management System 2.2, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /clinic/events_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6424 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6424</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Clinic Management System 2.2, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /clinic/disease_symptoms_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6425 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6425</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Clinic Management System 2.2, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /clinic/medical_records_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6426 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6426</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /invoicing/app/invoices_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6427 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in BigProf products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6427</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in BigProf Online Invoicing System 2.6, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in persistent XSS through /invoicing/app/invoices_view.php, in the FirstRecord parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacking user to store dangerous JavaScript payloads on the system that will be triggered when the page loads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36685 | WordPress CartFlows Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36685</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Brainstorm Force US LLC CartFlows Pro allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects CartFlows Pro: from n/a through 1.11.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6026 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) in PHPMemcachedAdmin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6026</link><description>A Path traversal vulnerability has been reported in elijaa/phpmemcachedadmin affecting version 1.3.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to delete files stored on the server due to lack of proper verification of user-supplied input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6027 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in PHPMemcachedAdmin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6027</link><description>A critical flaw has been identified in elijaa/phpmemcachedadmin affecting version 1.3.0, specifically related to a stored XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability allows malicious actors to insert a carefully crafted JavaScript payload. The issue arises from improper encoding of user-controlled entries in the "/pmcadmin/configure.php" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47645 | WordPress RegistrationMagic Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.2.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47645</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RegistrationMagic RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login: from n/a through 5.2.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47827 | WordPress Events Addon for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47827</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in NicheAddons Events Addon for Elementor allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Events Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4770 | Uncontrolled Search Path Element Vulnerability in 4D and 4D Windows Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4770</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability has been found on 4D and 4D server Windows executables applications, affecting version 19 R8 100218. This vulnerability consists in a DLL hijacking by replacing x64 shfolder.dll in the installation path, causing an arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48963 | Tenda i6 V1.0.0.8(3856) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/wifiSSIDget.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48963</link><description>Tenda i6 V1.0.0.8(3856) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/wifiSSIDget.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5965 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in EspoCRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5965</link><description>An authenticated privileged attacker could upload a specially crafted zip to the EspoCRM server in version 7.2.5, via the update form, which could lead to arbitrary PHP code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5966 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in EspoCRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5966</link><description>An authenticated privileged attacker could upload a specially crafted zip to the EspoCRM server in version 7.2.5, via the extension deployment form, which could lead to arbitrary PHP code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48279 | WordPress Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48279</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Seraphinite Solutions Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source: from n/a through 2.16.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48281 | WordPress Broken Link Checker for YouTube Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48281</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Super Blog Me Broken Link Checker for YouTube allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Broken Link Checker for YouTube: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48964 | Tenda i6 V1.0.0.8(3856) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/WifiMacFilterSet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48964</link><description>Tenda i6 V1.0.0.8(3856) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/WifiMacFilterSet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6410 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6410</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via editprofile.php in multiple parameters. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6411 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6411</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via home.php in the update parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6412 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6412</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via photo.php in multiple parameters. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6413 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6413</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via photos.php in the id and user parameters. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6414 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6414</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via perfil.php in the id and user parameters. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6415 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6415</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via signin.php in the user parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6416 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6416</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via signup2.php in the emailadd parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6417 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6417</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via update.php in the id parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6418 | SQL injection in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6418</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script that affects version 1.0 and consists of a SQL injection via videos.php in the id parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6419 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6419</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script version 1.0 that allows a XSS via editprofile.php in multiple parameters, the exploitation of which could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload and partially take over the browser session of an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6420 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Voovi Social Networking Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6420</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Voovi Social Networking Script version 1.0 that allows a XSS via 

signup2.php in the emailadd parameter, the exploitation of which could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload and partially take over the browser session of an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48282 | WordPress Taxonomy filter Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48282</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Andrea Landonio Taxonomy filter allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Taxonomy filter: from n/a through 2.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48283 | WordPress Simple Testimonials Showcase Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48283</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Testimonials Showcase allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Simple Testimonials Showcase: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48284 | WordPress Decorator – WooCommerce Email Customizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48284</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WebToffee Decorator – WooCommerce Email Customizer allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Decorator – WooCommerce Email Customizer: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48323 | WordPress Awesome Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48323</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Awesome Support Team Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 6.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48330 | WordPress Bulk Comment Remove Plugin &amp;lt;= 2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48330</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mike Strand Bulk Comment Remove allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Bulk Comment Remove: from n/a through 2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48331 | WordPress MyBookTable Bookstore Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48331</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Stormhill Media MyBookTable Bookstore by Stormhill Media allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects MyBookTable Bookstore by Stormhill Media: from n/a through 3.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48334 | WordPress League Table Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48334</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DAEXT League Table allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects League Table: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6071 | An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a command vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.9 allows a remote administrator ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6071</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a command vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.9 allows a remote administrator to execute arbitrary code as root on the ESM. This is possible as the input isn't correctly sanitized when adding a new data source.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6137 | WordPress Frontier Post Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6137</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in finnj Frontier Post allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Frontier Post: from n/a through 6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32291 | WordPress MonsterInsights Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.14.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32291</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MonsterInsights Pro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MonsterInsights Pro: from n/a through 8.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48744 | WordPress Availability Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48744</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Offshore Web Master Availability Calendar allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Availability Calendar: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38474 | WordPress Campaign Monitor for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38474</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Campaign Monitor Campaign Monitor for WordPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Campaign Monitor for WordPress: from n/a through 2.8.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40674 | WordPress Simple URLs Plugin &amp;lt;= 118 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40674</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lasso Simple URLs – Link Cloaking, Product Displays, and Affiliate Link Management allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple URLs – Link Cloaking, Product Displays, and Affiliate Link Management: from n/a through 118.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40680 | WordPress Yoast SEO Plugin &amp;lt;= 21.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Team Yoast Yoast SEO allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Yoast SEO: from n/a through 21.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41127 | WordPress Evergreen Content Poster Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Evergreen Content Poster Evergreen Content Poster – Auto Post and Schedule Your Best Content to Social Media allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Evergreen Content Poster – Auto Post and Schedule Your Best Content to Social Media: from n/a through 1.3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41128 | WordPress WP Roadmap Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41128</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Iqonic Design WP Roadmap – Product Feedback Board allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Roadmap – Product Feedback Board: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41136 | WordPress Simple Long Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41136</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Laurence/OhMyBox.Info Simple Long Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Long Form: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45050 | WordPress Jetpack Plugin &amp;lt;= 12.8-a.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45050</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic Jetpack – WP Security, Backup, Speed, &amp; Growth allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jetpack – WP Security, Backup, Speed, &amp; Growth: from n/a through 12.8-a.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47505 | WordPress Elementor Website Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.16.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47505</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elementor.Com Elementor allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Elementor: from n/a through 3.16.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47777 | WordPress WooCommerce and WooCommerce Blocks plugins - Auth. Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47777</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic WooCommerce, Automattic WooCommerce Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce: from n/a through 8.1.1; WooCommerce Blocks: from n/a through 11.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47850 | WordPress Community by PeepSo Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47850</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PeepSo Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles: from n/a through 6.2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49733 | Apache Cocoon&amp;#x27;s StreamGenerator is vulnerable to XXE injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49733</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in Apache Cocoon.This issue affects Apache Cocoon: from 2.2.0 before 2.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47851 | WordPress Bootstrap Shortcodes Ultimate Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47851</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akhtarujjaman Shuvo Bootstrap Shortcodes Ultimate allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bootstrap Shortcodes Ultimate: from n/a through 4.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47854 | WordPress Parallax Image Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47854</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Howard Ehrenberg Parallax Image allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Parallax Image: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48289 | WordPress Import Spreadsheets from Microsoft Excel Plugin &amp;lt;= 10.1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48289</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SpreadsheetConverter Import Spreadsheets from Microsoft Excel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Import Spreadsheets from Microsoft Excel: from n/a through 10.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48322 | WordPress eDoc Employee Job Application Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48322</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in eDoc Intelligence eDoc Employee Job Application – Best WordPress Job Manager for Employees allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects eDoc Employee Job Application – Best WordPress Job Manager for Employees: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48326 | WordPress Events Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48326</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pixelite Events Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Events Manager: from n/a through 6.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48329 | WordPress Fast Custom Social Share by CodeBard Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48329</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeBard Fast Custom Social Share by CodeBard allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fast Custom Social Share by CodeBard: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48336 | WordPress Easy Social Icons Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48336</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in cybernetikz Easy Social Icons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Social Icons: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48737 | WordPress TriPay Payment Gateway Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48737</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PT Trijaya Digital Grup TriPay Payment Gateway allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TriPay Payment Gateway: from n/a through 3.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48743 | WordPress Simply Exclude Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48743</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Paul Menard Simply Exclude allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simply Exclude: from n/a through 2.0.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-36806 | A reflected XSS vulnerability allows an open redirect when the victim clicks a malicious link to an error page on 

Sophos Email Appliance 
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36806</link><description>A reflected XSS vulnerability allows an open redirect when the victim clicks a malicious link to an error page on 

Sophos Email Appliance 

older than version 4.5.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49620 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Authenticated users could delete UDFs in resource center they were not authorized for</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49620</link><description>Before DolphinScheduler version 3.1.0, the login user could delete UDF function in the resource center unauthorized (which almost used in sql task), with unauthorized access vulnerability (IDOR), but after version 3.1.0 we fixed this issue. We mark this cve as moderate level because it still requires user login to operate, please upgrade to version 3.1.0 to avoid this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45135 | Apache Cocoon: SQL injection in DatabaseCookieAuthenticatorAction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Cocoon.This issue affects Apache Cocoon: from 2.2.0 before 2.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49701 | Out-of-bounds access a buffer in SIM management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49701</link><description>Memory Corruption in SIM management while USIMPhase2init</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49077 | mailcow-dockerized XSS Vulnerability in Quarantine UI Allows Unauthorized Access and Data Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49077</link><description>Mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified within the Quarantine UI of the system. This vulnerability poses a significant threat to administrators who utilize the Quarantine feature. An attacker can send a carefully crafted email containing malicious JavaScript code. This issue has been patched in version 2023-11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49095 | nexkey allows arbitrary users to impersonate any remote user due to missing signature validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49095</link><description>nexkey is a microblogging platform. Insufficient validation of ActivityPub requests received in inbox could allow any user to impersonate another user in certain circumstances. This issue has been patched in version 12.122.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49700 | Buffer Copy Without Checking size of input in IMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49700</link><description>Security best practices violations, a string operation in Streamingmedia will write past the end of fixed-size destination buffer if the source buffer is too large.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49699 | Out-of-bounds access a buffer in IMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49699</link><description>Memory Corruption in IMS while calling VoLTE Streamingmedia Interface</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49081 | aiohttp&amp;#x27;s ClientSession is vulnerable to CRLF injection via version</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49081</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Improper validation made it possible for an attacker to modify the HTTP request (e.g. to insert a new header) or create a new HTTP request if the attacker controls the HTTP version. The vulnerability only occurs if the attacker can control the HTTP version of the request. This issue has been patched in version 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49052 | File Upload vulnerability in Microweber v.2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the file upload f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49052</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Microweber v.2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the file upload function in the created forms component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49076 | Pimcore missing token/header to prevent CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49076</link><description>Customer-data-framework allows management of customer data within Pimcore. There are no tokens or headers to prevent CSRF attacks from occurring, therefore an attacker could abuse this vulnerability to create new customers. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49087 | Validation of SignedInfo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49087</link><description>xml-security is a library that implements XML signatures and encryption. Validation of an XML signature requires verification that the hash value of the related XML-document matches a specific DigestValue-value, but also that the cryptographic signature on the SignedInfo-tree (the one that contains the DigestValue) verifies and matches a trusted public key. If an attacker somehow (i.e. by exploiting a bug in PHP's canonicalization function) manages to manipulate the canonicalized version's DigestValue, it would be possible to forge the signature. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.12 and 5.0.0-alpha.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47418 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in o2oa version 8.1.2 and before, allows attackers to create a new interface in the service manage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47418</link><description>Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in o2oa version 8.1.2 and before, allows attackers to create a new interface in the service management function to execute JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49094 | Symbolicator Server Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49094</link><description>Symbolicator is a symbolication service for native stacktraces and minidumps with symbol server support. An attacker could make Symbolicator send arbitrary GET HTTP requests to internal IP addresses by using a specially crafted HTTP endpoint. The response could be reflected to the attacker if they have an account on Sentry instance. The issue has been fixed in the release 23.11.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49097 | ZITADEL vulnerable account takeover via malicious host header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49097</link><description>ZITADEL is an identity infrastructure system. ZITADEL uses the notification triggering requests Forwarded or X-Forwarded-Host header to build the button link sent in emails for confirming a password reset with the emailed code. If this header is overwritten and a user clicks the link to a malicious site in the email, the secret code can be retrieved and used to reset the users password and take over his account. Accounts with MFA or Passwordless enabled can not be taken over by this attack. This issue has been patched in versions 2.41.6, 2.40.10 and 2.39.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47463 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47463</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the gl_nas_sys authentication function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47464 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47464</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the upload API function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5247 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability due to External Control of File Name or Path in multiple Mitsubishi Electric FA Engineering Software ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5247</link><description>Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability due to External Control of File Name or Path in multiple Mitsubishi Electric FA Engineering Software Products allows a malicious attacker to execute a malicious code by having legitimate users open a specially crafted project file, which could result in information disclosure, tampering and deletion, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5772 | The Debug Log Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5772</link><description>The Debug Log Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the clear_log() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear the debug log via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35137 | An improper authentication vulnerability in the authentication module of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35137</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability in the authentication module of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain system information by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35138 | A command injection vulnerability in the “show_zysync_server_contents” function of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35138</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the “show_zysync_server_contents” function of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37927 | The improper neutralization of special elements in the CGI program of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37927</link><description>The improper neutralization of special elements in the CGI program of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37928 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37928</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4473 | A command injection vulnerability in the web server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4473</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the web server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4474 | The improper neutralization of special elements in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4474</link><description>The improper neutralization of special elements in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3741 | An OS Command injection vulnerability in NEC Platforms DT900 and DT900S Series all versions allows an attacker to execute any command on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3741</link><description>An OS Command injection vulnerability in NEC Platforms DT900 and DT900S Series all versions allows an attacker to execute any command on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40458 | AceManager DOS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40458</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Sierra Wireless, Inc ALEOS could potentially allow a remote attacker to trigger a 
Denial of Service (DoS) condition for ACEManager without impairing 
other router functions. This condition is cleared by restarting the 
device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49694 | NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Privilege Escalation Via MySQL Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49694</link><description>A low-privileged OS user with access to a Windows host where NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System is installed can create arbitrary JSP files in a Tomcat web application directory. The user can then execute the JSP files under the security context of SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49693 | NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System RCE via Unprotected Access to Java Debug Wire Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49693</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System has Java Debug Wire Protocol (JDWP) listening on port 11611 and it is remotely accessible by unauthenticated users, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42536 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42536</link><description>Remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42537 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42537</link><description>Remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42538 | Elevation of privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42538</link><description>Elevation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42539 | Information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42539</link><description>Information disclosure</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42540 | Elevation of privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42540</link><description>Elevation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42541 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42541</link><description>Remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48945 | A stack overflow in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted SQL statements.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48945</link><description>A stack overflow in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted SQL statements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48946 | An issue in the box_mpy function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48946</link><description>An issue in the box_mpy function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48947 | An issue in the cha_cmp function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48947</link><description>An issue in the cha_cmp function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48948 | An issue in the box_div function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48948</link><description>An issue in the box_div function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48949 | An issue in the box_add function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48949</link><description>An issue in the box_add function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48950 | An issue in the box_col_len function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after runni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48950</link><description>An issue in the box_col_len function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48951 | An issue in the box_equal function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48951</link><description>An issue in the box_equal function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48952 | An issue in the box_deserialize_reusing function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48952</link><description>An issue in the box_deserialize_reusing function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49082 | aiohttp&amp;#x27;s ClientSession is vulnerable to CRLF injection via method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49082</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Improper validation makes it possible for an attacker to modify the HTTP request (e.g. insert a new header) or even create a new HTTP request if the attacker controls the HTTP method. The vulnerability occurs only if the attacker can control the HTTP method (GET, POST etc.) of the request. If the attacker can control the HTTP version of the request it will be able to modify the request (request smuggling). This issue has been patched in version 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44383 | October CMS stored XSS by authenticated backend user with improper configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44383</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform to assist with development workflow. A user with access to the media manager that stores SVG files could create a stored XSS attack against themselves and any other user with access to the media manager when SVG files are supported. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49091 | Jwttoken in Cosmos server never expires after password changed and logging out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49091</link><description>Cosmos provides users the ability self-host a home server by acting as a secure gateway to your application, as well as a server manager. Cosmos-server is vulnerable due to to the authorization header used for user login remaining valid and not expiring after log out. This vulnerability allows an attacker to use the token to gain unauthorized access to the application/system even after the user has logged out. This issue has been patched in version 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 19:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49079 | Misskey&amp;#x27;s missing signature validation allows arbitrary users to impersonate any remote user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49079</link><description>Misskey is an open source, decentralized social media platform. Misskey's missing signature validation allows arbitrary users to impersonate any remote user. This issue has been patched in version 2023.11.1-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49083 | cryptography vulnerable to NULL-dereference when loading PKCS7 certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49083</link><description>cryptography is a package designed to expose cryptographic primitives and recipes to Python developers. Calling `load_pem_pkcs7_certificates` or `load_der_pkcs7_certificates` could lead to a NULL-pointer dereference and segfault. Exploitation of this vulnerability poses a serious risk of Denial of Service (DoS) for any application attempting to deserialize a PKCS7 blob/certificate. The consequences extend to potential disruptions in system availability and stability. This vulnerability has been patched in version 41.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6217 | MOVEit Transfer XSS via MOVEit Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6217</link><description>In Progress MOVEit Transfer versions released before 2022.0.9 (14.0.9), 2022.1.10 (14.1.10), 2023.0.7 (15.0.7), a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified when MOVEit Gateway is used in conjunction with MOVEit Transfer.  

An attacker could craft a malicious payload targeting the system which comprises a MOVEit Gateway and MOVEit Transfer deployment.  If a MOVEit user interacts with the crafted payload, the attacker would be able to execute malicious JavaScript within the context of the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6218 | MOVEit Transfer Group Admin Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6218</link><description>In Progress MOVEit Transfer versions released before 2022.0.9 (14.0.9), 2022.1.10 (14.1.10), 2023.0.7 (15.0.7), a privilege escalation path associated with group administrators has been identified.  It is possible for a group administrator to elevate a group members permissions to the role of an organization administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48880 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48880</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Menu Name field at /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=Index&amp;a=changeTableVal&amp;_ajax=1&amp;lang=cn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48881 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48881</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Field Title field at /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=Field&amp;a=arctype_add&amp;_ajax=1&amp;lang=cn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48882 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48882</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Document Properties field at /login.php m=admin&amp;c=Index&amp;a=changeTableVal&amp;_ajax=1&amp;lang=cn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49090 | CarrierWave has a content-type allowlist bypass vulnerability, possibly leading to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49090</link><description>CarrierWave is a solution for file uploads for Rails, Sinatra and other Ruby web frameworks. CarrierWave has a Content-Type allowlist bypass vulnerability, possibly leading to XSS. The validation in `allowlisted_content_type?` determines Content-Type permissions by performing a partial match. If the `content_type` argument of `allowlisted_content_type?` is passed a value crafted by the attacker, Content-Types not included in the `content_type_allowlist` will be allowed. This issue has been patched in versions 2.2.5 and 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 14:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49652 | Incorrect permission checks in Jenkins Google Compute Engine Plugin 4.550.vb_327fca_3db_11 and earlier allow attackers with global Item/Conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49652</link><description>Incorrect permission checks in Jenkins Google Compute Engine Plugin 4.550.vb_327fca_3db_11 and earlier allow attackers with global Item/Configure permission (while lacking Item/Configure permission on any particular job) to enumerate system-scoped credentials IDs of credentials stored in Jenkins and to connect to Google Cloud Platform using attacker-specified credentials IDs obtained through another method, to obtain information about existing projects. This fix has been backported to 4.3.17.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49653 | Jenkins Jira Plugin 3.11 and earlier does not set the appropriate context for credentials lookup, allowing attackers with Item/Configure per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49653</link><description>Jenkins Jira Plugin 3.11 and earlier does not set the appropriate context for credentials lookup, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to access and capture credentials they are not entitled to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49654 | Missing permission checks in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allow attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML file from the Jenkins con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49654</link><description>Missing permission checks in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allow attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML file from the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49655 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allows attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49655</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allows attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML file from the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49656 | Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier does not configure its XML parser to prevent XML external entity (XXE) attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49656</link><description>Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier does not configure its XML parser to prevent XML external entity (XXE) attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49673 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49673</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers to connect to an attacker-specified hostname and port using attacker-specified username and password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49674 | A missing permission check in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49674</link><description>A missing permission check in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to connect to an attacker-specified hostname and port using attacker-specified username and password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40626 | [20231101] - Core - Exposure of environment variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40626</link><description>The language file parsing process could be manipulated to expose environment variables. Environment variables might contain sensible information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6345 | Integer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6345</link><description>Integer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6346 | Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6346</link><description>Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6347 | Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6347</link><description>Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6348 | Type Confusion in Spellcheck in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6348</link><description>Type Confusion in Spellcheck in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6350 | Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6350</link><description>Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted avif file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6351 | Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6351</link><description>Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted avif file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6378 | Logback &amp;quot;receiver&amp;quot; DOS vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6378</link><description>A serialization vulnerability in logback receiver component part of 
logback version 1.4.11 allows an attacker to mount a Denial-Of-Service 
attack by sending poisoned data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6070 | A server-side request forgery vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.8 allows a low privileged authenticated user to upload arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6070</link><description>A server-side request forgery vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.8 allows a low privileged authenticated user to upload arbitrary content, potentially altering configuration. This is possible through the certificate validation functionality where the API accepts uploaded content and doesn't parse for invalid data</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45479 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter in the function sub_49E09...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45479</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter in the function sub_49E098.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45480 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the src parameter in the function sub_47D878...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45480</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the src parameter in the function sub_47D878.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45481 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the firewallEn parameter in the function Set...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45481</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the firewallEn parameter in the function SetFirewallCfg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45482 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_paren...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45482</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45483 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the function compare_p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45483</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the function compare_parentcontrol_time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45484 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the function fro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45484</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the function fromSetWifiGuestBasic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46886 | Dreamer CMS before version 4.0.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. Background template management allows arbitrary modification of the t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46886</link><description>Dreamer CMS before version 4.0.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. Background template management allows arbitrary modification of the template file, allowing system sensitive files to be read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46887 | In Dreamer CMS before 4.0.1, the backend attachment management office has an Arbitrary File Download vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46887</link><description>In Dreamer CMS before 4.0.1, the backend attachment management office has an Arbitrary File Download vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47462 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 v.3.215 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file shar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47462</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 v.3.215 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file sharing function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 04:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23324 | Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials for the Administrator account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23324</link><description>Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials for the Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23325 | Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the NetHostname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23325</link><description>Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the NetHostname parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24294 | Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard v3.74 - Firmware v3.80 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component NetlinkWeb::Information::S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24294</link><description>Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard v3.74 - Firmware v3.80 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component NetlinkWeb::Information::SetDeviceIdentification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>