<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 05:30:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2332 | Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp;amp; Users &amp;lt;= 2.13 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2332</link><description>The Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.13 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'returnMetaValueAsCustomerInput' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 05:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2685 | TablePress – Tables in WordPress made easy &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2685</link><description>The TablePress – Tables in WordPress made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘table-name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 05:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0273 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is susceptible to Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0273</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch stores potentially sensitive authentication token information in log files that could be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 05:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2833 | zhangyd-c OneBlog HTTP Header redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2833</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhangyd-c OneBlog up to 2.3.9. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 04:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2835 | zhangyd-c OneBlog RestApiController.java autoLink server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2835</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhangyd-c OneBlog up to 2.3.9. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function autoLink of the file com/zyd/blog/controller/RestApiController.java. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 04:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31165 | Cross Site Scripting in NightWolf Penetration Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31165</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Logbug module of NightWolf Penetration Testing Platform 1.2.2 allows attackers to execute JavaScript through the markdown editor feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 04:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2832 | mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2832</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 up to d4836f6b49cd0ac79a4021b15ce99ff7229d4694 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2831 | mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 bookList getBookList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2831</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 up to d4836f6b49cd0ac79a4021b15ce99ff7229d4694 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function getBookList of the file /admin/bookList?page=1&amp;amp;limit=10. The manipulation of the argument condition leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45352 | Xiaomi smarthome application Webview has code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45352</link><description>An code execution vulnerability exists in the Xiaomi smarthome application product. The vulnerability is caused by improper input validation and can be exploited by attackers to execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2481 | MediaView &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2481</link><description>The MediaView plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30355 | Synapse vulnerable to federation denial of service via malformed events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30355</link><description>Synapse is an open source Matrix homeserver implementation. A malicious server can craft events which, when received, prevent Synapse version up to 1.127.0 from federating with other servers. The vulnerability has been exploited in the wild and has been fixed in Synapse v1.127.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 01:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20230 | Missing Access Control and Incorrect Ownership of Data in App Key Value Store (KVStore) collections in the Splunk Secure Gateway App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20230</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.4.1, 9.3.3, 9.2.5, and 9.1.8, and versions below 3.8.38 and 3.7.23 of the Splunk Secure Gateway app on Splunk Cloud Platform, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin“ or “power“ Splunk roles could edit and delete other user data in App Key Value Store (KVStore) collections that the Splunk Secure Gateway app created. This is due to missing access control and incorrect ownership of the data in those KVStore collections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the affected versions, the `nobody` user owned the data in the KVStore collections. This meant that there was no specific owner assigned to the data in those collections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20227 | Information Disclosure through external content warning modal dialog box bypass in Splunk Enterprise Dashboard Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20227</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.4.1, 9.3.3, 9.2.5, and 9.1.8, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.3.2408.107, 9.2.2406.112, 9.2.2403.115, 9.1.2312.208 and 9.1.2308.214, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could bypass the external content warning modal dialog box in Dashboard Studio dashboards which could lead to an information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20228 | Maintenance mode state change of App Key Value Store (KVStore) through a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20228</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.3, 9.2.5, and 9.1.8 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.108, and 9.1.2312.204, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could change the maintenance mode state of App Key Value Store (KVStore) through a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20229 | Remote Code Execution through file upload to “$SPLUNK_HOME/var/run/splunk/apptemp“ directory in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20229</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.3, 9.2.5,  and 9.1.8, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.3.2408.104, 9.2.2406.108, 9.2.2403.114, and 9.1.2312.208, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could perform a Remote Code Execution (RCE) through a file upload to the "$SPLUNK_HOME/var/run/splunk/apptemp" directory due to missing authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20232 | Risky Command Safeguards Bypass in “/app/search/search“ endpoint through “s“ parameter in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20232</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.3, 9.2.5, and 9.1.8 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.3.2408.103, 9.2.2406.108, 9.2.2403.113, 9.1.2312.208 and 9.1.2308.212, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin“ or “power“ Splunk roles could run a saved search with a risky command using the permissions of a higher-privileged user to bypass the SPL safeguards for risky commands on the “/app/search/search“ endpoint through its “s“ parameter. &lt;br /&gt;The vulnerability requires the attacker to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser. The authenticated user should not be able to exploit the vulnerability at will.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20233 | Incorrect permissions set by the “chmod“ and “makedirs“ Python functions in Splunk App for Lookup File Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20233</link><description>In the Splunk App for Lookup File Editing versions below 4.0.5, a script in the app used the `chmod` and `makedirs` Python functions in a way that resulted in overly broad read and execute permissions. This could lead to improper access control for a low-privileged user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20226 | Risky command safeguards bypass in “/services/streams/search“ endpoint through “q“ parameter in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20226</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.4.1, 9.3.3, 9.2.5, and 9.1.8 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.3.2408.107, 9.2.2406.111, and 9.1.2308.214, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could run a saved search with a risky command using the permissions of a higher-privileged user to bypass the SPL safeguards for risky commands on the "/services/streams/search" endpoint through its "q" parameter. The vulnerability requires the attacker to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser. The authenticated user should not be able to exploit the vulnerability at will.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20231 | Sensitive Information Disclosure in Splunk Secure Gateway App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20231</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.4.1, 9.3.3, 9.2.5, and 9.1.8, and versions below 3.8.38 and 3.7.23 of the Splunk Secure Gateway app on Splunk Cloud Platform, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin“ or “power“ Splunk roles could run a search using the permissions of a higher-privileged user that could lead to disclosure of sensitive information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The vulnerability requires the attacker to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser. The authenticated low-privileged user should not be able to exploit the vulnerability at will.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30407 | Local privilege escalation due to a binary hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30407</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to a binary hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 39713.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2837 | Silicon Labs Gecko OS HTTP Request Handling Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2837</link><description>Silicon Labs Gecko OS HTTP Request Handling Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Silicon Labs Gecko OS. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of HTTP requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-23245.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2838 | Silicon Labs Gecko OS DNS Response Processing Infinite Loop Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2838</link><description>Silicon Labs Gecko OS DNS Response Processing Infinite Loop Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Silicon Labs Gecko OS. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of DNS responses. The issue results from a logic error that can lead to an infinite loop. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-23392.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2787 | Ingress-nginx vulnerability in KNIME Business Hub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2787</link><description>KNIME Business Hub is affected by the Ingress-nginx CVE-2025-1974 ( a.k.a IngressNightmare ) vulnerability which affects the ingress-nginx component. In the worst case a complete takeover of the Kubernetes cluster is possible. Since the affected component is only reachable from within the cluster, i.e. requires an authenticated user, the severity in the context of KNIME Business Hub is slightly lower.



Besides applying the publicly known workarounds, we strongly recommend updating to one of the following versions of KNIME Business Hub: 



  *  1.13.3 or above 






  *  1.12.4 or above 






  *  1.11.4 or above 






  *  1.10.4 or above








  *</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31160 | atop through 2.11.0 allows local users to cause a denial of service (e.g., assertion failure and application exit) or possibly have unspecif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31160</link><description>atop through 2.11.0 allows local users to cause a denial of service (e.g., assertion failure and application exit) or possibly have unspecified other impact by running certain types of unprivileged processes while a different user runs atop.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55965 | An issue was discovered in Appsmith before 1.51. Users invited as "App Viewer" incorrectly have access to development information of a works...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55965</link><description>An issue was discovered in Appsmith before 1.51. Users invited as "App Viewer" incorrectly have access to development information of a workspace (specifically, a list of datasources in a workspace they're a member of). This information disclosure does not expose sensitive data in the datasources, such as database passwords and API Keys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55963 | An issue was discovered in Appsmith before 1.51. A user on Appsmith that doesn't have admin permissions can trigger the restart API on Appsm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55963</link><description>An issue was discovered in Appsmith before 1.51. A user on Appsmith that doesn't have admin permissions can trigger the restart API on Appsmith, causing a server restart. This is still within the Appsmith container, and the impact is limited to Appsmith's own server only, but there is a denial of service because it can be continually restarted. This is due to incorrect access control checks, which should check for super user permissions on the incoming request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55964 | An issue was discovered in Appsmith before 1.52. An incorrectly configured PostgreSQL instance in the Appsmith image leads to remote command...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55964</link><description>An issue was discovered in Appsmith before 1.52. An incorrectly configured PostgreSQL instance in the Appsmith image leads to remote command execution inside the Appsmith Docker container. The attacker must be able to access Appsmith, login to it, create a datasource, create a query against that datasource, and execute that query.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30073 | An issue was discovered in OPC cardsystems Webapp Aufwertung 2.1.0. The reference assigned to transactions can be reused. When completing a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30073</link><description>An issue was discovered in OPC cardsystems Webapp Aufwertung 2.1.0. The reference assigned to transactions can be reused. When completing a payment, the first or all transactions with the same reference are completed, depending on timing. This can be used to transfer more money onto employee cards than is paid.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26008 | In Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4, an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability exists when requesting admin.cgi parameter with setSyncTimeHos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26008</link><description>In Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4, an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability exists when requesting admin.cgi parameter with setSyncTimeHost.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28361 | Unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability in Telesquare TLR-2005KSH v.1.1.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28361</link><description>Unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability in Telesquare TLR-2005KSH v.1.1.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the systemutil.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26011 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setUsernamePasswo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26011</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setUsernamePassword.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26006 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setAutorest.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26006</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setAutorest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26009 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an Information Disclosure vulnerability when requesting systemutilit.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26009</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an Information Disclosure vulnerability when requesting systemutilit.cgi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26010 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 allows unauthorized password modification when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setUserNamePassword.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26010</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 allows unauthorized password modification when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setUserNamePassword.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26005 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is vulnerable to unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting admin.cgi parameter with setNtp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26005</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is vulnerable to unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting admin.cgi parameter with setNtp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26007 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability in the login interface when requesting systemtil.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26007</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 has an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability in the login interface when requesting systemtil.cgi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26003 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is affected by an unauthorized command execution vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with set...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26003</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is affected by an unauthorized command execution vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setAutorest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26004 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is vulnerable to unauthorized stack buffer overflow vulnerability when requesting admin.cgi parameter with setD...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26004</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is vulnerable to unauthorized stack buffer overflow vulnerability when requesting admin.cgi parameter with setDdns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26002 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is affected by an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setSyn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26002</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is affected by an unauthorized stack overflow vulnerability when requesting the admin.cgi parameter with setSyncTimeHost.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26001 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the parameter getUserNamePassword.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26001</link><description>Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.1.4 is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the parameter getUserNamePassword.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25535 | HTTP Response Manipulation in SCRIPT CASE v.1.0.002 Build7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25535</link><description>HTTP Response Manipulation in SCRIPT CASE v.1.0.002 Build7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29322 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ScriptCase before v1.0.003 - Build 3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29322</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ScriptCase before v1.0.003 - Build 3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the "Connection Name" in the New Connection and Rename Connection pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41643 | An issue in Arris NVG443B 9.3.0h3d36 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via the cshell login component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41643</link><description>An issue in Arris NVG443B 9.3.0h3d36 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via the cshell login component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2600 | Improper authorization in the variable component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows allows an authenticated password to use th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2600</link><description>Improper authorization in the variable component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows allows an authenticated password to use the ELEVATED_PASSWORD variable even though not allowed by the "Allow password in variable policy". 





This issue affects Remote Desktop Manager versions from 2025.1.24 through 2025.1.25, and all versions up to 2024.3.29.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2528 | Improper authorization in application password policy in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows allows an authenticated user to 
use ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2528</link><description>Improper authorization in application password policy in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows allows an authenticated user to 
use a configuration different from the one mandated by the system administrators.





This issue affects Remote Desktop Manager versions from 2025.1.24 through 2025.1.25, and all versions up to 2024.3.29.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2562 | Insufficient logging in the autotyping feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows allows an authenticated user to use a stored...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2562</link><description>Insufficient logging in the autotyping feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows allows an authenticated user to use a stored password without generating a corresponding log event, via the use of the autotyping functionality.







This issue affects Remote Desktop Manager versions from 2025.1.24 through 2025.1.25, and all versions up to 2024.3.29.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30352 | Directus `search` query parameter allows enumeration of non permitted fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30352</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Starting in version 9.0.0-alpha.4 and prior to version 11.5.0, the `search` query parameter allows users with access to a collection to filter items based on fields they do not have permission to view. This allows the enumeration of unknown field contents. The searchable columns (numbers &amp; strings) are not checked against permissions when injecting the `where` clauses for applying the search query. This leads to the possibility of enumerating those un-permitted fields. Version 11.5.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30353 | Directus&amp;#x27;s webhook trigger flows can leak sensitive data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30353</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Starting in version 9.12.0 and prior to version 11.5.0, when a Flow with the "Webhook" trigger and the "Data of Last Operation" response body encounters a ValidationError thrown by a failed condition operation, the API response includes sensitive data. This includes environmental variables, sensitive API keys, user accountability information, and operational data. This issue poses a significant security risk, as any unintended exposure of this data could lead to potential misuse. Version 11.5.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2499 | Client side access control bypass in the permission component in 
Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows. An authenticated user can e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2499</link><description>Client side access control bypass in the permission component in 
Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager on Windows. An authenticated user can exploit this flaw to bypass certain permission restrictions—specifically View Password, Edit Asset, and Edit Permissions by performing specific actions. 

This issue affects Remote Desktop Manager versions from 2025.1.24 through 2025.1.25, and all versions up to 2024.3.29.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30351 | Suspended Directus user can continue to use session token to access API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30351</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Starting in version 10.10.0 and prior to version 11.5.0, a suspended user can use the token generated in session auth mode to access the API despite their status. This happens because there is a check missing in `verifySessionJWT` to verify that a user is actually still active and allowed to access the API. One can extract the session token obtained by, e.g. login in to the app while still active and then, after the user has been suspended continue to use that token until it expires. Version 11.5.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30350 | Directus&amp;#x27;s S3 assets become unavailable after a burst of HEAD requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30350</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. The `@directus/storage-driver-s3` package starting in version 9.22.0 and prior to version 12.0.1, corresponding to Directus starting in version 9.22.0 and prior to 11.5.0, is vulnerable to asset unavailability after a burst of HEAD requests. Some tools use Directus to sync content and assets, and some of those tools use the HEAD method to check the existence of files. When making many HEAD requests at once, at some point, all assets are eventually served as 403. This causes denial of assets for all policies of Directus, including Admin and Public. Version 12.0.1 of the `@directus/storage-driver-s3` package, corresponding to version 11.5.0 of Directus, fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30225 | Directus&amp;#x27;s S3 assets become unavailable after a burst of malformed transformations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30225</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. The `@directus/storage-driver-s3` package starting in version 9.22.0 and prior to version 12.0.1, corresponding to Directus starting in version 9.22.0 and prior to 11.5.0, is vulnerable to asset unavailability after a burst of malformed transformations. When making many malformed transformation requests at once, at some point, all assets are served as 403. This causes denial of assets for all policies of Directus, including Admin and Public. Version 12.0.1 of the `@directus/storage-driver-s3` package, corresponding to version 11.5.0 of Directus, fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27609 | Icinga Web 2 Vulnerable to Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27609</link><description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.11.5 and 2.12.13 allows an attacker to craft a request that, once transmitted to a victim's Icinga Web, allows to embed arbitrary Javascript into it and to act on behalf of that user. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.11.5 and 2.12.3 of Icinga Web 2. As a workaround, those who have Icinga Web 2.12.2 may enable a content security policy in the application settings. Any modern browser with a working CORS implementation also sufficiently guards against the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30164 | Icinga Web 2 has open redirect on login page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30164</link><description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.11.5 and 2.12.13 vulnerability allows an attacker to craft a URL that, once visited by an authenticated user (or one that is able to authenticate), allows to manipulate the backend to redirect the user to any location. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.11.5 and 2.12.3 of Icinga Web 2. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30217 | Frappe has possibility of SQL injection due to improper validations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30217</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.93.2 and 15.55.0, a SQL Injection vulnerability has been identified in Frappe Framework which could allow a malicious actor to access sensitive information. Versions 14.93.2 and 15.55.0 contain a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2783 | Incorrect handle provided in unspecified circumstances in Mojo in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 134.0.6998.177 allowed a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2783</link><description>Incorrect handle provided in unspecified circumstances in Mojo in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 134.0.6998.177 allowed a remote attacker to perform a sandbox escape via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2825 | CrushFTP HTTP Unauthenticated Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2825</link><description>CrushFTP versions 10.0.0 through 10.8.3 and 11.0.0 through 11.3.0 are affected by a vulnerability that may result in unauthenticated access. Remote and unauthenticated HTTP requests to CrushFTP may allow attackers to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27406 | Icinga Reporting Stored XSS leads to SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27406</link><description>Icinga Reporting is the central component for reporting related functionality in the monitoring web frontend and framework Icinga Web 2. A vulnerability present in versions 0.10.0 through 1.0.2 allows to set up a template that allows to embed arbitrary Javascript. This enables the attacker to act on behalf of the user, if the template is being previewed; and act on behalf of the headless browser, if a report using the template is printed to PDF. This issue has been resolved in version 1.0.3 of Icinga Reporting. As a workaround, review all templates and remove suspicious settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2098 | Dylib Hijacking in Fast CAD Reader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2098</link><description>Fast CAD Reader application on MacOS was found to be installed with incorrect file permissions (rwxrwxrwx). This is inconsistent with standard macOS security practices, where applications should have drwxr-xr-x permissions. Incorrect permissions allow for Dylib Hijacking. Guest account, other users and applications can exploit this vulnerability for privilege escalation. This issue affects Fast CAD Reader in possibly all versions since the vendor has not responded to our messages. The tested version was 4.1.5</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27405 | Icinga Web 2 has XSS in embedded content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27405</link><description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.11.5 and 2.12.13 allows an attacker to craft a URL that, once visited by any user, allows to embed arbitrary Javascript into Icinga Web and to act on behalf of that user. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.11.5 and 2.12.3 of Icinga Web 2. As a workaround, those who have Icinga Web 2.12.2 may enable a content security policy in the application settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26739 | WordPress newseqo theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26739</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themefunction newseqo allows Stored XSS.This issue affects newseqo: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26747 | WordPress RainbowNews theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26747</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 99colorthemes RainbowNews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects RainbowNews: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2820 | Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2820</link><description>An authenticated attacker can compromise the availability of the device via the network</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26869 | WordPress Build theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26869</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Build allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Build: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2819 | Unrestricted Fileupload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2819</link><description>There is a risk of unauthorized file uploads in GT-SoftControl and potential file overwrites due to insufficient validation in the file selection process. This could lead to data integrity issues and unauthorized access by an authenticated privileged user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26922 | WordPress AuraMart theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26922</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in techthemes AuraMart allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AuraMart: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26923 | WordPress Event post plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26923</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bastien Ho Event post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Event post: from n/a through 5.9.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26929 | WordPress Accounting for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26929</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NOUS Ouvert Utile et Simple Accounting for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accounting for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26941 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.18 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26941</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 5.0.18.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26986 | WordPress Pearl Theme &amp;lt; 3.4.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26986</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Pearl - Corporate Business allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pearl - Corporate Business: from n/a before 3.4.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27014 | WordPress Hostiko Theme &amp;lt; 30.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27014</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in designingmedia Hostiko allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Hostiko: from n/a before 30.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27015 | WordPress Hostiko Theme &amp;lt; 30.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27015</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in designingmedia Hostiko allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Hostiko: from n/a before 30.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22283 | WordPress GetSocial Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22283</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Riyaz GetSocial allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects GetSocial: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23459 | WordPress NS Simple Intro Loader plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23459</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound NS Simple Intro Loader allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects NS Simple Intro Loader: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23460 | WordPress RWS Enquiry And Lead Follow-up plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound RWS Enquiry And Lead Follow-up allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects RWS Enquiry And Lead Follow-up: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23466 | WordPress Site Editor Google Map plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23466</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpsiteeditor Site Editor Google Map allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Site Editor Google Map: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23542 | WordPress RDP Linkedin Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23542</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Robert D Payne RDP Linkedin Login allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects RDP Linkedin Login: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23543 | WordPress FOMO Pay Chinese Payment Solution plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23543</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound FOMO Pay Chinese Payment Solution allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FOMO Pay Chinese Payment Solution: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23546 | WordPress RDP inGroups+ plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23546</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound RDP inGroups+ allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects RDP inGroups+: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23612 | WordPress Pixobe Cartography plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23612</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Pixobe Cartography allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Pixobe Cartography: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23632 | WordPress CG Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rhizome Networks CG Button allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CG Button: from n/a through 1.0.5.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23633 | WordPress WP Database Audit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23633</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Database Audit allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Database Audit: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23638 | WordPress Frontend Post Submission plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Frontend Post Submission allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Frontend Post Submission: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23666 | WordPress Management-screen-droptiles plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Management-screen-droptiles allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Management-screen-droptiles: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23680 | WordPress Narnoo Operator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Narnoo Operator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Narnoo Operator: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23704 | WordPress Your Lightbox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23704</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Reuven Karasik Your Lightbox allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Your Lightbox: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23714 | WordPress AppReview plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23714</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound AppReview allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AppReview: from n/a through 0.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23728 | WordPress AuMenu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23728</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound AuMenu allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AuMenu: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23735 | WordPress Infugrator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23735</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cosmin Schiopu Infugrator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Infugrator: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23937 | WordPress LinkedIn Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23937</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound LinkedIn Lite allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects LinkedIn Lite: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23952 | WordPress Custom Field List Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23952</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ntm custom-field-list-widget allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects custom-field-list-widget: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23964 | WordPress Google Plus Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23964</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Google Plus allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Google Plus: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24690 | WordPress Formality Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24690</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Michele Giorgi Formality allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Formality: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25134 | WordPress Theme Demo Bar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Theme Demo Bar allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Demo Bar: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26536 | WordPress Another Events Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yendif Player Another Events Calendar allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Another Events Calendar: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26537 | WordPress GDPR Tools plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26537</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound GDPR Tools allows Stored XSS. This issue affects GDPR Tools: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26541 | WordPress Bitcoin / AltCoin Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26541</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeSolz Bitcoin / AltCoin Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bitcoin / AltCoin Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26542 | WordPress Zalo Live Chat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26542</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Zalo Live Chat allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Zalo Live Chat: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26544 | WordPressUTM tags + Landing page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26544</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound UTM tags tracking for Contact Form 7 allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects UTM tags tracking for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26546 | WordPress Cookies Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26546</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Cookies Pro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Cookies Pro: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26559 | WordPress Secure Invites plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Secure Invites allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Secure Invites: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26560 | WordPress WP Contact Form III Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2d - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26560</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Contact Form III allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Contact Form III: from n/a through 1.6.2d.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26564 | WordPress GNUCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26564</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kagla GNUCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects GNUCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26565 | WordPress GNUPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26565</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kagla GNUPress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects GNUPress: from n/a through 0.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26566 | WordPress In Stock Mailer for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound In Stock Mailer for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects In Stock Mailer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26573 | WordPress Rizzi Guestbook plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Rizzi Guestbook allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Rizzi Guestbook: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26575 | WordPress Display Post Meta plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5- Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kyle Maurer Display Post Meta allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Display Post Meta: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26576 | WordPress WP Simple Slideshow Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26576</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in takumin WP Simple Slideshow allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Simple Slideshow: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26579 | WordPress MicroPayments  Paid Membership plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26579</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in videowhisper MicroPayments allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MicroPayments: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26581 | WordPress Picture Gallery  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26581</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in videowhisper Picture Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Picture Gallery: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26583 | WordPress Video Share VOD plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26583</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in videowhisper Video Share VOD allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Video Share VOD: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26584 | WordPress TBTestimonials Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26584</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound TBTestimonials allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects TBTestimonials: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27267 | WordPress Random Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27267</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in srcoley Random Quotes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Random Quotes: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27404 | Icinga Web 2 DOM-based XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27404</link><description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.11.5 and 2.12.13 allows an attacker to craft a URL that, once visited by any user, allows to embed arbitrary Javascript into Icinga Web and to act on behalf of that user. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.11.5 and 2.12.3 of Icinga Web 2. As a workaround, those who have Icinga Web 2.12.2 may enable CSP in the application settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28855 | WordPress Teleport plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28855</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Teleport allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Teleport: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28858 | WordPress Arrow Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28858</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Arrow Plugins Arrow Maps allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Arrow Maps: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28865 | WordPress WP Colorful Tag Cloud plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28865</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in lionelroux WP Colorful Tag Cloud allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Colorful Tag Cloud: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28869 | WordPress NextGEN Gallery Voting plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28869</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound NextGEN Gallery Voting allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects NextGEN Gallery Voting: from n/a through 2.7.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28873 | WordPress Shuffle plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28873</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Shuffle allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Shuffle: from n/a through 0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28877 | WordPress Key4ce osTicket Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28877</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Key4ce osTicket Bridge allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Key4ce osTicket Bridge: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28880 | WordPress Blue Captcha  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28880</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Blue Captcha allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Blue Captcha: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28882 | WordPress Omnify plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28882</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Omnify, Inc. Omnify allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Omnify: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28885 | WordPress Fiverr.com Official Search Box plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28885</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Fiverr.com Official Search Box allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Fiverr.com Official Search Box: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28889 | WordPress Custom Product Stickers for Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Custom Product Stickers for Woocommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom Product Stickers for Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28890 | WordPress Lightview Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28890</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Lightview Plus allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Lightview Plus: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28893 | WordPress Visual Text Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28893</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Visual Text Editor allows Remote Code Inclusion. This issue affects Visual Text Editor: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28898 | WordPress WP Multistore Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28898</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound WP Multistore Locator allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Multistore Locator: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28899 | WordPress WP Event Ticketing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28899</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Event Ticketing allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Event Ticketing: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28903 | WordPress Driving Directions plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28903</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Driving Directions allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Driving Directions: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28911 | WordPress Gravity 2 PDF plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28911</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gravity2pdf Gravity 2 PDF allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Gravity 2 PDF: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28916 | WordPress Docpro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28916</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound Docpro allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Docpro: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28917 | WordPress Custom Smilies plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28917</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Custom Smilies allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Smilies: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28921 | WordPress SpatialMatch IDX plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28921</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound SpatialMatch IDX allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects SpatialMatch IDX: from n/a through 3.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28924 | WordPress ZenphotoPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28924</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound ZenphotoPress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ZenphotoPress: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28928 | WordPress Are you robot google recaptcha for Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sureshdsk Are you robot google recaptcha for wordpress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Are you robot google recaptcha for wordpress: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28934 | WordPress Simple Post Series plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28934</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Simple Post Series allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Simple Post Series: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28935 | WordPress Fancybox Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28935</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in puzich Fancybox Plus allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Fancybox Plus: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28939 | WordPress WP Google Calendar Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28939</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound WP Google Calendar Manager allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Google Calendar Manager: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28942 | WordPress Trust Payments Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28942</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Trust Payments Trust Payments Gateway for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Trust Payments Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30524 | WordPress Product Catalog plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30524</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in origincode Product Catalog allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Product Catalog: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24972 | Discourse may bypass user preference when adding users to chat groups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24972</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to versions `3.3.4` on the `stable` branch and `3.4.0.beta5` on the `beta` branch, in specific circumstances, users could be added to group direct messages despite disabling direct messaging in their preferences. Versions `3.3.4` and `3.4.0.beta5` contain a patch for the issue. A workaround is available. If a user disables chat in their preferences then they cannot be added to new group chats.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24808 | Discourse has race condition when adding users to a group DM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24808</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to versions `3.3.4` on the `stable` branch and `3.4.0.beta5` on the `beta` branch, someone who is about to reach the limit of users in a group DM may send requests to add new users in parallel. The requests might all go through ignoring the limit due to a race condition. The patch in versions `3.3.4` and `3.4.0.beta5` uses the `lock` step in service to wrap part of the `add_users_to_channel` service inside a distributed lock/mutex in order to avoid the race condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39163 | IBM Cognos Controller HTTP response smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39163</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.1.0 is vulnerable to a Client-Side Desync (CSD) attack where an attacker could exploit a desynchronized browser connection that could lead to further cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23203 | Icinga has rest API endpoints accessible to restricted users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23203</link><description>Icinga Director is an Icinga config deployment tool. A Security vulnerability has been found starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to 1.10.3 and 1.11.3 on several director endpoints of REST API. To reproduce this vulnerability an authenticated user with permission to access the Director is required (plus api access with regard to the api endpoints). And even though some of these Icinga Director users are restricted from accessing certain objects, are able to retrieve information related to them if their name is known. This makes it possible to change the configuration of these objects by those Icinga Director users restricted from accessing them. This results in further exploitation, data breaches and sensitive information disclosure. Affected endpoints include icingaweb2/director/service, if the host name is left out of the query; icingaweb2/directore/notification; icingaweb2/director/serviceset; and icingaweb2/director/scheduled-downtime. In addition, the endpoint `icingaweb2/director/services?host=filteredHostName` returns a status code 200 even though the services for the host is filtered. This in turn lets the restricted user know that the host `filteredHostName` exists even though the user is restricted from accessing it.  This could again result in further exploitation of this information and data breaches. Icinga Director has patches in versions 1.10.3 and 1.11.1. If upgrading is not feasible, disable the director module for the users other than admin role for the time being.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45351 | Game center application has code execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45351</link><description>A code execution vulnerability exists in the Xiaomi Game center application product. The vulnerability is caused by  improper input validation and can be exploited by attackers to execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2228 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2228</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.8 the 'register_user' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including usernames and passwords of any users who register via the Edit Login | Registration Form widget, as long as that user opens the email notification for successful registration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1911 | Product Import Export for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Limited Arbitrary File Deletion via admin_log_page Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1911</link><description>The Product Import Export for WooCommerce – Import Export Product CSV Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the admin_log_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary log files on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1912 | Product Import Export for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery via validate_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1912</link><description>The Product Import Export for WooCommerce – Import Export Product CSV Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the validate_file() Function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1913 | Product Import Export for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via form_data Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1913</link><description>The Product Import Export for WooCommerce – Import Export Product CSV Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'form_data' parameter This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13411 | Zapier for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via updated_user Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13411</link><description>The Zapier for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 via the updated_user() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13889 | WordPress Importer &amp;lt;= 0.8.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13889</link><description>The WordPress Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.3 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'maybe_unserialize' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1312 | Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1312</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'buttonTextColor’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1769 | Product Import Export for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Limited Arbitrary File Read via download_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1769</link><description>The Product Import Export for WooCommerce – Import Export Product CSV Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the download_file() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary log files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2110 | WP Compress &amp;lt;= 6.30.15 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2110</link><description>The WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp; Speed Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to missing capability checks on its on its AJAX functions in all versions up to, and including, 6.30.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to compromise the site in various ways depending on the specific function exploited - for example, by retrieving sensitive settings and configuration details, or by altering and deleting them, thereby disclosing sensitive information, disrupting the plugin’s functionality, and potentially impacting overall site performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1542 | Improper permission control in OXARI ServiceDesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1542</link><description>Improper permission control vulnerability in the OXARI ServiceDesk application could allow an attacker using a guest access or an unprivileged account to gain additional administrative permissions in the application.This issue affects OXARI ServiceDesk in versions before 2.0.324.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27551 | DBIx::Class::EncodedColumn until 0.00032 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for salting password hashes in Digest.pm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27551</link><description>DBIx::Class::EncodedColumn use the rand() function, which is not cryptographically secure to salt password hashes.

This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/DBIx/Class/EncodedColumn/Digest.pm.

This issue affects DBIx::Class::EncodedColumn until 0.00032.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27552 | DBIx::Class::EncodedColumn until 0.00032 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for salting password hashes in Crypt/Eksblowfish/Bcrypt.pm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27552</link><description>DBIx::Class::EncodedColumn use the rand() function, which is not cryptographically secure to salt password hashes.

This vulnerability is associated with program files Crypt/Eksblowfish/Bcrypt.pm.

This issue affects DBIx::Class::EncodedColumn until 0.00032.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2596 | Session logout can be overwritten by long lasting request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2596</link><description>Session logout could be overwritten in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p30, &lt;2.2.0p41, and 2.1.0p49 (EOL)</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 10:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1310 | Jobs for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.7.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1310</link><description>The Jobs for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.11 via the 'job_postings_get_file' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1437 | Advanced iFrame &amp;lt;= 2024.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1437</link><description>The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'advanced_iframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2024.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1439 | Advanced iFrame &amp;lt;= 2024.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Host Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1439</link><description>The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'advanced_iframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2024.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes through the 'src' attribute when the src supplied returns a header with an injected value . This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1440 | Advanced iFrame &amp;lt;= 2024.5 - Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1440</link><description>The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized excessive creation of options on the aip_map_url_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 2024.5 due to insufficient restrictions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the advancediFrameParameterData option with an excessive amount of unvalidated data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1703 | Ultimate Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via content Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1703</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13702 | CRM and Lead Management by vcita &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13702</link><description>The CRM and Lead Management by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vCitaMeetingScheduler' and 'vCitaSchedulingCalendar' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13801 | BWL Advanced FAQ Manager &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13801</link><description>The BWL Advanced FAQ Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'baf_set_notice_status' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to '1' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1514 | Active Products Tables for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.6.7 -  Unauthenticated Arbitrary Filter Call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1514</link><description>The Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Use constructor to create tables plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized filter calling due to insufficient restrictions on the get_smth() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call arbitrary WordPress filters with a single parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2009 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2009</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the logging functionality in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2167 | Event post &amp;lt;= 5.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2167</link><description>The Event post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'events_list' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2257 | Total Upkeep – WordPress Backup Plugin plus Restore &amp;amp; Migrate by BoldGrid &amp;lt;= 1.16.10 - Authenticated (Admin+) Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2257</link><description>The Total Upkeep – WordPress Backup Plugin plus Restore &amp; Migrate by BoldGrid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.16.10 via the compression_level setting. This is due to the plugin using the compression_level setting in proc_open() without any validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30155 | HCL SX is susceptible to cookie with Insecure, Improper, or Missing SameSite attribute vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30155</link><description>HCL SX does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may potentially be able to obtain access to the cookie values via a Cross-Site-Forgery-Request (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52972 | Huawei PCs have a vulnerability that allows low-privilege users to bypass SDDL permission checks . Successful exploitation this vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52972</link><description>Huawei PCs have a vulnerability that allows low-privilege users to bypass SDDL permission checks . Successful exploitation this vulnerability could lead to termination of some system processes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11847 | WP SVG Upload &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11847</link><description>The wp-svg-upload WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which enables users with at least the author role to SVG with malicious JavaScript to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12683 | Smart Maintenance Mode &amp;lt; 1.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12683</link><description>The Smart Maintenance Mode WordPress plugin before 1.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13146 | Booknetic &amp;lt; 4.1.5 - Staff Creation via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13146</link><description>The Booknetic WordPress plugin before 4.1.5 does not have CSRF check when creating Staff accounts, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add arbitrary Staff members via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1784 | Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.19.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1784</link><description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the uagb block in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 05:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30742 | httpd.c in atophttpd 2.8.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant out-of-bounds read because a certain 1024-character req string would not ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30742</link><description>httpd.c in atophttpd 2.8.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant out-of-bounds read because a certain 1024-character req string would not have a final '\0' character.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1490 | Smart Maintenance Mode &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via setstatus Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1490</link><description>The Smart Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘setstatus’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2165 | SH Email Alert &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2165</link><description>The SH Email Alert plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2573 | Amazing service box Addons For WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2573</link><description>The Amazing service box Addons For WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2576 | Ayyash Studio &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2576</link><description>The Ayyash Studio — The kick-start kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47516 | Pagure: argument injection in pagurerepo.log()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47516</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pagure. An argument injection in Git during retrieval of the repository history leads to remote code execution on the Pagure instance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2276 | Ultimate Dashboard &amp;lt;= 3.8.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Modules Activation/Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2276</link><description>The Ultimate Dashboard – Custom WordPress Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_module_actions function in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate/deactivate plugin modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2302 | Advanced Woo Search &amp;lt;= 3.28 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via aws_search_terms Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2302</link><description>The Advanced Woo Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aws_search_terms shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30222 | Shescape has potential environment variable exposure on Windows with CMD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30222</link><description>Shescape is a simple shell escape library for JavaScript. Versions 1.7.2 through 2.1.1 are vulnerable to potential environment variable exposure on Windows with CMD. This impact users of Shescape on Windows that explicitly configure `shell: 'cmd.exe'` or `shell: true` using any of `quote`/`quoteAll`/`escape`/`escapeAll`. An attacker may be able to get read-only access to environment variables. This bug has been patched in v2.1.2. For those who are already using v2 of Shescape, no further changes are required. Those who are are using v1 of Shescape should follow the migration guide to upgrade to v2. There is no plan to release a patch compatible with v1 of Shescape. As a workaround, users can remove all instances of `%` from user input before using Shescape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30219 | RabbitMQ has XSS Vulnerability in an Error Message in Management UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30219</link><description>RabbitMQ is a messaging and streaming broker. Versions prior to 4.0.3 are vulnerable to a sophisticated attack that could modify virtual host name on disk and then make it unrecoverable (with other on disk file modifications) can lead to arbitrary JavaScript code execution in the browsers of management UI users. When a virtual host on a RabbitMQ node fails to start, recent versions
will display an error message (a notification) in the management UI. The error message includes virtual host name, which was not escaped prior to open source RabbitMQ 4.0.3 and Tanzu RabbitMQ 4.0.3, 3.13.8. An attack that both makes a virtual host fail to start and creates a new virtual host name with an XSS code snippet or changes the name of an existing virtual host on disk could trigger arbitrary JavaScript code execution in the management UI (the user's browser). Open source RabbitMQ `4.0.3` and Tanzu RabbitMQ `4.0.3` and `3.13.8` patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27837 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. Access to arbitrary files can occur through a truncated path with invalid UTF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27837</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. Access to arbitrary files can occur through a truncated path with invalid UTF-8 characters, for base/gp_mswin.c and base/winrtsup.cpp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30741 | pixelfed before 0.12.5 allows anyone to follow private accounts on other Fediverse servers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30741</link><description>pixelfed before 0.12.5 allows anyone to follow private accounts on other Fediverse servers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27830 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs during serialization of DollarBlend in a font, for b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27830</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs during serialization of DollarBlend in a font, for base/write_t1.c and psi/zfapi.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27831 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The DOCXWRITE TXTWRITE device has a text buffer overflow via long characters ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27831</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The DOCXWRITE TXTWRITE device has a text buffer overflow via long characters to devices/vector/doc_common.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27832 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The NPDL device has a Compression buffer overflow for contrib/japanese/gdevnp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27832</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The NPDL device has a Compression buffer overflow for contrib/japanese/gdevnpdl.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27833 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs for a long TTF font name to pdf/pdf_fmap.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27833</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs for a long TTF font name to pdf/pdf_fmap.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27835 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs when converting glyphs to Unicode in psi/zbfont.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27835</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs when converting glyphs to Unicode in psi/zbfont.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27836 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The BJ10V device has a Print buffer overflow in contrib/japanese/gdev10v.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27836</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The BJ10V device has a Print buffer overflow in contrib/japanese/gdev10v.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29789 | OpenEMR Has Directory Traversal in Load Code feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29789</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions prior to 7.3.0 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal in the Load Code feature. Version 7.3.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55028 | A template injection vulnerability in the Dashboard of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55028</link><description>A template injection vulnerability in the Dashboard of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted Vue file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55029 | NASA Fprime v3.4.3 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55029</link><description>NASA Fprime v3.4.3 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55030 | A command injection vulnerability in the Command Dispatcher Service of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55030</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the Command Dispatcher Service of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25371 | NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to path traversal in the OSAL module, allowing the override of any arbitrary file on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25371</link><description>NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to path traversal in the OSAL module, allowing the override of any arbitrary file on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25372 | NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to segmentation fault via sending a malicious telecommand to the Memory Management Module...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25372</link><description>NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to segmentation fault via sending a malicious telecommand to the Memory Management Module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25373 | The Memory Management Module of NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila has insecure permissions, which can be exploited to gain an RCE on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25373</link><description>The Memory Management Module of NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila has insecure permissions, which can be exploited to gain an RCE on the platform.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25374 | In NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila, it is possible to put the onboard software in a state that will prevent the launch of any external ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25374</link><description>In NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila, it is possible to put the onboard software in a state that will prevent the launch of any external application, causing a platform denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27834 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs via an oversized Type 4 function in a PDF document t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27834</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs via an oversized Type 4 function in a PDF document to pdf/pdf_func.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48818 | An issue in IIT Bombay, Mumbai, India Bodhitree of cs101 version allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48818</link><description>An issue in IIT Bombay, Mumbai, India Bodhitree of cs101 version allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30118 | An issue was discovered on the Audi Universal Traffic Recorder 2.88. It has Susceptibility to denial of service. It uses the same default cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30118</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Audi Universal Traffic Recorder 2.88. It has Susceptibility to denial of service. It uses the same default credentials for all devices and does not implement proper multi-device authentication, allowing attackers to deny the owner access by occupying the only available connection. The SSID remains broadcast at all times, increasing exposure to potential attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30216 | CryptoLib Has Heap Overflow in Crypto_TM_ProcessSecurity due to Unchecked Secondary Header Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30216</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. In versions 1.3.3 and prior, a Heap Overflow vulnerability occurs in the `Crypto_TM_ProcessSecurity` function (`crypto_tm.c:1735:8`). When processing the Secondary Header Length of a TM protocol packet, if the Secondary Header Length exceeds the packet's total length, a heap overflow is triggered during the memcpy operation that copies packet data into the dynamically allocated buffer `p_new_dec_frame`. This allows an attacker to overwrite adjacent heap memory, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution or system instability. A patch is available at commit 810fd66d592c883125272fef123c3240db2f170f.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 19:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31896 | IBM SPSS Statistics information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31896</link><description>IBM SPSS Statistics 26.0, 27.0.1, 28.0.1, and 29.0.2 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28904 | WordPress Web Directory Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28904</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Shamalli Web Directory Free allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Web Directory Free: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30567 | WordPress WP01 &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30567</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wp01ru WP01 allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WP01: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2312 | cifs.upcall  makes an upcall to the wrong namespace in containerized environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2312</link><description>A flaw was found in cifs-utils. When trying to obtain Kerberos credentials, the cifs.upcall program from the cifs-utils package makes an upcall to the wrong namespace in containerized environments. This issue may lead to disclosing sensitive data from the host's Kerberos credentials cache.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58104 | A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58104</link><description>A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing security and execute arbitrary code on affected installations. 

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58105 | A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58105</link><description>A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing security and execute arbitrary code on affected installations. 

This CVE address an addtional bypass not covered in CVE-2024-58104.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30214 | Frappe vulnerable to information disclosure leading to account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30214</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0, making crafted requests could lead to information disclosure that could further lead to account takeover. Versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0 fix the issue. There's no workaround to fix this without upgrading.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30213 | Frappe has Possibility of Remote Code Execution due to improper validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30213</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.91.0 and 15.52.0, a system user was able to create certain documents in a specific way that could lead to remote code execution. Versions 14.9.1 and 15.52.0 contain a patch for the vulnerability. There's no workaround; an upgrade is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26742 | WordPress Gallery for Social Photo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0.35 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Gallery for Social Photo allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gallery for Social Photo: from n/a through 1.0.0.35.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27147 | GLPI Inventory plugin has Improper Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27147</link><description>The GLPI Inventory Plugin handles various types of tasks for GLPI agents, including network discovery and inventory (SNMP), software deployment, VMWare ESX host remote inventory, and data collection (files, Windows registry, WMI). Versions prior to 1.5.0 have an improper access control vulnerability. Version 1.5.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30212 | Frappe has possibility of SQL injection due to improper validations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30212</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. An SQL Injection vulnerability has been identified in Frappe Framework prior to versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0 which could allow a malicious actor to access sensitive information. Versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0 fix the issue. Upgrading is required; no other workaround is present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55604 | Appsmith&amp;#x27;s Broken Access Control Allows Viewer Role User to Query Datasources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55604</link><description>Appsmith is a platform to build admin panels, internal tools, and dashboards. Users invited as "App Viewer" should not have access to development information of a workspace. Datasources are such a component in a workspace. Yet, in versions of Appsmith prior to 1.51, app viewers are able to get a list of datasources in a workspace they're a member of. This information disclosure does NOT expose sensitive data in the datasources, such as database passwords and API Keys. The attacker needs to have been invited to a workspace as a "viewer", by someone in that workspace with access to invite. The attacker then needs to be able to signup/login to that Appsmith instance. The issue is patched in version 1.51. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2530 | Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Access of Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2530</link><description>Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Access of Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of dae files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23698.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2531 | Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2531</link><description>Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of dae files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23704.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2532 | Luxion KeyShot USDC File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2532</link><description>Luxion KeyShot USDC File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of usdc files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42533 | SQL injection vulnerability in the authentication module in Convivance StandVoice 4.5 through 6.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42533</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the authentication module in Convivance StandVoice 4.5 through 6.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the GEST_LOGIN parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22230 | Authentication bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22230</link><description>VMware Tools for Windows contains an authentication bypass vulnerability due to improper access control. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges on a guest VM may gain ability to perform certain high privilege operations within that VM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30091 | In Tiny MoxieManager PHP before 4.0.0, remote code execution can occur in the installer command. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30091</link><description>In Tiny MoxieManager PHP before 4.0.0, remote code execution can occur in the installer command. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary code. Attacker-controlled data to InstallCommand can be inserted into config.php, and InstallCommand is available after an installation has completed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29635 | A command injection vulnerability in D-Link DIR-823X 240126 and 240802 allows an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary commands on remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29635</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in D-Link DIR-823X 240126 and 240802 allows an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary commands on remote devices by sending a POST request to /goform/set_prohibiting via the corresponding function, triggering remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11499 | A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-4-104 controlled station functionality, that allows an authenticated and authorized attacker to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11499</link><description>A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-4-104 controlled station functionality, that allows an authenticated and authorized attacker to perform a CMU restart. The vulnerability can be triggered if certificates are updated while in use on active connections.

The affected CMU will automatically recover itself if an attacker successfully exploits this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12169 | A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-5-104 controlled station functionality and IEC 61850 functionality, that allows an attacker perfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12169</link><description>A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-5-104 controlled station functionality and IEC 61850 functionality, that allows an attacker performing a specific attack sequence to restart the affected CMU. This vulnerability only applies, if secure communication using IEC 62351-3 (TLS) is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1445 | A vulnerability exists in RTU IEC 61850 client and server functionality that could impact the availability if renegotiation of an open IEC61...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1445</link><description>A vulnerability exists in RTU IEC 61850 client and server functionality that could impact the availability if renegotiation of an open IEC61850 TLS connection takes place in specific timing situations, when IEC61850 communication is active.

Precondition is that IEC61850 as client or server are configured using TLS on RTU500 device. It affects the CMU the IEC61850 stack is configured on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27631 | The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to LDAP injection attack potentially allowing an attacker to inject code into a query and execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27631</link><description>The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to LDAP injection attack potentially allowing an attacker to inject code into a query and execute remote commands that can read and update data on the website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27632 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability in TRMTracker application may allow an attacker by modifying the host header value in an HTTP request ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27632</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability in TRMTracker application may allow an attacker by modifying the host header value in an HTTP request to leverage multiple attack vectors, including defacing the site content through web-cache poisoning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27633 | The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to reflected Cross-site scripting attack. The application allows client-side code injection tha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27633</link><description>The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to reflected Cross-site scripting attack. The application allows client-side code injection that might be used to compromise the confidentiality and integrity of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29932 | In JetBrains GoLand before 2025.1 an XXE during debugging was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29932</link><description>In JetBrains GoLand before 2025.1 an XXE during debugging was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-1804 | Accountsservice incorrectly drops privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1804</link><description>accountsservice no longer drops permissions when writting .pam_environment</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10037 | A vulnerability exists in the RTU500 web server component that can cause a denial of service to the RTU500 CMU application if a specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10037</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the RTU500 web server component that can cause a denial of service to the RTU500 CMU application if a specially crafted message sequence is executed on a WebSocket connection.
An attacker must be properly authenticated and the test mode function of RTU500 must be enabled to exploit this vulnerability.

The affected CMU will automatically recover itself if an attacker successfully exploits this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2109 | WP Compress &amp;lt;= 6.30.15 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery via init Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2109</link><description>The WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp; Speed Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.30.15 via the init() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53678 | Apache VCL: SQL injection vulnerability in New Block Allocation form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache VCL. Users can modify form data submitted when requesting a new Block Allocation such that a SELECT SQL statement is modified. The data returned by the SELECT statement is not viewable by the attacker.

This issue affects all versions of Apache VCL from 2.2 through 2.5.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.5.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53679 | Apache VCL: XSS vulnerability in User Lookup impacting user privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache VCL in the User Lookup form. A user with sufficient rights to be able to view this part of the site can craft a URL or be tricked in to clicking a URL that will give a specified user elevated rights.



This issue affects all versions of Apache VCL through 2.5.1.



Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.5.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2756 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp AC3D File ACLoader.cpp ConvertObjectSection heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2756</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This affects the function Assimp::AC3DImporter::ConvertObjectSection of the file code/AssetLib/AC/ACLoader.cpp of the component AC3D File Handler. The manipulation of the argument tmp leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2757 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp MD5 File MD5Parser.cpp AI_MD5_PARSE_STRING_IN_QUOTATION heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2757</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This vulnerability affects the function AI_MD5_PARSE_STRING_IN_QUOTATION of the file code/AssetLib/MD5/MD5Parser.cpp of the component MD5 File Handler. The manipulation of the argument data leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2542 | Your Simple SVG Support &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2542</link><description>The Your Simple SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2635 | Digital License Manager &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via remove_query_arg Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2635</link><description>The Digital License Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg() function without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2755 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp AC3D File ACLoader.cpp ConvertObjectSection out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2755</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function Assimp::AC3DImporter::ConvertObjectSection of the file code/AssetLib/AC/ACLoader.cpp of the component AC3D File Handler. The manipulation of the argument src.entries leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2753 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp LWS File LWSLoader.cpp MergeScenes out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function SceneCombiner::MergeScenes of the file code/AssetLib/LWS/LWSLoader.cpp of the component LWS File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2754 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp AC3D File ACLoader.cpp ConvertObjectSection heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2754</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Assimp::AC3DImporter::ConvertObjectSection of the file code/AssetLib/AC/ACLoader.cpp of the component AC3D File Handler. The manipulation of the argument it leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13690 | WP Church Donation &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13690</link><description>The WP Church Donation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several donation form submission parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13710 | Estatebud – Properties &amp;amp; Listings &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13710</link><description>The Estatebud – Properties &amp; Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'estatebud_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13731 | Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Alert Box Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13731</link><description>The Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Alert Box block in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2319 | EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup 4.11.13 - 5.25.08 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2319</link><description>The EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions 4.11.13 to 5.25.08. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ELISQLREPORTS_menu' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Version 5.25.10 adds a nonce check, which makes this vulnerability exploitable by admins only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2510 | Frndzk Expandable Bottom Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2510</link><description>The Frndzk Expandable Bottom Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'text' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2559 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: jwt token cache exhaustion leading to denial of service (dos) in keycloak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2559</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. When the configuration uses JWT tokens for authentication, the tokens are cached until expiration. If a client uses JWT tokens with an excessively long expiration time, for example, 24 or 48 hours, the cache can grow indefinitely, leading to an OutOfMemoryError. This issue could result in a denial of service condition, preventing legitimate users from accessing the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2752 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSM File fast_atof.h fast_atoreal_move out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2752</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function fast_atoreal_move in the library include/assimp/fast_atof.h of the component CSM File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2750 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSM File CSMLoader.cpp InternReadFile out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2750</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This affects the function Assimp::CSMImporter::InternReadFile of the file code/AssetLib/CSM/CSMLoader.cpp of the component CSM File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds write. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2751 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSM File CSMLoader.cpp InternReadFile out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2751</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function Assimp::CSMImporter::InternReadFile of the file code/AssetLib/CSM/CSMLoader.cpp of the component CSM File Handler. The manipulation of the argument na leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12623 | DICOM Support &amp;lt;= 0.10.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12623</link><description>The DICOM Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'dcm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.10.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1320 | teachPress &amp;lt;= 9.0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Import Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1320</link><description>The teachPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the import.php page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete imports via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2252 | Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy &amp;lt;= 3.3.6.1 - Unauthenticated Private Post Title Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2252</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.6.1 via the edd_ajax_get_download_title() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract private post titles of downloads. The impact here is minimal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2743 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Material Upload Interface upload-temporary path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2743</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin-api/mp/material/upload-temporary of the component Material Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2744 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Material Upload Interface upload-news-image path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2744</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-api/mp/material/upload-news-image of the component Material Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2740 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System eligibility.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2740</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/eligibility.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2742 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Material Upload Interface upload-permanent path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2742</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin-api/mp/material/upload-permanent of the component Material Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10105 | Jobs for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.7.11 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10105</link><description>The Job Postings WordPress plugin before 2.7.11 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10472 | Stylish Price List  &amp;lt; 7.1.12 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10472</link><description>The Stylish Price List  WordPress plugin before 7.1.12 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10554 | WP-Advanced-Search &amp;lt; 3.3.9.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10554</link><description>The WordPress WP-Advanced-Search WordPress plugin before 3.3.9.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10560 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.30 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10560</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.30 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10565 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.62 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10565</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.62 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10566 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.62 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10566</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.62 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10638 | Product Labels For Woocommerce &amp;lt; 1.5.11 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10638</link><description>The Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) WordPress plugin before 1.5.11 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10679 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt; 9.2.1 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10679</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10703 | Registrations for The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 2.13.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10703</link><description>The Registrations for the Events Calendar  WordPress plugin before 2.13.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11272 | Contact Form &amp;amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms &amp;lt; 2.6.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11272</link><description>The Contact Form &amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms WordPress plugin before 2.6.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11273 | Contact Form &amp;amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms &amp;lt; 2.6.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11273</link><description>The Contact Form &amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms WordPress plugin before 2.6.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11503 | WP Tabs &amp;lt; 2.2.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11503</link><description>The WP Tabs  WordPress plugin before 2.2.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12109 | Product Labels For Woocommerce &amp;lt; 1.5.9 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12109</link><description>The Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) WordPress plugin before 1.5.9 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12682 | Smart Maintenance Mode &amp;lt; 1.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12682</link><description>The Smart Maintenance Mode WordPress plugin before 1.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12769 | Simple Banner &amp;lt; 3.0.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12769</link><description>The Simple Banner  WordPress plugin before 3.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13118 | IP Based Login &amp;lt; 2.4.1 - Log Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13118</link><description>The IP Based Login WordPress plugin before 2.4.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users delete all logs via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13122 | AFI &amp;lt; 1.100.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13122</link><description>The AFI  WordPress plugin before 1.100.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13123 | AFI &amp;lt; 1.100.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13123</link><description>The AFI  WordPress plugin before 1.100.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13617 | Downloable by American Osteopathic Association &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13617</link><description>The aoa-downloadable WordPress plugin through 0.1.0 doesn't validate a parameter in its download function, allowing unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary files from the server</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13618 | Downloable by American Osteopathic Association &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Unauthenticated SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13618</link><description>The aoa-downloadable WordPress plugin through 0.1.0 lacks authorization and authentication for requests to its download.php endpoint, allowing unauthenticated visitors to make requests to arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13863 | Stylish Google Sheet Reader &amp;lt; 4.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13863</link><description>The Stylish Google Sheet Reader 4.0  WordPress plugin before 4.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9770 | WP-Recall &amp;lt; 16.26.12 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9770</link><description>The WP-Recall  WordPress plugin before 16.26.12 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0717 | Social Slider Feed &amp;lt; 2.2.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0717</link><description>To exploit the vulnerability, it is necessary:</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1452 | Favorites  &amp;lt; 2.3.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1452</link><description>The Favorites WordPress plugin before 2.3.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1798 | Design Comuni Italia &amp;lt; 1.1.2 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1798</link><description>The  does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputting them back in a page, allowing unauthenticated users the ability to perform stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2738 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System manage-scdetails.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2738</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/manage-scdetails.php. The manipulation of the argument namesc leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2739 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System manage-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2739</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sertitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44903 | SQL Injection can occur in the SirsiDynix Horizon Information Portal (IPAC20): through 3.25_9382. This is in ipac.jsp in a SELECT WHERE stat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44903</link><description>SQL Injection can occur in the SirsiDynix Horizon Information Portal (IPAC20): through 3.25_9382. This is in ipac.jsp in a SELECT WHERE statement, in a part of the uri= variable in the second part of the full= inner variable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27810 | Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, in some cases of failed memory allocation or hardware errors, uses uninitialized stack memory ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27810</link><description>Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, in some cases of failed memory allocation or hardware errors, uses uninitialized stack memory to compose the TLS Finished message, potentially leading to authentication bypasses such as replays.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10210 | Path traversal in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10210</link><description>An External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-005P may allow an authenticated network-based attacker to access data from the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27809 | Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, on the client side, accepts servers that have trusted certificates for arbitrary hostnames unl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27809</link><description>Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, on the client side, accepts servers that have trusted certificates for arbitrary hostnames unless the TLS client application calls mbedtls_ssl_set_hostname.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2737 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2737</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0845 | DesignThemes Core Features &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0845</link><description>The DesignThemes Core Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2224 | Directorist &amp;lt;= 8.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Publishing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2224</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access  and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'parse_query' function in all versions up to, and including, 8.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the post_status of any post to 'publish'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2735 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System add-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2735</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sertitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2736 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System bwdates-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bwdates-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45481 | Improper authentication in SSH of B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45481</link><description>An Incomplete Filtering of Special Elements vulnerability in scripts using the SSH server on B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated local attacker to authenticate as another legitimate user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45482 | Privilege escalation in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45482</link><description>An Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere vulnerability in the SSH server on B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P1 may allow an authenticated local attacker from a trusted remote server to execute malicious commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45483 | Missing GRUB password in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45483</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in the GRUB configuration used B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-01 may allow an unauthenticated physical attacker to alter the boot configuration of the operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45484 | Enabled ICMP redirection in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45484</link><description>An Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in the operating system network configuration used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to per-form Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks against the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10208 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10208</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated network-based attacker to insert malicious code which is then executed in the context of the user’s browser session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10209 | Incorrect Permission Assignment in APROL file system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10209</link><description>An Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in the file system used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-01 may allow an authenticated local attacker to read and alter the configuration of another engineering or runtime user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45480 | Unauthorized local file reading in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45480</link><description>An improper control of generation of code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in the AprolCreateReport component of B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated network-based attacker to read files from the local system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10207 | Server-Side Request Forgery (authenticated) in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10207</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated network-based attacker to force the web server to request arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10206 | Server-Side Request Forgery (unauthenticated) in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10206</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated network-based attacker to force the web server to request arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8313 | Default or Guessable SNMP community names in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8313</link><description>An Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere and Initialization of a Resource with an Insecure Default vulnerability in the SNMP component of B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated adjacent-based attacker to read and alter configuration using SNMP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8314 | Improper session handling in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8314</link><description>An Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm and Exposure of Data Element to Wrong Ses-sion vulnerability in the session handling used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated network attacker to take over a currently active user session without login credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8315 | Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8315</link><description>An Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerability in scripts used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated local attacker to read credential information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2733 | mannaandpoem OpenManus Prompt python_execute.py os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2733</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in mannaandpoem OpenManus up to 2025.3.13. This affects an unknown part of the file app/tool/python_execute.py of the component Prompt Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2734 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2734</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2732 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getWifiNeighbour command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2732</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/wizard/getWifiNeighbour of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2731 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getDualbandSync command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2731</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/wizard/getDualbandSync of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 03:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2729 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request networkSetup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2729</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/wizard/networkSetup of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 03:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2730 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getssidname command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/wizard/getssidname of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 03:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2727 | H3C Magic NX30 Pro HTTP POST Request getNetworkStatus command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2727</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in H3C Magic NX30 Pro up to V100R007. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/wizard/getNetworkStatus of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2728 | H3C Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400 getNetworkConf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2728</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in H3C Magic NX30 Pro and Magic NX400 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/wizard/getNetworkConf. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2725 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request auth command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2725</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/login/auth of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2726 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request esps command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2726</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/esps of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2724 | GNOME libgsf sorting_key_copy out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2724</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. Affected is the function sorting_key_copy. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2723 | GNOME libgsf gsf_property_settings_collec heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2723</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function gsf_property_settings_collec. The manipulation of the argument n_alloced_params leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2722 | GNOME libgsf gsf_prop_settings_collect_va heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2722</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function gsf_prop_settings_collect_va. The manipulation of the argument n_alloced_params leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2721 | GNOME libgsf gsf_base64_encode_simple heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2721</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function gsf_base64_encode_simple. The manipulation of the argument size_t leads to heap-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>