<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-38465 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows username enumeration because of the response discrepancy of incorrect versus erro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38465</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows username enumeration because of the response discrepancy of incorrect versus error.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38466 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 has a 123456Qw default password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38466</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 has a 123456Qw default password.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38467 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized user information retrieval via the queryUser API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38467</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized user information retrieval via the queryUser API.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38468 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized password resets via the resetPassword API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38468</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized password resets via the resetPassword API.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38461 | irodsServerMonPerf in iRODS before 4.3.2 attempts to proceed with use of a path even if it is not a directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38461</link><description>irodsServerMonPerf in iRODS before 4.3.2 attempts to proceed with use of a path even if it is not a directory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38462 | iRODS before 4.3.2 provides an msiSendMail function with a problematic dependency on the mail binary, such as in the mailMS.cpp#L94-L106 ref...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38462</link><description>iRODS before 4.3.2 provides an msiSendMail function with a problematic dependency on the mail binary, such as in the mailMS.cpp#L94-L106 reference.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38459 | langchain_experimental (aka LangChain Experimental) before 0.0.61 for LangChain provides Python REPL access without an opt-in step. NOTE; th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38459</link><description>langchain_experimental (aka LangChain Experimental) before 0.0.61 for LangChain provides Python REPL access without an opt-in step. NOTE; this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-27444.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38460 | In SonarQube before 10.4 and 9.9.4 LTA, encrypted values generated using the Settings Encryption feature are potentially exposed in cleartex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38460</link><description>In SonarQube before 10.4 and 9.9.4 LTA, encrypted values generated using the Settings Encryption feature are potentially exposed in cleartext as part of the URL parameters in the logs (such as SonarQube Access Logs, Proxy Logs, etc).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38457 | Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows CSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38457</link><description>Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows CSRF.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38458 | Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows code injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38458</link><description>Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows code injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38454 | ExpressionEngine before 7.4.11 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38454</link><description>ExpressionEngine before 7.4.11 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38448 | htags in GNU Global through 6.6.12 allows code execution in situations where dbpath (aka -d) is untrusted, because shell metacharacters may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38448</link><description>htags in GNU Global through 6.6.12 allows code execution in situations where dbpath (aka -d) is untrusted, because shell metacharacters may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38443 | C/sorting/binary_insertion_sort.c in The Algorithms - C through e5dad3f has a segmentation fault for deep recursion, which may affect common...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38443</link><description>C/sorting/binary_insertion_sort.c in The Algorithms - C through e5dad3f has a segmentation fault for deep recursion, which may affect common use cases such as sorting an array of 50 elements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38439 | Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[PASSWDLEN] to '\0' in FPLoginExt in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38439</link><description>Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[PASSWDLEN] to '\0' in FPLoginExt in login in etc/uams/uams_pam.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38440 | Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of incorrectly using FPLoginExt in BN_bin2bn in etc/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38440</link><description>Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of incorrectly using FPLoginExt in BN_bin2bn in etc/uams/uams_dhx_pam.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38441 | Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[len] to '\0' in FPMapName in afp_map...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38441</link><description>Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[len] to '\0' in FPMapName in afp_mapname in etc/afp/directory.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36397 | Vantiva - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36397</link><description>Vantiva - MediaAccess DGA2232 v19.4 - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 08:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38428 | url.c in GNU Wget through 1.24.5 mishandles semicolons in the userinfo subcomponent of a URI, and thus there may be insecure behavior in whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38428</link><description>url.c in GNU Wget through 1.24.5 mishandles semicolons in the userinfo subcomponent of a URI, and thus there may be insecure behavior in which data that was supposed to be in the userinfo subcomponent is misinterpreted to be part of the host subcomponent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 02:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38427 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX before 85ce74e, a logic flaw in CIccTagXmlProfileSequenceId::ParseXml in IccXML/IccLibXML/IccTa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38427</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX before 85ce74e, a logic flaw in CIccTagXmlProfileSequenceId::ParseXml in IccXML/IccLibXML/IccTagXml.cpp results in unconditionally returning false.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38395 | In iTerm2 before 3.5.2, the "Terminal may report window title" setting is not honored, and thus remote code execution might occur but "is no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38395</link><description>In iTerm2 before 3.5.2, the "Terminal may report window title" setting is not honored, and thus remote code execution might occur but "is not trivially exploitable."</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38394 | Mismatches in interpreting USB authorization policy between GNOME Settings Daemon (GSD) through 46.0 and the Linux kernel's underlying devic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38394</link><description>Mismatches in interpreting USB authorization policy between GNOME Settings Daemon (GSD) through 46.0 and the Linux kernel's underlying device matching logic allow a physically proximate attacker to access some unintended Linux kernel USB functionality, such as USB device-specific kernel modules and filesystem implementations. NOTE: the GSD supplier indicates that consideration of a mitigation for this within GSD would be in the context of "a new feature, not a CVE."</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6016 | itsourcecode Online Laundry Management System admin_class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6016</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Online Laundry Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268724.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6015 | itsourcecode Online House Rental System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6015</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Online House Rental System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument month_of leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268723.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 17:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6014 | itsourcecode Document Management System edithis.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6014</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file edithis.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268722 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6013 | itsourcecode Online Book Store admin_delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6013</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Book Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin_delete.php. The manipulation of the argument bookisbn leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268721 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6009 | itsourcecode Event Calendar process.php regDelete sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6009</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Event Calendar 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function regConfirm/regDelete of the file process.php. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268699.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6008 | itsourcecode Online Book Store edit_book.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6008</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Online Book Store up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit_book.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27275 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27275</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability caused by an insufficient authority requirement. A local user without administrator privilege can configure a physical file trigger to execute with the privileges of a user socially engineered to access the target file. The correction is to require administrator privilege to configure trigger support.  IBM X-Force ID:  285203.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31870 | IBM i information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31870</link><description>IBM Db2 for i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 supplies user defined table function is vulnerable to user enumeration by a local authenticated attacker, without having authority to the related *USRPRF objects.  This can be used by a malicious actor to gather information about users that can be targeted in further attacks.  IBM X-Force ID:  287174.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6007 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway deleteiscgwrouteconf.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6007</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /protocol/iscgwtunnel/deleteiscgwrouteconf.php. The manipulation of the argument messagecontent leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268695. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6006 | ZKTeco ZKBio CVSecurity V5000 Summer Schedule cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6006</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZKTeco ZKBio CVSecurity V5000 4.1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Summer Schedule Handler. The manipulation of the argument Schedule Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268694 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 11:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5611 | Stratum – Elementor Widgets &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5611</link><description>The Stratum – Elementor Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘label_years’ attribute within the Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 09:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6005 | ZKTeco ZKBio CVSecurity V5000 Department Section cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6005</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZKTeco ZKBio CVSecurity V5000 4.1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Department Section. The manipulation of the argument Department Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268693 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2695 | Shariff Wrapper &amp;lt;= 4.6.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2695</link><description>The Shariff Wrapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'shariff' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'borderradius' and 'timestamp'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3105 | Woody code snippets – Insert Header Footer Code, AdSense Ads &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 -Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3105</link><description>The Woody code snippets – Insert Header Footer Code, AdSense Ads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the 'insert_php' shortcode. This is due to the plugin not restricting the usage of the functionality to high level authorized users. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4095 | Collapse-O-Matic &amp;lt;= 1.8.5.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4095</link><description>The Collapse-O-Matic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'expand' and 'expandsub' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4258 | Video Gallery – YouTube Playlist, Channel Gallery by YotuWP &amp;lt;= 1.3.13 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4258</link><description>The Video Gallery – YouTube Playlist, Channel Gallery by YotuWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.13 via the settings parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4551 | Video Gallery – YouTube Playlist, Channel Gallery by YotuWP &amp;lt;= 1.3.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4551</link><description>The Video Gallery – YouTube Playlist, Channel Gallery by YotuWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.13 via the display function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to include and execute arbitrary php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5858 | Infographic Maker iList &amp;lt;= 4.7.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Title Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5858</link><description>The AI Infographic Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the qcld_openai_title_generate_desc AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary post titles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1399 | Restaurant Menu and Food Ordering &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1399</link><description>The Restaurant Menu – Food Ordering System – Table Reservation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5868 | WooCommerce - Social Login &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Email Verification due to Insufficient Randomness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5868</link><description>The WooCommerce - Social Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Email Verification in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via the use of insufficiently random activation code. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the email verification.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 03:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5871 | WooCommerce - Social Login &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5871</link><description>The WooCommerce - Social Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'woo_slg_verify' vulnerable parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 03:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6000 | FooEvents for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.19.20 - Improper Authorization to (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6000</link><description>The FooEvents for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary file uploads due to an improper capability setting on the 'display_ticket_themes_page' function in versions up to, and including, 1.19.20. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This was partially patched in 1.19.20, and fully patched in 1.19.21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 03:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6696 | Popup Builder – Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 - Missing Authorization and Nonce Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6696</link><description>The Popup Builder – Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functionality due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.1. While some functions contain a nonce check, the nonce can be obtained from the profile page of a logged-in user. This allows subscribers to perform several actions including deleting subscribers and perform blind Server-Side Request Forgery.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2544 | Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Missing Authorization in Multiple AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2544</link><description>The Popup Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on all AJAX actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform multiple unauthorized actions, such as deleting subscribers, and importing subscribers to conduct stored cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3813 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3813</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.8 via the 'td_block_title' shortcode 'block_template_id' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3814 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Attachment Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3814</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'single' module in all versions up to, and including, 4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3815 | Newspaper &amp;lt;= 12.6.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Attachment Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3815</link><description>The Newspaper theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via attachment meta in the archive page in all versions up to, and including, 12.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4479 | Jeg Elementor Kit &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via JKit - Tabs and JKit - Accordion Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4479</link><description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the sg_general_toggle_tab_enable and sg_accordion_style attributes within the plugin's JKit - Tabs and JKit - Accordion widget, respectively, in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5263 | ElementsKit Elementor addons and Templates Library &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Motion Text and Table Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5263</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Motion Text and Table widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21988 | CVE-2024-21988 SSH Cryptographic Implementation Vulnerability in StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21988</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 
11.7.0.9 and 11.8.0.5 are susceptible to disclosure of sensitive 
information via complex MiTM attacks due to a vulnerability in the SSH 
cryptographic implementation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 21:51:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30120 | HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by an Unused Parameter in the web application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30120</link><description>HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by an Unused Parameter in the web application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 21:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30119 | HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by a missing Strict Transport Security Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30119</link><description>HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by a missing Strict Transport Security Header.  This could allow an attacker to intercept or manipulate data during redirection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6003 | Guangdong Baolun Electronics IP Network Broadcasting Service Platform maps sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6003</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Guangdong Baolun Electronics IP Network Broadcasting Service Platform 2.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/v2/maps. The manipulation of the argument orderColumn leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268692. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 21:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37831 | Itsourcecode Payroll Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in payroll_items.php via the ID parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37831</link><description>Itsourcecode Payroll Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in payroll_items.php via the ID parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37889 | MyFinances Allows Unauthorized Access to Other Customer Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37889</link><description>MyFinances is a web application for managing finances. MyFinances has a way to access other customer invoices while signed in as a user. This method allows an actor to access PII and financial information from another account. The vulnerability is fixed in 0.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36600 | Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in libcdio v2.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ISO 9660 image file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36600</link><description>Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in libcdio v2.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ISO 9660 image file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36597 | Aegon Life v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the client_id parameter at clientStatus.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36597</link><description>Aegon Life v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the client_id parameter at clientStatus.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36598 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Aegon Life v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted image file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36598</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Aegon Life v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted image file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36599 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Aegon Life v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36599</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Aegon Life v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the name parameter at insertClient.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24320 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Mgt-commerce CloudPanel v.2.0.0 thru v.2.4.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24320</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Mgt-commerce CloudPanel v.2.0.0 thru v.2.4.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the service parameter of the load-logfiles function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37888 | The Open Link CKEditor plugin has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in open link functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37888</link><description>The Open Link is a CKEditor plugin, extending context menu with a possibility to open link in a new tab. The vulnerability allowed to execute JavaScript code by abusing link href attribute. It affects all users using the Open Link plugin at version &lt; **1.0.5**.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37369 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability via Local File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5659 | Rockwell Automation Multicast Request Causes major nonrecoverable fault on Select Controllers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link><description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37887 | Nextcloud Server&amp;#x27;s events information leaked with shared calendars on recurrence exceptions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37641 | TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the submit-url parameter at /formNewSchedule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37641</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the submit-url parameter at /formNewSchedule</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37885 | Code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link><description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37886 | Nextcloud user_oidc&amp;#x27;s ID4me does not validate signature or expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link><description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37883 | Nextcloud Deck can access comments and attachments of deleted cards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link><description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37884 | Nextcloud Server&amp;#x27;s users can delete old versions of read-only shared files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37884</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A malicious user was able to send delete requests for old versions of files they only got shared with read permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37316 | Nextcloud Calendar&amp;#x27;s event create can create attachments that link to other websites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link><description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37317 | Nextcloud Notes app can be tricked into using a received share created before the user logged in</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link><description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37642 | TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ipv4_ping, ipv6_ping parameter at /fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37642</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ipv4_ping, ipv6_ping parameter at /formSystemCheck .</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37643 | TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a stack overflow vulnerability via the submit-url parameter at /formPasswordAut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37643</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a stack overflow vulnerability via the submit-url parameter at /formPasswordAuth .</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37645 | TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a stack overflow vulnerability via the submit-url parameter at /formSysLog .</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37645</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a stack overflow vulnerability via the submit-url parameter at /formSysLog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37882 | Nextcloud Server can reshare read&amp;amp;share only folder with more permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33373 | An issue in the LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 router allows attackers to bypass password complexity requirements and set single digit passwords for...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33373</link><description>An issue in the LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 router allows attackers to bypass password complexity requirements and set single digit passwords for authentication. This vulnerability can allow attackers to access the router via a brute-force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37315 | Nextcloud Server&amp;#x27;s read-only users can restore old versions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33377 | LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 was discovered to contain a clickjacking vulnerability via the Administrator login page. Attackers can cause victim u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33377</link><description>LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 was discovered to contain a clickjacking vulnerability via the Administrator login page. Attackers can cause victim users to perform arbitrary operations via interaction with crafted elements on the web page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36656 | In MintHCM 4.0.3, a registered user can execute arbitrary JavaScript code and achieve a reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36656</link><description>In MintHCM 4.0.3, a registered user can execute arbitrary JavaScript code and achieve a reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37314 | Nextcloud Photos&amp;#x27; shared albums have no restriction on photo removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link><description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33374 | Incorrect access control in the UART/Serial interface on the LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 router allows attackers to access the root terminal with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33374</link><description>Incorrect access control in the UART/Serial interface on the LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 router allows attackers to access the root terminal without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34539 | Hardcoded credentials in TerraMaster TOS firmware through 5.1 allow a remote attacker to successfully login to the mail or webmail server. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34539</link><description>Hardcoded credentials in TerraMaster TOS firmware through 5.1 allow a remote attacker to successfully login to the mail or webmail server. These credentials can also be used to login to the administration panel and to perform privileged actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37312 | Nextcloud user_oidc app&amp;#x27;s ID4me feature is available even when disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link><description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37313 | Nextcloud server allows the by-pass the second factor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link><description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33375 | LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 was discovered to store user credentials in plaintext within the router's firmware.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33375</link><description>LB-LINK BL-W1210M v2.0 was discovered to store user credentials in plaintext within the router's firmware.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34694 | LNbits improperly handles potential network and payment failures when using Eclair backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34694</link><description>LNbits is a Lightning wallet and accounts system. Paying invoices in Eclair that do not get settled within the internal timeout (about 30s) lead to a payment being considered failed, even though it may still be in flight. This vulnerability can lead to a total loss of funds for the node backend. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.12.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37368 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v11 Information Leakage Vulnerability via Authentication Restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link><description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23442 | Kibana open redirect issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23442</link><description>An open redirect issue was discovered in Kibana that could lead to a user being redirected to an arbitrary website if they use a maliciously crafted Kibana URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37367 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12 Information Leakage Vulnerability via Authentication Restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link><description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37644 | TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow.sample, which allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37644</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-814DAP v1_(FW1.01B01) was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow.sample, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5731 | A vulnerability in the IPS Manager, Central Manager, and Local Manager communication workflow allows an attacker to control the destination ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5731</link><description>A vulnerability in the IPS Manager, Central Manager, and Local Manager communication workflow allows an attacker to control the destination of a request by manipulating the parameter, thereby leveraging sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37640 | TOTOLINK A3700R V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via ssid5g in the function setWiFiEasyGuestCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37640</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via ssid5g in the function setWiFiEasyGuestCfg.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5671 | Insecure Deserialization in some workflows of the IPS Manager allows unauthenticated remote attackers to perform arbitrary code execution an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5671</link><description>Insecure Deserialization in some workflows of the IPS Manager allows unauthenticated remote attackers to perform arbitrary code execution and access to the vulnerable Trellix IPS Manager.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37637 | TOTOLINK A3700R V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via ssid5g in the function setWizardCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37637</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via ssid5g in the function setWizardCfg.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37639 | TOTOLINK A3700R V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via eport in the function setIpPortFilterRules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37639</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via eport in the function setIpPortFilterRules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2023 | Folders &amp;lt;= 3.0 and Folders Pro &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Directory Traversal via handle_folders_file_upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2023</link><description>The Folders and Folders Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.0 in Folders and 3.0.2 in Folders Pro via the 'handle_folders_file_upload' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author access and above, to upload files to arbitrary locations on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2024 | Folders Pro &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Authenticated(Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via handle_folders_file_upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2024</link><description>The Folders Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'handle_folders_file_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36459 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Symantec SiteMinder Web Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36459</link><description>A CRLF cross-site scripting vulnerability has been identified in certain configurations of the SiteMinder Web Agent for IIS Web Server and SiteMinder Web Agent for Domino Web Server. As a result, an attacker can execute arbitrary Javascript code in a client browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51376 | WordPress ProjectHuddle Client Site plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.34 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51376</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Brainstorm Force ProjectHuddle Client Site.This issue affects ProjectHuddle Client Site: from n/a through 1.0.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5685 | Broken Function Level Authorization (BFLA) in snipe/snipe-it</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5685</link><description>Users with "User:edit" and "Self:api" permissions can promote or demote themselves or other users by performing changes to the group's memberships via API call.This issue affects snipe-it: from v4.6.17 through v6.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34012 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cloud Manager (Windows) before b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34012</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cloud Manager (Windows) before build 6.2.24135.272.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2472 | LatePoint Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Missing Authorization and Sensitive Information Exposure via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2472</link><description>The LatePoint Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'start_or_use_session_for_customer' function in all versions up to and including 4.9.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view other customer's cabinets, including the ability to view PII such as email addresses and to change their LatePoint user password, which may or may not be associated with a WordPress account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3912 | ASUS Router - Upload arbitary firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link><description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36287 | Bypass of TCC restrictions on macOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36287</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.7.0 fail to disable certain Electron debug flags which allows for bypassing TCC restrictions on macOS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37182 | Lack of permissions prompting when opening external URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37182</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.7.0 fail to correctly prompt for permission when opening external URLs which allows a remote attacker to force a victim over the Internet to run arbitrary programs on the victim's system via custom URI schemes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4863 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features &amp;lt;= 3.2.38 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via titleFont Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4863</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘titleFont’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.38 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25142 | Apache Airflow: Cache Control - Storage of Sensitive Data in Browser Cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25142</link><description>Use of Web Browser Cache Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Apache Airflow. 

Airflow did not return "Cache-Control" header for dynamic content, which in case of some browsers could result in potentially storing sensitive data in local cache of the browser.

This issue affects Apache Airflow: before 2.9.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5996 | Soar Cloud HR Portal - Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5996</link><description>The notification emails sent by Soar Cloud HR Portal contain a link with a embedded session. These emails are sent without using an encrypted transmission protocol. If an attacker intercepts the packets, they can obtain the plaintext session information and use it to log into the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5961 | Reflected XSS in 2ClickPortal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5961</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability in 2ClickPortal software allows reflected cross-site scripting (XSS). An attacker might trick somebody into using a crafted URL, which will cause a script to be run in user's browser. This issue affects 2ClickPortal software versions from 7.2.31 through 7.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5464 | Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the NearLink module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5464</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the NearLink module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5465 | Function vulnerabilities in the Calendar module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5465</link><description>Function vulnerabilities in the Calendar module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5577 | Where I Was, Where I Will Be &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Remote File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5577</link><description>The Where I Was, Where I Will Be plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in version &lt;= 1.1.1 via the WIW_HEADER parameter of the /system/include/include_user.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files hosted on external servers, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution. This requires allow_url_include to be set to true in order to exploit, which is not commonly enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36501 | Memory management vulnerability in the boottime module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can affect integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36501</link><description>Memory management vulnerability in the boottime module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can affect integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36502 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the audio module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36502</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the audio module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36503 | Memory management vulnerability in the Gralloc module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36503</link><description>Memory management vulnerability in the Gralloc module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36499 | Vulnerability of unauthorized screenshot capturing in the WMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36499</link><description>Vulnerability of unauthorized screenshot capturing in the WMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36500 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the AMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36500</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the AMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5995 | Soar Cloud HR Portal - Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5995</link><description>The notification emails sent by Soar Cloud HR Portal contain a link with a embedded session. The expiration of the session is not properly configured, remaining valid for more than 7 days and can be reused.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31163 | ASUS Download Master - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link><description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5994 | WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) &amp;lt;= 9.0.38 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5994</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom JS option in versions up to, and including, 9.0.38. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers that have been explicitly granted permissions by an administrator, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Version 9.0.39 adds a caution to make administrators aware of the possibility for abuse if permissions are granted to lower-level users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31162 | ASUS Download Master - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link><description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1295 | The Events Calendar (Free &amp;lt; 6.4.0.1, Pro &amp;lt; 6.4.0.1) - Contributor+ Arbitrary Events Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1295</link><description>The events-calendar-pro WordPress plugin before 6.4.0.1, The Events Calendar WordPress plugin before 6.4.0.1 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role from leaking details about events they shouldn't have access to. (e.g. password-protected events, drafts, etc.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2218 | LuckyWP Table of Contents &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2218</link><description>The LuckyWP Table of Contents WordPress plugin through 2.1.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3754 | Alemha Watermarker &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3754</link><description>The Alemha watermarker WordPress plugin through 1.3.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3965 | Pray For Me &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3965</link><description>The Pray For Me WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3966 | Pray For Me &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3966</link><description>The Pray For Me WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could unauthenticated visitors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks that trigger when an admin visits the Prayer Requests in the WP Admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3971 | Similarity &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Plugin Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3971</link><description>The Similarity WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not have CSRF check in place when resetting its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin reset them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3972 | Similarity &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3972</link><description>The Similarity WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3977 | WordPress Jitsi Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3977</link><description>The WordPress Jitsi Shortcode WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3978 | WordPress Jitsi Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3978</link><description>The WordPress Jitsi Shortcode WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3992 | Amen &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3992</link><description>The Amen WordPress plugin through 3.3.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3993 | AZAN Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3993</link><description>The AZAN Plugin WordPress plugin through 0.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4005 | Social Pixel &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4005</link><description>The Social Pixel WordPress plugin through 2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4270 | SVGMagic &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4270</link><description>The SVGMagic WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which enables users with at least the author role to SVG with malicious JavaScript to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4271 | SVGator &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4271</link><description>The SVGator  WordPress plugin through 1.2.6 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which enables users with at least the author role to SVG with malicious JavaScript to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4480 | WP Prayer II &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Email Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4480</link><description>The WP Prayer II WordPress plugin through 2.4.7 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its email settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4751 | WP Prayer II &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4751</link><description>The WP Prayer II WordPress plugin through 2.4.7 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5155 | Inquiry Cart &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5155</link><description>The Inquiry cart WordPress plugin through 3.4.2 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51377 | WordPress Everest Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51377</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEverest Everest Forms.This issue affects Everest Forms: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51495 | WordPress WooCommerce Warranty Requests plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51495</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo WooCommerce Warranty Requests.This issue affects WooCommerce Warranty Requests: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51496 | WordPress WooCommerce Warranty Requests plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51496</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo WooCommerce Warranty Requests.This issue affects WooCommerce Warranty Requests: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23504 | WordPress Ninja Tables plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23504</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPManageNinja LLC Ninja Tables.This issue affects Ninja Tables: from n/a through 5.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2122 | FooGallery &amp;lt;= 2.4.15 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Gallery Custom URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2122</link><description>The Best WordPress Gallery Plugin – FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via album gallery custom URLs in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4404 | ElementsKit PRO &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4404</link><description>The ElementsKit PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 via the 'render_raw' function. This can allow authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5551 | WP STAGING PRO - Backup Duplicator &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 5.6.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5551</link><description>The WP STAGING Pro WordPress Backup Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'sub' parameter called from the WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin - Backup Duplicator &amp; Migration plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include any local files that end in '-settings.php' via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51497 | WordPress WooCommerce Ship to Multiple Addresses plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51497</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo WooCommerce Ship to Multiple Addresses.This issue affects WooCommerce Ship to Multiple Addresses: from n/a through 3.8.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 05:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1094 | Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking with Visual Seat Plan and ultimate Calendar Scheduling Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Missing Authorization to Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1094</link><description>The Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking with Visual Seat Plan and ultimate Calendar Scheduling plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the make_staff() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to grant users staff permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4936 | Canto &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Unauthenticated Remote File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4936</link><description>The Canto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 via the abspath parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include remote files on the server, resulting in code execution. This required allow_url_include to be enabled on the target site in order to exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3496 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3496</link><description>Attackers can bypass the web login authentication process to gain access to the printer's system information and upload malicious drivers to the printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3497 | Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3497</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the web server of the Toshiba printer enables attacker to overwrite orginal files or add new ones to the printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3498 | Incorrect Permission Assignment Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3498</link><description>Attackers can then execute malicious files by enabling certain services of the printer via the web configuration page and elevate its privileges to root. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27173 | insecure upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27173</link><description>Remote Command program allows an attacker to get Remote Code Execution by overwriting existing Python files containing executable code. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27174 | insecure upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27174</link><description>Remote Command program allows an attacker to get Remote Code Execution. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27175 | Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27175</link><description>Remote Command program allows an attacker to read any file using a Local File Inclusion vulnerability. An attacker can read any file on the printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27176 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27176</link><description>An attacker can get Remote Code Execution by overwriting files. Overwriting files is enable by falsifying session ID variable. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27177 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27177</link><description>An attacker can get Remote Code Execution by overwriting files.  Overwriting files is enable by falsifying package name variable. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27178 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27178</link><description>An attacker can get Remote Code Execution by overwriting files.  Overwriting files is enable by falsifying file name variable. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27179 | Session disclosure inside the log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27179</link><description>Admin cookies are written in clear-text in logs. An attacker can retrieve them and bypass the authentication mechanism. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27180 | TOCTOU vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27180</link><description>An attacker with admin access can install rogue applications. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5469 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link><description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27168 | Hardcoded keys used to generate authentication cookies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27168</link><description>It appears that some hardcoded keys are used for authentication to internal API. Knowing these private keys may allow attackers to bypass authentication and reach administrative interfaces. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27169 | Lack of authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27169</link><description>Toshiba printers provides API without authentication for internal access. A local attacker can bypass authentication in applications, providing administrative access. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27170 | Hardcoded credentials for WebDAV access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27170</link><description>It was observed that all the Toshiba printers contain credentials used for WebDAV access in the readable file. Then, it is possible to get a full access with WebDAV to the printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27171 | Insecure permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27171</link><description>A remote attacker using the insecure upload functionality will be able to overwrite any Python file and get Remote Code Execution. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27172 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27172</link><description>Remote Command program allows an attacker to get Remote Code Execution. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31161 | ASUS Download Master - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link><description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27166 | Insecure permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27166</link><description>Coredump binaries in Toshiba printers have incorrect permissions. A local attacker can steal confidential information. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27167 | Insecure permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27167</link><description>Toshiba printers use Sendmail to send emails to recipients. Sendmail is used with several insecure directories. A local attacker can inject a malicious Sendmail configuration file. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27162 | DOM-based XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27162</link><description>Toshiba printers provide a web interface that will load the JavaScript file. The file contains insecure codes vulnerable to XSS and is loaded inside all the webpages provided by the printer. An attacker can steal the cookie of an admin user. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27163 | Leak of admin password and passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27163</link><description>Toshiba printers will display the password of the admin user in clear-text and additional passwords when sending 2 specific HTTP requests to the internal API. An attacker stealing the cookie of an admin or abusing a XSS vulnerability can recover this password in clear-text and compromise the printer. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27164 | Hardcoded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27164</link><description>Toshiba printers contain hardcoded credentials. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27165 | Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27165</link><description>Toshiba printers contain a suidperl binary and it has a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. A local attacker can get root privileges. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31160 | ASUS Download Master - Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link><description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6492 | Simple Sitemap &amp;lt;= 3.5.13 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via admin_notices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6492</link><description>The Simple Sitemap – Create a Responsive HTML Sitemap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the 'admin_notices' hook found in class-settings.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin options to a default state via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0892 | Schema App Structured Data &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0892</link><description>The Schema App Structured Data plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the MarkUpdate function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update and delete post metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27160 | Hardcoded password used to encrypt logs and use of weak cipher</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27160</link><description>All the Toshiba printers contain a shell script using the same hardcoded key to encrypt logs. An attacker can decrypt the encrypted files using the hardcoded key. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27161 | Hardcoded password used to encrypt files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27161</link><description>all the Toshiba printers have programs containing a hardcoded key used to encrypt files. An attacker can decrypt the encrypted files using the hardcoded key. Insecure algorithm is used for the encryption. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27156 | Leak of authentication sessions in secure logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27156</link><description>The session cookies, used for authentication, are stored in clear-text logs. An attacker can retrieve authentication sessions. A remote attacker can retrieve the credentials and bypass the authentication mechanism. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27157 | Leak of authentication sessions in secure logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27157</link><description>The sessions are stored in clear-text logs. An attacker can retrieve authentication sessions. A remote attacker can retrieve the credentials and bypass the authentication mechanism. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27158 | Hardcoded root password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27158</link><description>All the Toshiba printers share the same hardcoded root password. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27159 | Hardcoded password used to encrypt logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27159</link><description>All the Toshiba printers contain a shell script using the same hardcoded key to encrypt logs. An attacker can decrypt the encrypted files using the hardcoded key. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31159 | ASUS Download Master - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link><description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27155 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using insecure permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27155</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. The programs can be replaced by malicious programs by any local or remote attacker. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27154 | Passwords are stored in clear-text logs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27154</link><description>Passwords are stored in clear-text logs. An attacker can retrieve passwords. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27149 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using insecure LD_PRELOAD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27149</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27150 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using insecure LD_LIBRARY_PATH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27150</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27151 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using insecure permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27151</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. The programs can be replaced by malicious programs by any local or remote attacker. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27152 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using insecure permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27152</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27153 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27153</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3080 | ASUS Router - Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link><description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27147 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using snmpd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27147</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27148 | Local Privilege Escalation and Remote Code Execution using insecure PATH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27148</link><description>The Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27142 | Pre-authenticated XXE injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27142</link><description>Toshiba printers use XML communication for the API endpoint provided by the printer. For the endpoint, XML parsing library is used and it is vulnerable to a time-based blind XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability. An attacker can DoS the printers. An attacker can exploit the XXE to retrieve information. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27143 | Pre-authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27143</link><description>Toshiba printers use SNMP for configuration. Using the private community, it is possible to remotely execute commands as root on the remote printer. Using this vulnerability will allow any attacker to get a root access on a remote Toshiba printer. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27144 | Pre-authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27144</link><description>The Toshiba printers provide several ways to upload files using the web interface without authentication. An attacker can overwrite any insecure files. And the Toshiba printers are vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. The programs can be replaced by malicious programs by any local or remote attacker. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27145 | Multiple Post-authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27145</link><description>The Toshiba printers provide several ways to upload files using the admin web interface. An attacker can remotely compromise any Toshiba printer. An attacker can overwrite any insecure files. This vulnerability can be executed in combination with other vulnerabilities and  difficult to execute alone. So, the CVSS score for this vulnerability alone is lower than the score listed in the "Base Score" of this vulnerability. For detail on related other vulnerabilities, please ask to the below contact point.
 https://www.toshibatec.com/contacts/products/ 
As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27146 | Lack of privileges separation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27146</link><description>The Toshiba printers do not implement privileges separation. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3079 | ASUS Router - Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link><description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27141 | Pre-authenticated Time-Based Blind XXE injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27141</link><description>Toshiba printers use XML communication for the API endpoint provided by the printer. For the endpoint, XML parsing library is used and it is vulnerable to a time-based blind XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability. An attacker can DoS the printers by sending a HTTP request without authentication. An attacker can exploit the XXE to retrieve information. As for the affected products/models/versions, see the reference URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5985 | SourceCodester Best Online News Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5985</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Online News Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268461 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5983 | itsourcecode Online Bookstore bookPerPub.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5983</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Bookstore 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file bookPerPub.php. The manipulation of the argument pubid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268459.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5984 | itsourcecode Online Bookstore book.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5984</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Bookstore 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file book.php. The manipulation of the argument bookisbn leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268460.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51507 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51507</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through 8.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51516 | WordPress Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.9  - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51516</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Business Directory Team Business Directory Plugin.This issue affects Business Directory Plugin: from n/a through 6.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51523 | WordPress WooCommerce Easy Duplicate Product plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.0.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51523</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WriterSystem WooCommerce Easy Duplicate Product.This issue affects WooCommerce Easy Duplicate Product: from n/a through 0.3.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5981 | itsourcecode Online House Rental System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5981</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online House Rental System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>