<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:38:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1598 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software asset_crud.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1598</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/asset_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument photo1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1596 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software fpassword.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1596</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /fpassword.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1597 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software redirect.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1597</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/redirect.php. The manipulation of the argument a leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22631 | WordPress Marketing Automation Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vbout Marketing Automation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Marketing Automation: from n/a through 1.2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22632 | WordPress WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in totalsoft WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22633 | WordPress Give – Divi Donation Modules plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22633</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in Matt Cromwell Give – Divi Donation Modules allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Give – Divi Donation Modules: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22635 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt; 3.9.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22635</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jyothis Joy Eventer allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1595 | Anhui Xufan Information Technology EasyCVR getbaseconfig information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Anhui Xufan Information Technology EasyCVR up to 2.7.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/v1/getbaseconfig. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 22:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1594 | FFmpeg AAC Encoder aacenc_tns.c ff_aac_search_for_tns stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1594</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FFmpeg up to 7.1. This affects the function ff_aac_search_for_tns of the file libavcodec/aacenc_tns.c of the component AAC Encoder. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 21:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1593 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Profile Picture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1593</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /_hr_soft/assets/uploadImage/Profile/ of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1592 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Add Role Page Role.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1592</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/Operations/Role.php of the component Add Role Page. The manipulation of the argument assign_name/description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1591 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Department Page department.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1591</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /department.php of the component Department Page. The manipulation of the argument Department Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1590 | SourceCodester E-Learning System List of Lessons Page index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1590</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/lesson/index.php of the component List of Lessons Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1589 | SourceCodester E-Learning System User Registration register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1589</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /register.php of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1588 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System manage-nurse.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1588</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/manage-nurse.php. The manipulation of the argument profilepic leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting vulnerability classes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1467 | Versions of the package tarteaucitronjs before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the getElemWidth() and getElemHeight(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1467</link><description>Versions of the package tarteaucitronjs before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the getElemWidth() and getElemHeight(). This is related to [SNYK-JS-TARTEAUCITRONJS-8366541](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-TARTEAUCITRONJS-8366541)</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1587 | SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System Add New Record main.cpp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1587</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file main.cpp of the component Add New Record. The manipulation of the argument name leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1586 | code-projects Blood Bank System A-.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1586</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Blood/A-.php. The manipulation of the argument Bloodname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1585 | otale header.html OptionsService cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1585</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in otale tale up to 2.0.5. This issue affects the function OptionsService of the file src/main/resources/templates/themes/default/partial/header.html. The manipulation of the argument logo_url leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1584 | opensolon Solon StaticMappings.java path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1584</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in opensolon Solon up to 3.0.8. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file solon-projects/solon-web/solon-web-staticfiles/src/main/java/org/noear/solon/web/staticfiles/StaticMappings.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.9 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is f46e47fd1f8455b9467d7ead3cdb0509115b2ef1. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1583 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System search-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/search-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1582 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System all-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/all-request.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1581 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System book-nurse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /book-nurse.php?bookid=1. The manipulation of the argument contactname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1580 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System search-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting parameter names to be affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1579 | code-projects Blood Bank System user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/user.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1578 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal search-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1578</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /search-result.php. The manipulation of the argument product leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1577 | code-projects Blood Bank System prostatus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1577</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /prostatus.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 07:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13728 | Accept Donations with PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13728</link><description>The Accept Donations with PayPal &amp; Stripe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the rf parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1576 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System ajax_state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1576</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax_state.php. The manipulation of the argument StateName as part of String leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1575 | Harpia DiagSystem atualatendimento_jpeg.php resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1575</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Harpia DiagSystem 12. Affected is an unknown function of the file /diagsystem/PACS/atualatendimento_jpeg.php. The manipulation of the argument cod/codexame leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28339 | Trend Micro HouseCall for Home Networks version 5.3.1302 and below contains an uncontrolled search patch element vulnerability that could al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28339</link><description>Trend Micro HouseCall for Home Networks version 5.3.1302 and below contains an uncontrolled search patch element vulnerability that could allow an attacker with low user privileges to create a malicious DLL that could lead to escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 21:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26750 | WordPress Vitepos Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26750</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in appsbd Vitepos allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Vitepos: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26756 | WordPress Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26756</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in grimdonkey Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips: from n/a through 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26757 | WordPress FULL – Cliente plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.26 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26757</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in FULL SERVICES FULL Customer allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects FULL Customer: from n/a through 3.1.26.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26760 | WordPress Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26760</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Wow-Company Calculator Builder allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Calculator Builder: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26763 | WordPress Slider, Gallery, and Carousel by MetaSlider – Image Slider, Video Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.94.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26763</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MetaSlider Responsive Slider by MetaSlider allows Object Injection. This issue affects Responsive Slider by MetaSlider: from n/a through 3.94.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26764 | WordPress Distance Based Shipping Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26764</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology Distance Based Shipping Calculator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Distance Based Shipping Calculator: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26774 | WordPress Responsive Modal Builder for High Conversion – Easy Popups plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26774</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rock Solid Responsive Modal Builder for High Conversion – Easy Popups allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Responsive Modal Builder for High Conversion – Easy Popups: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26776 | WordPress Chaty Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26776</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NotFound Chaty Pro allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Chaty Pro: from n/a through 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26973 | WordPress Social Warfare Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26973</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WarfarePlugins Social Warfare allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Social Warfare: from n/a through 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27012 | WordPress A1POST.BG Shipping for Woo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27012</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in a1post A1POST.BG Shipping for Woo allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects A1POST.BG Shipping for Woo: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12577 | GPU DDK - rgxfw_pcset_ungrab OOB write via psFWMemContext-&amp;gt;uiPageCatBaseRegSet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12577</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52939 | GPU DDK - RGXFWIF_HWPERF_CTL_BLK.uiNumCounters OOB write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52939</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may post improper commands to the GPU Firmware to trigger a write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47896 | GPU DDK - rgxfw_hwr_log_info OOB write via psHWRInfoBuf-&amp;gt;ui32WriteIndex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47896</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46975 | GPU DDK - rgxfw_write_robustness_buffer allows arbitrary catreg set mapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46975</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to write data into another Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0957 | Vulnerability: SMTP for Amazon SES &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0957</link><description>The SMTP for Amazon SES – YaySMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 13:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1557 | OFCMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1557</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in OFCMS 1.1.3. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 13:03:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13869 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid &amp;lt;= 0.9.112 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload via wpvivid_upload_file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13869</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'upload_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.112. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. NOTE: Uploaded files are only accessible on WordPress instances running on the NGINX web server as the existing .htaccess within the target file upload folder prevents access on Apache servers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0918 | SMTP for SendGrid – YaySMTP &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0918</link><description>The SMTP for SendGrid – YaySMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0953 | SMTP for Sendinblue – YaySMTP &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0953</link><description>The SMTP for Sendinblue – YaySMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1556 | westboy CicadasCMS Template Management system deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1556</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /system of the component Template Management. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21704 | usb: cdc-acm: Check control transfer buffer size before access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21704</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: cdc-acm: Check control transfer buffer size before access

If the first fragment is shorter than struct usb_cdc_notification, we can't
calculate an expected_size. Log an error and discard the notification
instead of reading lengths from memory outside the received data, which can
lead to memory corruption when the expected_size decreases between
fragments, causing `expected_size - acm-&gt;nb_index` to wrap.

This issue has been present since the beginning of git history; however,
it only leads to memory corruption since commit ea2583529cd1
("cdc-acm: reassemble fragmented notifications").

A mitigating factor is that acm_ctrl_irq() can only execute after userspace
has opened /dev/ttyACM*; but if ModemManager is running, ModemManager will
do that automatically depending on the USB device's vendor/product IDs and
its other interfaces.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 09:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1553 | pankajindevops scale project cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1553</link><description>A vulnerability was found in pankajindevops scale up to 3633544a00245d3df88b6d13d9b3dd0f411be7f6. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /scale/project. The manipulation of the argument goal leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 09:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13564 | Rife Elementor Extensions &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Writing Effect Headline Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13564</link><description>The Rife Elementor Extensions &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Writing Effect Headline shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 08:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1361 | IP2Location Country Blocker &amp;lt;= 2.38.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure via admin_init Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1361</link><description>The IP2Location Country Blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.38.8 due to missing capability checks on the admin_init() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12038 | Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;buddyforms_nav&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12038</link><description>The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'buddyforms_nav' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12467 | Pago por Redsys &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12467</link><description>The Pago por Redsys plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Ds_MerchantParameters' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13474 | LTL Freight Quotes – Purolator Edition &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13474</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Purolator Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13798 | Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks – ComboBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Unauthenticated Paid Order Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13798</link><description>The Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized order creation in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This is due to insufficient verification on form fields. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new orders for products and mark them as paid without actually completing a payment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13873 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Photo Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13873</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.8 via the deleteUserPhoto() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to remove profile photos from users accounts. Please note that this does not officially delete the file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13899 | Mambo Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13899</link><description>The Mambo Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input via the $data parameter in the fImportMenu function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1509 | Show Me The Cookies &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1509</link><description>The The Show Me The Cookies plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1510 | Custom Post Type Date Archives &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1510</link><description>The The Custom Post Type Date Archives plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22341 | IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22341</link><description>IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.0 through 4.0.9, 4.5.0 through 4.5.3, 4.6.0 through 4.6.6, 4.7.0 through 4.7.4, and 4.8.0 through 4.8.7 could allow unauthorized data access from a remote data source object due to improper privilege management.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:05:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45674 | IBM Security Verify Bridge information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45674</link><description>IBM Security Verify Bridge Directory Sync 1.0.1 through 1.0.12, IBM Security Verify Gateway for Windows Login 1.0.1 through 1.0.10, and IBM Security Verify Gateway for Radius 1.0.1 through 1.0.11 

stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26622 | sqrt doesn&amp;#x27;t define rounding behavior in Vyper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26622</link><description>vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. Vyper `sqrt()` builtin uses the babylonian method to calculate square roots of decimals. Unfortunately, improper handling of the oscillating final states may lead to sqrt incorrectly returning rounded up results. This issue is being addressed and a fix is expected in version 0.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as the patched release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27104 | double eval in For List Iter in Vyper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27104</link><description>vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. Multiple evaluation of a single expression is possible in the iterator target of a for loop. While the iterator expression cannot produce multiple writes, it can consume side effects produced in the loop body (e.g. read a storage variable updated in the loop body) and thus lead to unexpected program behavior. Specifically, reads in iterators which contain an ifexp (e.g. `for s: uint256 in ([read(), read()] if True else [])`) may interleave reads with writes in the loop body. Vyper for loops allow two kinds of iterator targets, namely the `range()` builtin and an iterable type, like SArray and DArray. During codegen, iterable lists are required to not produce any side-effects (in the following code, `range_scope` forces `iter_list` to be parsed in a constant context, which is checked against `is_constant`). However, this does not prevent the iterator from consuming side effects provided by the body of the loop. For SArrays on the other hand, `iter_list` is instantiated in the body of a `repeat` ir, so it can be evaluated several times. This issue is being addressed and is expected to be available in version 0.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as the patched release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27105 | AugAssign evaluation order causing OOB write within the object in Vyper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27105</link><description>vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. Vyper handles AugAssign statements by first caching the target location to avoid double evaluation. However, in the case when target is an access to a DynArray and the rhs modifies the array, the cached target will evaluate first, and the bounds check will not be re-evaluated during the write portion of the statement. This issue has been addressed in version 0.4.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27106 | Code injection in binance-trading-bot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27106</link><description>binance-trading-bot is an automated Binance trading bot with trailing buy/sell strategy. Authenticated users of binance-trading-bot can achieve Remote Code Execution on the host system due to a command injection vulnerability in the `/restore` endpoint. The restore endpoint of binance-trading-bot is vulnerable to command injection via the `/restore` endpoint. The name of the uploaded file is passed to shell.exec without sanitization other than path normalization, resulting in Remote Code Execution. This may allow any authorized user to execute code in the context of the host machine. This issue has been addressed in version 0.0.100 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-8900 | A vulnerability in the SecureROM of some Apple devices can be exploited by an unauthenticated local attacker to execute arbitrary code upon ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8900</link><description>A vulnerability in the SecureROM of some Apple devices can be exploited by an unauthenticated local attacker to execute arbitrary code upon booting those devices. This vulnerability allows arbitrary code to be executed on the device. Exploiting the vulnerability requires physical access to the device: the device must be plugged in to a computer upon booting, and it must be put into Device Firmware Update (DFU) mode. The exploit is not persistent; rebooting the device overrides any changes to the device's software that were made during an exploited session on the device. Additionally, unless an attacker has access to the device's unlock PIN or fingerprint, an attacker cannot gain access to information protected by Apple's Secure Enclave or Touch ID features.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27108 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability due to improper use of string.replace in dom-expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27108</link><description>dom-expressions is a Fine-Grained Runtime for Performant DOM Rendering. In affected versions the use of javascript's `.replace()` opens up to potential Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities with the special replacement patterns beginning with `$`. Particularly, when the attributes of `Meta` tag from solid-meta are user-defined, attackers can utilise the special replacement patterns, either `$'` or `$\`` to achieve XSS. The solid-meta package has this issue since it uses `useAffect` and context providers, which injects the used assets in the html header. "dom-expressions" uses `.replace()` to insert the assets, which is vulnerable to the special replacement patterns listed above.  This effectively means that if the attributes of an asset tag contained user-controlled data, it would be vulnerable to XSS. For instance, there might be meta tags for the open graph protocol in a user profile page, but if attackers set the user query to some payload abusing `.replace()`, then they could execute arbitrary javascript in the victim's web browser. Moreover, it could be stored and cause more problems. This issue has been addressed in version 0.39.5 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27109 | Lack of Escaping of HTML in JSX Fragments allows for Cross-site Scripting in solid-js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27109</link><description>solid-js is a declarative, efficient, and flexible JavaScript library for building user interfaces. In affected versions Inserts/JSX expressions inside illegal inlined JSX fragments lacked escaping, allowing user input to be rendered as HTML when put directly inside JSX fragments. This issue has been addressed in version 1.9.4 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25282 | Potential Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in ragflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25282</link><description>RAGFlow is an open-source RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) engine based on deep document understanding. An authenticated user can exploit the Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability that may lead to unauthorized cross-tenant access (list tenant user accounts, add user account into other tenant). Unauthorized cross-tenant access: list user from other tenant (e.g., via GET //user/list), add user account to other tenant (POST //user). This issue has not yet been patched. Users are advised to reach out to the project maintainers to coordinate a fix.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1555 | hzmanyun Education and Training System saveImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1555</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in hzmanyun Education and Training System 3.1.1. This vulnerability affects the function saveImage. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25604 | Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the vif_disable function in mtkwifi.lua.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25604</link><description>Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the vif_disable function in mtkwifi.lua.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25605 | Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the apcli_wps_gen_pincode function in mtkwifi.lua.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25605</link><description>Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the apcli_wps_gen_pincode function in mtkwifi.lua.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-19248 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PbootCMS 1.4.1 in parsing if statements in templates, resulting in a malicious user's ability to contaminate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-19248</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PbootCMS 1.4.1 in parsing if statements in templates, resulting in a malicious user's ability to contaminate template content by searching for page contamination URLs, thus triggering vulnerabilities when the program uses eval statements to parse templates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25767 | A vertical privilege escalation vulnerability in the component /controller/UserController.java of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to arbitrari...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25767</link><description>A vertical privilege escalation vulnerability in the component /controller/UserController.java of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to arbitrarily delete users via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25768 | MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the component \servlet\DispatcherServlet.jav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25768</link><description>MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the component \servlet\DispatcherServlet.java. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25769 | Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /controller/UserController.java.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25769</link><description>Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /controller/UserController.java.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25770 | Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /agency/AgencyUserController.java.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25770</link><description>Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /agency/AgencyUserController.java.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25772 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /back/UserController.java of Jspxcms v9.0 to v9.5 allows attackers to arbitrarily add A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25772</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /back/UserController.java of Jspxcms v9.0 to v9.5 allows attackers to arbitrarily add Administrator accounts via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55156 | An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the deserializeArgs() method of Java SDK for CloudEvents v4.0.1 allows attackers to access sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55156</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the deserializeArgs() method of Java SDK for CloudEvents v4.0.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via supplying a crafted XML-formatted event message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55159 | GFast between v2 to v3.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the SortName parameter at /system/loginLog/list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55159</link><description>GFast between v2 to v3.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the SortName parameter at /system/loginLog/list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25765 | MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file write vulnerability via the component /file/save.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25765</link><description>MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file write vulnerability via the component /file/save.do.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25766 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /file/savefile.do of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25766</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /file/savefile.do of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted .jsp file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25877 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin.php. The atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25877</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25878 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /del.php. The attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25878</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /del.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57176 | An issue in the shiroFilter function of White-Jotter project v0.2.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal and access sensitive e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57176</link><description>An issue in the shiroFilter function of White-Jotter project v0.2.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal and access sensitive endpoints via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25876 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /delete.php. The att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25876</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /delete.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25875 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /message.php. The at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25875</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /message.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1548 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1548</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/archives/edit. The manipulation of the argument editorValue/answer/content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25505 | Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the sub_452A4 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25505</link><description>Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the sub_452A4 function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25507 | There is a RCE vulnerability in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi. In the formexeCommand function, the parameter cmdinput will cause remote comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25507</link><description>There is a RCE vulnerability in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi. In the formexeCommand function, the parameter cmdinput will cause remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25510 | Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the get_parentControl_list_Info function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25510</link><description>Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the get_parentControl_list_Info function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1403 | Qiskit SDK denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1403</link><description>Qiskit SDK 0.45.0 through 1.2.4 could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service using a maliciously crafted QPY file containing a malformed symengine serialization stream which can cause a segfault within the symengine library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45673 | IBM Security Verify Bridge information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45673</link><description>IBM Security Verify Bridge Directory Sync 1.0.1 through 1.0.12, IBM Security Verify Gateway for Windows Login 1.0.1 through 1.0.10, and IBM Security Verify Gateway for Radius 1.0.1 through 1.0.11 stores user credentials in configuration files which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1546 | BDCOM Behavior Management and Auditing System operate.mds log_operate_clear os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1546</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in BDCOM Behavior Management and Auditing System up to 20250210 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function log_operate_clear of the file /webui/modules/log/operate.mds. The manipulation of the argument start_code leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26014 | A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the path parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26014</link><description>A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26013 | An issue in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the read.py component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26013</link><description>An issue in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the read.py component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1543 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS ueditor-1.4.3.3 path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1543</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /resource/js/ueditor-1.4.3.3. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1544 | dingfanzu CMS loadShopInfo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1544</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in dingfanzu CMS up to 20250210. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ajax/loadShopInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument shopId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1538 | D-Link DAP-1320 api set_ws_action heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1538</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DAP-1320 1.00. Affected by this vulnerability is the function set_ws_action of the file /dws/api/. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1539 | D-Link DAP-1320 storagein.pd-XXXXXX replace_special_char stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1539</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAP-1320 1.00. Affected by this issue is the function replace_special_char of the file /storagein.pd-XXXXXX. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1536 | Raisecom Multi-Service Intelligent Gateway Request Parameter vpn_template_style.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1536</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom Multi-Service Intelligent Gateway up to 20250208. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /vpn/vpn_template_style.php of the component Request Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1537 | Harpia DiagSystem atualatendimento_jpeg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1537</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Harpia DiagSystem 12. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /diagsystem/PACS/atualatendimento_jpeg.php. The manipulation of the argument codexame leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0838 | Heap Buffer overflow in Abseil</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0838</link><description>There exists a heap buffer overflow vulnerable in Abseil-cpp. The sized constructors, reserve(), and rehash() methods of absl::{flat,node}hash{set,map} did not impose an upper bound on their size argument. As a result, it was possible for a caller to pass a very large size that would cause an integer overflow when computing the size of the container's backing store, and a subsequent out-of-bounds memory write. Subsequent accesses to the container might also access out-of-bounds memory. We recommend upgrading past commit 5a0e2cb5e3958dd90bb8569a2766622cb74d90c1</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10222 | SVG Support &amp;lt;= 2.5.10 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10222</link><description>The SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. By default, this can only be exploited by administrators, but the ability to upload SVG files can be extended to authors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-6158 | Opera Mini for Android before version 52.2 is vulnerable to an address bar spoofing attack. The vulnerability allows a malicious page to tri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6158</link><description>Opera Mini for Android before version 52.2 is vulnerable to an address bar spoofing attack. The vulnerability allows a malicious page to trick the browser into showing an address of a different page. This may allow the malicious page to impersonate another page and trick a user into providing sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26794 | Exim 4.98 before 4.98.1, when SQLite hints and ETRN serialization are used, allows remote SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26794</link><description>Exim 4.98 before 4.98.1, when SQLite hints and ETRN serialization are used, allows remote SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1535 | Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System admin.ticket.close.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1535</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System 8.142.100.161. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /wuser/admin.ticket.close.php. The manipulation of the argument ticket_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9150 | Code Injection in Wyn Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9150</link><description>Report generation functionality in Wyn Enterprise allows for code inclusion, but not sufficiently limits what code might be included. An attacker is able use a low privileges account in order to abuse this functionality and execute malicious code, load DLL libraries and executing OS commands on a host system with applications high privileges.
This issue has been fixed in version 8.0.00204.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13455 | igumbi Online Booking &amp;lt;= 1.40 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13455</link><description>The igumbi Online Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'igumbi_calendar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13713 | WPExperts Square For GiveWP &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13713</link><description>The WPExperts Square For GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13846 | Indeed Ultimate Learning Pro &amp;lt;= 3.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via post_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13846</link><description>The Indeed Ultimate Learning Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘post_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13900 | Head, Footer and Post Injections &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Code Injection in Multisite Environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13900</link><description>The Head, Footer and Post Injections plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject PHP Code in multisite environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1402 | Event Tickets and Registration &amp;lt;= 5.19.1.1 - Missing Authorization to Ticket Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1402</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_ticket_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.19.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary Attendee tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1489 | WP-Appbox &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via appbox Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1489</link><description>The WP-Appbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's appbox shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1470 | Eclipse OMR: Null pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1470</link><description>In Eclipse OMR, from the initial contribution to version 0.4.0, some OMR internal port library and utilities consumers of z/OS atoe functions do not check their return values for NULL memory pointers or for memory allocation failures.  This can lead to NULL pointer dereference crashes.  Beginning in version 0.5.0, internal OMR consumers of atoe functions handle NULL return values and memory allocation failures correctly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1471 | Eclipse OMR: Buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1471</link><description>In Eclipse OMR versions 0.2.0 to 0.4.0, some of the z/OS atoe print functions use a constant length buffer for string conversion. If the input format string and arguments are larger than the buffer size then buffer overflow occurs.  Beginning in version 0.5.0, the conversion buffers are sized correctly and checked appropriately to prevent buffer overflows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12276 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12276</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to second-order SQL Injection via filenames in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with  access to upload files and manage filenames through a third-party plugin like a File Manager, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. The risk of this vulnerability is very minimal as it requires a user to be able to manipulate filenames in order to successfully exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12452 | Ziggeo &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12452</link><description>The Ziggeo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ziggeo_event' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13353 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13353</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 via several widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13461 | Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13461</link><description>The Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'autoship-create-scheduled-order-action' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13648 | Maps for WP &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13648</link><description>The Maps for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'MapOnePoint' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0727 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0727</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length in one packet smaller than the data 
request size of the other packet. A possible workaround is to disable 
HTTP PUT support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0728 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0728</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length smaller than the data request size. A
 possible workaround is to disable HTTP PUT support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1410 | Events Calendar Made Simple – Pie Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via piecal Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1410</link><description>The Events Calendar Made Simple – Pie Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's piecal shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0726 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0726</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service by specially 
crafted packets. The core issue is missing closing of a file in case of 
an error condition, resulting in the 404 error for each further file 
request. Users can work-around the issue by disabling the PUT request 
support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13314 | Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel &amp;lt; 2.7.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13314</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel  WordPress plugin before 2.7.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13585 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt; 4.12.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13585</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite  WordPress plugin before 4.12.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11260 | Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! &amp;lt;= 6.6.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via Event Status Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11260</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the active_status parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 05:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13235 | Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13235</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'language' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13379 | C9 Admin Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13379</link><description>The C9 Admin Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13388 | TCBD Tooltip &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13388</link><description>The TCBD Tooltip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcbdtooltip_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13537 | C9 Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13537</link><description>The C9 Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.7. This is due the plugin containing a publicly accessible composer-setup.php file with error display enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13672 | Mini Course Generator | Embed mini-courses and interactive content &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13672</link><description>The Mini Course Generator | Embed mini-courses and interactive content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mcg' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13751 | 3D Photo Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13751</link><description>The 3D Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'des[]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13818 | Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.9 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Log Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13818</link><description>The Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3.9 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information about users contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13883 | WPUpper Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 3.51 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom CSS Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13883</link><description>The WPUpper Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.51. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_custom_css_request' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject custom CSS to modify a site via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1406 | Newpost Catch &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via npc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1406</link><description>The Newpost Catch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's npc shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1407 | AMO Team Showcase &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via amoteam_skills Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1407</link><description>The AMO Team Showcase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's amoteam_skills shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38657 | External control of a file name in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.4 and Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.3 allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38657</link><description>External control of a file name in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.4 and Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1001 | Medixant RadiAnt DICOM Viewer Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1001</link><description>Medixant RadiAnt DICOM Viewer is vulnerable due to failure of the update mechanism to verify the update server's certificate which could allow an attacker to alter network traffic and carry out a machine-in-the-middle attack (MITM). An attacker could modify the server's response and deliver a malicious update to the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27100 | An authenticated user can crash lakeFS by exhausting server memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27100</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms your object storage into a Git-like repository. In affected versions an authenticated user can crash lakeFS by exhausting server memory.  This is an authenticated denial-of-service issue. This problem has been patched in version 1.50.0. Users on versions 1.49.1 and below are affected. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should either set the environment variable `LAKEFS_BLOCKSTORE_S3_DISABLE_PRE_SIGNED_MULTIPART` to `true` or configure the `disable_pre_signed_multipart` key to true in their config yaml.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>