<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-54016 | compression bomb attack in Apache Seata Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54016</link><description>Improper Handling of Highly Compressed Data (Data Amplification) vulnerability in Apache Seata (incubating).

This issue affects Apache Seata (incubating): through &lt;=2.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47552 | Apache Seata (incubating): Deserialization of untrusted Data in jraft mode in Apache Seata Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47552</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Seata (incubating).

This issue affects Apache Seata (incubating): from 2.0.0 before 2.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.2.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2505 | Age Gate &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Unauthenticated Local PHP File Inclusion via &amp;#x27;lang&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2505</link><description>The Age Gate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local PHP File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.3 via the 'lang' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 07:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12016 | SQLi in CM Informatics&amp;#x27; CM News</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12016</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CM Informatics CM News allows SQL Injection.This issue affects CM News: through 6.0.





NOTE: The vendor was contacted and it was learned that the product is not supported.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 07:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1385 | Fail input validation in clickhouse-library-bridge API could lead to RCE under specific configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1385</link><description>When the library bridge feature is enabled, the clickhouse-library-bridge exposes an HTTP API on localhost. This allows clickhouse-server to dynamically load a library from a specified path and execute it in an isolated process. Combined with the ClickHouse table engine functionality that permits file uploads to specific directories, a misconfigured server can be exploited by an attacker with privilege to access to both table engines to execute arbitrary code on the ClickHouse server.

You can check if your ClickHouse server is vulnerable to this vulnerability by inspecting the configuration file and confirming if the following setting is enabled:


   9019</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 07:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2108 | 140+ Widgets | Xpro Addons For Elementor – FREE &amp;lt;= 1.4.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Site Title&amp;#x27; widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2108</link><description>The 140+ Widgets | Xpro Addons For Elementor – FREE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘Site Title’ widget's 'title_tag' and 'html_tag' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 07:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13875 | WP Programmmanager &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13875</link><description>The WP-PManager WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13876 | Meintopf &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13876</link><description>The mEintopf WordPress plugin through 0.2.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13877 | Passbeemedia Web Push Notifications &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13877</link><description>The Passbeemedia Web Push Notification WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13878 | SpotBot &amp;lt;= 0.1.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13878</link><description>The SpotBot WordPress plugin through 0.1.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13880 | My Quota &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13880</link><description>The My Quota WordPress plugin through 1.0.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13881 | LinkMyPosts &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13881</link><description>The Link My Posts WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22228 | CVE-2025-22228: Spring Security BCryptPasswordEncoder does not enforce maximum password length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22228</link><description>BCryptPasswordEncoder.matches(CharSequence,String) will incorrectly return true for passwords larger than 72 characters as long as the first 72 characters are the same.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 05:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1314 | Custom Twitter Feeds &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Cache Reset via ctf_clear_cache_admin Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1314</link><description>The Custom Twitter Feeds – A Tweets Widget or X Feed Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ctf_clear_cache_admin() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin's cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 05:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1766 | Event Manager, Events Calendar, Tickets, Registrations – Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.24 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1766</link><description>The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Tickets, Registrations – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'payment_complete' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.24. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the status of ticket payments to 'completed', possibly resulting in financial loss.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 05:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1770 | Event Manager, Events Calendar, Tickets, Registrations – Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1770</link><description>The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Tickets, Registrations – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.24 via the 'style' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 05:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30259 | The WhatsApp cloud service before late 2024 did not block certain crafted PDF content that can defeat a sandbox protection mechanism and con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30259</link><description>The WhatsApp cloud service before late 2024 did not block certain crafted PDF content that can defeat a sandbox protection mechanism and consequently allow remote access to messaging applications by third parties, as exploited in the wild in 2024 for installation of Android malware associated with BIGPRETZEL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 23:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55009 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AutoBib - Bibliographic collection management system 3.1.140 and earlier allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55009</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AutoBib - Bibliographic collection management system 3.1.140 and earlier allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of a victim's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the WCE=topFrame&amp;amp;WCU= parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26816 | A vulnerability in Intrexx Portal Server 12.0.2 and earlier which was classified as problematic potentially allows users with particular per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26816</link><description>A vulnerability in Intrexx Portal Server 12.0.2 and earlier which was classified as problematic potentially allows users with particular permissions under certain conditions to see potentially sensitive data from a different user context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27774 | Applio allows SSRF and file write in model_download.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27774</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.7 and prior are vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) and file write in `model_download.py` (line 156 in 3.2.7). The blind SSRF allows for sending requests on behalf of Applio server and can be leveraged to probe for other vulnerabilities on the server itself or on other back-end systems on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach. The blind SSRF can also be coupled with the an arbitrary file read (e.g., CVE-2025-27784) to read files from hosts on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach, which would make it a full SSRF. The file write allows for writing files on the server, which can be coupled with other vulnerabilities, for example an unsafe deserialization, to achieve remote code execution on the Applio server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27775 | Applio allows SSRF and file write in model_download.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27775</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.7 and prior are vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) and file write in `model_download.py` (line 143 in 3.2.7). The blind SSRF allows for sending requests on behalf of Applio server and can be leveraged to probe for other vulnerabilities on the server itself or on other back-end systems on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach. The file write allows for writing files on the server, which can be coupled with other vulnerabilities, for example an unsafe deserialization, to achieve remote code execution on the Applio server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27776 | Applio allows SSRF and file write in model_download.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27776</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.7 and prior are vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) and file write in `model_download.py` (line 240 in 3.2.7). The blind SSRF allows for sending requests on behalf of Applio server and can be leveraged to probe for other vulnerabilities on the server itself or on other back-end systems on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach. The blind SSRF can also be coupled with the arbitrary file read CVE-2025-27784 to read files from hosts on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach, which would make it a full SSRF. The file write allows for writing files on the server, which can be coupled with other vulnerabilities, for example an unsafe deserialization, to achieve remote code execution on the Applio server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27777 | Applio allows SSRF and file write in model_download.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27777</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.7 and prior are vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) in `model_download.py` (line 195 in 3.2.7). The blind SSRF allows for sending requests on behalf of Applio server and can be leveraged to probe for other vulnerabilities on the server itself or on other back-end systems on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach. The blind SSRF can also be coupled with a arbitrary file read (e.g., CVE-2025-27784) to read files from hosts on the internal network, that the Applio server can reach, which would make it a full SSRF. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27778 | Applio allows unsafe deserialization in infer.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27778</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization in `infer.py`. The issue can lead to remote code execution. As of time of publication, a fix is available on the `main` branch of the Applio repository but not attached to a numbered release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27779 | Applio allows unsafe deserialization in model_blender.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27779</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization in `model_blender.py` lines 20 and 21. `model_fusion_a` and `model_fusion_b` from voice_blender.py take user-supplied input (e.g. a path to a model) and pass that value to the `run_model_blender_script` and later to `model_blender` function, which loads these two models with `torch.load` in `model_blender.py (on lines 20-21 in 3.2.8-bugfix), which is vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The issue can lead to remote code execution. A patch is available on the `main` branch of the Applio repository.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27782 | Applio allows arbitrary file write in inference.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27782</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to arbitrary file write in inference.py. This issue may lead to writing arbitrary files on the Applio server. It can also be used in conjunction with an unsafe deserialization to achieve remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27783 | Applio allows arbitrary file write in train.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27783</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to arbitrary file write in train.py. This issue may lead to writing arbitrary files on the Applio server. It can also be used in conjunction with an unsafe deserialization to achieve remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27784 | Applio allows arbitrary file read in train.py export_pth function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27784</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to arbitrary file read in train.py's `export_pth` function. This issue may lead to reading arbitrary files on the Applio server. It can also be used in conjunction with blind server-side request forgery to read files from servers on the internal network that the Applio server has access to. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27786 | Applio allows arbitrary file removal in core.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27786</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to arbitrary file removal in core.py. `output_tts_path` in tts.py takes arbitrary user input and passes it to `run_tts_script` function in core.py, which checks if the path in `output_tts_path` exists, and if yes, removes that path, which leads to arbitrary file removal. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27787 | Applio allows a DoS in restart.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27787</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to denial of service (DoS) in restart.py. `model_name` in train.py takes user input, and passes it to the `stop_train` function in restart.py, which uses it construct a path to a folder with `config.json`. That `config.json` is opened and the list of values under "process_pids" are read. Next all the process IDs listed in the JSON are killed. Using one of the arbitrary file writes, one can  write to `logs/foobar` a `config.json` file, which contains a list of process IDs. Then one can access this endpoint to kill these processes. Since an attacker can't know what process is running on which process ID, they can send a list of hundreds of process IDs, which can kill the process that applio is using to run, as well as other, potentially important processes, which leads to DoS. Note that constructing a path with user input also enables path traversal. For example, by supplying "../../" in `model_name` one can access `config.json` freom locations two folders down on the server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30092 | Intrexx Portal Server 12.x &lt;= 12.0.2 and 11.x &lt;= 11.9.2 allows XSS in multiple Velocity scripts.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30092</link><description>Intrexx Portal Server 12.x &lt;= 12.0.2 and 11.x &lt;= 11.9.2 allows XSS in multiple Velocity scripts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27785 | Applio allows arbitrary file read in train.py export_index function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27785</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to arbitrary file read in train.py's `export_index` function. This issue may lead to reading arbitrary files on the Applio server. It can also be used in conjunction with blind server-side request forgery to read files from servers on the internal network that the Applio server has access to. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27781 | Applio allows unsafe deserialization in inference.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27781</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization in inference.py. `model_file` in inference.py as well as `model_file` in tts.py take user-supplied input (e.g. a path to a model) and pass that value to the `change_choices` and later to `get_speakers_id` function, which loads that model with `torch.load` in inference.py (line 326 in 3.2.8-bugfix), which is vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The issue can lead to remote code execution. A patch is available on the `main` branch of the repository.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27780 | Applio allows unsafe deserialization in model_information.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27780</link><description>Applio is a voice conversion tool. Versions 3.2.8-bugfix and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization in model_information.py. `model_name` in model_information.py takes user-supplied input (e.g. a path to a model) and pass that value to the `run_model_information_script` and later to `model_information` function, which loads that model with `torch.load` in rvc/train/process/model_information.py (on line 16 in 3.2.8-bugfix), which is vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The issue can lead to remote code execution. A patch is available in the `main` branch of the repository.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30258 | In GnuPG before 2.5.5, if a user chooses to import a certificate with certain crafted subkey data that lacks a valid backsig or that has inc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30258</link><description>In GnuPG before 2.5.5, if a user chooses to import a certificate with certain crafted subkey data that lacks a valid backsig or that has incorrect usage flags, the user loses the ability to verify signatures made from certain other signing keys, aka a "verification DoS."</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27705 | There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.53.
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27705</link><description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.53.
Attackers with system administrator permissions can interfere with another
system administrator’s use of the management console when the second
administrator logs in.  Attack complexity is high, attack requirements are
present, privileges required are none, user interaction is required. The impact
to confidentiality is low, the impact to availability is none, and the impact
to system integrity is none.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27704 | There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.53.
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27704</link><description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.53.
Attackers with system administrator permissions can interfere with another
system administrator’s use of the management console when the second
administrator logs in.  Attack complexity is high, attack requirements are
present, privileges required are none, user interaction is required. The impact
to confidentiality is low, the impact to availability is none, and the impact
to system integrity is none.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27415 | Nuxt allows DOS via cache poisoning with payload rendering response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27415</link><description>Nuxt is an open-source web development framework for Vue.js. Prior to 3.16.0, by sending a crafted HTTP request to a server behind an CDN, it is possible in some circumstances to poison the CDN cache and highly impacts the availability of a site. It is possible to craft a request, such as https://mysite.com/?/_payload.json which will be rendered as JSON. If the CDN in front of a Nuxt site ignores the query string when determining whether to cache a route, then this JSON response could be served to future visitors to the site. An attacker can perform this attack to a vulnerable site in order to make a site unavailable indefinitely. It is also possible in the case where the cache will be reset to make a small script to send a request each X seconds (=caching duration) so that the cache is permanently poisoned making the site completely unavailable. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.16.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2476 | Use after free in Lens in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.117 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2476</link><description>Use after free in Lens in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.117 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2536 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on Liferay Portal 7.4.3.82 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2536</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on Liferay Portal 7.4.3.82 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 update 82 through update 92 in the Frontend JS module's layout-taglib/__liferay__/index.js allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via toastData parameter</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7631 | Openshift-console: openshift console: path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7631</link><description>A flaw was found in the OpenShift Console, an endpoint for plugins to serve resources in multiple languages: /locales/resources.json. This endpoint's lng and ns parameters are used to construct a filepath in pkg/plugins/handlers unsafely.go#L112 Because of this unsafe filepath construction, an authenticated user can manipulate the path to retrieve any JSON files on the console's pod by using sequences of ../ and valid directory paths.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57061 | An issue in Termius Version 9.9.0 through v.9.16.0 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via the insecure Electro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57061</link><description>An issue in Termius Version 9.9.0 through v.9.16.0 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via the insecure Electron Fuses configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51459 | IBM InfoSphere Server Information command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51459</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a local user to execute privileged commands due to the improper handling of permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25132 | Openshift-dedicated: hive: hibernation controller denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25132</link><description>A flaw was found in the Hive hibernation controller component of OpenShift Dedicated. The ClusterDeployment.hive.openshift.io/v1 resource can be created with the spec.installed field set to true, regardless of the installation status, and a positive timespan for the spec.hibernateAfter value. If a ClusterSync.hiveinternal.openshift.io/v1alpha1 resource is also created, the hive hibernation controller will enter the reconciliation loop leading to a panic when accessing a non-existing field in the ClusterDeployment’s status section, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29926 | The WikiManager REST API allows any user to create wikis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29926</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to 15.10.15, 16.4.6, and 16.10.0, any user can exploit the WikiManager REST API to create a new wiki, where the user could become an administrator and so performs other attacks on the farm. Note that this REST API is not bundled in XWiki Standard by default: it needs to be installed manually through the extension manager. The problem has been patched in versions 15.10.15, 16.4.6 and 16.10.0 of the REST module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29924 | XWiki uses the wrong wiki reference in AuthorizationManager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29924</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to 15.10.14, 16.4.6, and 16.10.0-rc-1, it's possible for an user to get access to private information through the REST API - but could also be through another API - when a sub wiki is using "Prevent unregistered users to view pages". The vulnerability only affects subwikis, and it only concerns specific right options such as "Prevent unregistered users to view pages". or "Prevent unregistered users to edit pages". It's possible to detect the vulnerability by enabling "Prevent unregistered users to view pages" and then trying to access a page through the REST API without using any credentials. The vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.10.14, 16.4.6 and 16.10.0RC1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29925 | XWiki allows unregistered users to access private pages information through REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29925</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to 15.10.14, 16.4.6, and 16.10.0-rc-1, protected pages are listed when requesting the REST endpoints /rest/wikis/[wikiName]/pages even if the user doesn't have view rights on them. It's particularly true if the entire wiki is protected with "Prevent unregistered user to view pages": the endpoint would still list the pages of the wiki, though only for the main wiki. The problem has been patched in XWiki 15.10.14, 16.4.6, 16.10.0RC1. In those versions the endpoint can still be requested but the result is filtered out based on pages rights.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29405 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /admin/template.php of emlog pro 2.5.0 and pro 2.5.* allows attackers to execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29405</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /admin/template.php of emlog pro 2.5.0 and pro 2.5.* allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0431 | Enterprise Protection Backslash URL Rewrite Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0431</link><description>Enterprise Protection contains a vulnerability in URL rewriting that allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to send an email which bypasses URL protections impacting the integrity of recipient's email.  This occurs due to improper filtering of backslashes within URLs and affects all versions of 8.21, 8.20 and 8.18 prior to 8.21.0 patch 5115, 8.20.6 patch 5114 and 8.18.6 patch 5113 respectively.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53967 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (DOM-based XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53967</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's browser session. By manipulating the DOM environment in the victim's browser, a low privileged attacker can inject malicious scripts that are executed by the victim's browser. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, typically in the form of following a malicious link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53968 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (DOM-based XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53968</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's browser session. By manipulating the DOM environment in the victim's browser, a low privileged attacker can inject malicious scripts that are executed by the victim's browser. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, typically in the form of following a malicious link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53969 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (DOM-based XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53969</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's browser session. By manipulating the DOM environment in the victim's browser, a low privileged attacker can inject malicious scripts that are executed by the victim's browser. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, typically in the form of following a malicious link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53970 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53970</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29118 | Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the src parameter in the function sub_47D878.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29118</link><description>Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the src parameter in the function sub_47D878.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30153 | Improper Handling of Highly Compressed Data (Data Amplification) in github.com/getkin/kin-openapi/openapi3filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30153</link><description>kin-openapi is a Go project for handling OpenAPI files. Prior to 0.131.0, when validating a request with a multipart/form-data schema, if the OpenAPI schema allows it, an attacker can upload a crafted ZIP file (e.g., a ZIP bomb), causing the server to consume all available system memory. The root cause comes from the ZipFileBodyDecoder, which is registered automatically by the module (contrary to what the documentation says). This vulnerability is fixed in 0.131.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30152 | Sylius PayPal Plugin has an Order Manipulation Vulnerability after PayPal Checkout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30152</link><description>The Syliud PayPal Plugin is the Sylius Core Team’s plugin for the PayPal Commerce Platform. Prior to 1.6.2, 1.7.2, and 2.0.2, a discovered vulnerability allows users to modify their shopping cart after completing the PayPal Checkout process and payment authorization. If a user initiates a PayPal transaction from a product page or the cart page and then returns to the order summary page, they can still manipulate the cart contents before finalizing the order. As a result, the order amount in Sylius may be higher than the amount actually captured by PayPal, leading to a scenario where merchants deliver products or services without full payment. The issue is fixed in versions: 1.6.2, 1.7.2, 2.0.2 and above.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26486 | Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm, Use of Password Hash 
With Insufficient Computational Effort, Use of Weak Hash, Use of a 
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26486</link><description>Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm, Use of Password Hash 
With Insufficient Computational Effort, Use of Weak Hash, Use of a 
One-Way Hash with a Predictable Salt vulnerability in Beta80 Life 1st 
allows an 
Attacker to Bruteforce User
Passwords or find a collision to gain access to a target application using BETA80
“Life 1st Identity Manager” as a service for authentication.This issue affects Life 1st: 1.5.2.14234.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30144 | Fast-JWT Improperly Validates iss Claims</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30144</link><description>fast-jwt provides fast JSON Web Token (JWT) implementation. Prior to 5.0.6, the fast-jwt library does not properly validate the iss claim based on the RFC 7519. The iss (issuer) claim validation within the fast-jwt library permits an array of strings as a valid iss value. This design flaw enables a potential attack where a malicious actor crafts a JWT with an iss claim structured as ['https://attacker-domain/', 'https://valid-iss']. Due to the permissive validation, the JWT will be deemed valid. Furthermore, if the application relies on external libraries like get-jwks that do not independently validate the iss claim, the attacker can leverage this vulnerability to forge a JWT that will be accepted by the victim application. Essentially, the attacker can insert their own domain into the iss array, alongside the legitimate issuer, and bypass the intended security checks. This issue is fixed in 5.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29770 | vLLM denial of service via outlines unbounded cache on disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29770</link><description>vLLM is a high-throughput and memory-efficient inference and serving engine for LLMs. The outlines library is one of the backends used by vLLM to support structured output (a.k.a. guided decoding). Outlines provides an optional cache for its compiled grammars on the local filesystem. This cache has been on by default in vLLM. Outlines is also available by default through the OpenAI compatible API server. The affected code in vLLM is vllm/model_executor/guided_decoding/outlines_logits_processors.py, which unconditionally uses the cache from outlines. A malicious user can send a stream of very short decoding requests with unique schemas, resulting in an addition to the cache for each request. This can result in a Denial of Service if the filesystem runs out of space. Note that even if vLLM was configured to use a different backend by default, it is still possible to choose outlines on a per-request basis using the guided_decoding_backend key of the extra_body field of the request. This issue applies only to the V0 engine and is fixed in 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29783 | vLLM  Allows Remote Code Execution via Mooncake Integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29783</link><description>vLLM is a high-throughput and memory-efficient inference and serving engine for LLMs. When vLLM is configured to use Mooncake, unsafe deserialization exposed directly over ZMQ/TCP on all network interfaces will allow attackers to execute remote code on distributed hosts. This is a remote code execution vulnerability impacting any deployments using Mooncake to distribute KV across distributed hosts. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30196 | Jenkins AnchorChain Plugin 1.0 does not limit URL schemes for links it creates based on workspace content, allowing the `javascript:` scheme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30196</link><description>Jenkins AnchorChain Plugin 1.0 does not limit URL schemes for links it creates based on workspace content, allowing the `javascript:` scheme, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to control the input file for the Anchor Chain post-build step.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30197 | Jenkins Zoho QEngine Plugin 1.0.29.vfa_cc23396502 and earlier does not mask the QEngine API Key form field, increasing the potential for att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30197</link><description>Jenkins Zoho QEngine Plugin 1.0.29.vfa_cc23396502 and earlier does not mask the QEngine API Key form field, increasing the potential for attackers to observe and capture it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1758 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Progress LoadMaster allows : Buffer OverflowThis issue affects:

* LoadMaster: 7.2.40.0 and above...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1758</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Progress LoadMaster allows : Buffer OverflowThis issue affects:

* LoadMaster: 7.2.40.0 and above

* ECS: All versions

* Multi-Tenancy: 7.1.35.4 and above</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23382 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.26, contain(s) an Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23382</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.26, contain(s) an Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure.c</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26485 | The Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor 
vulnerability impacting Beta80 Life 1st Identity Manager  allows User 
Enume...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26485</link><description>The Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor 
vulnerability impacting Beta80 Life 1st Identity Manager  allows User 
Enumeration using Authentication Rest APIs. Affected: Life 1st version 
1.5.2.14234. Different error messages are returned to failed authentication attempts 
in case of the usage of a wrong password or a non existent user. 


This issue affects Life 1st: 1.5.2.14234.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29137 | Tenda AC7 V1.0 V15.03.06.44 found a buffer overflow caused by the timeZone parameter in the form_fast_setting_wifi_set function, which can c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29137</link><description>Tenda AC7 V1.0 V15.03.06.44 found a buffer overflow caused by the timeZone parameter in the form_fast_setting_wifi_set function, which can cause RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29401 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /views/plugin.php of emlog pro v2.5.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29401</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /views/plugin.php of emlog pro v2.5.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2324 | A MOVEit Transfer user configured as a Shared Account can gain unintended List permissions on a folder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2324</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability for users configured as Shared Accounts in Progress MOVEit Transfer (SFTP module) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects MOVEit Transfer: from 2023.1.0 before 2023.1.12, from 2024.0.0 before 2024.0.8, from 2024.1.0 before 2024.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26475 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.26, Enables Live-Restore setting which enhances security by keeping cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26475</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.26, Enables Live-Restore setting which enhances security by keeping containers running during daemon restarts, reducing attack exposure, preventing accidental misconfigurations, and ensuring security controls remain active.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30154 | Multiple Reviewdog actions were compromised during a specific time period</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30154</link><description>reviewdog/action-setup is a GitHub action that installs reviewdog. reviewdog/action-setup@v1 was compromised March 11, 2025, between 18:42 and 20:31 UTC, with malicious code added that dumps exposed secrets to Github Actions Workflow Logs. Other reviewdog actions that use `reviewdog/action-setup@v1` that would also be compromised, regardless of version or pinning method, are reviewdog/action-shellcheck, reviewdog/action-composite-template, reviewdog/action-staticcheck, reviewdog/action-ast-grep, and reviewdog/action-typos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42176 | HCL MyXalytics is affected by concurrent login vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42176</link><description>HCL MyXalytics is affected by concurrent login vulnerability. A concurrent login vulnerability occurs when simultaneous active sessions are allowed for a single credential allowing an attacker to potentially obtain access to a user's account or sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1472 | Unauthorized View Access to Site Statistics and Team Statistics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1472</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8 fail to properly perform authorization of the Viewer role which allows an attacker with the Viewer role configured with No Access to Reporting to still view team and site statistics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55551 | An issue was discovered in Exasol jdbc driver 24.2.0. Attackers can inject malicious parameters into the JDBC URL, triggering JNDI injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55551</link><description>An issue was discovered in Exasol jdbc driver 24.2.0. Attackers can inject malicious parameters into the JDBC URL, triggering JNDI injection during the process when the JDBC Driver uses this URL to connect to the database. This can further lead to remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2512 | File Away &amp;lt;= 3.9.9.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated File Upload via upload Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2512</link><description>The File Away plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability check and missing file type validation in the upload() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12920 | FoodBakery | Delivery Restaurant Directory WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Missing Authorization in Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12920</link><description>The FoodBakery | Delivery Restaurant Directory WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the foodbakery_var_backup_file_delete, foodbakery_widget_file_delete, theme_option_save, export_widget_settings, ajax_import_widget_data, foodbakery_var_settings_backup_generate, foodbakery_var_backup_file_restore, and theme_option_rest_all functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files, update theme options, export widget options, import widget options, generate backups, restore backups, and reset theme options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13442 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13442</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 5.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to (1) performing a post-booking auto-login or (2) updating their profile details (e.g. password). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to (1) login as an arbitrary user if their email address is known or (2) change an arbitrary user's password, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13933 | FoodBakery | Delivery Restaurant Directory WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery in Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13933</link><description>The FoodBakery | Delivery Restaurant Directory WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the foodbakery_var_backup_file_delete, foodbakery_widget_file_delete, theme_option_save, export_widget_settings, ajax_import_widget_data, foodbakery_var_settings_backup_generate, foodbakery_var_backup_file_restore, and theme_option_rest_all functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, update theme options, export widget options, import widget options, generate backups, restore backups, and reset theme options via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45644 | IBM Security ReaQta file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45644</link><description>IBM Security ReaQta 3.12 allows a privileged user to upload or transfer files of dangerous types that can be automatically processed within the product's environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2511 | AHAthat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2511</link><description>The AHAthat Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27018 | Apache Airflow MySQL Provider: SQL injection in MySQL provider core function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27018</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Airflow MySQL Provider.

When user triggered a DAG with dump_sql or load_sql functions they could pass a table parameter from a UI, that could cause SQL injection by running SQL that was not intended.
It could lead to data corruption, modification and others.
This issue affects Apache Airflow MySQL Provider: before 6.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.2.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 09:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12136 | Improper Access Control in Elfatek Elektronics&amp;#x27; ANKA JPD-00028</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12136</link><description>Missing Critical Step in Authentication vulnerability in Elfatek Elektronics ANKA JPD-00028 allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects ANKA JPD-00028: through 19.03.2025.

NOTE: The vendor did not inform about the completion of the fixing process within the specified time. The CVE will be updated when new information becomes available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12137 | Authentication Bypass in Elfatek Elektronics&amp;#x27; ANKA JPD-00028</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12137</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability in Elfatek Elektronics ANKA JPD-00028 allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects ANKA JPD-00028: through 19.03.2025.


NOTE: The vendor did not inform about the completion of the fixing process within the specified time. The CVE will be updated when new information becomes available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13790 | MinimogWP – The High Converting eCommerce WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.7.0 - Unauthenticated Local PHP File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13790</link><description>The MinimogWP – The High Converting eCommerce WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.0 via the 'template' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 08:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13410 | CozyStay &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 and TinySalt &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection in ajax_handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13410</link><description>The CozyStay and TinySalt plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0, and in all versions up to, and including 3.9.0, respectively, via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'ajax_handler' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 07:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13412 | CozyStay &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Action Execution in ajax_handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13412</link><description>The CozyStay theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary actions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 07:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1232 | Site Reviews &amp;lt; 7.2.5 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1232</link><description>The Site Reviews WordPress plugin before 7.2.5 does not properly sanitise and escape some of its Review fields, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Stored XSS attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30235 | Shearwater SecurEnvoy SecurAccess Enrol before 9.4.515 is intended to disable accounts that have had more than 10 failed authentication atte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30235</link><description>Shearwater SecurEnvoy SecurAccess Enrol before 9.4.515 is intended to disable accounts that have had more than 10 failed authentication attempts, but instead allows hundreds of failed authentication attempts, because concurrent attempts are mishandled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30236 | Shearwater SecurEnvoy SecurAccess Enrol before 9.4.515 allows authentication through only a six-digit TOTP code (skipping a password check) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30236</link><description>Shearwater SecurEnvoy SecurAccess Enrol before 9.4.515 allows authentication through only a six-digit TOTP code (skipping a password check) if an HTTP POST request contains a SESSION parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50629 | Improper encoding or escaping of output vulnerability in the webapi component in Synology BeeStation Manager (BSM) before 1.1-65374, Synolog...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50629</link><description>Improper encoding or escaping of output vulnerability in the webapi component in Synology BeeStation Manager (BSM) before 1.1-65374, Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 6.2.4-25556-8, 7.1.1-42962-7, 7.2-64570-4, 7.2.1-69057-6 and 7.2.2-72806-1 and Synology Unified Controller (DSMUC) before 3.1.4-23079 allows remote attackers to read limited files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 05:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50630 | Missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in the webapi component in Synology Drive Server before 3.0.4-12699, 3.2.1-23280,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50630</link><description>Missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in the webapi component in Synology Drive Server before 3.0.4-12699, 3.2.1-23280, 3.5.0-26085 and 3.5.1-26102 allows remote attackers to obtain administrator credentials via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 05:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50631 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in the system syncing daemon in Synology ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50631</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in the system syncing daemon in Synology Drive Server before 3.0.4-12699, 3.2.1-23280, 3.5.0-26085 and 3.5.1-26102 allows remote attackers to inject SQL commands, limited to write operations, via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 05:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12922 | Altair &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update via pp_import_current</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12922</link><description>The Altair theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check within functions.php in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 05:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12295 | BoomBox Theme Extensions &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Password Reset/Account Takeover in boombox_ajax_reset_password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12295</link><description>The BoomBox Theme Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password through the 'boombox_ajax_reset_password' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level privileges and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 04:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2290 | LifterLMS &amp;lt;= 8.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Post Trashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2290</link><description>The LifterLMS – WP LMS for eLearning, Online Courses, &amp; Quizzes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Post Trashing due to a missing capability check on the delete_access_plan function and the related AJAX calls in all versions up to, and including, 8.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change status to "Trash" for every published post, therefore limiting the availability of the website's content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 04:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30234 | SmartOS, as used in Triton Data Center and other products, has static host SSH keys in the 60f76fd2-143f-4f57-819b-1ae32684e81b image (a Deb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30234</link><description>SmartOS, as used in Triton Data Center and other products, has static host SSH keys in the 60f76fd2-143f-4f57-819b-1ae32684e81b image (a Debian 12 LX zone image from 2024-07-26).</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 04:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10442 | Off-by-one error vulnerability in the transmission component in Synology Replication Service before 1.0.12-0066, 1.2.2-0353 and 1.3.0-0423 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10442</link><description>Off-by-one error vulnerability in the transmission component in Synology Replication Service before 1.0.12-0066, 1.2.2-0353 and 1.3.0-0423 and Synology Unified Controller (DSMUC) before 3.1.4-23079 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, potentially leading to a broader impact across the system via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11131 | A vulnerability regarding out-of-bounds read is found in the video interface. This allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11131</link><description>A vulnerability regarding out-of-bounds read is found in the video interface. This allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.2.0-0525 may be affected: BC500, CC400W and TC500.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10441 | Improper encoding or escaping of output vulnerability in the system plugin daemon in Synology BeeStation Manager (BSM) before 1.1-65374, Syn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10441</link><description>Improper encoding or escaping of output vulnerability in the system plugin daemon in Synology BeeStation Manager (BSM) before 1.1-65374, Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 6.2.4-25556-8, 7.1.1-42962-7, 7.2-64570-4, 7.2.1-69057-6 and 7.2.2-72806-1 and Synology Unified Controller (DSMUC) before 3.1.4-23079 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 02:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10444 | Improper certificate validation vulnerability in the LDAP utilities in Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 7.1.1-42962-8, 7.2.1-69057-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10444</link><description>Improper certificate validation vulnerability in the LDAP utilities in Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 7.1.1-42962-8, 7.2.1-69057-7 and 7.2.2-72806-3 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to hijack the authentication of administrators via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 02:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10445 | Improper certificate validation vulnerability in the update functionality in Synology BeeStation Manager (BSM) before 1.1-65374, Synology Di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10445</link><description>Improper certificate validation vulnerability in the update functionality in Synology BeeStation Manager (BSM) before 1.1-65374, Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 6.2.4-25556-8, 7.1.1-42962-7, 7.2-64570-4, 7.2.1-69057-6 and 7.2.2-72806-1 and Synology Unified Controller (DSMUC) before 3.1.4-23079 allows remote attackers to write limited files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 02:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57151 | SQL Injection vulnerability in rainrocka xinhu v.2.6.5 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the inputAction.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57151</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in rainrocka xinhu v.2.6.5 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the inputAction.php file and the saveAjax function</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12563 | s2Member Pro &amp;lt;= 250214 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12563</link><description>The s2Member Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 250214 via the 'template' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30140 | An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. A Public Domain name is Used for the Internal Domain Name. It uses an unregistered...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30140</link><description>An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. A Public Domain name is Used for the Internal Domain Name. It uses an unregistered public domain name as an internal domain, creating a security risk. This domain was not owned by GNET originally, allowing an attacker to register it and potentially intercept sensitive device traffic (it has since been registered by the vulnerability discoverer). If the dashcam or related services attempt to resolve this domain over the public Internet instead of locally, it could lead to data exfiltration or man-in-the-middle attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30137 | An issue was discovered in the G-Net GNET APK 2.6.2. Hardcoded credentials exist in in APK for ports 9091 and 9092. The GNET mobile applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30137</link><description>An issue was discovered in the G-Net GNET APK 2.6.2. Hardcoded credentials exist in in APK for ports 9091 and 9092. The GNET mobile application contains hardcoded credentials that provide unauthorized access to the dashcam's API endpoints on ports 9091 and 9092. Once the GNET SSID is connected to, the attacker sends a crafted authentication command with TibetList and 000000 to list settings of the dashcam at port 9091. There's a separate set of credentials for port 9092 (stream) that is also exposed in cleartext: admin + tibet. For settings, the required credentials are adim + 000000.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:17:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30138 | An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. Managing Settings and Obtaining Sensitive Data and Sabotaging Car Battery can be p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30138</link><description>An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. Managing Settings and Obtaining Sensitive Data and Sabotaging Car Battery can be performed by unauthorized persons. It allows unauthorized users to modify critical system settings once connected to its network. Attackers can extract sensitive car and driver information, mute dashcam alerts to prevent detection, disable recording functionality, or even factory reset the device. Additionally, they can disable battery protection, causing the dashcam to drain the car battery when left on overnight. These actions not only compromise privacy but also pose potential physical harm by rendering the dashcam non-functional or causing vehicle battery failure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30139 | An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. Default credentials for SSID cannot be changed. It broadcasts a fixed SSID with de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30139</link><description>An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. Default credentials for SSID cannot be changed. It broadcasts a fixed SSID with default credentials that cannot be changed. This allows any nearby attacker to connect to the dashcam's network without restriction. Once connected, an attacker can sniff on connected devices such as the user's smartphone. The SSID is also always broadcasted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30141 | An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. One can Remotely Dump Video Footage and the Live Video Stream. It exposes API endp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30141</link><description>An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. One can Remotely Dump Video Footage and the Live Video Stream. It exposes API endpoints on ports 9091 and 9092 that allow remote access to recorded and live video feeds. An attacker who connects to the dashcam's network can retrieve all stored recordings and convert them from JDR format to MP4. Additionally, port 9092's RTSP stream can be accessed remotely, allowing real-time video feeds to be extracted without the owner's knowledge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30142 | An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. Bypassing of Device Pairing can occur. It uses MAC address verification as the sol...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30142</link><description>An issue was discovered on G-Net Dashcam BB GONX devices. Bypassing of Device Pairing can occur. It uses MAC address verification as the sole mechanism for recognizing paired devices, allowing attackers to bypass authentication. By capturing the MAC address of an already-paired device through ARP scanning or other means, an attacker can spoof the MAC address and connect to the dashcam without going through the pairing process. This enables full access to the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25040 | Failure to Properly Enforce Port ACLs on CPU generated packets in CX 9300 Switches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25040</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the port ACL functionality of AOS-CX software running on the HPE Aruba Networking CX 9300 Switch Series only and affects: 

     - AOS-CX 10.14.xxxx : All patches
     - AOS-CX 10.15.xxxx : 10.15.1000 and below 
The vulnerability is specific to traffic originated by the CX 9300 switch platform and could allow an attacker to bypass ACL rules applied to routed ports on egress. As a result, port ACLs are not correctly enforced, which could lead to unauthorized traffic flow and violations of security policies. Egress VLAN ACLs and Routed VLAN ACLs are not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 19:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25042 | Authenticated Access Control Vulnerability allows Sensitive Information Disclosure in AOS-CX REST Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25042</link><description>A vulnerability in the AOS-CX REST interface could allow an authenticated remote attacker with low privileges to view sensitive information. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to read encrypted credentials of other users on the switch, potentially leading to further unauthorized access or data breaches.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27080 | Authenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure exposes Credentials in AOS-CX Command Line Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27080</link><description>Vulnerabilities in the command line interface of AOS-CX could allow an authenticated remote attacker to expose sensitive information. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain unauthorized access to services outside of the impacted switch, potentially leading to lateral movement involving those services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29930 | imFAQ allows local file inclusion in seo.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29930</link><description>imFAQ is an advanced questions and answers management system for ImpressCMS. Prior to 1.0.1, if the $_GET['seoOp'] parameter is manipulated to include malicious input (e.g., seoOp=php://filter/read=convert.base64-encode/resource=/var/www/html/config.php), the application could allow an attacker to read sensitive files on the server (Local File Inclusion, LFI). The $_GET['seoOp'] and $_GET['seoArg'] parameters are directly used without sanitization or validation. This is partly mitigated by the fact that the ImpressCMS sensitive files are stored outside the web root, in a folder with a randomized name. The issue has been resolved in imFaq 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29907 | jsPDF Bypass Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29907</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 3.0.1, user control of the first argument of the addImage method results in CPU utilization and denial of service. If given the possibility to pass unsanitised image urls to the addImage method, a user can provide a harmful data-url that results in high CPU utilization and denial of service. Other affected methods are html and addSvgAsImage. The vulnerability was fixed in jsPDF 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21619 | GLPI allows SQL injection through the rules configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21619</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. An administrator user can perfom a SQL injection through the rules configuration forms. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.18.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24799 | GLPI allows unauthenticated SQL injection through the inventory endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24799</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. An unauthenticated user can perform a SQL injection through the inventory endpoint. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.18.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24801 | GLPI allows authenticated remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24801</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. An authenticated user can upload and force the execution of *.php files located on the GLPI server. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.18.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29790 | Contao allows cross-site scripting through SVG uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29790</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. Users can upload SVG files with malicious code, which is then executed in the back end and/or front end. This vulnerability is fixed in Contao 4.13.54, 5.3.30, or 5.5.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25595 | A lack of rate limiting in the login page of Safe App version a3.0.9 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25595</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the login page of Safe App version a3.0.9 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26137 | Systemic Risk Value &lt;=2.8.0 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via /GetFile.aspx?ReportUrl=. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26137</link><description>Systemic Risk Value &lt;=2.8.0 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via /GetFile.aspx?ReportUrl=. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this issue to read arbitrary system files by supplying a crafted file path, potentially exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26138 | Systemic Risk Value &lt;=2.8.0 is vulnerable to improper access control in /RiskValue/GroupingEntities/Controls/GetFile.aspx?ID=. Uploaded file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26138</link><description>Systemic Risk Value &lt;=2.8.0 is vulnerable to improper access control in /RiskValue/GroupingEntities/Controls/GetFile.aspx?ID=. Uploaded files are accessible via a predictable numerical ID parameter, allowing unauthorized users to increment or decrement the ID to access and download files they do not have permission to view.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2487 | 389-ds-base: null pointer dereference leads to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2487</link><description>A flaw was found in the 389-ds-base LDAP Server. This issue occurs when issuing a Modify DN LDAP operation through the ldap protocol, when the function return value is not tested and a NULL pointer is dereferenced. If a privileged user performs a ldap MODDN operation after a failed operation, it could lead to a Denial of Service (DoS) or system crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56346 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56346</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2 and 7.3 nimesis NIM master service could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands due to improper process controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56347 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56347</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2 and 7.3 nimsh service SSL/TLS protection mechanisms could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands due to improper process controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27688 | Dell ThinOS 2408 and prior, contains an improper permissions vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27688</link><description>Dell ThinOS 2408 and prior, contains an improper permissions vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57169 | A file upload bypass vulnerability exists in SOPlanning 1.53.00, specifically in /process/upload.php. This vulnerability allows remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57169</link><description>A file upload bypass vulnerability exists in SOPlanning 1.53.00, specifically in /process/upload.php. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass upload restrictions and potentially achieve remote code execution by uploading malicious files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57170 | SOPlanning 1.53.00 is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue in /process/upload.php. The "fichier_to_delete" parameter allows authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57170</link><description>SOPlanning 1.53.00 is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue in /process/upload.php. The "fichier_to_delete" parameter allows authenticated attackers to specify file paths containing directory traversal sequences (e.g., ../). This vulnerability enables attackers to delete arbitrary files outside the intended upload directory, potentially leading to denial of service or disruption of application functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25582 | yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the selectNoticeList() method at /xml/OaNoticeMapper.x...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25582</link><description>yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the selectNoticeList() method at /xml/OaNoticeMapper.xml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25586 | yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain an information disclosure vulnerability via the component /resources/application.yml.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25586</link><description>yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain an information disclosure vulnerability via the component /resources/application.yml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25589 | An XML external entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in the component /weixin/aes/XMLParse.java of yimioa before v2024.07.04 allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25589</link><description>An XML external entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in the component /weixin/aes/XMLParse.java of yimioa before v2024.07.04 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted XML file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25580 | yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the listNameBySql() method at /xml/UserMapper.xml.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25580</link><description>yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the listNameBySql() method at /xml/UserMapper.xml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25585 | Incorrect access control in the component /config/WebSecurityConfig.java of yimioa before v2024.07.04 allows unauthorized attackers to arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25585</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /config/WebSecurityConfig.java of yimioa before v2024.07.04 allows unauthorized attackers to arbitrarily modify Administrator passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25590 | yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /mapper/xml/AddressDao.xml.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25590</link><description>yimioa before v2024.07.04 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /mapper/xml/AddressDao.xml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30122 | An issue was discovered on ROADCAM X3 devices. It has a uniform default credential set that cannot be modified by users, making it easy for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30122</link><description>An issue was discovered on ROADCAM X3 devices. It has a uniform default credential set that cannot be modified by users, making it easy for attackers to gain unauthorized access to multiple devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30123 | An issue was discovered on ROADCAM X3 devices. The mobile app APK (Viidure) contains hardcoded FTP credentials for the FTPX user account, en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30123</link><description>An issue was discovered on ROADCAM X3 devices. The mobile app APK (Viidure) contains hardcoded FTP credentials for the FTPX user account, enabling attackers to gain unauthorized access and extract sensitive recorded footage from the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44314 | TastyIgniter 3.7.6 contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in the Orders Management System, allowing unauthorized users to update...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44314</link><description>TastyIgniter 3.7.6 contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in the Orders Management System, allowing unauthorized users to update order statuses. The issue occurs in the index_onUpdateStatus() function within Orders.php, which fails to verify if the user has permission to modify an order's status. This flaw can be exploited remotely, leading to unauthorized order manipulation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30114 | An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Bypassing of Device Pairing can occur. The pairing mechanism reli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30114</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Bypassing of Device Pairing can occur. The pairing mechanism relies solely on the connecting device's MAC address. By obtaining the MAC address through network scanning and spoofing it, an attacker can bypass the authentication process and gain full access to the dashcam's features without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30116 | An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Remotely Dumping of Video Footage and the Live Video Stream can o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30116</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Remotely Dumping of Video Footage and the Live Video Stream can occur. It allows remote attackers to access and download recorded video footage from the SD card via port 9091. Additionally, attackers can connect to port 9092 to stream the live video feed by bypassing the challenge-response authentication mechanism. This exposes sensitive location and personal data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30117 | An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Managing Settings and Obtaining Sensitive Data and Sabotaging the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30117</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Managing Settings and Obtaining Sensitive Data and Sabotaging the Car Battery can be performed by unauthorized parties. After bypassing the device pairing, an attacker can obtain sensitive user and vehicle information through the settings interface. Remote attackers can modify power management settings, disable recording, delete stored footage, and turn off battery protection, leading to potential denial-of-service conditions and vehicle battery drainage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2491 | Dromara ujcms Edit Template File Page WebFileTemplateController.java update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2491</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Dromara ujcms 9.7.5. This affects the function update of the file /main/java/com/ujcms/cms/ext/web/backendapi/WebFileTemplateController.java of the component Edit Template File Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30113 | An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Hardcoded Credentials exist in the APK for Ports 9091 and 9092. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30113</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Hardcoded Credentials exist in the APK for Ports 9091 and 9092. The dashcam's Android application contains hardcoded credentials that allow unauthorized access to device settings through ports 9091 and 9092. These credentials, stored in cleartext, can be exploited by an attacker who gains access to the dashcam's network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30115 | An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Default Credentials Cannot Be Changed. It uses a fixed default SS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30115</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Forvia Hella HELLA Driving Recorder DR 820. Default Credentials Cannot Be Changed. It uses a fixed default SSID and password ("qwertyuiop"), which cannot be modified by users. The SSID is continuously broadcast, allowing unauthorized access to the device network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44313 | TastyIgniter 3.7.6 contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in the invoice() function within Orders.php which allows unauthorized ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44313</link><description>TastyIgniter 3.7.6 contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in the invoice() function within Orders.php which allows unauthorized users to access and generate invoices due to missing permission checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49822 | IBM QRadar Advisor server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49822</link><description>IBM QRadar Advisor 1.0.0 through 2.6.5 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30107 | On IROAD V9 devices, Managing Settings and Obtaining Sensitive Data and Sabotaging the Car Battery can be performed by unauthorized parties....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30107</link><description>On IROAD V9 devices, Managing Settings and Obtaining Sensitive Data and Sabotaging the Car Battery can be performed by unauthorized parties. A vulnerability in the dashcam's configuration management allows unauthorized users to modify settings, disable critical functions, and turn off battery protection, potentially causing physical damage to the vehicle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30111 | On IROAD v9 devices, one can Remotely Dump Video Footage and the Live Video Stream. The dashcam exposes endpoints that allow unauthorized us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30111</link><description>On IROAD v9 devices, one can Remotely Dump Video Footage and the Live Video Stream. The dashcam exposes endpoints that allow unauthorized users, who gained access through other means, to list and download recorded videos, as well as access live video streams without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30132 | An issue was discovered on IROAD Dashcam V devices. It uses an unregistered public domain name as an internal domain, creating a security ri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30132</link><description>An issue was discovered on IROAD Dashcam V devices. It uses an unregistered public domain name as an internal domain, creating a security risk. During analysis, it was found that this domain was not owned by IROAD, allowing an attacker to register it and potentially intercept sensitive device traffic. If the dashcam or related services attempt to resolve this domain over the public Internet instead of locally, it could lead to data exfiltration or man-in-the-middle attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30109 | In the IROAD APK 5.2.5, there are Hardcoded Credentials in the APK for ports 9091 and 9092. The mobile application for the dashcam contains ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30109</link><description>In the IROAD APK 5.2.5, there are Hardcoded Credentials in the APK for ports 9091 and 9092. The mobile application for the dashcam contains hardcoded credentials that allow an attacker on the local Wi-Fi network to access API endpoints and retrieve sensitive device information, including live and recorded footage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30110 | On IROAD X5 devices, a Bypass of Device Pairing can occur via MAC Address Spoofing. The dashcam's pairing mechanism relies solely on MAC add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30110</link><description>On IROAD X5 devices, a Bypass of Device Pairing can occur via MAC Address Spoofing. The dashcam's pairing mechanism relies solely on MAC address verification, allowing an attacker to bypass authentication by spoofing an already-paired MAC address that can be captured via an ARP scan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25500 | An issue in CosmWasm prior to v2.2.0 allows attackers to bypass capability restrictions in blockchains by exploiting a lack of runtime capab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25500</link><description>An issue in CosmWasm prior to v2.2.0 allows attackers to bypass capability restrictions in blockchains by exploiting a lack of runtime capability validation. This allows attackers to deploy a contract without capability enforcement, and execute unauthorized actions on the blockchain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2490 | Dromara ujcms File Upload WebFileUploadController.java upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2490</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara ujcms 9.7.5. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function uploadZip/upload of the file /main/java/com/ujcms/cms/ext/web/backendapi/WebFileUploadController.java of the component File Upload. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30106 | On IROAD v9 devices, the dashcam has hardcoded default credentials ("qwertyuiop") that cannot be changed by the user. This allows an attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30106</link><description>On IROAD v9 devices, the dashcam has hardcoded default credentials ("qwertyuiop") that cannot be changed by the user. This allows an attacker within Wi-Fi range to connect to the device's network to perform sniffing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47539 | An improper access control vulnerability in FortiMail version 7.4.0 configured with RADIUS authentication and remote_wildcard enabled may al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47539</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability in FortiMail version 7.4.0 configured with RADIUS authentication and remote_wildcard enabled may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass admin login via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21760 | An improper control of generation of code ('Code Injection') vulnerability [CWE-94] in FortiSOAR Connector FortiSOAR 7.4 all versions, 7.3 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21760</link><description>An improper control of generation of code ('Code Injection') vulnerability [CWE-94] in FortiSOAR Connector FortiSOAR 7.4 all versions, 7.3 all versions, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the host via a playbook code snippet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8997 | SQLi in Vestel&amp;#x27;s EVC04 Configuration Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8997</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Vestel EVC04 Configuration Interface allows SQL Injection.This issue affects EVC04 Configuration Interface: through 18.03.2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2449 | NI FlexLogger usiReg URI File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2449</link><description>NI FlexLogger usiReg URI File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of NI FlexLogger. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of URI files by the usiReg component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-21805.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2450 | NI Vision Builder AI VBAI File Processing Missing Warning Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2450</link><description>NI Vision Builder AI VBAI File Processing Missing Warning Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NI Vision Builder AI. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of VBAI files. The issue results from allowing the execution of dangerous script without user warning. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22833.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2489 | Insecure storage of sensitive information in NTFS Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2489</link><description>Insecure information storage vulnerability in NTFS Tools version 3.5.1. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to know the application password, stored in /Users/user/Library/Application Support/ntfs-tool/config.json.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2494 | Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2494</link><description>Unrestricted file upload to Softdial Contact Center of Sytel Ltd. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to upload files to the server via the ‘/softdial/phpconsole/upload.php’ endpoint, which is protected by basic HTTP authentication. The files are uploaded to a directory exposed by the web application, which could result in code execution, giving the attacker full control over the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2495 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2495</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Softdial Contact Center of Sytel Ltd. This vulnerability allows an attacker to upload XML files to the server with JavaScript code injected via the ‘/softdial/scheduler/save.php’ resource. The injected code will execute when the uploaded file is loaded via the ‘/softdial/scheduler/load.php’ resource and can redirect the victim to malicious sites or steal their login information to spoof their identity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2493 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2493</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center of Sytel Ltd. This vulnerability allows an attacker to manipulate the ‘id’ parameter of the ‘/softdial/scheduler/load.php’ endpoint to navigate beyond the intended directory. This can allow unauthorised access to sensitive files outside the expected scope, posing a security risk.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23943 | MB connect line: Cloud API access due to a lack of authentication for a critical function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23943</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain access to the cloud API due to a lack of authentication for a critical function in the affected devices. Availability is not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41975 | CODESYS (Edge) Gateway for Windows insecure default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41975</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain limited information of the PLC network but the user management of the PLCs prevents the actual access to the PLCs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0694 | CODESYS Control V3 removable media path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0694</link><description>Insufficient path validation in CODESYS Control allows low privileged attackers with physical access to gain full filesystem access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23942 | MB connect line: Configuration File on the client workstation is not encrypted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23942</link><description>A local user may find a configuration file on the client workstation with unencrypted sensitive data. This allows an attacker to impersonate the device or prevent the device from accessing the cloud portal which leads to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1468 | CODESYS Control V3 - OPC UA Server Authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1468</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain access to sensitive information including authentication information when using CODESYS OPC UA Server with the non-default Basic128Rsa15 security policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0755 | MongoDB C Driver bson library may be susceptible to buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0755</link><description>The various bson_append functions in the MongoDB C driver library may be susceptible to buffer overflow when performing operations that could result in a final BSON document which exceeds the maximum allowable size (INT32_MAX), resulting in a segmentation fault and possible application crash. This issue affected libbson versions prior to 1.27.5, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.1 and MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.16</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24306 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24306</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0.0_1101. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25220 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25220</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0.1_1101. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a remote authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2262 | Logo Slider &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2262</link><description>The The Logo Slider – Logo Showcase, Logo Carousel, Logo Gallery and Client Logo Presentation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.3. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2473 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System Sign In index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2473</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Sign In. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>