<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:35:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-1406 | Linksys WRT54GL Web Management Interface SysInfo1.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1406</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys WRT54GL 4.30.18. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /SysInfo1.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253330 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0594 | The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to union-based SQL Injection via the 'q' parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0594</link><description>The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to union-based SQL Injection via the 'q' parameter of the wpas_get_users action in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0595 | The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0595</link><description>The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpas_get_users() function hooked via AJAX in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve user data such as emails.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0596 | The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0596</link><description>The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the editor_html() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to view password protected and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1405 | Linksys WRT54GL Web Management Interface wlaninfo.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1405</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys WRT54GL 4.30.18. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /wlaninfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253329 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 05:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21490 | This affects versions of the package angular from 1.3.0. A regular expression used to split the value of the ng-srcset directive is vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21490</link><description>This affects versions of the package angular from 1.3.0. A regular expression used to split the value of the ng-srcset directive is vulnerable to super-linear runtime due to backtracking. With a large carefully-crafted input, this can result in catastrophic backtracking and cause a denial of service. &#13;&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This package is EOL and will not receive any updates to address this issue. Users should migrate to [@angular/core](https://www.npmjs.com/package/@angular/core).</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 05:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45698 | HCL Sametime is impacted by clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45698</link><description>Sametime is impacted by lack of clickjacking protection in Outlook add-in. The application is not implementing appropriate protections in order to protect users from clickjacking attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 03:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28077 | Dell BSAFE SSL-J, versions prior to 6.5, and versions 7.0 and 7.1 contain a debug message revealing unnecessary information vulnerability. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28077</link><description>Dell BSAFE SSL-J, versions prior to 6.5, and versions 7.0 and 7.1 contain a debug message revealing unnecessary information vulnerability. This may lead to disclosing sensitive information to a locally privileged user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 03:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45696 | HCL Sametime is impacted by an autocomplete enabled vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45696</link><description>Sametime is impacted by sensitive fields with autocomplete enabled in the Legacy web chat client. By default, this allows user entered data to be stored by the browser.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 03:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23322 | Envoy crashes when idle and request per try timeout occur within the backoff interval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23322</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. Envoy will crash when certain timeouts happen within the same interval. The crash occurs when the following are true: 1. hedge_on_per_try_timeout is enabled, 2. per_try_idle_timeout is enabled (it can only be done in configuration), 3. per-try-timeout is enabled, either through headers or configuration and its value is equal, or within the backoff interval of the per_try_idle_timeout. This issue has been addressed in released 1.29.1, 1.28.1, 1.27.3, and 1.26.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 23:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23323 | Excessive CPU usage when URI template matcher is configured using regex in Envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23323</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. The regex expression is compiled for every request and can result in high CPU usage and increased request latency when multiple routes are configured with such matchers. This issue has been addressed in released 1.29.1, 1.28.1, 1.27.3, and 1.26.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 23:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23324 | Envoy ext auth can be bypassed when Proxy protocol filter sets invalid UTF-8 metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23324</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. External authentication can be bypassed by downstream connections. Downstream clients can force invalid gRPC requests to be sent to ext_authz, circumventing ext_authz checks when failure_mode_allow is set to true. This issue has been addressed in released 1.29.1, 1.28.1, 1.27.3, and 1.26.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 23:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23325 | Envoy crashes when using an address type that isn’t supported by the OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23325</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. Envoy crashes in Proxy protocol when using an address type that isn’t supported by the OS. Envoy is susceptible to crashing on a host with IPv6 disabled and a listener config with proxy protocol enabled when it receives a request where the client presents its IPv6 address.  It is valid for a client to present its IPv6 address to a target server even though the whole chain is connected via IPv4. This issue has been addressed in released 1.29.1, 1.28.1, 1.27.3, and 1.26.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23327 | Crash in proxy protocol when command type of LOCAL in Envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23327</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. When PPv2 is enabled both on a listener and subsequent cluster, the Envoy instance will segfault when attempting to craft the upstream PPv2 header. This occurs when the downstream request has a command type of LOCAL and does not have the protocol block. This issue has been addressed in releases 1.29.1, 1.28.1, 1.27.3, and 1.26.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1404 | Linksys WRT54GL Web Management Interface SysInfo.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1404</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys WRT54GL 4.30.18 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /SysInfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253328. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6935 | Marvin Attack vulnerability in SP Math All RSA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6935</link><description>wolfSSL SP Math All RSA implementation is vulnerable to the Marvin Attack, new variation of a timing Bleichenbacher style attack, when built with the following options to configure:

--enable-all CFLAGS="-DWOLFSSL_STATIC_RSA"

The define “WOLFSSL_STATIC_RSA” enables static RSA cipher suites, which is not recommended, and has been disabled by default since wolfSSL 3.6.6.  Therefore the default build since 3.6.6, even with "--enable-all", is not vulnerable to the Marvin Attack. The vulnerability is specific to static RSA cipher suites, and expected to be padding-independent.

The vulnerability allows an attacker to decrypt ciphertexts and forge signatures after probing with a large number of test observations. However the server’s private key is not exposed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25109 | Cross-Site Scripting in the extensions, settings, permissions and namespaces subpages of ManageWiki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25109</link><description>ManageWiki is a MediaWiki extension allowing users to manage wikis. Special:ManageWiki does not escape escape interface messages on the `columns` and `help` keys on the form descriptor. An attacker may exploit this and would have a cross site scripting attack vector. Exploiting this on-wiki requires the `(editinterface)` right. Users should apply the code changes in commits `886cc6b94`, `2ef0f50880`, and `6942e8b2c` to resolve this vulnerability. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21624 | Potential Information Leak in User-Constructed Message Templates in nonebot2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21624</link><description>nonebot2 is a cross-platform Python asynchronous chatbot framework written in Python. This security advisory pertains to a potential information leak (e.g., environment variables) in instances where developers utilize `MessageTemplate` and incorporate user-provided data into templates. The identified vulnerability has been remedied in pull request #2509 and will be included in versions released from 2.2.0. Users are strongly advised to upgrade to these patched versions to safeguard against the vulnerability. A temporary workaround involves filtering underscores before incorporating user input into the message template.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24828 | Local Privilege Escalation in execuatables bundled by pkg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24828</link><description>pkg is tool design to bundle Node.js projects into an executables. Any native code packages built by `pkg` are written to a hardcoded directory. On unix systems, this is `/tmp/pkg/*` which is a shared directory for all users on the same local system. There is no uniqueness to the package names within this directory, they are predictable. An attacker who has access to the same local system has the ability to replace the genuine executables in the shared directory with malicious executables of the same name. A user may then run the malicious executable without realising it has been modified. This package is deprecated. Therefore, there will not be a patch provided for this vulnerability. To check if your executable build by pkg depends on native code and is vulnerable, run the executable and check if `/tmp/pkg/` was created. Users should transition to actively maintained alternatives. We would recommend investigating Node.js 21’s support for single executable applications. Given the decision to deprecate the pkg package, there are no official workarounds or remediations provided by our team. Users should prioritize migrating to other packages that offer similar functionality with enhanced security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45718 | HCL Sametime is impacted by a failure to invalidate sessions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45718</link><description>Sametime is impacted by a failure to invalidate sessions.  The application is setting sensitive cookie values in a persistent manner in Sametime Web clients. When this happens, cookie values can remain valid even after a user has closed out their session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 21:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45716 | HCL Sametime is impacted by a sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45716</link><description>Sametime is impacted by sensitive information passed in URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50349 | HCL Sametime is impacted by a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50349</link><description>Sametime is impacted by a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.  Some REST APIs in the Sametime Proxy application can allow an attacker to perform malicious actions on the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 20:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1245 | Concrete CMS version 9 before 9.2.5 is vulnerable to stored XSS in file tags and description attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1245</link><description>Concrete CMS version 9 before 9.2.5 is vulnerable to stored XSS in file tags and description attributes since administrator entered file attributes are not sufficiently sanitized in the Edit Attributes page. A rogue administrator could put malicious code into the file tags or description attributes and, when another administrator opens the same file for editing, the malicious code could execute. The Concrete CMS Security team scored this 2.4 with CVSS v3 vector AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1246 | Concrete CMS in version 9 before 9.2.5 is vulnerable to reflected XSS via the Image URL Import Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1246</link><description>Concrete CMS in version 9 before 9.2.5 is vulnerable to reflected XSS via the Image URL Import Feature due to insufficient validation of administrator provided data. A rogue administrator could inject malicious code when importing images, leading to the execution of the malicious code on the website user’s browser. The Concrete CMS Security team scored this 2 with CVSS v3 vector AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N. This does not affect Concrete versions prior to version 9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1247 | Concrete CMS version 9 before 9.2.5 vulnerable to stored XSS via the Role Name field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1247</link><description>Concrete CMS version 9 before 9.2.5 is vulnerable to  stored XSS via the Role Name field since there is insufficient validation of administrator provided data for that field. A rogue administrator could inject malicious code into the Role Name field which might be executed when users visit the affected page. The Concrete CMS Security team scored this 2 with CVSS v3 vector  AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator . Concrete versions below 9 do not include group types so they are not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 19:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50291 | Apache Solr: System Property redaction logic inconsistency can lead to leaked passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50291</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Apache Solr.

This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.0.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.3.0.
One of the two endpoints that publishes the Solr process' Java system properties, /admin/info/properties, was only setup to hide system properties that had "password" contained in the name.
There are a number of sensitive system properties, such as "basicauth" and "aws.secretKey" do not contain "password", thus their values were published via the "/admin/info/properties" endpoint.
This endpoint populates the list of System Properties on the home screen of the Solr Admin page, making the exposed credentials visible in the UI.

This /admin/info/properties endpoint is protected under the "config-read" permission.
Therefore, Solr Clouds with Authorization enabled will only be vulnerable through logged-in users that have the "config-read" permission.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.3.0 or 8.11.3, which fixes the issue.
A single option now controls hiding Java system property for all endpoints, "-Dsolr.hiddenSysProps".
By default all known sensitive properties are hidden (including "-Dbasicauth"), as well as any property with a name containing "secret" or "password".

Users who cannot upgrade can also use the following Java system property to fix the issue:
  '-Dsolr.redaction.system.pattern=.*(password|secret|basicauth).*'</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50292 | Apache Solr: Solr Schema Designer blindly &amp;quot;trusts&amp;quot; all configsets, possibly leading to RCE by unauthenticated users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50292</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource, Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources vulnerability in Apache Solr.

This issue affects Apache Solr: from 8.10.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.3.0.

The Schema Designer was introduced to allow users to more easily configure and test new Schemas and configSets.
However, when the feature was created, the "trust" (authentication) of these configSets was not considered.
External library loading is only available to configSets that are "trusted" (created by authenticated users), thus non-authenticated users are unable to perform Remote Code Execution.
Since the Schema Designer loaded configSets without taking their "trust" into account, configSets that were created by unauthenticated users were allowed to load external libraries when used in the Schema Designer.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50298 | Apache Solr: Solr can expose ZooKeeper credentials via Streaming Expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50298</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Solr.This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.0.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.4.1.

Solr Streaming Expressions allows users to extract data from other Solr Clouds, using a "zkHost" parameter.
When original SolrCloud is setup to use ZooKeeper credentials and ACLs, they will be sent to whatever "zkHost" the user provides.
An attacker could setup a server to mock ZooKeeper, that accepts ZooKeeper requests with credentials and ACLs and extracts the sensitive information,
then send a streaming expression using the mock server's address in "zkHost".
Streaming Expressions are exposed via the "/streaming" handler, with "read" permissions.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.11.3 or 9.4.1, which fix the issue.
From these versions on, only zkHost values that have the same server address (regardless of chroot), will use the given ZooKeeper credentials and ACLs when connecting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50386 | Apache Solr: Backup/Restore APIs allow for deployment of executables in malicious ConfigSets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50386</link><description>Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources, Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type, Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere vulnerability in Apache Solr.This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.0.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.4.1.

In the affected versions, Solr ConfigSets accepted Java jar and class files to be uploaded through the ConfigSets API.
When backing up Solr Collections, these configSet files would be saved to disk when using the LocalFileSystemRepository (the default for backups).
If the backup was saved to a directory that Solr uses in its ClassPath/ClassLoaders, then the jar and class files would be available to use with any ConfigSet, trusted or untrusted.

When Solr is run in a secure way (Authorization enabled), as is strongly suggested, this vulnerability is limited to extending the Backup permissions with the ability to add libraries.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.11.3 or 9.4.1, which fix the issue.
In these versions, the following protections have been added:

  *  Users are no longer able to upload files to a configSet that could be executed via a Java ClassLoader.
  *  The Backup API restricts saving backups to directories that are used in the ClassLoader.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1402 | Denial of service in mattermost mobile apps and server via emoji reactions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1402</link><description>Mattermost fails to check if a custom emoji reaction exists when sending it to a post and to limit the amount of custom emojis allowed to be added in a post, allowing an attacker sending a huge amount of non-existent custom emojis in a post to crash the mobile app of a user seeing the post.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24776 |  Incorrect Authorization leads to Channel Member Count Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24776</link><description>Mattermost fails to check the required permissions in the POST /api/v4/channels/stats/member_count API resulting in channel member counts being leaked to a user without permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23319 | CSRF issue allows disconnecting a user&amp;#x27;s Jira connection through a simple post message (Jira Plugin)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23319</link><description>Mattermost Jira Plugin fails to protect against logout CSRF allowing an attacker to post a specially crafted message that would disconnect a user's Jira connection in Mattermost only by viewing the message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24774 | Missing authorization allows users to access arbitrary security levels on Jira through webhooks (Jira Plugin)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24774</link><description>Mattermost Jira Plugin handling subscriptions fails to check the security level of an incoming issue or limit it based on the user who created the subscription resulting in registered users on Jira being able to create webhooks that give them access to all Jira issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25442 | An issue in the HuginBase::PanoramaMemento::loadPTScript function of Hugin v2022.0.0 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25442</link><description>An issue in the HuginBase::PanoramaMemento::loadPTScript function of Hugin v2022.0.0 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25443 | An issue in the HuginBase::ImageVariable&lt;double&gt;::linkWith function of Hugin v2022.0.0 allows attackers to cause a heap-use-after-free via p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25443</link><description>An issue in the HuginBase::ImageVariable&lt;double&gt;::linkWith function of Hugin v2022.0.0 allows attackers to cause a heap-use-after-free via parsing a crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25445 | Improper handling of values in HuginBase::PTools::Transform::transform of Hugin 2022.0.0 leads to an assertion failure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25445</link><description>Improper handling of values in HuginBase::PTools::Transform::transform of Hugin 2022.0.0 leads to an assertion failure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25446 | An issue in the HuginBase::PTools::setDestImage function of Hugin v2022.0.0 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25446</link><description>An issue in the HuginBase::PTools::setDestImage function of Hugin v2022.0.0 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25447 | An issue in the imlib_load_image_with_error_return function of imlib2 v1.9.1 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25447</link><description>An issue in the imlib_load_image_with_error_return function of imlib2 v1.9.1 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25448 | An issue in the imlib_free_image_and_decache function of imlib2 v1.9.1 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25448</link><description>An issue in the imlib_free_image_and_decache function of imlib2 v1.9.1 allows attackers to cause a heap buffer overflow via parsing a crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25450 | imlib2 v1.9.1 was discovered to mishandle memory allocation in the function init_imlib_fonts().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25450</link><description>imlib2 v1.9.1 was discovered to mishandle memory allocation in the function init_imlib_fonts().</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25451 | Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain an out-of-memory bug via the AP4_DataBuffer::ReallocateBuffer() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25451</link><description>Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain an out-of-memory bug via the AP4_DataBuffer::ReallocateBuffer() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25452 | Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain an out-of-memory bug via the AP4_UrlAtom::AP4_UrlAtom() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25452</link><description>Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain an out-of-memory bug via the AP4_UrlAtom::AP4_UrlAtom() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25453 | Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the AP4_StszAtom::GetSampleSize() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25453</link><description>Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the AP4_StszAtom::GetSampleSize() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25454 | Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the AP4_DescriptorFinder::Test() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25454</link><description>Bento4 v1.6.0-640 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the AP4_DescriptorFinder::Test() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25314 | Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0, allows SQL Injection via the 'sid' parameter in Hotel/admin/show.php?sid=2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25314</link><description>Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0, allows SQL Injection via the 'sid' parameter in Hotel/admin/show.php?sid=2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25315 | Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0, allows SQL Injection via the 'rid' parameter in Hotel/admin/roombook.php?rid=2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25315</link><description>Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0, allows SQL Injection via the 'rid' parameter in Hotel/admin/roombook.php?rid=2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25316 | Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'eid' parameter in Hotel/admin/usersettingdel.php?eid=2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25316</link><description>Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'eid' parameter in Hotel/admin/usersettingdel.php?eid=2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25318 | Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'pid' parameter in Hotel/admin/print.php?pid=2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25318</link><description>Code-projects Hotel Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'pid' parameter in Hotel/admin/print.php?pid=2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25307 | Code-projects Cinema Seat Reservation System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter at "/Cinema-Reservation/booking.php?id=1."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25307</link><description>Code-projects Cinema Seat Reservation System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter at "/Cinema-Reservation/booking.php?id=1."</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6677 | SQLi in Oduyo Online Collection Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6677</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Oduyo Financial Technology Online Collection allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Online Collection: before v.1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25302 | Sourcecodester Event Student Attendance System 1.0, allows SQL Injection via the 'student' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25302</link><description>Sourcecodester Event Student Attendance System 1.0, allows SQL Injection via the 'student' parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25310 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter at "School/delete.php?id=5."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25310</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter at "School/delete.php?id=5."</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25312 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter at "School/sub_delete.php?id=5."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25312</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter at "School/sub_delete.php?id=5."</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25304 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'apass' parameter at "School/index.php."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25304</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'apass' parameter at "School/index.php."</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25305 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows Authentication Bypass via the username and password parameters at School/index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25305</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows Authentication Bypass via the username and password parameters at School/index.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25308 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'name' parameter at School/teacher_login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25308</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'name' parameter at School/teacher_login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25309 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'pass' parameter at School/teacher_login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25309</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'pass' parameter at School/teacher_login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 13:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25306 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'aname' parameter at "School/index.php".</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25306</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'aname' parameter at "School/index.php".</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 12:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25313 | Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows Authentication Bypass via the username and password parameters at School/teacher_log...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25313</link><description>Code-projects Simple School Managment System 1.0 allows Authentication Bypass via the username and password parameters at School/teacher_login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 12:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6724 | IDOR in Simgesel Software&amp;#x27;s Hearing Tracking System (Barosel)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6724</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Software Engineering Consultancy Machine Equipment Limited Company Hearing Tracking System allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Hearing Tracking System: before for IOS 7.0, for Android Latest release 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 12:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25678 | In LiteSpeed QUIC (LSQUIC) Library before 4.0.4, DCID validation is mishandled.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25678</link><description>In LiteSpeed QUIC (LSQUIC) Library before 4.0.4, DCID validation is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25679 | In PQUIC before 5bde5bb, retention of unused initial encryption keys allows attackers to disrupt a connection with a PSK configuration by se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25679</link><description>In PQUIC before 5bde5bb, retention of unused initial encryption keys allows attackers to disrupt a connection with a PSK configuration by sending a CONNECTION_CLOSE frame that is encrypted via the initial key computed. Network traffic sniffing is needed as part of exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25674 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.184. Organisation logo upload is insecure because of a lack of checks for the file extension and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25674</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.184. Organisation logo upload is insecure because of a lack of checks for the file extension and MIME type.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25675 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.184. A client does not need to use POST to start an export generation process. This is related to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25675</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.184. A client does not need to use POST to start an export generation process. This is related to app/Controller/JobsController.php and app/View/Events/export.ctp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25677 | In Min before 1.31.0, local files are not correctly treated as unique security origins, which allows them to improperly request cross-origin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25677</link><description>In Min before 1.31.0, local files are not correctly treated as unique security origins, which allows them to improperly request cross-origin resources. For example, a local file may request other local files through an XML document.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22119 | Stored XSS in graph items select form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22119</link><description>The cause of vulnerability is improper validation of form input field “Name” on Graph page in Items section.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 08:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21762 | A out-of-bounds write in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, 6.4.0 through 6.4.14, 6.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21762</link><description>A out-of-bounds write in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, 6.4.0 through 6.4.14, 6.2.0 through 6.2.15, 6.0.0 through 6.0.17, FortiProxy versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.14, 2.0.0 through 2.0.13, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted requests</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 08:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46350 | SQL injection vulnerability in InnovaDeluxe "Manufacturer or supplier alphabetical search" (idxrmanufacturer) module for PrestaShop versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46350</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in InnovaDeluxe "Manufacturer or supplier alphabetical search" (idxrmanufacturer) module for PrestaShop versions 2.0.4 and before, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the methods IdxrmanufacturerFunctions::getCornersLink, IdxrmanufacturerFunctions::getManufacturersLike and IdxrmanufacturerFunctions::getSuppliersLike.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50026 | SQL injection vulnerability in Presta Monster "Multi Accessories Pro" (hsmultiaccessoriespro) module for PrestaShop versions 5.1.1 and befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50026</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Presta Monster "Multi Accessories Pro" (hsmultiaccessoriespro) module for PrestaShop versions 5.1.1 and before, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the method HsAccessoriesGroupProductAbstract::getAccessoriesByIdProducts().</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24308 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Boostmyshop (boostmyshopagent) module for Prestashop versions 1.1.9 and before, allows remote attackers to es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24308</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Boostmyshop (boostmyshopagent) module for Prestashop versions 1.1.9 and before, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via changeOrderCarrier.php, relayPoint.php, and shippingConfirmation.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23749 | KiTTY versions 0.76.1.13 and before is vulnerable to command injection via the filename variable, occurs due to insufficient input sanitizat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23749</link><description>KiTTY versions 0.76.1.13 and before is vulnerable to command injection via the filename variable, occurs due to insufficient input sanitization and validation, failure to escape special characters, and insecure system calls (at lines 2369-2390). This allows an attacker to add inputs inside the filename variable, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25003 | KiTTY versions 0.76.1.13 and before is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow via the hostname, occurs due to insufficient bounds check...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25003</link><description>KiTTY versions 0.76.1.13 and before is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow via the hostname, occurs due to insufficient bounds checking and input sanitization. This allows an attacker to overwrite adjacent memory, which leads to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25004 | KiTTY versions 0.76.1.13 and before is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow via the username, occurs due to insufficient bounds check...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25004</link><description>KiTTY versions 0.76.1.13 and before is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow via the username, occurs due to insufficient bounds checking and input sanitization (at line 2600). This allows an attacker to overwrite adjacent memory, which leads to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31506 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Grav versions 1.7.44 and before, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31506</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Grav versions 1.7.44 and before, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via the onmouseover attribute of an ISINDEX element.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39683 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EasyEmail v.4.12.2 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the user inp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39683</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EasyEmail v.4.12.2 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the user input parameter(s). NOTE: Researcher claims issue is present in all versions prior and later than tested version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0229 | Xorg-x11-server: reattaching to different master device may lead to out-of-bounds memory access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0229</link><description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the X.Org server. This issue can be triggered when a device frozen by a sync grab is reattached to a different master device. This issue may lead to an application crash, local privilege escalation (if the server runs with extended privileges), or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0657 | The Internal Link Juicer: SEO Auto Linker for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0657</link><description>The Internal Link Juicer: SEO Auto Linker for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings such as 'ilj_settings_field_links_per_page'  in all versions up to, and including, 2.23.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0842 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Denial of Service in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0842</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Denial of Service in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This is due to direct access of the backuply/restore_ins.php file and. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make excessive requests that result in the server running out of resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1122 | The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Events Tickets for WooCommerce – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1122</link><description>The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Events Tickets for WooCommerce – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.50. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export event data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43609 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43609</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an unauthenticated user with network access could obtain access to sensitive information or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46687 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46687</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an unauthenticated user with network access could execute arbitrary commands in root context from a remote computer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49716 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49716</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an authenticated user with network access could run arbitrary commands from a remote computer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51761 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51761</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an unauthenticated user with network access could bypass authentication and acquire admin capabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32341 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32341</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.8 and 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to uncontrolled resource consumption.  IBM X-Force ID:  255827.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42016 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42016</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.8 and 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.  IBM X-Force ID:  265559.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22332 | IBM Integration Bus for z/OS denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22332</link><description>The IBM Integration Bus for z/OS 10.1 through 10.1.0.2 AdminAPI is vulnerable to a denial of service due to file system exhaustion.  IBM X-Force ID:  279972.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45187 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45187</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  268749.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45190 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization HTTP header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45190</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers.  This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.  IBM X-Force ID:  268754.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45191 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45191</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  268755.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1353 | PHPEMS index.api.php index deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPEMS up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function index of the file app/weixin/controller/index.api.php. The manipulation of the argument picurl leads to deserialization. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253226 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22318 | IBM i Access Client Solutions information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22318</link><description>IBM i Access Client Solutions (ACS) 1.1.2 through 1.1.4 and 1.1.4.3 through 1.1.9.4 is vulnerable to NT LAN Manager (NTLM) hash disclosure by an attacker modifying UNC capable paths within ACS configuration files to point to a hostile server. If NTLM is enabled, the Windows operating system will try to authenticate using the current user's session. The hostile server could capture the NTLM hash information to obtain the user's credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  279091.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23639 | micronaut-core  management endpoints vulnerable to drive-by localhost attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23639</link><description>Micronaut Framework is a modern, JVM-based, full stack Java framework designed for building modular, easily testable JVM applications with support for Java, Kotlin and the Groovy language. Enabled but unsecured management endpoints are susceptible to drive-by localhost attacks. While not typical of a production application, these attacks may have more impact on a development environment where such endpoints may be flipped on without much thought. A malicious/compromised website can make HTTP requests to `localhost`. Normally, such requests would trigger a CORS preflight check which would prevent the request; however, some requests are "simple" and do not require a preflight check. These endpoints, if enabled and not secured, are vulnerable to being triggered. Production environments typically disable unused endpoints and secure/restrict access to needed endpoints. A more likely victim is the developer in their local development host, who has enabled endpoints without security for the sake of easing development. This issue has been addressed in version 3.8.3. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24819 | icingaweb2-module-incubator base implementation for HTML forms is susceptible to CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24819</link><description>icingaweb2-module-incubator is a working project of bleeding edge Icinga Web 2 libraries. In affected versions the class `gipfl\Web\Form` is the base for various concrete form implementations [1] and provides protection against cross site request forgery (CSRF) by default. This is done by automatically adding an element with a CSRF token to any form, unless explicitly disabled, but even if enabled, the CSRF token (sent during a client's submission of a form relying on it) is not validated. This enables attackers to perform changes on behalf of a user which, unknowingly, interacts with a prepared link or website. The version 0.22.0 is available to remedy this issue. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24820 | Icinga Director configuration is susceptible to Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24820</link><description>Icinga Director is a tool designed to make Icinga 2 configuration handling easy. Not any of Icinga Director's configuration forms used to manipulate the monitoring environment are protected against cross site request forgery (CSRF). It enables attackers to perform changes in the monitoring environment managed by Icinga Director without the awareness of the victim. Users of the map module in version 1.x, should immediately upgrade to v2.0. The mentioned XSS vulnerabilities in Icinga Web are already fixed as well and upgrades to the most recent release of the 2.9, 2.10 or 2.11 branch must be performed if not done yet. Any later major release is also suitable. Icinga Director will receive minor updates to the 1.8, 1.9, 1.10 and 1.11 branches to remedy this issue. Upgrade immediately to a patched release. If that is not feasible, disable the director module for the time being.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24821 | Code execution and possible privilege escalation via compromised InstalledVersions.php or installed.php in Composer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24821</link><description>Composer is a dependency Manager for the PHP language. In affected versions several files within the local working directory are included during the invocation of Composer and in the context of the executing user. As such, under certain conditions arbitrary code execution may lead to local privilege escalation, provide lateral user movement or malicious code execution when Composer is invoked within a directory with tampered files. All Composer CLI commands are affected, including composer.phar's self-update. The following scenarios are of high risk: Composer being run with sudo, Pipelines which may execute Composer on untrusted projects, Shared environments with developers who run Composer individually on the same project. This vulnerability has been addressed in versions 2.7.0 and 2.2.23. It is advised that the patched versions are applied at the earliest convenience. Where not possible, the following should be addressed: Remove all sudo composer privileges for all users to mitigate root privilege escalation, and avoid running Composer within an untrusted directory, or if needed, verify that the contents of `vendor/composer/InstalledVersions.php` and `vendor/composer/installed.php` do not include untrusted code.  A reset can also be done on these files by the following:```sh
rm vendor/composer/installed.php vendor/composer/InstalledVersions.php
composer install --no-scripts --no-plugins
```</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24829 | SSRF in Sentry via Phabricator integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24829</link><description>Sentry is an error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Sentry’s integration platform provides a way for external services to interact with Sentry. One of such integrations, the Phabricator integration (maintained by Sentry) with version &lt;=24.1.1 contains a constrained SSRF vulnerability. An attacker could make Sentry send POST HTTP requests to arbitrary URLs (including internal IP addresses) by providing an unsanitized input to the Phabricator integration. However, the body payload is constrained to a specific format. If an attacker has access to a Sentry instance, this allows them to: 1. interact with internal network; 2. scan local/remote ports. This issue has been fixed in Sentry self-hosted release 24.1.2, and has already been mitigated on sentry.io on February 8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24825 | TokenManager not checking permissions on cached tokens in DIRAC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24825</link><description>DIRAC is a distributed resource framework. In affected versions any user could get a token that has been requested by another user/agent. This may expose resources to unintended parties. This issue has been addressed in release version 8.0.37. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24830 | OpenObserve Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in Users API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24830</link><description>OpenObserve is a observability platform built specifically for logs, metrics, traces, analytics, designed to work at petabyte scale. A vulnerability has been identified in the "/api/{org_id}/users" endpoint. This vulnerability allows any authenticated regular user ('member') to add new users with elevated privileges, including the 'root' role, to an organization. This issue circumvents the intended security controls for role assignments. The vulnerability resides in the user creation process, where the payload does not validate the user roles. A regular user can manipulate the payload to assign root-level privileges. This vulnerability leads to Unauthorized Privilege Escalation and significantly compromises the application's role-based access control system. It allows unauthorized control over application resources and poses a risk to data security. All users, particularly those in administrative roles, are impacted. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25106 | OpenObserve Unauthorized Access Vulnerability in Users API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25106</link><description>OpenObserve is a observability platform built specifically for logs, metrics, traces, analytics, designed to work at petabyte scale. A critical vulnerability has been identified in the "/api/{org_id}/users/{email_id}" endpoint. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user within an organization to remove any other user from that same organization, irrespective of their respective roles. This includes the ability to remove users with "Admin" and "Root" roles. By enabling any organizational member to unilaterally alter the user base, it opens the door to unauthorized access and can cause considerable disruptions in operations. The core of the vulnerability lies in the `remove_user_from_org` function in the user management system. This function is designed to allow organizational users to remove members from their organization. The function does not check if the user initiating the request has the appropriate administrative privileges to remove a user. Any user who is part of the organization, irrespective of their role, can remove any other user, including those with higher privileges. This vulnerability is categorized as an Authorization issue leading to Unauthorized User Removal. The impact is severe, as it compromises the integrity of user management within organizations. By exploiting this vulnerability, any user within an organization, without the need for administrative privileges, can remove critical users, including "Admins" and "Root" users. This could result in unauthorized system access, administrative lockout, or operational disruptions. Given that user accounts are typically created by "Admins" or "Root" users, this vulnerability can be exploited by any user who has been granted access to an organization, thereby posing a critical risk to the security and operational stability of the application. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25107 | Cross-Site Scripting in WikiDiscover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25107</link><description>WikiDiscover is an extension designed for use with a CreateWiki managed farm to display wikis. On Special:WikiDiscover, the `Language::date` function is used when making the human-readable timestamp for inclusion on the wiki_creation column. This function uses interface messages to translate the names of months and days. It uses the `-&gt;text()` output mode, returning unescaped interface messages. Since the output is not escaped later, the unescaped interface message is included on the output, resulting in an XSS vulnerability. Exploiting this on-wiki requires the `(editinterface)` right. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `267e763a0`. Users are advised to update their installations. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47132 | An issue discovered in N-able N-central before 2023.6 and earlier allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via API calls.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47132</link><description>An issue discovered in N-able N-central before 2023.6 and earlier allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via API calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47131 | The N-able PassPortal extension before 3.29.2 for Chrome inserts sensitive information into a log file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47131</link><description>The N-able PassPortal extension before 3.29.2 for Chrome inserts sensitive information into a log file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40262 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Script...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40262</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the administration component via Access Request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40263 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated command injection via ftp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40263</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated command injection via ftp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40264 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated path traversal in the user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40264</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated path traversal in the user interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51630 | Paessler PRTG Network Monitor Cross-Site Scripting Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51630</link><description>Paessler PRTG Network Monitor Cross-Site Scripting Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Paessler PRTG Network Monitor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the web console. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21182.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49101 | WebAdmin in Axigen 10.3.x before 10.3.3.61, 10.4.x before 10.4.24, and 10.5.x before 10.5.10 allows XSS attacks against admins because of mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49101</link><description>WebAdmin in Axigen 10.3.x before 10.3.3.61, 10.4.x before 10.4.24, and 10.5.x before 10.5.10 allows XSS attacks against admins because of mishandling of viewing the usage of SSL certificates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40265 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows authenticated remote code ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40265</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows authenticated remote code execution via file upload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40266 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows path traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40266</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows path traversal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24393 | File Upload vulnerability index.php in Pichome v.1.1.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted POST request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24393</link><description>File Upload vulnerability index.php in Pichome v.1.1.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25365 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability found in October CMS v.3.2.0 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file type .mp3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25365</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability found in October CMS v.3.2.0 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file type .mp3</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27001 | An issue discovered in Egerie Risk Manager v4.0.5 allows attackers to bypass the signature mechanism and tamper with the values inside the J...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27001</link><description>An issue discovered in Egerie Risk Manager v4.0.5 allows attackers to bypass the signature mechanism and tamper with the values inside the JWT payload resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24498 | Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Employee Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the edit-pho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24498</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Employee Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the edit-photo.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24499 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtfullna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24499</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtfullname and txtphone parameters in the edit_profile.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24496 | An issue in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to manipulate trackers via the home.php, add-tracker.php, delete-tracker.php,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24496</link><description>An issue in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to manipulate trackers via the home.php, add-tracker.php, delete-tracker.php, update-tracker.php components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24497 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtuserna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24497</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtusername and txtpassword parameters in the login.php components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24495 | SQL Injection vulnerability in delete-tracker.php in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24495</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in delete-tracker.php in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24494 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the day, exercise, pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24494</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the day, exercise, pray, read_book, vitamins, laundry, alcohol and meat parameters in the add-tracker.php and update-tracker.php components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23756 | The HTTP PUT and DELETE methods are enabled in the Plone official Docker version 5.2.13 (5221), allowing unauthenticated attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23756</link><description>The HTTP PUT and DELETE methods are enabled in the Plone official Docker version 5.2.13 (5221), allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute dangerous actions such as uploading files to the server or deleting them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23660 | The Binance Trust Wallet app for iOS in commit 3cd6e8f647fbba8b5d8844fcd144365a086b629f, git tag 0.0.4 misuses the trezor-crypto library and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23660</link><description>The Binance Trust Wallet app for iOS in commit 3cd6e8f647fbba8b5d8844fcd144365a086b629f, git tag 0.0.4 misuses the trezor-crypto library and consequently generates mnemonic words for which the device time is the only entropy source, leading to economic losses, as exploited in the wild in July 2023. An attacker can systematically generate mnemonics for each timestamp within an applicable timeframe, and link them to specific wallet addresses in order to steal funds from those wallets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24115 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Page function of Cotonti CMS v0.9.24 allows authenticated attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24115</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Page function of Cotonti CMS v0.9.24 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0242 | Unauthorized access to settings in Qolsys IQ Panel 4 and IQ4 Hub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0242</link><description>Under certain circumstances IQ Panel4 and IQ4 Hub panel software prior to version 4.4.2 could allow unauthorized access to settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22836 | An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Akaunting v3.1.3 and earlier. An attacker can manipulate the company locale when installing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22836</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Akaunting v3.1.3 and earlier. An attacker can manipulate the company locale when installing an app to execute system commands on the hosting server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1329 | Nomad Vulnerable to Arbitrary Write Through Symlink Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1329</link><description>HashiCorp Nomad and Nomad Enterprise 1.5.13 up to 1.6.6, and 1.7.3 template renderer is vulnerable to arbitrary file write on the host as the Nomad client user through symlink attacks. Fixed in Nomad 1.7.4, 1.6.7, 1.5.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22795 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v.11.3.06.0063 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Rechec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22795</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v.11.3.06.0063 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Recheck Compliance Status component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23764 | Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15 and later, WithSecure Server Securi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23764</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15 and later, WithSecure Server Security 15 and later, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15 and later, and WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24215 | An issue in the component /cgi-bin/GetJsonValue.cgi of Cellinx NVT Web Server 5.0.0.014 allows attackers to leak configuration information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24215</link><description>An issue in the component /cgi-bin/GetJsonValue.cgi of Cellinx NVT Web Server 5.0.0.014 allows attackers to leak configuration information via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24213 | Supabase PostgreSQL v15.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /pg_meta/default/query.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24213</link><description>Supabase PostgreSQL v15.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /pg_meta/default/query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24321 | An issue in Dlink DIR-816A2 v.1.10CNB05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wizardstep4_ssid_2 parameter in the sub_4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24321</link><description>An issue in Dlink DIR-816A2 v.1.10CNB05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wizardstep4_ssid_2 parameter in the sub_42DA54 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50061 | PrestaShop Op'art Easy Redirect &gt;= 1.3.8 and &lt;= 1.3.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via Oparteasyredirect::hookActionDispatcher().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50061</link><description>PrestaShop Op'art Easy Redirect &gt;= 1.3.8 and &lt;= 1.3.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via Oparteasyredirect::hookActionDispatcher().</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25190 | l8w8jwt 2.2.1 uses memcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25190</link><description>l8w8jwt 2.2.1 uses memcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25189 | libjwt 1.15.3 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25189</link><description>libjwt 1.15.3 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25191 | php-jwt 1.0.0 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25191</link><description>php-jwt 1.0.0 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42282 | An issue in NPM IP Package v.1.1.8 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the isPublic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42282</link><description>An issue in NPM IP Package v.1.1.8 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the isPublic() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47020 | Multiple Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) chaining in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows privileges to be escalated by an attacker through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47020</link><description>Multiple Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) chaining in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows privileges to be escalated by an attacker through a crafted request involving user account creation and adding the user to an administrator group. This is exploited by an undisclosed function in the WSDL that lacks security controls and can accept custom content types.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24834 | WordPress BEAR Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 BEAR – Bulk Editor and Products Manager Professional for WooCommerce by Pluginus.Net allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BEAR – Bulk Editor and Products Manager Professional for WooCommerce by Pluginus.Net: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1150 | Improper validation of update packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1150</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Snow Software Inventory Agent on Unix allows File Manipulation through Snow Update Packages.This issue affects Inventory Agent: through 7.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24836 | WordPress GDPR Data Request Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24836</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Audrasjb GDPR Data Request Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GDPR Data Request Form: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24871 | WordPress Blocksy Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.19 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24871</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative Themes Blocksy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blocksy: from n/a through 2.0.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7169 | Impersonate vendor signed Powershell scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7169</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Snow Software Snow Inventory Agent on Windows allows Signature Spoof.This issue affects Snow Inventory Agent: through 6.14.5. Customers advised to upgrade to version 7.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0985 | PostgreSQL non-owner REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY executes arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0985</link><description>Late privilege drop in REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY in PostgreSQL allows an object creator to execute arbitrary SQL functions as the command issuer. The command intends to run SQL functions as the owner of the materialized view, enabling safe refresh of untrusted materialized views. The victim is a superuser or member of one of the attacker's roles. The attack requires luring the victim into running REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY on the attacker's materialized view. As part of exploiting this vulnerability, the attacker creates functions that use CREATE RULE to convert the internally-built temporary table to a view. Versions before PostgreSQL 15.6, 14.11, 13.14, and 12.18 are affected. The only known exploit does not work in PostgreSQL 16 and later. For defense in depth, PostgreSQL 16.2 adds the protections that older branches are using to fix their vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1149 | Improper validation of update packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1149</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Snow Software Inventory Agent on MacOS, Snow Software Inventory Agent on Windows, Snow Software Inventory Agent on Linux allows File Manipulation through Snow Update Packages.This issue affects Inventory Agent: through 6.12.0; Inventory Agent: through 6.14.5; Inventory Agent: through 6.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24877 | WordPress Wonder Slider Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 13.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24877</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Magic Hills Pty Ltd Wonder Slider Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Wonder Slider Lite: from n/a through 13.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24878 | WordPress Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PT Woo Plugins (by Webdados) Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1312 | Kernel: race condition leads to use after free during vma lock in lock_vma_under_rcu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1312</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel's Memory Management subsystem when a user wins two races at the same time with a fail in the mas_prev_slot function. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24113 | xxl-job =&lt; 2.4.1 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, which causes low-privileged users to control executor to RCE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24113</link><description>xxl-job =&lt; 2.4.1 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, which causes low-privileged users to control executor to RCE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24879 | WordPress Link Library Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.5.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24880 | WordPress Apollo13 Framework Extensions Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24880</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apollo13Themes Apollo13 Framework Extensions allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Apollo13 Framework Extensions: from n/a through 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6519 | Seeing admin password hash value in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6519</link><description>Exposure of Data Element to Wrong Session vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6518 | Password Disclosure in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6518</link><description>Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6517 | Seeing the SMS Verification Code in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6517</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6564 | Improper Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24881 | WordPress WP SMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24881</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VeronaLabs WP SMS – Messaging &amp; SMS Notification for WordPress, WooCommerce, GravityForms, etc allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP SMS – Messaging &amp; SMS Notification for WordPress, WooCommerce, GravityForms, etc: from n/a through 6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24885 | WordPress Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24885</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lê Văn Toản Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24886 | WordPress Product Labels For Woocommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24886</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Acowebs Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges): from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 10:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6515 | IDOR in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6515</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22464 | Dell EMC AppSync, versions from 4.2.0.0 to 4.6.0.0 including all Service Pack releases, contain an exposure of sensitive information vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22464</link><description>Dell EMC AppSync, versions from 4.2.0.0 to 4.6.0.0 including all Service Pack releases, contain an exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in AppSync server logs. A high privileged remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable system with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23452 | Apache bRPC: HTTP request smuggling vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23452</link><description>Request smuggling vulnerability in HTTP server in Apache bRPC 0.9.5~1.7.0 on all platforms allows attacker to smuggle request.

Vulnerability Cause Description：

The http_parser does not comply with the RFC-7230 HTTP 1.1 specification.

Attack scenario:
If a message is received with both a Transfer-Encoding and a Content-Length header field, such a message might indicate an attempt to perform request smuggling or response splitting.
One particular attack scenario is that a bRPC made http server on the backend receiving requests in one persistent connection from frontend server that uses TE to parse request with the logic that 'chunk' is contained in the TE field. in that case an attacker can smuggle a request into the connection to the backend server. 

Solution:
You can choose one solution from below:
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.8.0, which fixes this issue. Download link:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/releases/tag/1.8.0
 2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/2518</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0965 | The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0965</link><description>The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's page restriction and view page content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1207 | The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'calendar_request_params[dates_ddmmyy_csv]' parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1207</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'calendar_request_params[dates_ddmmyy_csv]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24034 | Setor Informatica S.I.L version 3.0 is vulnerable to Open Redirect via the hprinter parameter, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24034</link><description>Setor Informatica S.I.L version 3.0 is vulnerable to Open Redirect via the hprinter parameter, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24091 | Yealink Meeting Server before v26.0.0.66 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the file upload interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24091</link><description>Yealink Meeting Server before v26.0.0.66 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the file upload interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0511 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0511</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpr_update_form_action_meta function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to post metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24216 | Zentao v18.0 to v18.10 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the checkConnection method of /app/zentao/m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24216</link><description>Zentao v18.0 to v18.10 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the checkConnection method of /app/zentao/module/repo/model.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24202 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /upgrade/control.php of ZenTao Community Edition v18.10, ZenTao Biz v8.10, and ZenTao Max v4.10 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24202</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /upgrade/control.php of ZenTao Community Edition v18.10, ZenTao Biz v8.10, and ZenTao Max v4.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted .txt file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 04:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25148 | In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25148</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions the `doAsUserId` URL parameter may get leaked when creating linked content using the WYSIWYG editor and while impersonating a user. This may allow remote authenticated users to impersonate a user after accessing the linked content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25146 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 18, and o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25146</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 18, and older unsupported versions returns with different responses depending on whether a site does not exist or if the user does not have permission to access the site, which allows remote attackers to discover the existence of sites by enumerating URLs. This vulnerability occurs if locale.prepend.friendly.url.style=2 and if a custom 404 page is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5665 | The Payment Forms for Paystack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5665</link><description>The Payment Forms for Paystack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25144 | The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25144</link><description>The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before update 6, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions does not check the URL of the IFrame, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) via a self referencing IFrame.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47798 | Account lockout in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.0, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.2 before fix pack 5, and older unsu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47798</link><description>Account lockout in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.0, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.2 before fix pack 5, and older unsupported versions does not invalidate existing user sessions, which allows remote authenticated users to remain authenticated after an account has been locked.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22394 | An improper authentication vulnerability has been identified in SonicWall SonicOS SSL-VPN feature, which in specific conditions could allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22394</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been identified in SonicWall SonicOS SSL-VPN feature, which in specific conditions could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication. 

This issue affects only firmware version SonicOS 7.1.1-7040.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24003 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutMate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24003</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutMaterialCount() function of jshERP does not filter `column` and `order` parameters well enough, and an attacker can construct malicious payload to bypass jshERP's protection mechanism in `safeSqlParse` method for sql injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24014 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24014</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/author/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24017 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24017</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /common/dict/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24021 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24021</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/userFeedback/list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48974 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Axigen WebMail v.10.5.7 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48974</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Axigen WebMail v.10.5.7 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the serverName_input parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24018 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24018</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /system/dataPerm/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24025 | An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: upload(). ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24025</link><description>An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: upload(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filename parameter to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24350 | File Upload vulnerability in Software Publico e-Sic Livre v.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the extens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24350</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Software Publico e-Sic Livre v.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the extension filtering component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24023 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24023</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/bookContent/list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24024 | An arbitrary File download vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: fileDown...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24024</link><description>An arbitrary File download vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: fileDownload(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filePath and fieName parameters to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24026 | An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions at com.java2nb.system.controller.SysUserController...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24026</link><description>An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions at com.java2nb.system.controller.SysUserController: uploadImg(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filename parameter to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>