<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:08:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-46982 | Cache Poisoning in next.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46982</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. By sending a crafted HTTP request, it is possible to poison the cache of a non-dynamic server-side rendered route in the pages router (this does not affect the app router). When this crafted request is sent it could coerce Next.js to cache a route that is meant to not be cached and send a `Cache-Control: s-maxage=1, stale-while-revalidate` header which some upstream CDNs may cache as well. To be potentially affected all of the following must apply: 1. Next.js between 13.5.1 and 14.2.9, 2. Using pages router, &amp; 3. Using non-dynamic server-side rendered routes e.g. `pages/dashboard.tsx` not `pages/blog/[slug].tsx`. This vulnerability was resolved in Next.js v13.5.7, v14.2.10, and later. We recommend upgrading regardless of whether you can reproduce the issue or not. There are no official or recommended workarounds for this issue, we recommend that users patch to a safe version.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8904 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8904</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8905 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit stack corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8905</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit stack corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8906 | Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8906</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8907 | Insufficient data validation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8907</link><description>Insufficient data validation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to inject arbitrary scripts or HTML (XSS) via a crafted set of UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8908 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8908</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8909 | Inappropriate implementation in UI in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8909</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in UI in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 129.0.6668.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45815 | Prototype pollution in @backstage/plugin-catalog-backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45815</link><description>Backstage is an open framework for building developer portals. A malicious actor with authenticated access to a Backstage instance with the catalog backend plugin installed is able to interrupt the service using a specially crafted query to the catalog API. This has been fixed in the `1.26.0` release of the `@backstage/plugin-catalog-backend`. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45816 | Storage bucket Directory Traversal in @backstage/plugin-techdocs-backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45816</link><description>Backstage is an open framework for building developer portals. When using the AWS S3 or GCS storage provider for TechDocs it is possible to access content in the entire storage bucket. This can leak contents of the bucket that are not intended to be accessible, as well as bypass permission checks in Backstage. This has been fixed in the 1.10.13 release of the `@backstage/plugin-techdocs-backend` package. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46976 | Circumvention of cross site scripting Protection in @backstage/plugin-techdocs-backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46976</link><description>Backstage is an open framework for building developer portals. An attacker with control of the contents of the TechDocs storage buckets is able to inject executable scripts in the TechDocs content that will be executed in the victim's browser when browsing documentation or navigating to an attacker provided link. This has been fixed in the 1.10.13 release of the `@backstage/plugin-techdocs-backend` package. users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8957 | PTZOptics NDI and SDI Cameras Command Injection via NTP Address Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8957</link><description>PTZOptics PT30X-SDI/NDI-xx before firmware 6.3.40 is vulnerable to an OS command injection issue. The camera does not sufficiently validate the ntp_addr configuration value which may lead to arbitrary command execution when ntp_client is started. When chained with CVE-2024-8956, a remote and unauthenticated attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands on affected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45811 | server.fs.deny bypassed when using ?import&amp;amp;raw in vite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45811</link><description>Vite a frontend build tooling framework for javascript. In affected versions the contents of arbitrary files can be returned to the browser. `@fs` denies access to files outside of Vite serving allow list. Adding `?import&amp;amp;raw` to the URL bypasses this limitation and returns the file content if it exists. This issue has been patched in versions 5.4.6, 5.3.6, 5.2.14, 4.5.5, and 3.2.11. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45812 | DOM Clobbering gadget found in vite bundled scripts that leads to XSS in Vite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45812</link><description>Vite a frontend build tooling framework for javascript. Affected versions of vite were discovered to contain a DOM Clobbering vulnerability when building scripts to `cjs`/`iife`/`umd` output format. The DOM Clobbering gadget in the module can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) in web pages where scriptless attacker-controlled HTML elements (e.g., an img tag with an unsanitized name attribute) are present. DOM Clobbering is a type of code-reuse attack where the attacker first embeds a piece of non-script, seemingly benign HTML markups in the webpage (e.g. through a post or comment) and leverages the gadgets (pieces of js code) living in the existing javascript code to transform it into executable code. We have identified a DOM Clobbering vulnerability in Vite bundled scripts, particularly when the scripts dynamically import other scripts from the assets folder and the developer sets the build output format to `cjs`, `iife`, or `umd`. In such cases, Vite replaces relative paths starting with `__VITE_ASSET__` using the URL retrieved from `document.currentScript`. However, this implementation is vulnerable to a DOM Clobbering attack. The `document.currentScript` lookup can be shadowed by an attacker via the browser's named DOM tree element access mechanism. This manipulation allows an attacker to replace the intended script element with a malicious HTML element. When this happens, the src attribute of the attacker-controlled element is used as the URL for importing scripts, potentially leading to the dynamic loading of scripts from an attacker-controlled server. This vulnerability can result in cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks on websites that include Vite-bundled files (configured with an output format of `cjs`, `iife`, or `umd`) and allow users to inject certain scriptless HTML tags without properly sanitizing the name or id attributes. This issue has been patched in versions 5.4.6, 5.3.6, 5.2.14, 4.5.5, and 3.2.11. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8951 | SourceCodester Resort Reservation System manage_fee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8951</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Resort Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_fee.php. The manipulation of the argument toview leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8956 | PTZOptics NDI and SDI Cameras /cgi-bin/param.cgi Insufficient Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8956</link><description>PTZOptics PT30X-SDI/NDI-xx before firmware 6.3.40 is vulnerable to an insufficient authentication issue. The camera does not properly enforce authentication to /cgi-bin/param.cgi when requests are sent without an HTTP Authorization header. The result is a remote and unauthenticated attacker can leak sensitive data such as usernames, password hashes, and configurations details. Additionally, the attacker can update individual configuration values or overwrite the whole file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45398 | Remote command execution through file upload in contao/core-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45398</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In affected versions a back end user with access to the file manager can upload malicious files and execute them on the server. Users are advised to update to Contao 4.13.49, 5.3.15 or 5.4.3. Users unable to update are advised to configure their web server so it does not execute PHP files and other scripts in the Contao file upload directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45604 | Directory traversal in the file selector widget in contao/core-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45604</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In affected versions authenticated users in the back end can list files outside the document root in the file selector widget. Users are advised to update to Contao 4.13.49. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45605 | Improper authorization on deletion of user issue alert notifications in sentry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45605</link><description>Sentry is a developer-first error tracking and performance monitoring platform. An authenticated user delete the user issue alert notifications for arbitrary users given a know alert ID. A patch was issued to ensure authorization checks are properly scoped on requests to delete user alert notifications. Sentry SaaS users do not need to take any action. Self-Hosted Sentry users should upgrade to version 24.9.0 or higher. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45606 | Improper authorization on muting of alert rules in sentry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45606</link><description>Sentry is a developer-first error tracking and performance monitoring platform. An authenticated user can mute alert rules from arbitrary organizations and projects with a know rule ID. The user does not need to be a member of the organization or have permissions on the project.  In our review, we have identified no instances where alerts have been muted by unauthorized parties.  A patch was issued to ensure authorization checks are properly scoped on requests to mute alert rules. Authenticated users who do not have the necessary permissions are no longer able to mute alerts.  Sentry SaaS users do not need to take any action. Self-Hosted Sentry users should upgrade to version **24.9.0** or higher. The rule mute feature was generally available as of 23.6.0 but users with early access may have had the feature as of 23.4.0. Affected users are advised to upgrade to version 24.9.0. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8949 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Cart Content Master.php improper ownership management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8949</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Master.php of the component Cart Content Handler. The manipulation of the argument cart_id/id leads to improper ownership management. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8948 | MicroPython objint.c mpz_as_bytes heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8948</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroPython 1.23.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function mpz_as_bytes of the file py/objint.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 908ab1ceca15ee6fd0ef82ca4cba770a3ec41894. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. In micropython objint component, converting zero from int to bytes leads to heap buffer-overflow-write at mpz_as_bytes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45384 | Apache Druid: Padding oracle in druid-pac4j extension that allows an attacker to manipulate a pac4j session cookie via Padding Oracle Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45384</link><description>Padding Oracle vulnerability in Apache Druid extension, druid-pac4j.
This could allow an attacker to manipulate a pac4j session cookie.

This issue affects Apache Druid versions 0.18.0 through 30.0.0.
Since the druid-pac4j extension is optional and disabled by default, Druid installations not using the druid-pac4j extension are not affected by this vulnerability.

While we are not aware of a way to meaningfully exploit this flaw, we 
nevertheless recommend upgrading to version 30.0.1 or higher which fixes the issue
and ensuring you have a strong 
druid.auth.pac4j.cookiePassphrase as a precaution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45537 | Apache Druid: Users can provide MySQL JDBC properties not on allow list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45537</link><description>Apache Druid allows users with certain permissions to read data from other database systems using JDBC. This functionality allows trusted users to set up Druid lookups or run ingestion tasks. Druid also allows administrators to configure a list of allowed properties that users are able to provide for their JDBC connections. By default, this allowed properties list restricts users to TLS-related properties only. However, when configuration a MySQL JDBC connection, users can use a particularly-crafted JDBC connection string to provide properties that are not on this allow list.

Users without the permission to configure JDBC connections are not able to exploit this vulnerability.
CVE-2021-26919 describes a similar vulnerability which was partially addressed in Apache Druid 0.20.2.

This issue is fixed in Apache Druid 30.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45612 | Insert tag injection via canonical URL in Contao</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45612</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In affected versions an untrusted user can inject insert tags into the canonical tag, which are then replaced on the web page (front end). Users are advised to update to Contao 4.13.49, 5.3.15 or 5.4.3. Users unable to upgrade should disable canonical tags in the root page settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45803 | Cross site scripting (XSS) Vulnerability on route /wireui/button?label=Content in wireui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45803</link><description>Wire UI is a library of components and resources to empower Laravel and Livewire application development. A potential Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the `/wireui/button` endpoint, specifically through the `label` query parameter. Malicious actors could exploit this vulnerability by injecting JavaScript into the `label` parameter, leading to the execution of arbitrary code in the victim's browser. The `/wireui/button` endpoint dynamically renders button labels based on user-provided input via the `label` query parameter. Due to insufficient sanitization or escaping of this input, an attacker can inject malicious JavaScript. By crafting such a request, an attacker can inject arbitrary code that will be executed by the browser when the endpoint is accessed. If exploited, this vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the affected website. This could lead to: **Session Hijacking**: Stealing session cookies, tokens, or other sensitive information. **User Impersonation**: Performing unauthorized actions on behalf of authenticated users. **Phishing**: Redirecting users to malicious websites. **Content Manipulation**: Altering the appearance or behavior of the affected page to mislead users or execute further attacks. The severity of this vulnerability depends on the context of where the affected component is used, but in all cases, it poses a significant risk to user security. This issue has been addressed in release versions 1.19.3 and 2.1.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8946 | MicroPython VFS Unmount vfs.c mp_vfs_umount heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8946</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroPython 1.23.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function mp_vfs_umount of the file extmod/vfs.c of the component VFS Unmount Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 29943546343c92334e8518695a11fc0e2ceea68b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8947 | MicroPython objarray.c use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8947</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroPython 1.22.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file py/objarray.c. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 1.23.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 4bed614e707c0644c06e117f848fa12605c711cd. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38183 | GroupMe Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38183</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43460 | Dynamics 365 Business Central Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43460</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45798 | Multiple Poisoned Pipeline Execution (PPE) vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45798</link><description>arduino-esp32 is an Arduino core for the ESP32, ESP32-S2, ESP32-S3, ESP32-C3, ESP32-C6 and ESP32-H2 microcontrollers. The `arduino-esp32` CI is vulnerable to multiple Poisoned Pipeline Execution (PPE) vulnerabilities. Code injection in `tests_results.yml` workflow (`GHSL-2024-169`) and environment Variable injection (`GHSL-2024-170`). These issue have been addressed but users are advised to verify the contents of the downloaded artifacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8660 | Stored XSS in the &amp;quot;Top Navigator Bar&amp;quot; block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8660</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 through 9.3.3 are affected by a
stored XSS vulnerability in the "Top Navigator Bar" block.
Since the "Top Navigator Bar" output was not sufficiently sanitized, a rogue administrator could add a malicious payload that could be executed when targeted users visited the home page.The Concrete CMS Security Team gave this vulnerability a CVSS v4 score of 4.6
with vector  CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:L/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:N/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/4.0#CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:L/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:N/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N . This
does not affect versions below 9.0.0  since they do not have the Top
Navigator Bar Block. Thanks, Chu Quoc Khanh for reporting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8900 | An attacker could write data to the user's clipboard, bypassing the user prompt, during a certain sequence of navigational events. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8900</link><description>An attacker could write data to the user's clipboard, bypassing the user prompt, during a certain sequence of navigational events. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8944 | code-projects Hospital Management System check_availability.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8944</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file check_availability.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8945 | CodeCanyon RISE Ultimate Project Manager save sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8945</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeCanyon RISE Ultimate Project Manager 3.7.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php/dashboard/save. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38380 | Millbeck Communications Proroute H685t-w Cross-site Scripting.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38380</link><description>This vulnerability occurs when user-supplied input is improperly sanitized and then reflected back to the user's browser, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38812 | Heap-overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38812</link><description>The vCenter Server contains a heap-overflow vulnerability in the implementation of the DCERPC protocol. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted network packet potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38813 | Privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38813</link><description>The vCenter Server contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger this vulnerability to escalate privileges to root by sending a specially crafted network packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42501 | Authenticated Path Traversal Vulnerability Leads to a Remote Command Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42501</link><description>An authenticated Path Traversal vulnerabilities exists in the ArubaOS. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability allows an attacker to install unsigned packages on the underlying operating system, enabling the threat actor to execute arbitrary code or install implants.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42502 | Authenticated Remote Command Execution (RCE) Vulnerability in the AOS Command Line Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42502</link><description>Authenticated command injection vulnerability exists in the ArubaOS command line interface. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability result in the ability to inject shell commands on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42503 | Authenticated Remote Command Execution (RCE) Vulnerability in the Lua Package Within the AOS Command Line Interface (CLI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42503</link><description>Authenticated command execution vulnerability exist in the  ArubaOS command line interface (CLI). Successful exploitation of this vulnerabilities result in the ability to run arbitrary commands as a priviledge user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45682 | Millbeck Communications Proroute H685t-w Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45682</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability that may allow an attacker to inject malicious input on the device's operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8796 | Insufficient Default OTP Shared Secret Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8796</link><description>Under the default configuration, Devise-Two-Factor versions &gt;= 2.2.0 &amp; &lt; 6.0.0 generate TOTP shared secrets that are 120 bits instead of the 128-bit minimum defined by RFC 4226. Using a shared secret shorter than the minimum to generate a multi-factor authentication code could make it easier for an attacker to guess the shared secret and generate valid TOTP codes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8768 | Vllm: a completions api request with an empty prompt will crash the vllm api server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8768</link><description>A flaw was found in the vLLM library. A completions API request with an empty prompt will crash the vLLM API server, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8939 | Vllm: denials of service in vllm json web api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8939</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the ilab model serve component, where improper handling of the best_of parameter in the vllm JSON web API can lead to a Denial of Service (DoS). The API used for LLM-based sentence or chat completion accepts a best_of parameter to return the best completion from several options. When this parameter is set to a large value, the API does not handle timeouts or resource exhaustion properly, allowing an attacker to cause a DoS by consuming excessive system resources. This leads to the API becoming unresponsive, preventing legitimate users from accessing the service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7788 | Signatures in &amp;quot;repair mode&amp;quot; should not be trusted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7788</link><description>Improper Digital Signature Invalidation  vulnerability in Zip Repair Mode of The Document Foundation LibreOffice allows Signature forgery vulnerability in LibreOfficeThis issue affects LibreOffice: from 24.2 before &lt; 24.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27916 | Relative Path Traversal / Arbitrary File Deletion in Mautic (GrapesJS Builder)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27916</link><description>Prior to the patched version, logged in users of Mautic are vulnerable to Relative Path Traversal/Arbitrary File Deletion. Regardless of the level of access the Mautic user had, they could delete files other than those in the media folders such as system files, libraries or other important files.

This vulnerability exists in the implementation of the GrapesJS builder in Mautic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27915 | XSS Cross-site Scripting Stored (XSS) - Description field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27915</link><description>Prior to the patched version, there is an XSS vulnerability in the description fields within the Mautic application which could be exploited by a logged in user of Mautic with the appropriate permissions.

This could lead to the user having elevated access to the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38860 | Reflected links in error message facilitate phishing attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38860</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p16 and 2.2.0p34 allows attackers to craft malicious links that can facilitate phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22303 | WordPress Houzez theme &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22303</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in favethemes Houzez houzez allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47049 | The czim/file-handling package before 1.5.0 and 2.x before 2.3.0 (used with PHP Composer) does not properly validate URLs within makeFromUrl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47049</link><description>The czim/file-handling package before 1.5.0 and 2.x before 2.3.0 (used with PHP Composer) does not properly validate URLs within makeFromUrl and makeFromAny, leading to SSRF, and to directory traversal for the reading of local files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21743 | WordPress Houzez Login Register plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21743</link><description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in favethemes Houzez Login Register houzez-login-register.This issue affects Houzez Login Register: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47047 | An issue was discovered in the powermail extension through 12.4.0 for TYPO3. It fails to validate the mail parameter of the createAction, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47047</link><description>An issue was discovered in the powermail extension through 12.4.0 for TYPO3. It fails to validate the mail parameter of the createAction, resulting in Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in some configurations. An unauthenticated attacker can use this to display user-submitted data of all forms persisted by the extension. The fixed versions are 7.5.1, 8.5.1, 10.9.1, and 12.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46085 | FrogCMS V0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/rename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46085</link><description>FrogCMS V0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/rename</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46362 | FrogCMS V0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/create_directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46362</link><description>FrogCMS V0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/create_directory</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7873 | Stored XSS in Veribilim Software&amp;#x27;s Veribase Order Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7873</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting'), Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output, CWE - 83 Improper Neutralization of Script in Attributes in a Web Page vulnerability in Veribilim Software Veribase Order allows Stored XSS, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), Exploit Script-Based APIs, XSS Through HTTP Headers.This issue affects Veribase Order: before v4.010.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8897 | Under certain conditions, an attacker with the ability to redirect users to a malicious site via an open redirect on a trusted site, may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8897</link><description>Under certain conditions, an attacker with the ability to redirect users to a malicious site via an open redirect on a trusted site, may be able to spoof the address bar contents. This can lead to a malicious site to appear to have the same URL as the trusted site.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox for Android &lt; 130.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5998 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5998</link><description>A vulnerability in the FAISS.deserialize_from_bytes function of langchain-ai/langchain allows for pickle deserialization of untrusted data. This can lead to the execution of arbitrary commands via the os.system function. The issue affects the latest version of the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8767 | Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to unnecessary privileges assignment. The following products are affected: Acronis Backup plu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8767</link><description>Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to unnecessary privileges assignment. The following products are affected: Acronis Backup plugin for cPanel &amp; WHM (Linux) before build 619, Acronis Backup extension for Plesk (Linux) before build 555, Acronis Backup plugin for DirectAdmin (Linux) before build 147.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8761 | Share This Image &amp;lt;= 2.03 - Open Redirect via link Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8761</link><description>The Share This Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 2.03. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect url supplied via the link parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8490 | PropertyHive &amp;lt;= 2.0.19 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via save_account_details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8490</link><description>The PropertyHive plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.19. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_account_details' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to edit the name, email address, and password of an administrator account via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5170 | Logo Manager For Enamad &amp;lt;= 0.7.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5170</link><description>The Logo Manager For Enamad WordPress plugin through 0.7.1 does not sanitise and escape in its widgets settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8043 | Vikinghammer Tweet &amp;lt;= 0.2.4 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8043</link><description>The Vikinghammer Tweet WordPress plugin through 0.2.4 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8044 | infolinks Ad Wrap &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8044</link><description>The infolinks Ad Wrap WordPress plugin through 1.0.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8047 | Visual Sound (old) &amp;lt;= 1.06 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8047</link><description>The Visual Sound (old) WordPress plugin through 1.06 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8051 | Special Feed Items &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8051</link><description>The Special Feed Items WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8052 | Review Ratings &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8052</link><description>The Review Ratings WordPress plugin through 1.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8091 | Enhanced Search Box &amp;lt;= 0.6.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8091</link><description>The Enhanced Search Box WordPress plugin through 0.6.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8092 | Accordion Image Menu &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8092</link><description>The Accordion Image Menu WordPress plugin through 3.1.3 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8093 | Posts reminder &amp;lt;= 0.20 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8093</link><description>The Posts reminder WordPress plugin through 0.20 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8110 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability has been found in Dual-redundant Platform for Computer.
If a computer on which the affected product is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8110</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability has been found in Dual-redundant Platform for Computer.
If a computer on which the affected product is installed receives a large number of UDP broadcast packets in a short period, occasionally that computer may restart.
If both the active and standby computers are restarted at the same time, the functionality on that computer may be temporarily unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45496 | Openshift-controller-manager: elevated build pods can lead to node compromise in openshift</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45496</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift. This issue occurs due to the misuse of elevated privileges in the OpenShift Container Platform's build process. During the build initialization step, the git-clone container is run with a privileged security context, allowing unrestricted access to the node. An attacker with developer-level access can provide a crafted .gitconfig file containing commands executed during the cloning process, leading to arbitrary command execution on the worker node. An attacker running code in a privileged container could escalate their permissions on the node running the container.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7387 | Openshift/builder: path traversal allows command injection in privileged buildcontainer using docker build strategy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7387</link><description>A flaw was found in openshift/builder. This vulnerability allows command injection via path traversal, where a malicious user can execute arbitrary commands on the OpenShift node running the builder container. When using the “Docker” strategy, executable files inside the privileged build container can be overridden using the `spec.source.secrets.secret.destinationDir` attribute of the `BuildConfig` definition. An attacker running code in a privileged container could escalate their permissions on the node running the container.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23237 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23237</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27795 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A camera extension may be able to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27795</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A camera extension may be able to access the internet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27858 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27858</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27860 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An application may be able to read restricte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27860</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27861 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An application may be able to read restricte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27861</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27869 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to record th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27869</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to record the screen without an indicator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27874 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A remote attacker may be able to ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27874</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27875 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. Privacy Indicators for microphone or ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27875</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. Privacy Indicators for microphone or camera access may be attributed  incorrectly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27876 | A race condition was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, iOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27876</link><description>A race condition was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Unpacking a maliciously crafted archive may allow an attacker to write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27879 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27879</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker may be able to cause unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27880 | An out-of-bounds read issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27880</link><description>An out-of-bounds read issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, tvOS 18. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40770 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A non-privileged user may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40770</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A non-privileged user may be able to modify restricted network settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40790 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2. An app may be able to read sensitive data from ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40790</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2. An app may be able to read sensitive data from the GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40791 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40791</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access information about a user's contacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40797 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40797</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Visiting a malicious website may lead to user interface spoofing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40801 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40801</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40825 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app with root privileges may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40825</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app with root privileges may be able to modify the contents of system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40826 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An unencrypted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40826</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An unencrypted document may be written to a temporary file when using print preview.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40830 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An app may be able to enumerate a user'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40830</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40831 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access a user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40831</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access a user's Photos Library.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40837 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40837</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40838 | A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data to a protected location. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40838</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data to a protected location. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app may be able to access notifications from the user's device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40840 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40840</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access may be able to use Siri to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40841 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Proces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40841</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously crafted video file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40842 | An issue was addressed with improved validation of environment variables. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40842</link><description>An issue was addressed with improved validation of environment variables. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40843 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40843</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40844 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Ventura 13.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40844</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to observe data displayed to the user by Shortcuts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40845 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40845</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously crafted video file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40846 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40846</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously crafted video file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40847 | The issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40847</link><description>The issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40848 | A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40848</link><description>A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An attacker may be able to read sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40850 | A file access issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40850</link><description>A file access issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, tvOS 18. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40852 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40852</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker may be able to see recent photos without authentication in Assistive Access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40856 | An integrity issue was addressed with Beacon Protection. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40856</link><description>An integrity issue was addressed with Beacon Protection. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An attacker may be able to force a device to disconnect from a secure network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40857 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40857</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to universal cross site scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40859 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40859</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40860 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40860</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40861 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40861</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40862 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16. An attacker may be able to determine the Apple ID...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40862</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16. An attacker may be able to determine the Apple ID of the owner of the computer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40863 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An app may be able to leak sensitive us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40863</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40866 | The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, macOS Sequoia 15. Visiting a malicious website may lead to addre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40866</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, macOS Sequoia 15. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44124 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A malicious Bluetooth input device ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44124</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A malicious Bluetooth input device may bypass pairing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44125 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious application may be abl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44125</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious application may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44127 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Private B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44127</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Private Browsing tabs may be accessed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44128 | This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44128</link><description>This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An Automator Quick Action workflow may be able to bypass Gatekeeper.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44129 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to leak sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44129</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44130 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app with root privileges may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44130</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app with root privileges may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44131 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44131</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44132 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to break out of its...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44132</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44133 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. On MDM managed devices, an app may be abl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44133</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. On MDM managed devices, an app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44134 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44134</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44135 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44135</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected files within an App Sandbox container.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44139 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access may be able to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44139</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44146 | A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to break out of its san...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44146</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44147 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An app may gain unauthorized access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44147</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An app may gain unauthorized access to Local Network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44148 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of file attributes. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to break o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44148</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of file attributes. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44149 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44149</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44151 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44151</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44152 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44152</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44153 | The issue was addressed with improved permissions logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44153</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved permissions logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44154 | A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44154</link><description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44158 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44158</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. A shortcut may output sensitive user data without consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44160 | A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Seq...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44160</link><description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously crafted texture may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44161 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44161</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Processing a maliciously crafted texture may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44162 | This issue was addressed by enabling hardened runtime. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16. A malicious application may gain access to a user's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44162</link><description>This issue was addressed by enabling hardened runtime. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16. A malicious application may gain access to a user's Keychain items.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44163 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44163</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious application may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44164 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44164</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44165 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44165</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. Network traffic may leak outside a VPN tunnel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44166 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44166</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44167 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44167</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to overwrite arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44168 | A library injection issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44168</link><description>A library injection issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44169 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44169</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, tvOS 18. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44170 | A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data to a more secure location. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, watchOS 11, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44170</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data to a more secure location. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44171 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, watchOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44171</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, watchOS 11. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to Control Nearby Devices via accessibility features.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44176 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44176</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, tvOS 18. Processing an image may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44177 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44177</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44178 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44178</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44180 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access may be able to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44180</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. An attacker with physical access may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44181 | An issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44181</link><description>An issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44182 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44182</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access sensitive data logged when a shortcut fails to launch another app.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44183 | A logic error was addressed with improved error handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44183</link><description>A logic error was addressed with improved error handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, tvOS 18. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44184 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44184</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44186 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44186</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44187 | A cross-origin issue existed with "iframe" elements. This was addressed with improved tracking of security origins. This issue is fixed in S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44187</link><description>A cross-origin issue existed with "iframe" elements. This was addressed with improved tracking of security origins. This issue is fixed in Safari 18, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18. A malicious website may exfiltrate data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44188 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44188</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44189 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A logic issue existed where a process may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44189</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. A logic issue existed where a process may be able to capture screen contents without user consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44190 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44190</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44191 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, Xcode 16, visionOS 2, watchOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44191</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, Xcode 16, visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18. An app may gain unauthorized access to Bluetooth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44198 | An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44198</link><description>An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2, watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44202 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Private Browsing tabs may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44202</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. Private Browsing tabs may be accessed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4283 | URL Redirection to Untrusted Site (&amp;#x27;Open Redirect&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4283</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.1 before 17.1.7, 17.2 before 17.2.5, and 17.3 before 17.3.2. Under certain conditions an open redirect vulnerability could allow for an account takeover by breaking the OAuth flow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6685 | Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6685</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.1.7, 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and 17.3 prior to 17.3.2,  where group runners information was disclosed to unauthorised group members.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45416 | The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a local file inclusion vulnerability in session_init function. The session -LUA- files are stor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45416</link><description>The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a local file inclusion vulnerability in session_init function. The session -LUA- files are stored in the directory /var/lua_session, the function iterates on all files in this directory and executes them using the function dofile without any validation if it is a valid session file or not. An attacker who is able to write a malicious file in the sessions directory can get RCE as root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45413 | The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in rsa_decrypt function. This function is an API wr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45413</link><description>The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in rsa_decrypt function. This function is an API wrapper for LUA to decrypt RSA encrypted ciphertext, the decrypted data is stored on the stack without checking its length. An authenticated attacker can get RCE as root by exploiting this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45414 | The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in webPrivateDecrypt function. This function is res...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45414</link><description>The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in webPrivateDecrypt function. This function is responsible for decrypting RSA encrypted ciphertext, the encrypted data is supplied base64 encoded. The decoded ciphertext is stored on the stack without checking its length. An unauthenticated attacker can get RCE as root by exploiting this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45415 | The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in check_data_integrity function. This function is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45415</link><description>The HTTPD binary in multiple ZTE routers has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in check_data_integrity function. This function is responsible for validating the checksum of data in post request. The checksum is sent encrypted in the request, the function decrypts it and stores the checksum on the stack without validating it. An unauthenticated attacker can get RCE as root by exploiting this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22013 | U-Boot environment is read from unauthenticated partition.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22013</link><description>U-Boot environment is read from unauthenticated partition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44445 | An issue was discovered in BSC Smart Contract 0x0506e571aba3dd4c9d71bed479a4e6d40d95c833. Attackers are able to perform state manipulation a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44445</link><description>An issue was discovered in BSC Smart Contract 0x0506e571aba3dd4c9d71bed479a4e6d40d95c833. Attackers are able to perform state manipulation attacks by borrowing a large amount of money and then using this amount to inflate the token balance in the token pair, leading to increased profits without cost.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8766 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8766</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 38235.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34016 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34016</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 38235.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42798 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/index.php?page=user_list and /music/index.php?page=edit_user in Kashipara Musi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42798</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/index.php?page=user_list and /music/index.php?page=edit_user in Kashipara Music Management System v1.0. This allows a low privileged attacker to take over the administrator account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42794 | Kashipara Music Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /music/ajax.php?action=save_user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42794</link><description>Kashipara Music Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /music/ajax.php?action=save_user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45800 | Multiple mXSS found in snappymail HTML parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45800</link><description>Snappymail is an open source web-based email client. SnappyMail uses the `cleanHtml()` function to cleanup HTML and CSS in emails. Research discovered that the function has a few bugs which cause an mXSS exploit. Because the function allowed too many (invalid) HTML elements, it was possible (with incorrect markup) to trick the browser to "fix" the broken markup into valid markup. As a result a motivated attacker may be able to inject javascript. However, due to the default Content Security Policy the impact of the exploit is minimal. It could be possible to create an attack which leaks some data when loading images through the proxy.
This way it might be possible to use the proxy to attack the local system, like with `http://localhost:5000/leak`. Another attack could be to load a JavaScript attachment of the email. This is very tricky as the email must link to every possible UID as each email has a unique UID which has a value between 1 and 18446744073709551615 **v2.38.0** and up now remove unsupported HTML elements which mitigates the issue. Users are advised to upgrade. Older versions can install an extension named "Security mXSS" as a mitigation. This will be available at the administration area at `/?admin#/packages`. **NOTE:** this extension can not "fix" malicious code in encrypted messages or (html) attachments as it can't manipulate the JavaScript code for this. It only protects normal message HTML.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42795 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/view_user.php?id=3 and /music/controller.php?page=edit_user&amp;id=3 in Kashipara ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42795</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/view_user.php?id=3 and /music/controller.php?page=edit_user&amp;amp;id=3 in Kashipara Music Management System v1.0. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to view valid user details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42796 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/ajax.php?action=delete_genre in Kashipara Music Management System v1.0. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42796</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/ajax.php?action=delete_genre in Kashipara Music Management System v1.0. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to delete the valid music genre entries.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32034 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) in the decidim admin activity log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32034</link><description>decidim is a Free Open-Source participatory democracy, citizen participation and open government for cities and organizations. The admin panel is subject to potential Cross-site scripting (XSS) attach in case an admin assigns a valuator to a proposal, or does any other action that generates an admin activity log where one of the resources has an XSS crafted. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.27.7, 0.28.2, and newer. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may redirect the pages /admin and /admin/logs to other admin pages to prevent this access (i.e. `/admin/organization/edit`).</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39910 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) in the decidim admin panel with QuillJS WYSWYG editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39910</link><description>decidim is a Free Open-Source participatory democracy, citizen participation and open government for cities and organizations. The WYSWYG editor QuillJS is subject to potential XSS attach in case the attacker manages to modify the HTML before being uploaded to the server. The attacker is able to change e.g. to &lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt; if they know how to craft these requests themselves. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.27.7. All users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should review the user accounts that have access to the admin panel (i.e. general Administrators, and participatory space's Administrators) and remove access to them if they don't need it. Disable the "Enable rich text editor for participants" setting in the admin dashboard</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45799 | Javascript Injection in Vending Info/Buyers Info Module in FluxCP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45799</link><description>FluxCP is a web-based Control Panel for rAthena servers written in PHP. A javascript injection is possible via venders/buyers list pages and shop names, that are currently not sanitized. This allows executing arbitrary javascript code on the user's browser just by visiting the shop pages. As a result all logged in to fluxcp users can have their session info stolen. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.3. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45801 | Tampering by prototype polution in DOMPurify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45801</link><description>DOMPurify is a DOM-only, super-fast, uber-tolerant XSS sanitizer for HTML, MathML and SVG. It has been discovered that malicious HTML using special nesting techniques can bypass the depth checking added to DOMPurify in recent releases. It was also possible to use Prototype Pollution to weaken the depth check. This renders dompurify unable to avoid cross site scripting (XSS) attacks. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.5.4 and 3.1.3 of DOMPurify. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45854 | A Business Logic vulnerability in Shopkit 1.0 allows an attacker to add products with negative quantities to the shopping cart via the qtd p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45854</link><description>A Business Logic vulnerability in Shopkit 1.0 allows an attacker to add products with negative quantities to the shopping cart via the qtd parameter in the add-to-cart function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8661 | Stored XSS in the &amp;quot;Next&amp;amp;Previous Nav&amp;quot; block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8661</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 to 9.3.4 and below 8.5.18 are vulnerable to Stored XSS in the "Next&amp;amp;Previous Nav" block. A rogue administrator could add a malicious payload  by executing it in the browsers of targeted users. The Concrete CMS Security Team gave this vulnerability a CVSS v4 score of 4.6 with vector  CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:L/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:N/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/4.0#CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:L/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:N/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N  Since the "Next&amp;amp;Previous Nav" block output was not sufficiently sanitized, the malicious payload could be executed in the browsers of targeted users. Thanks, Chu Quoc Khanh for reporting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22351 | Out-of-bounds write in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22351</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23904 | NULL pointer dereference in the UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23904</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in the UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25546 | Out-of-bounds read in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25546</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41833 | A race condition in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41833</link><description>A race condition in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42772 | Untrusted pointer dereference in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) reference processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42772</link><description>Untrusted pointer dereference in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) reference processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43626 | Improper access control in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43626</link><description>Improper access control in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43753 | Improper conditions check in some Intel(R) Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43753</link><description>Improper conditions check in some Intel(R) Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21781 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to enable information disclosure or deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21781</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to enable information disclosure or denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21829 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware error handler for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21829</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware error handler for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21871 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21871</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23599 | Race condition in Seamless Firmware Updates for some Intel(R) reference platforms may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23599</link><description>Race condition in Seamless Firmware Updates for some Intel(R) reference platforms may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23984 | Observable discrepancy in RAPL interface for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23984</link><description>Observable discrepancy in RAPL interface for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24968 | Improper finite state machines (FSMs) in hardware logic in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an privileged user to potentially enable a den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24968</link><description>Improper finite state machines (FSMs) in hardware logic in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an privileged user to potentially enable a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28170 | Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28170</link><description>Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32666 | NULL pointer dereference in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32666</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32940 | Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32940</link><description>Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33848 | Uncaught exception in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33848</link><description>Uncaught exception in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34153 | Uncontrolled search path element in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34153</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34543 | Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34543</link><description>Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software for all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34545 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) RAID Web Console software all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34545</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) RAID Web Console software all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36247 | Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36247</link><description>Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36261 | Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36261</link><description>Improper access control in Intel(R) RAID Web Console software all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44623 | An issue in TuomoKu SPx-GC v.1.3.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the child_process.js function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44623</link><description>An issue in TuomoKu SPx-GC v.1.3.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the child_process.js function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8752 | WebIQ 2.15.9 Runtime on Windows - Directory Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8752</link><description>The Windows version of WebIQ 2.15.9 is affected by a directory traversal vulnerability that allows remote attackers to read any file on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38315 | IBM Aspera Shares session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38315</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.0 through 1.10.0 PL3 does not invalidate session after a password reset which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6401 | SQLi in SFS Consulting&amp;#x27;s InsureE GL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6401</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SFS Consulting InsureE GL allows SQL Injection.This issue affects InsureE GL: before 4.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7098 | XML Injection in SFS Consulting&amp;#x27;s ww.Winsure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7098</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in SFS Consulting ww.Winsure allows XML Injection.This issue affects ww.Winsure: before 4.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 14:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7104 | Remote Code Execution in SFS Consulting&amp;#x27;s ww.Winsure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7104</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in SFS Consulting ww.Winsure allows Code Injection.This issue affects ww.Winsure: before 4.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 14:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39772 | Silent Desktop Screenshot Capture</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39772</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.8.0 fail to safeguard screen capture functionality which allows an attacker to silently capture high-quality screenshots via JavaScript APIs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 14:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45835 | Insufficient Electron Fuses Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45835</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.8.0 fail to sufficiently configure Electron Fuses which allows an attacker to gather Chromium cookies or abuse other misconfigurations via remote/local access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 14:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46419 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 v4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the setWizardCfg function via the ssid5g parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46419</link><description>TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 v4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the setWizardCfg function via the ssid5g parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 13:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46424 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 v4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the UploadCustomModule function, which allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46424</link><description>TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 v4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the UploadCustomModule function, which allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via the File parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46451 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 v4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the setWiFiAclRules function via the desc parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46451</link><description>TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 v4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the setWiFiAclRules function via the desc parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46937 | An improper access control (IDOR) vulnerability in the /api-selfportal/get-info-token-properties endpoint in MFASOFT Secure Authentication S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46937</link><description>An improper access control (IDOR) vulnerability in the /api-selfportal/get-info-token-properties endpoint in MFASOFT Secure Authentication Server (SAS) 1.8.x through 1.9.x before 1.9.040924 allows remote attackers gain access to user tokens without authentication. The is a brute-force attack on the serial parameter by number identifier: GA00001, GA00002, GA00003, etc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22399 | Apache Seata: Remote Code Execution vulnerability via Hessian Deserialization in Apache Seata Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22399</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Seata. 

When developers disable authentication on the Seata-Server and do not use the Seata client SDK dependencies, they may construct uncontrolled serialized malicious requests by directly sending bytecode based on the Seata private protocol.

This issue affects Apache Seata: 2.0.0, from 1.0.0 through 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.0/1.8.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 11:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46970 | In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2024.1 hTML injection via the project name was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46970</link><description>In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2024.1 hTML injection via the project name was possible</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 10:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1578 | Multiple MiCard PLUS card reader dropped characters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1578</link><description>The MiCard PLUS Ci and MiCard PLUS BLE reader products developed by rf IDEAS and rebranded by NT-ware have a firmware fault that may result in characters randomly being dropped from some ID card reads, which would result in the wrong ID card number being assigned during ID card self-registration and might result in failed login attempts for end-users. Random characters being dropped from ID card numbers compromises the uniqueness of ID cards that can, therefore, result in a security issue if the users are using the ‘ID card self-registration’ function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 07:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45697 | D-Link WiFi router - Hidden Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45697</link><description>Certain models of D-Link wireless routers have a hidden functionality where the telnet service is enabled when the WAN port is plugged in. Unauthorized remote attackers can log in and execute OS commands using hard-coded credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 07:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45698 | D-Link WiFi router - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45698</link><description>Certain models of D-Link wireless routers do not properly validate user input in the telnet service, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to use hard-coded credentials to log into telnet and inject arbitrary OS commands, which can then be executed on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 07:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39613 | RCE in desktop app in Windows by local attacker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39613</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.8.0 fail to specify an absolute path when searching the cmd.exe file,  which allows a local attacker who is able to put an cmd.exe file in the Downloads folder of a user's machine to cause remote code execution on that machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45695 | D-Link WiFi router - Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45695</link><description>The web service of certain models of D-Link wireless routers contains a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability, which allows unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45696 | D-Link WiFi router - Hidden Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45696</link><description>Certain models of D-Link wireless routers contain hidden functionality. By sending specific packets to the web service, the attacker can forcibly enable the telnet service and log in using hard-coded credentials. The telnet service enabled through this method can only be accessed from within the same local network as the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45833 | Mobile password gets saved in dictionary under conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45833</link><description>Mattermost Mobile Apps versions &lt;=2.18.0 fail to disable autocomplete during login while typing the password and visible password is selected, which allows the password to get saved in the dictionary when the user has Swiftkey as the default keyboard, the masking is off and the password contains a special character..</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45694 | D-Link WiFi router - Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45694</link><description>The web service of certain models of D-Link wireless routers contains a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability, which allows unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8779 | The SYSCOM Group OMFLOW - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8779</link><description>OMFLOW from The SYSCOM Group does not properly restrict access to the system settings modification functionality, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to update system settings or create accounts with administrator privileges, thereby gaining control of the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8780 | The SYSCOM Group OMFLOW - Improper Authorization for Data Query Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8780</link><description>OMFLOW from The SYSCOM Group does not properly restrict the query range of its data query functionality, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to obtain accounts and password hashes of other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8777 | The SYSCOM Group OMFLOW - Information Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8777</link><description>OMFLOW from The SYSCOM Group has an information leakage vulnerability, allowing unauthorized remote attackers to read arbitrary system configurations. If LDAP authentication is enabled, attackers can obtain plaintext credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 05:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8778 | The SYSCOM Group OMFLOW - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8778</link><description>OMFLOW from The SYSCOM Group does not properly validate user input of the download functionality, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 05:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8776 | INTUMIT SmartRobot - Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8776</link><description>SmartRobot from INTUMIT does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unautheticated remote attackers to inject JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 05:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46958 | In Nextcloud Desktop Client 3.13.1 through 3.13.3 on Linux, synchronized files (between the server and client) may become world writable or ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46958</link><description>In Nextcloud Desktop Client 3.13.1 through 3.13.3 on Linux, synchronized files (between the server and client) may become world writable or world readable. This is fixed in 3.13.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 02:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8880 | playSMS Template index.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8880</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in playSMS 1.4.4/1.4.5/1.4.6/1.4.7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /playsms/index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=core_auth&amp;amp;route=forgot&amp;amp;op=forgot of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument username/email/captcha leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The project maintainer was informed early about the issue. Investigation shows that playSMS up to 1.4.3 contained a fix but later versions re-introduced the flaw. As long as the latest version of the playsms/tpl package is used, the software is not affected. Version &gt;=1.4.4 shall fix this issue for sure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 01:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46942 | In OpenDaylight Model-Driven Service Abstraction Layer (MD-SAL) through 13.0.1, a controller with a follower role can configure flow entries...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46942</link><description>In OpenDaylight Model-Driven Service Abstraction Layer (MD-SAL) through 13.0.1, a controller with a follower role can configure flow entries in an OpenDaylight clustering deployment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 23:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46943 | An issue was discovered in OpenDaylight Authentication, Authorization and Accounting (AAA) through 0.19.3. A rogue controller can join a clu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46943</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenDaylight Authentication, Authorization and Accounting (AAA) through 0.19.3. A rogue controller can join a cluster to impersonate an offline peer, even if this rogue controller does not possess the complete cluster configuration information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 23:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8876 | xiaohe4966 TpMeCMS lang path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8876</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in xiaohe4966 TpMeCMS up to 1.3.3.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index/ajax/lang. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.3.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 22:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46938 | An issue was discovered in Sitecore Experience Platform (XP), Experience Manager (XM), and Experience Commerce (XC) 8.0 Initial Release thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46938</link><description>An issue was discovered in Sitecore Experience Platform (XP), Experience Manager (XM), and Experience Commerce (XC) 8.0 Initial Release through 10.4 Initial Release. An unauthenticated attacker can read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 21:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8875 | vedees wcms finder.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8875</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in vedees wcms up to 0.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /wex/finder.php. The manipulation of the argument p leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 21:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46918 | app/Controller/UserLoginProfilesController.php in MISP before 2.4.198 does not prevent an org admin from viewing sensitive login fields of a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46918</link><description>app/Controller/UserLoginProfilesController.php in MISP before 2.4.198 does not prevent an org admin from viewing sensitive login fields of another org admin in the same org.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8869 | TOTOLINK A720R exportOvpn os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8869</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A720R 4.1.5. Affected is the function exportOvpn. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44053 | WordPress Opor Ayam theme &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mohammad Arif Opor Ayam allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Opor Ayam: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44054 | WordPress Fluida theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44054</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Fluida allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fluida: from n/a through 1.8.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44056 | WordPress Mantra theme &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44056</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Mantra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mantra: from n/a through 3.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44057 | WordPress Nirvana theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Nirvana allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Nirvana: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44058 | WordPress Parabola theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44058</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Parabola allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Parabola: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44059 | WordPress Custom Query Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44059</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MediaRon LLC Custom Query Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Query Blocks: from n/a through 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44060 | WordPress filmix theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44060</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jennifer Hall Filmix allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Filmix: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44062 | WordPress Custom Field Template plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44062</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hiroaki Miyashita Custom Field Template allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Field Template: from n/a through 2.6.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44063 | WordPress Happyforms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44063</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Happyforms allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Happyforms: from n/a through 1.26.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45455 | WordPress WP Meta SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45455</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Meta SEO allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Meta SEO: from n/a through 4.5.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45456 | WordPress WP Meta SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45456</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Meta SEO allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Meta SEO: from n/a through 4.5.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45457 | WordPress Spiffy Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45457</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins Spiffy Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Spiffy Calendar: from n/a through 4.9.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45458 | WordPress Spiffy Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.13 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45458</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins Spiffy Calendar allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Spiffy Calendar: from n/a through 4.9.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45459 | WordPress Product Slider for WooCommerce by PickPlugins plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.50 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45459</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Product Slider for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Product Slider for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.13.50.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45460 | WordPress Flipping Cards plugin &amp;lt;= 1.30 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Manu225 Flipping Cards allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Flipping Cards: from n/a through 1.30.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8868 | code-projects Crud Operation System savedata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8868</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file savedata.php. The manipulation of the argument sname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 03:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8867 | Perfex CRM Parameter Clients.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8867</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Perfex CRM 3.1.6. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file application/controllers/Clients.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 02:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8866 | AutoCMS robot.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8866</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AutoCMS 5.4. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/robot.php. The manipulation of the argument sidebar leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 01:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8865 | composiohq composio api.py path path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in composiohq composio up to 0.5.8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function path of the file composio\server\api.py. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8864 | composiohq composio calculator.py Calculator code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8864</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in composiohq composio up to 0.5.6 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Calculator of the file python/composio/tools/local/mathematical/actions/calculator.py. The manipulation leads to code injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 01:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>