<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-62419 | DataEase vulnerable to JDBC URL injection in DB2 and MongoDB data source configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62419</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a JDBC URL injection vulnerability exists in the DB2 and MongoDB data source configuration handlers. In the DB2 data source handler, when the extraParams field is empty, the HOSTNAME, PORT, and DATABASE values are directly concatenated into the JDBC URL without filtering illegal parameters. This allows an attacker to inject a malicious JDBC string into the HOSTNAME field to bypass previously patched vulnerabilities CVE-2025-57773 and CVE-2025-58045. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62420 | DataEase vulnerable to remote code execution via H2 JDBC driver bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62420</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a JDBC driver bypass vulnerability exists in the H2 database connection handler. The getJdbc function in H2.java checks if the jdbcUrl starts with jdbc:h2 but returns a separate jdbc field as the actual connection URL. An attacker can provide a jdbcUrl that starts with jdbc:h2 while supplying a different jdbc field with an arbitrary JDBC driver and connection string. This allows an authenticated attacker to trigger arbitrary JDBC connections with malicious drivers, potentially leading to remote code execution. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62421 | DataEase vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting via file upload bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62421</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists due to improper file upload validation and authentication bypass. The StaticResourceApi interface defines a route upload/{fileId} that uses a URL path parameter where both the filename and extension of uploaded files are controllable by users. During permission validation, the TokenFilter invokes the WhitelistUtils#match method to determine if the URL path is in the allowlist. If the requestURI ends with .js or similar extensions, it is directly deemed safe and bypasses permission checks. This allows an attacker to access "upload/1.js" while specifying arbitrary file extensions, enabling the upload of HTML files containing malicious JavaScript. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62422 | DataEase SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62422</link><description>DataEase is an open source data visualization and analytics platform. In versions 2.10.13 and earlier, the /de2api/datasetData/tableField interface is vulnerable to SQL injection. An attacker can construct a malicious tableName parameter to execute arbitrary SQL commands. This issue is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62171 | ImageMagick vulnerable to denial of service via integer overflow in BMP decoder on 32-bit systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62171</link><description>ImageMagick is an open source software suite for displaying, converting, and editing raster image files. In ImageMagick versions prior to 7.1.2-7 and 6.9.13-32, an integer overflow vulnerability exists in the BMP decoder on 32-bit systems. The vulnerability occurs in coders/bmp.c when calculating the extent value by multiplying image columns by bits per pixel. On 32-bit systems with size_t of 4 bytes, a malicious BMP file with specific dimensions can cause this multiplication to overflow and wrap to zero. The overflow check added to address CVE-2025-57803 is placed after the overflow occurs, making it ineffective. A specially crafted 58-byte BMP file with width set to 536,870,912 and 32 bits per pixel can trigger this overflow, causing the bytes_per_line calculation to become zero. This vulnerability only affects 32-bit builds of ImageMagick where default resource limits for width, height, and area have been manually increased beyond their defaults. 64-bit systems with size_t of 8 bytes are not vulnerable, and systems using default ImageMagick resource limits are not vulnerable. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 7.1.2-7 and 6.9.13-32.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62168 | Squid vulnerable to information disclosure via authentication credential leakage in error handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62168</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. In Squid versions prior to 7.2, a failure to redact HTTP authentication credentials in error handling allows information disclosure. The vulnerability allows a script to bypass browser security protections and learn the credentials a trusted client uses to authenticate. This potentially allows a remote client to identify security tokens or credentials used internally by a web application using Squid for backend load balancing. These attacks do not require Squid to be configured with HTTP authentication. The vulnerability is fixed in version 7.2. As a workaround, disable debug information in administrator mailto links generated by Squid by configuring squid.conf with email_err_data off.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59043 | OpenBao vulnerable to denial of service via malicious JSON request processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59043</link><description>OpenBao is an open source identity-based secrets management system. In OpenBao versions prior to 2.4.1, JSON objects after decoding may use significantly more memory than their serialized version. It is possible to craft a JSON payload to maximize the factor between serialized memory usage and deserialized memory usage, similar to a zip bomb, with factors reaching approximately 35. This can be used to circumvent the max_request_size configuration parameter which is intended to protect against denial of service attacks. The request body is parsed into a map very early in the request handling chain before authentication, which means an unauthenticated attacker can send a specifically crafted JSON object and cause an out-of-memory crash. Additionally, for requests with large numbers of strings, the audit subsystem can consume large quantities of CPU. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8414 | Zigbee Green Power Host Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8414</link><description>Due to improper input validation, a buffer overflow vulnerability is present in 

Zigbee EZSP Host Applications. If the buffer overflows, stack corruption is possible. In certain

conditions, this could lead to arbitrary code execution. Access to a network key is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58747 | Dify MCP OAuth Flow Vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58747</link><description>Dify is an LLM application development platform. In Dify versions through 1.9.1, the MCP OAuth component is vulnerable to cross-site scripting when a victim connects to an attacker-controlled remote MCP server. The vulnerability exists in the OAuth flow implementation where the authorization_url provided by a remote MCP server is directly passed to window.open without validation or sanitization. An attacker can craft a malicious MCP server that returns a JavaScript URI (such as javascript:alert(1)) in the authorization_url field, which is then executed when the victim attempts to connect to the MCP server. This allows the attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the Dify application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11905 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS gather.js getArticle code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11905</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. This vulnerability affects the function getArticle of the file app\modules\cms\controller\gather.js. The manipulation results in code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62356 | A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Qodo Qodo Gen IDE enables a threat actor to read arbitrary local files in and outside ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62356</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Qodo Qodo Gen IDE enables a threat actor to read arbitrary local files in and outside of current projects on an end user’s system. The vulnerability can be reached directly and through indirect prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26625 | Git LFS may write to arbitrary files via crafted symlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26625</link><description>Git LFS is a Git extension for versioning large files. In Git LFS versions 0.5.2 through 3.7.0, when populating a Git repository's working tree with the contents of Git LFS objects, certain Git LFS commands may write to files visible outside the current Git working tree if symbolic or hard links exist which collide with the paths of files tracked by Git LFS. The git lfs checkout and git lfs pull commands do not check for symbolic links before writing to files in the working tree, allowing an attacker to craft a repository containing symbolic or hard links that cause Git LFS to write to arbitrary file system locations accessible to the user running these commands. As well, when the git lfs checkout and git lfs pull commands are run in a bare repository, they could write to files visible outside the repository. The vulnerability is fixed in version 3.7.1. As a workaround, support for symlinks in Git may be disabled by setting the core.symlinks configuration option to false, after which further clones and fetches will not create symbolic links. However, any symbolic or hard links in existing repositories will still provide the opportunity for Git LFS to write to their targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49655 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the Keras framework running versions 3.11.0 up to but not including 3.11.3, enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49655</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the Keras framework running versions 3.11.0 up to but not including 3.11.3, enabling a maliciously uploaded Keras file containing a TorchModuleWrapper class to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when loaded despite safe mode being enabled. The vulnerability can be triggered through both local and remote files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57567 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the PluXml CMS theme editor, specifically in the minify.php file located under the def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57567</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the PluXml CMS theme editor, specifically in the minify.php file located under the default theme directory (/themes/defaut/css/minify.php). An authenticated administrator user can overwrite this file with arbitrary PHP code via the admin panel, enabling execution of system commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62353 | A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Windsurf IDE enables a threat actor to read and write arbitrary local files in and out...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62353</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Windsurf IDE enables a threat actor to read and write arbitrary local files in and outside of current projects on an end user’s system. The vulnerability can be reached directly and through indirect prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60279 | A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Illia Cloud illia-Builder before v4.8.5 allows authenticated users to send arbitrary r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60279</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Illia Cloud illia-Builder before v4.8.5 allows authenticated users to send arbitrary requests to internal services via the API. An attacker can leverage this to enumerate open ports based on response discrepancies and interact with internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11904 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS hasUse sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11904</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. This affects the function hasUse of the file /cms/model/hasUse. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55085 | Web http client: Unchecked Server-Side Malicious Packet Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55085</link><description>In NextX Duo before 6.4.4, in the HTTP client module, the network support code for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, the parsing of HTTP header fields was missing bounds verification. A crafted server response could cause undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60361 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function bochs_open.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60361</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function bochs_open.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48087 | WordPress Memberlite Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48087</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason C. Memberlite Shortcodes memberlite-shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Memberlite Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11902 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS findField sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11902</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function findField of the file /cms/article/findField. Performing manipulation of the argument cid results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11903 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS update sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11903</link><description>A flaw has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this issue is the function update of the file /cms/article/update. Executing manipulation of the argument cid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60359 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r_bin_object_new.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60359</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r_bin_object_new.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60360 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r2r_subprocess_init.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60360</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r2r_subprocess_init.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48044 | Authorization bypass when bypass policy condition evaluates to true</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48044</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in ash-project ash allows Authentication Bypass. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/ash/policy/policy.ex and program routines 'Elixir.Ash.Policy.Policy':expression/2.

This issue affects ash: from pkg:hex/ash@3.6.3 before pkg:hex/ash@3.7.1, from 3.6.3 before 3.7.1, from 79749c2685ea031ebb2de8cf60cc5edced6a8dd0 before 8b83efa225f657bfc3656ad8ee8485f9b2de923d.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28815 | Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product contain insufficient parameter validation, resulting in a command injection vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28815</link><description>Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product contain insufficient parameter validation, resulting in a command injection vulnerability. Attackers may exploit this to gain platform privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the system.iSecure Center is software released for China's domestic market only, with no overseas release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28814 | Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product have an improper file upload control vulnerability. Due to the improper verification of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28814</link><description>Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product have an improper file upload control vulnerability. Due to the improper verification of file to be uploaded, attackers may upload malicious files to the server. iSecure Center is software released for China's domestic market only, with no overseas release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11895 | Binary MLM Plan &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11895</link><description>The Binary MLM Plan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to insecure direct object reference in versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to the bmp_user_payout_detail_of_current_user() function selecting payout records solely by id without verifying ownership. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with the bmp_user role (often subscribers) to view other members' payout summaries via direct requests to the /bmp-account-detail/ endpoint with a crafted payout-id parameter granted they can access the shortcode output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 09:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55087 | In NextX Duo's snmp addon versions before 6.4.4, a part of the Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, an attacker could cause an out-of-bound read by a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55087</link><description>In NextX Duo's snmp addon versions before 6.4.4, a part of the Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, an attacker could cause an out-of-bound read by a crafted SNMPv3 security parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 06:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55097 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_streaming_sampling_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55097</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_streaming_sampling_get() when parsing a descriptor of an USB streaming device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55098 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_device_type_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55098</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_device_type_get()
      when parsing a descriptor of an USB audio device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55099 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_alternate_setting_locate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55099</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_alternate_setting_locate() when parsing a descriptor with attacker-controlled frequency fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55100 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio10_sam_parse_func()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55100</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio10_sam_parse_func() when parsing a list of sampling frequencies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55094 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _nx_icmpv6_validate_options()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55094</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in  _nx_icmpv6_validate_options() when handling a packet with ICMP6 options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55096 | Inadequate bounds check and potential underflow in _ux_host_class_hid_report_descriptor_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55096</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_hid_report_descriptor_get()
 when parsing a descriptor of an USB HID device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55092 | Potential out of bound read in _nx_ipv4_option_process()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55092</link><description>In Eclipse Foundation NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_option_process() when processing an IPv4 packet with the timestamp option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55093 | Out of bound read and write in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() when handling unicast DHCP messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55093</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() when handling unicast DHCP messages that could cause corruption of 4 bytes of memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11849 | Versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11849</link><description>Versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth before 1.11.0; versions of the package org.zwobble.mammoth:mammoth before 1.11.0 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal due to the lack of path or file type validation when processing a docx file containing an image with an external link (r:link attribute instead of embedded r:embed). The library resolves the URI to a file path and after reading, the content is encoded as base64 and included in the HTML output as a data URI. An attacker can read arbitrary files on the system where the conversion is performed or cause an excessive resources consumption by crafting a docx file that links to special device files such as /dev/random or /dev/zero.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11898 | Flowring Technology｜Agentflow - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11898</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Arbitrary File Reading vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11899 | Flowring Technology｜Agentflow - Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11899</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit the fixed key to generate verification information, thereby logging into the system as any user. Attacker must first obtain an user ID in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11900 | HGiga｜iSherlock - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11900</link><description>The iSherlock developed by HGiga has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6949 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A critical aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6949</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A critical authorization flaw in the API allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to create a new administrator account, including accounts with usernames identical to existing users. In certain scenarios, this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control over the affected device, leading to potential account impersonation. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6950 | An Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. The system employs a h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6950</link><description>An Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. The system employs a hard-coded secret key to sign JSON Web Tokens (JWT) used for authentication. This insecure implementation allows an unauthenticated attacker to forge valid tokens, thereby bypassing authentication controls and impersonating any user. Exploitation of this vulnerability can result in complete system compromise, enabling unauthorized access, data theft, and full administrative control over the affected device. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6893 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in brok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6893</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in broken access control has been identified in the /api/v1/setting/data endpoint of the affected device. This flaw allows a low-privileged authenticated user to call the API without the required permissions, thereby gaining the ability to access or modify system configuration data. Successful exploitation may lead to privilege escalation, allowing the attacker to access or modify sensitive system settings. While the overall impact is high, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6894 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6894</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authorization logic of the affected device allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to execute the administrative `ping` function, which is restricted to higher-privileged roles. This vulnerability enables the user to perform internal network reconnaissance, potentially discovering internal hosts or services that would otherwise be inaccessible. Repeated exploitation could lead to minor resource consumption. While the overall impact is limited, it may result in some loss of confidentiality and availability on the affected device. There is no impact on the integrity of the device, and the vulnerability does not affect any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6892 | An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6892</link><description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authentication mechanism allows unauthorized access to protected API endpoints, including those intended for administrative functions. This vulnerability can be exploited after a legitimate user has logged in, as the system fails to properly validate session context or privilege boundaries. An attacker may leverage this flaw to perform unauthorized privileged operations. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 02:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11896 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in PDF CMap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11896</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in a CMap, via the "UseCMap" entry, leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62504 | Envoy Lua filter use-after-free when oversized rewritten response body causes crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62504</link><description>Envoy is an open source edge and service proxy. Envoy versions earlier than 1.36.2, 1.35.6, 1.34.10, and 1.33.12 contain a use-after-free vulnerability in the Lua filter. When a Lua script executing in the response phase rewrites a response body so that its size exceeds the configured per_connection_buffer_limit_bytes (default 1MB), Envoy generates a local reply whose headers override the original response headers, leaving dangling references and causing a crash. This results in denial of service. Updating to versions 1.36.2, 1.35.6, 1.34.10, or 1.33.12 fixes the issue. Increasing per_connection_buffer_limit_bytes (and for HTTP/2 the initial_stream_window_size) or increasing per_request_buffer_limit_bytes / request_body_buffer_limit can reduce the likelihood of triggering the condition but does not correct the underlying memory safety flaw.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62506 | MinIO vulnerable to privilege escalation via session policy bypass in service accounts and STS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62506</link><description>MinIO is a high-performance object storage system. In all versions prior to RELEASE.2025-10-15T17-29-55Z, a privilege escalation vulnerability allows service accounts and STS (Security Token Service) accounts with restricted session policies to bypass their inline policy restrictions when performing operations on their own account, specifically when creating new service accounts for the same user. The vulnerability exists in the IAM policy validation logic where the code incorrectly relied on the DenyOnly argument when validating session policies for restricted accounts. When a session policy is present, the system should validate that the action is allowed by the session policy, not just that it is not denied. An attacker with valid credentials for a restricted service or STS account can create a new service account for itself without policy restrictions, resulting in a new service account with full parent privileges instead of being restricted by the inline policy. This allows the attacker to access buckets and objects beyond their intended restrictions and modify, delete, or create objects outside their authorized scope. The vulnerability is fixed in version RELEASE.2025-10-15T17-29-55Z.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11864 | NucleoidAI Nucleoid Outbound Request cluster.ts extension.apply server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11864</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in NucleoidAI Nucleoid up to 0.7.10. The impacted element is the function extension.apply of the file /src/cluster.ts of the component Outbound Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument https/ip/port/path/headers leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42192 | HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to a credential leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42192</link><description>HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to a credential leakage which could allow an attacker to access other computers or applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60358 | radare2 v.5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function _load_relocations.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60358</link><description>radare2 v.5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function _load_relocations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61554 | A divide-by-zero in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows local a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61554</link><description>A divide-by-zero in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows local attackers to cause a denial of service (host hypervisor crash) via a crafted PCI configuration space access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11492 | HTTP Configuration and Encryption in Transit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11492</link><description>In the ConnectWise Automate Agent, communications could be configured to use HTTP instead of HTTPS. In such cases, an on-path threat actor with a man-in-the-middle network position could intercept, modify, or replay agent-server traffic. Additionally, the encryption method used to obfuscate some communications over the HTTP channel is updated in the Automate 2025.9 patch to enforce HTTPS for all agent communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11493 | Self-Update Verification Mechanism Process in ConnectWise Automate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11493</link><description>The ConnectWise Automate Agent does not fully verify the authenticity of files downloaded from the server, such as updates, dependencies, and integrations. This creates a risk where an on-path attacker could perform a man-in-the-middle attack and substitute malicious files for legitimate ones by impersonating a legitimate server. This risk is mitigated when HTTPS is enforced and is related to CVE-2025-11492.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11852 | Apeman ID71 ONVIF Service device_service missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11852</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apeman ID71 218.53.203.117. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /onvif/device_service of the component ONVIF Service. Performing manipulation results in missing authentication. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11853 | Sismics Teedy API Endpoint file access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11853</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sismics Teedy up to 1.11. This affects an unknown function of the file /api/file of the component API Endpoint. Executing manipulation can lead to improper access controls. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61553 | An out-of-bounds write in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61553</link><description>An out-of-bounds write in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows local attackers to cause a denial of service (host hypervisor crash) via a crafted PCI configuration space access. Given it's a heap overflow in a privileged hypervisor context, exploitation may enable arbitrary code execution or guest-to-host privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34253 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt;= v1.3.1.4 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34253</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt;= 1.3.1.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to improper sanitization of the 'Network' field when editing the configuration, creating a profile, and adding a network. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript to be executed in the context of other users viewing the profile entry. NOTE: D-Link states that a fix is under development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34254 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt;= v1.3.1.4 Login Account Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34254</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt;= 1.3.1.4 contain an observable response discrepancy vulnerability. The application's 'Login' endpoint returns distinct JSON responses depending on whether the supplied username is associated with an existing account. Because the responses differ in the `error.message`string value, an unauthenticated remote attacker can enumerate valid usernames/accounts on the server. NOTE: D-Link states that a fix is under development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34255 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt;= v1.3.1.4 Forgot Password Account Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34255</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt;= 1.3.1.4 contain an observable response discrepancy vulnerability. The application's 'Forgot Password' endpoint returns distinct JSON responses depending on whether the supplied email address is associated with an existing account. Because the responses differ in the `data.exist` boolean value, an unauthenticated remote attacker can enumerate valid email addresses/accounts on the server. NOTE: D-Link states that a fix is under development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62428 | Drawing-Captcha APP Host Header Injection in `/register` and `/confirm-email` Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62428</link><description>Drawing-Captcha APP provides interactive, engaging verification for Web-Based Applications. The vulnerability is a Host Header Injection in the /register and /confirm-email endpoints. It allows an attacker to manipulate the Host header in HTTP requests to generate malicious email confirmation links. These links can redirect users to attacker-controlled domains. This vulnerability affects all users relying on email confirmation for account registration or verification. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.5-alpha-patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62425 | Matrix Authentication Service account password can be changed using an authenticated session without supplying the current password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62425</link><description>MAS (Matrix Authentication Service) is a user management and authentication service for Matrix homeservers, written and maintained by Element. A logic flaw in matrix-authentication-service 0.20.0 through 1.4.0 allows an attacker with access to an authenticated MAS session to perform sensitive operations without entering the current password. These include changing the current password, adding or removing an e-mail address and deactivating the account. The vulnerability only affects instances which have the local password database feature enabled (passwords section in the config). Patched in matrix-authentication-service 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62427 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Angular SSR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62427</link><description>The Angular CLI is a command-line interface tool for Angular applications. The vulnerability is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) flaw within the URL resolution mechanism of Angular's Server-Side Rendering package (@angular/ssr) before 19.2.18, 20.3.6, and 21.0.0-next.8. The function createRequestUrl uses the native URL constructor. When an incoming request path (e.g., originalUrl or url) begins with a double forward slash (//) or backslash (\\), the URL constructor treats it as a schema-relative URL. This behavior overrides the security-intended base URL (protocol, host, and port) supplied as the second argument, instead resolving the URL against the scheme of the base URL but adopting the attacker-controlled hostname. This allows an attacker to specify an external domain in the URL path, tricking the Angular SSR environment into setting the page's virtual location (accessible via DOCUMENT or PlatformLocation tokens) to this attacker-controlled domain. Any subsequent relative HTTP requests made during the SSR process (e.g., using HttpClient.get('assets/data.json')) will be incorrectly resolved against the attacker's domain, forcing the server to communicate with an arbitrary external endpoint. This vulnerability is fixed in 19.2.18, 20.3.6, and 21.0.0-next.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61514 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SageMath, Inc CoCalc before commit 0d2ff58 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61514</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SageMath, Inc CoCalc before commit 0d2ff58 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62414 | bagisto - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Create New Customer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62414</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. In Bagisto v2.3.7, the “Create New Customer” feature (in the admin panel) is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker with access to the admin create-customer form can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into certain input fields. These payloads may later execute in the context of an admin’s browser or another user viewing the customer data, enabling session theft or admin-level actions. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62415 | bagisto - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in TinyMCE Image Upload (HTML)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62415</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. In Bagisto v2.3.7, the TinyMCE image upload functionality allows an attacker with sufficient privileges (e.g. admin) to upload a crafted HTML file containing embedded JavaScript. When viewed, the malicious code executes in the context of the admin/user’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62416 | bagisto - Server Side Template Injection (SSTI) in Product Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62416</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. Bagisto v2.3.7 is vulnerable to Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) due to unsanitized user input being processed by the server-side templating engine when rendering product descriptions. This allows an attacker with product creation privileges to inject arbitrary template expressions that are evaluated by the backend — potentially leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62417 | bagisto - CSV Formula Injection in Create New Product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62417</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. When product data that begins with a spreadsheet formula character (for example =, +, -, or @) is accepted and later exported or saved into a CSV and opened in spreadsheet software, the spreadsheet will interpret that cell as a formula. This allows an attacker to supply a CSV field (e.g., product name) that contains a formula which may be evaluated by a victim’s spreadsheet application — potentially leading to data exfiltration and remote command execution (via older Excel exploits / OLE/cmd constructs or Excel macros). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62418 | bagisto - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in TinyMCE Image Upload (SVG)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62418</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. In Bagisto v2.3.7, the TinyMCE image upload functionality allows an attacker with sufficient privileges (e.g. admin) to upload a crafted SVG file containing embedded JavaScript. When viewed, the malicious code executes in the context of the admin/user’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62423 | ClipBucket V5 Blind SQL injection in the Admin Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62423</link><description>ClipBucket V5 provides open source video hosting with PHP. In version5.5.2 - #140 and earlier, a Blind SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Admin Area’s “/admin_area/login_as_user.php” file. Exploiting this vulnerability requires access privileges to the Admin Area.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60855 | Reolink Video Doorbell WiFi DB_566128M5MP_W performs insufficient validation of firmware update signatures. This allows attackers to load ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60855</link><description>Reolink Video Doorbell WiFi DB_566128M5MP_W performs insufficient validation of firmware update signatures. This allows attackers to load malicious firmware images, resulting in arbitrary code execution with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60639 | Hardcoded credentials in gsigel14 ATLAS-EPIC commit f29312c (2025-05-26).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60639</link><description>Hardcoded credentials in gsigel14 ATLAS-EPIC commit f29312c (2025-05-26).</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62413 | MQTTX vulnerable to cross-site scripting via improper message payload rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62413</link><description>MQTTX is an MQTT 5.0 desktop client and MQTT testing tool. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was introduced in MQTTX v1.12.0 due to improper handling of MQTT message payload rendering. Malicious payloads containing HTML or JavaScript could be rendered directly in the MQTTX message viewer. If exploited, this could allow attackers to execute arbitrary scripts in the context of the application UI — for example, attempting to access MQTT connection credentials or trigger unintended actions through script injection. This vulnerability is especially relevant when MQTTX is used with brokers in untrusted or multi-tenant environments, where message content cannot be fully controlled. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.12.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34512 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34512</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in index.php that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34513 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34513</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an OS command injection vulnerability in mbus_build_from_csv.php that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34514 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34514</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain authenticated OS command injection vulnerabilities in multiple web-accessible PHP scripts that call exec() and allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34515 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Root Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34515</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability in sync_project.sh that allows an attacker to escalate privileges to root. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34516 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34516</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain a use of default credentials vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain remote access. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34517 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34517</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an absolute path traversal vulnerability in get_file_content.php that allows an attacker to read arbitrary files. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34518 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34518</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain a relative path traversal vulnerability in get_file_content.php that allows an attacker to read arbitrary files. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34519 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Insecure Hashing Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34519</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an insecure hashing algorithm vulnerability. The product stores passwords using the MD5 hash function without applying a per‑password salt. Because MD5 is a fast, unsalted hash, an attacker who obtains the password database can efficiently perform offline dictionary, rainbow‑table, or brute‑force attacks to recover the original passwords. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62412 | LibreNMS alert-rules Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62412</link><description>LibreNMS  is a community-based GPL-licensed network monitoring system. The alert rule name in the Alerts &gt; Alert Rules page is not properly sanitized, and can be used to inject HTML code. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60641 | The file mexcel.php in the Vfront 0.99.52 codebase contains a vulnerable call to unserialize(base64_decode($_POST['mexcel'])), where $_POST[...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60641</link><description>The file mexcel.php in the Vfront 0.99.52 codebase contains a vulnerable call to unserialize(base64_decode($_POST['mexcel'])), where $_POST['mexcel'] is user-controlled input. This input is decoded from base64 and deserialized without validation or use of the allowed_classes option, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary PHP objects. This can lead to malicious behavior, such as Remote Code Execution (RCE), SQL Injection, Path Traversal, or Denial of Service, depending on the availability of exploitable classes in the Vfront codebase or its dependencies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62409 | Envoy allows large requests and responses to cause TCP connection pool crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62409</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Prior to 1.36.1, 1.35.5, 1.34.9, and 1.33.10, large requests and responses can potentially trigger TCP connection pool crashes due to flow control management in Envoy. It will happen when the connection is closing but upstream data is still coming, resulting in a buffer watermark callback nullptr reference. The vulnerability impacts TCP proxy and HTTP 1 &amp; 2 mixed use cases based on ALPN. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.1, 1.35.5, 1.34.9, and 1.33.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62411 | Stored XSS in Alert Transport name field in LibreNMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62411</link><description>LibreNMS &lt;= 25.8.0 contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Alert Transports management functionality. When an administrator creates a new Alert Transport, the value of the Transport name field is stored and later rendered in the Transports column of the Alert Rules page without proper input validation or output encoding. This leads to arbitrary JavaScript execution in the admin’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61330 | A hard-coded weak password vulnerability has been discovered in all Magic-branded devices from Chinese network equipment manufacturer H3C. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61330</link><description>A hard-coded weak password vulnerability has been discovered in all Magic-branded devices from Chinese network equipment manufacturer H3C. The vulnerability stems from the use of a hard-coded weak password for the root account in the /etc/shadow configuration or even the absence of any password at all. Some of these devices have the Telnet service enabled by default, or users can choose to enable the Telnet service in other device management interfaces (e.g. /debug.asp or /debug_telnet.asp). In addition, these devices have related interfaces called Virtual Servers, which can map the devices to the public network, posing the risk of remote attacks. Therefore, attackers can obtain the highest root privileges of the devices through the Telnet service using the weak password hardcoded in the firmware (or without a password), and remote attacks are possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62407 | Frappe has an Open Redirect on Login Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62407</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 14.98.0 and 15.83.0, an open redirect was possible  through the redirect argument on the login page, if a specific type of URL was passed in. This vulnerability is fixed in 14.98.0 and 15.83.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61923 | PrestaShop Checkout Backoffice directory traversal allows arbitrary file disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61923</link><description>PrestaShop Checkout is the PrestaShop official payment module in partnership with PayPal. In versions prior to 4.4.1 and 5.0.5, the backoffice is missing validation on input resulting in a directory traversal and arbitrary file disclosure. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 4.4.1 and 5.0.5. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61924 | PrestaShop Checkout Target PayPal merchant account hijacking from backoffice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61924</link><description>PrestaShop Checkout is the PrestaShop official payment module in partnership with PayPal. In versions prior to 4.4.1 and 5.0.5, the Target PayPal merchant account hijacking from backoffice due to wrong usage of the PHP array_search(). The vulnerability is fixed in versions 4.4.1 and 5.0.5. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61909 | Icinga 2 signals sent as root to processes based on PID file written by the Icinga 2 daemon user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61909</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. From 2.10.0 to before 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13, the safe-reload script (also used during systemctl reload icinga2) and logrotate configuration shipped with Icinga 2 read the PID of the main Icinga 2 process from a PID file writable by the daemon user, but send the signal as the root user. This can allow the Icinga user to send signals to processes it would otherwise not permitted to. A fix is included in the following Icinga 2 versions: 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61922 | PrestaShop Checkout allows customer account takeover via email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61922</link><description>PrestaShop Checkout is the PrestaShop official payment module in partnership with PayPal. In versions prior to 4.4.1 and 5.0.5, missing validation on the Express Checkout feature allows silent login, enabling account takeover via email. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 4.4.1 and 5.0.5. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62586 | OPEXUS FOIAXpress unauthenticated administrator password reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62586</link><description>OPEXUS FOIAXpress allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to reset the administrator password. Fixed in FOIAXpress version 11.13.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61907 | Icinga 2 API users could access restricted values in filter expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61907</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. In Icinga 2 versions 2.4 through 2.15.0, filter expressions provided to the various /v1/objects endpoints could access variables or objects that would otherwise be inaccessible for the user. This allows authenticated API users to learn information that should be hidden from them, including global variables not permitted by the variables permission and objects not permitted by the corresponding objects/query permissions. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61908 | Icinga 2 Denial of Service (DoS) By Dereferencing Invalid Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61908</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. From 2.10.0 to before 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13, when creating an invalid reference, such as a reference to null, dereferencing results in a segmentation fault. This can be used by any API user with access to an API endpoint that allows specifying a filter expression to crash the Icinga 2 daemon. A fix is included in the following Icinga 2 versions: 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61789 | Icinga DB Web hidden/protected custom variables are prone to filter enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61789</link><description>Icinga DB Web provides a graphical interface for Icinga monitoring. Before 1.1.4 and 1.2.3, an authorized user with access to Icinga DB Web, can use a custom variable in a filter that is either protected by icingadb/protect/variables or hidden by icingadb/denylist/variables, to guess values assigned to it. Versions 1.1.4 and 1.2.3 respond with an error if such a custom variable is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36128 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36128</link><description>IBM MQ 9.1, 9.2, 9.3, 9.4 LTS and 9.3, 9.4 CD is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by improper enforcement of the timeout on individual read operations. By conducting slowloris-type attacks, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58051 | Nextcloud Tables app allowed to include local file via PhpSpreadsheet when importing a table</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58051</link><description>Nextcloud Tables allows you to create your own tables with individual columns. Prior 0.7.6, 0.8.8, and 0.9.5, when importing a table, a user was able to specify files on the server and when their format is supported by the used PhpSpreadsheet library they would be included and their content leaked to the user. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Tables app is upgraded to 0.7.6, 0.8.8 or 0.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56699 | SQL injection vulnerability in the cmd component of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows an unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56699</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the cmd component of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows an unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the sender parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53092 | Strapi core vulnerable to sensitive data exposure via CORS misconfiguration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53092</link><description>Strapi is an open source headless content management system. Strapi versions prior to 5.20.0 contain a CORS misconfiguration vulnerability in default installations. By default, Strapi reflects the value of the Origin header back in the Access-Control-Allow-Origin response header without proper validation or whitelisting. This allows an attacker-controlled site to send credentialed requests to the Strapi backend. An attacker can exploit this by hosting a malicious site on a different origin (e.g., different port) and sending requests with credentials to the Strapi API. The vulnerability is fixed in version 5.20.0. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56700 | Boolean SQL injection vulnerability in the web app of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows a low level privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56700</link><description>Boolean SQL injection vulnerability in the web app of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows a low level priviliged user that has access to the platform, to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the datafine parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25298 | Missing Maximum Password Length Validation in Strapi Password Hashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25298</link><description>Strapi is an open source headless CMS. The @strapi/core package before version 5.10.3 does not enforce a maximum password length when using bcryptjs for password hashing. Bcryptjs ignores any bytes beyond 72, so passwords longer than 72 bytes are silently truncated. A user can create an account with a password exceeding 72 bytes and later authenticate with only the first 72 bytes. This reduces the effective entropy of overlong passwords and may mislead users who believe characters beyond 72 bytes are required, creating a low likelihood of unintended authentication if an attacker can obtain or guess the truncated portion. Long over‑length inputs can also impose unnecessary processing overhead. The issue is fixed in version 5.10.3. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56143 | Strapi Allows Unauthorized Access to Private Fields via parms.lookup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56143</link><description>Strapi is an open-source headless content management system. In versions from 5.0.0 to before 5.5.2, the lookup operator provided by the document service does not properly sanitize query parameters for private fields. An attacker can access private fields, including admin passwords and reset tokens, by crafting queries with the lookup parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11851 | Apeman ID71 set_alias.cgi cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11851</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Apeman ID71 EN75.8.53.20. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /set_alias.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument alias leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62490 | Use-after-free in js_print_object in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62490</link><description>In quickjs, in js_print_object, when printing an array, the function first fetches the array length and then loops over it. The issue is, printing a value is not side-effect free. An attacker-defined callback could run during js_print_value, during which the array could get resized and len1 become out of bounds. This results in a use-after-free.A second instance occurs in the same function during printing of a map or set objects. The code iterates over ms-&gt;records list, but once again, elements could be removed from the list during js_print_value call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62491 | Use-after-free in js_std_promise_rejection_check in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62491</link><description>A Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability exists in the QuickJS engine's standard library when iterating over the global list of unhandled rejected promises (ts-&gt;rejected_promise_list).

  *  The function js_std_promise_rejection_check attempts to iterate over the rejected_promise_list to report unhandled rejections using a standard list loop.


  *  The reason for a promise rejection is processed inside the loop, including calling js_std_dump_error1(ctx, rp-&gt;reason).


  *  If the promise rejection reason is an Error object that defines a custom property getter (e.g., via Object.defineProperty), this getter is executed during the error dumping process.


  *  The malicious custom getter can execute JavaScript code that calls catch() on the same rejected promise being processed.


  *  Calling catch() internally triggers js_std_promise_rejection_tracker, which then removes and frees the current promise entry (JSRejectedPromiseEntry) from the rejected_promise_list.


  *  Since the list iteration continues using the now-freed memory pointer (el), the subsequent loop access results in a Use-After-Free condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62492 | Heap out-of-bounds read in js_typed_array_indexOf in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62492</link><description>A vulnerability stemming from floating-point arithmetic precision errors exists in the QuickJS engine's implementation of TypedArray.prototype.indexOf() when a negative fromIndex argument is supplied.

  *  The fromIndex argument (read as a double variable, $d$) is used to calculate the starting position for the search.


  *  If d is negative, the index is calculated relative to the end of the array by adding the array's length (len) to d:



$$d_{new} = d + \text{len}$$


  *  Due to the inherent limitations of floating-point arithmetic, if the negative value $d$ is extremely small (e.g., $-1 \times 10^{-20}$), the addition $d + \text{len}$ can result in a loss of precision, yielding an outcome that is exactly equal to $\text{len}$.


  *  The result is then converted to an integer index $k$: $k = \text{len}$.


  *  The search function proceeds to read array elements starting from index $k$. Since valid indices are $0$ to $\text{len}-1$, starting the read at index $\text{len}$ is one element past the end of the array.


This allows an attacker to cause an Out-of-Bounds Read of one element immediately following the buffer. While the scope of this read is small (one element), it can potentially lead to Information Disclosure of adjacent memory contents, depending on the execution environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62493 | Heap out-of-bounds read in js_bigint_to_string1 in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62493</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the QuickJS engine's BigInt string conversion logic (js_bigint_to_string1) due to an incorrect calculation of the required number of digits, which in turn leads to reading memory past the allocated BigInt structure.

  *  The function determines the number of characters (n_digits) needed for the string representation by calculating:

$$ \\ \text{n\_digits} = (\text{n\_bits} + \text{log2\_radix} - 1) / \text{log2\_radix}$$

$$$$This formula is off-by-one in certain edge cases when calculating the necessary memory limbs. For instance, a 127-bit BigInt using radix 32 (where $\text{log2\_radix}=5$) is calculated to need $\text{n\_digits}=26$.


  *  The maximum number of bits actually stored is $\text{n\_bits}=127$, which requires only two 64-bit limbs ($\text{JS\_LIMB\_BITS}=64$).


  *  The conversion loop iterates $\text{n\_digits}=26$ times, attempting to read 5 bits in each iteration, totaling $26 \times 5 = 130$ bits.


  *  In the final iterations of the loop, the code attempts to read data that spans two limbs:

C



c = (r-&gt;tab[pos] &gt;&gt; shift) | (r-&gt;tab[pos + 1] &lt;&lt; (JS_LIMB_BITS - shift));









  *  Since the BigInt was only allocated two limbs, the read operation for r-&gt;tab[pos + 1] becomes an Out-of-Bounds Read when pos points to the last valid limb (e.g., $pos=1$).


This vulnerability allows an attacker to cause the engine to read and process data from the memory immediately following the BigInt buffer. This can lead to Information Disclosure of sensitive data stored on the heap adjacent to the BigInt object.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62494 | Type confusion in string addition in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62494</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in the handling of the string addition (+) operation within the QuickJS engine.

  *  The code first checks if the left-hand operand is a string.


  *  It then attempts to convert the right-hand operand to a primitive value using JS_ToPrimitiveFree. This conversion can trigger a callback (e.g., toString or valueOf).


  *  During this callback, an attacker can modify the type of the left-hand operand in memory, changing it from a string to a different type (e.g., an object or an array).


  *  The code then proceeds to call JS_ConcatStringInPlace, which still treats the modified left-hand value as a string.


This mismatch between the assumed type (string) and the actual type allows an attacker to control the data structure being processed by the concatenation logic, resulting in a type confusion condition. This can lead to out-of-bounds memory access, potentially resulting in memory corruption and arbitrary code execution in the context of the QuickJS runtime.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62495 | Type confusion in string addition in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62495</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the QuickJS regular expression engine (libregexp) due to an inconsistent representation of the bytecode buffer size.

  *  The regular expression bytecode is stored in a DynBuf structure, which correctly uses a $\text{size}\_\text{t}$ (an unsigned type, typically 64-bit) for its size member.


  *  However, several functions, such as re_emit_op_u32 and other internal parsing routines, incorrectly cast or store this DynBuf $\text{size}\_\text{t}$ value into a signed int (typically 32-bit).


  *  When a large or complex regular expression (such as those generated by a recursive pattern in a Proof-of-Concept) causes the bytecode size to exceed $2^{31}$ bytes (the maximum positive value for a signed 32-bit integer), the size value wraps around, resulting in a negative integer when stored in the int variable (Integer Overflow).


  *  This negative value is subsequently used in offset calculations. For example, within functions like re_parse_disjunction, the negative size is used to compute an offset (pos) for patching a jump instruction.


  *  This negative offset is then incorrectly added to the buffer pointer (s-&gt;byte\_code.buf + pos), leading to an out-of-bounds write on the first line of the snippet below:

put_u32(s-&gt;byte_code.buf + pos, len);</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62496 | Integer overflow in js_bigint_from_string in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62496</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the QuickJS engine's BigInt string parsing logic (js_bigint_from_string) when attempting to create a BigInt from a string with an excessively large number of digits.

The function calculates the necessary number of bits (n_bits) required to store the BigInt using the formula:

$$\text{n\_bits} = (\text{n\_digits} \times 27 + 7) / 8 \quad (\text{for radix 10})$$

  *  For large input strings (e.g., $79,536,432$ digits or more for base 10), the intermediate calculation $(\text{n\_digits} \times 27 + 7)$ exceeds the maximum value of a standard signed 32-bit integer, resulting in an Integer Overflow.


  *  The resulting n_bits value becomes unexpectedly small or even negative due to this wrap-around.


  *  This flawed n_bits is then used to compute n_limbs, the number of memory "limbs" needed for the BigInt object. Since n_bits is too small, the calculated n_limbs is also significantly underestimated.


  *  The function proceeds to allocate a JSBigInt object using this underestimated n_limbs.


  *  When the function later attempts to write the actual BigInt data into the allocated object, the small buffer size is quickly exceeded, leading to a Heap Out-of-Bounds Write as data is written past the end of the allocated r-&gt;tab array.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11840 | GNU Binutils ldmisc.c vfinfo out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11840</link><description>A weakness has been identified in GNU Binutils 2.45. The affected element is the function vfinfo of the file ldmisc.c. Executing manipulation can lead to out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This patch is called 16357. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11842 | Shazwazza Smidge Bundle path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11842</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Shazwazza Smidge up to 4.5.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Bundle Handler. The manipulation of the argument Version leads to path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. Upgrading to version 4.6.0 is sufficient to resolve this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9559 | Pega Platform versions 8.7.5 to Infinity 24.2.2 are affected by a Insecure Direct Object Reference issue in a user interface component that can only be used to read data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9559</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.7.5 to Infinity 24.2.2 are affected by a Insecure Direct Object Reference issue in a user interface component that can only be used to read data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55035 | Mattermost Desktop DoS when user has basic authentication server configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55035</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.13.0 fail to manage modals in the Mattermost Desktop App that stops a user with a server that uses basic authentication from accessing their server which allows an attacker that provides a malicious server to the user to deny use of the Desktop App via having the user configure the malicious server and forcing a modal popup that cannot be closed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36002 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36002</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 stores user credentials in configuration files which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41254 | Spring Framework STOMP CSRF Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41254</link><description>STOMP over WebSocket applications may be vulnerable to a security bypass that allows an attacker to send unauthorized messages.

Affected Spring Products and VersionsSpring Framework:

  *  6.2.0 - 6.2.11
  *  6.1.0 - 6.1.23
  *  6.0.x - 6.0.29
  *  5.3.0 - 5.3.45
  *  Older, unsupported versions are also affected.


MitigationUsers of affected versions should upgrade to the corresponding fixed version.

Affected version(s)Fix versionAvailability6.2.x6.2.12OSS6.1.x6.1.24 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ 6.0.xN/A Out of support https://spring.io/projects/spring-framework#support 5.3.x5.3.46 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ No further mitigation steps are necessary.

CreditThis vulnerability was discovered and responsibly reported by Jannis Kaiser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61536 | FelixRiddle dev-jobs-handlebars 1.0 uses absolute password-reset (magic) links using the untrusted `req.headers.host` header and forces the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61536</link><description>FelixRiddle dev-jobs-handlebars 1.0 uses absolute password-reset (magic) links using the untrusted `req.headers.host` header and forces the `http://` scheme. An attacker who can control the `Host` header (or exploit a misconfigured proxy/load-balancer that forwards the header unchanged) can cause reset links to point to attacker-controlled domains or be delivered via insecure HTTP, enabling token theft, phishing, and account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61541 | Webmin 2.510 is vulnerable to a Host Header Injection in the password reset functionality (forgot_send.cgi). The reset link sent to users is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61541</link><description>Webmin 2.510 is vulnerable to a Host Header Injection in the password reset functionality (forgot_send.cgi). The reset link sent to users is constructed using the HTTP Host header via get_webmin_email_url(). An attacker can manipulate the Host header to inject a malicious domain into the reset email. If a victim follows the poisoned link, the attacker can intercept the reset token and gain full control of the target account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61543 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability exists in the password reset functionality of CraftMyCMS 4.0.2.2. The system uses `$_SERVER['HTTP_HOST...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61543</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability exists in the password reset functionality of CraftMyCMS 4.0.2.2. The system uses `$_SERVER['HTTP_HOST']` directly to construct password reset links sent via email. An attacker can manipulate the Host header to send malicious reset links, enabling phishing attacks or account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22381 | Aggie 2.6.1 has a Host Header injection vulnerability in the forgot password functionality, allowing an attacker to reset a user's password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22381</link><description>Aggie 2.6.1 has a Host Header injection vulnerability in the forgot password functionality, allowing an attacker to reset a user's password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61539 | Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the u_name parameter in lostpassword.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61539</link><description>Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the u_name parameter in lostpassword.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61540 | SQL injection vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the username field in lostpassword.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61540</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the username field in lostpassword.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41253 | Spring Cloud Gateway Webflux SpEL Injection Vulnerability Allowing Exposure of Environment Variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41253</link><description>The following versions of Spring Cloud Gateway Server Webflux may be vulnerable to the ability to expose environment variables and system properties to attackers.

An application should be considered vulnerable when all the following are true:

  *  The application is using Spring Cloud Gateway Server Webflux (Spring Cloud Gateway Server WebMVC is not vulnerable).
  *  An admin or untrusted third party using Spring Expression Language (SpEL) to access environment variables or system properties via routes.
  *  An untrusted third party could create a route that uses SpEL to access environment variables or system properties if:  *  The Spring Cloud Gateway Server Webflux actuator web endpoint is enabled via management.endpoints.web.exposure.include=gateway and management.endpoint.gateway.enabled=trueor management.endpoint.gateway.access=unrestricte.
  *  The actuator endpoints are available to attackers.
  *  The actuator endpoints are unsecured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11839 | GNU Binutils prdbg.c tg_tag_type return value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11839</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in GNU Binutils 2.45. Impacted is the function tg_tag_type of the file prdbg.c. Performing manipulation results in unchecked return value. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46752 | A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiDLP 12.0.0 through 12.0.5, 11.5.1, 11.4.6, 11.4.5 allows attacker to inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46752</link><description>A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiDLP 12.0.0 through 12.0.5, 11.5.1, 11.4.6, 11.4.5 allows attacker to information disclosure via re-using the enrollment code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53950 | An Exposure of Private Personal Information ('Privacy Violation') vulnerability [CWE-359] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53950</link><description>An Exposure of Private Personal Information ('Privacy Violation') vulnerability [CWE-359] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin for MacOS and Windows 11.5.1 and 11.4.2 through 11.4.6 and 11.3.2 through 11.3.4 and 11.2.0 through 11.2.3 and 11.1.1. through 11.1.2 and 11.0.1 and 10.5.1 and 10.4.0, and 10.3.1 may allow an authenticated administrator to collect current user's email information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53951 | An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outloo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53951</link><description>An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin for Windows 11.5.1 and 11.4.2 through 11.4.6 and 11.3.2 through 11.3.4 and 11.2.0 through 11.2.3 and 11.1.1 through 11.1.2 and  11.0.1 and 10.5.1 and 10.4.0, and 10.3.1 may allow an authenticated attacker to escalate their privilege to LocalService via sending a crafted request to a local listening port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54658 | An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outloo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54658</link><description>An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin for MacOS 11.5.1 and 11.4.2 through 11.4.6 and 11.3.2 through 11.3.4 and 11.2.0 through 11.2.3 and 11.1.1 through 11.1.2 and 11.0.1 and 10.5.1 and 10.4.0, and 10.3.1 may allow an authenticated attacker to escalate their privilege to Root via sending a crafted request to a local listening port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9152 | Improper Privilege Management in Multiple WSO2 API Manager via keymanager-operations DCR Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9152</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability exists in WSO2 API Manager due to missing authentication and authorization checks in the keymanager-operations Dynamic Client Registration (DCR) endpoint.

A malicious user can exploit this flaw to generate access tokens with elevated privileges, potentially leading to administrative access and the ability to perform unauthorized operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9804 | Improper Access Control in Multiple WSO2 Products via Internal SOAP Admin Services and System REST APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9804</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to insufficient permission enforcement in certain internal SOAP Admin Services and System REST APIs. A low-privileged user may exploit this flaw to perform unauthorized operations, including accessing server-level information.

This vulnerability affects only internal administrative interfaces. APIs exposed through the WSO2 API Manager's API Gateway remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10611 | Potential Broken Access Control in Multiple WSO2 Products via System REST APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10611</link><description>Due to an insufficient access control implementation in multiple WSO2 Products, authentication and authorization checks for certain REST APIs can be bypassed, allowing them to be invoked without proper validation.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to a malicious actor gaining administrative access and performing unauthenticated and unauthorized administrative operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9955 | Improper Access Control in WSO2 Enterprise Integrator Product via SOAP Admin Services for Logs and User-Store Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9955</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in WSO2 Enterprise Integrator product due to insufficient permission restrictions on internal SOAP admin services related to system logs and user-store configuration. A low-privileged user can access log data and user-store configuration details that are not intended to be exposed at that privilege level.

While no credentials or sensitive user information are exposed, this vulnerability may allow unauthorized visibility into internal operational details, which could aid in further exploitation or reconnaissance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3930 | Lack of JWT Expiration after Log Out in Strapi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3930</link><description>Strapi uses JSON Web Tokens (JWT) for authentication. After logout or account deactivation, the JWT is not invalidated, which allows an attacker who has stolen or intercepted the token to freely reuse it until its expiration date (which is set to 30 days by default, but can be changed). 
The existence of /admin/renew-token endpoint allows anyone to renew near-expiration tokens indefinitely, further increasing the impact of this attack. 

This issue has been fixed in version 5.24.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24833 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO versions V4.0R1.0–V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24833</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO versions V4.0R1.0–V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52583 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's Web Server allows execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52583</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's Web Server allows execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54760 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54760</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54859 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54859</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55072 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V2.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55072</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V2.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58079 | Improper Protection of Alternate Path (CWE-424) in the AppSuite of desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allows an attacker to create malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58079</link><description>Improper Protection of Alternate Path (CWE-424) in the AppSuite of desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allows an attacker to create malicious AppSuite applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58426 | desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 contains a hard-coded cryptographic key, which allows an attacker to create malicious AppSuite applicatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58426</link><description>desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 contains a hard-coded cryptographic key, which allows an attacker to create malicious AppSuite applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6338 | Possible denial of service with multiple incoming connections to a Schannel based server with a TLS backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6338</link><description>There is an incomplete cleanup vulnerability in Qt Network's Schannel support on Windows which can lead to a Denial of Service over a long period.This issue affects Qt from 5.15.0 through 6.8.3, from 6.9.0 before 6.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53858 | ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Chat Rooms. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53858</link><description>ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Chat Rooms. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is accessing the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54461 | ChatLuck contains an insufficient granularity of access control vulnerability in Invitation of Guest Users. If exploited, an uninvited guest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54461</link><description>ChatLuck contains an insufficient granularity of access control vulnerability in Invitation of Guest Users. If exploited, an uninvited guest user may register itself as a guest user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58115 | ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Guest User Sign-up. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58115</link><description>ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Guest User Sign-up. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is accessing the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41410 | Slack import bypasses email verification for team access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41410</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to validate email ownership during Slack import process which allows attackers to create verified user accounts with arbitrary email domains via malicious Slack import data to bypass email-based team access restrictions</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58073 | Arbitrary Mattermost Team can be joined by manipulating the OAuth state</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58073</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.1, 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10 fail to verify a user has permission to join a Mattermost team using the original invite token which allows any attacked to join any team on a Mattermost server regardless of restrictions via manipulating the OAuth state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61581 | Apache Traffic Control: ReDoS issue in Traffic Router configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61581</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity vulnerability in Apache Traffic Control.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Control: all versions.

People with access to the management interface of the Traffic Router component could specify malicious patterns and cause unavailability.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0277 | HCL BigFix Mobile is affected by an insecure Content Security Policy (CSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0277</link><description>HCL BigFix Mobile 3.3 and earlier are vulnerable to certain insecure directives within the Content Security Policy (CSP).  An attacker could trick users into performing actions by not properly restricting the sources of scripts and other content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0276 | HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) is affected by an insecure Content Security Policy (CSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0276</link><description>HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) 3.3 and earlier are vulnerable to certain insecure directives within the Content Security Policy (CSP).  An attacker could trick users into performing actions by not properly restricting the sources of scripts and other content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10545 | Guest user can add unauthorized team users to private channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10545</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to properly validate guest user permissions when adding channel members which allows guest users to add any team members to their private channels via the `/api/v4/channels/{channel_id}/members` endpoint</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54499 | Insecure string comparison enables timing attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54499</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to use constant-time comparison for sensitive string comparisons which allows attackers to exploit timing oracles to perform byte-by-byte brute force attacks via response time analysis on Cloud API keys and OAuth client secrets</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54539 | Apache ActiveMQ NMS AMQP Client: Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54539</link><description>A Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability exists in the Apache ActiveMQ NMS AMQP Client.

This issue affects all versions of Apache ActiveMQ NMS AMQP up to and including 2.3.0, when establishing connections to untrusted AMQP servers. Malicious servers could exploit unbounded deserialization logic present in the client to craft responses that may lead to arbitrary code execution on the client side.

Although version 2.1.0 introduced a mechanism to restrict deserialization via allow/deny lists, the protection was found to be bypassable under certain conditions.

In line with Microsoft’s deprecation of binary serialization in .NET 9, the project is evaluating the removal of .NET binary serialization support from the NMS API entirely in future releases.

Mitigation and Recommendations:
Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade to version 2.4.0 or later, which resolves the issue. Additionally, projects depending on NMS-AMQP should migrate away from .NET binary serialization as part of a long-term hardening strategy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58075 | Arbitrary Mattermost Team can be joined by manipulating the SAML RelayState</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58075</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.1, 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10 fail to verify a user has permission to join a Mattermost team using the original invite token which allows any attacked to join any team on a Mattermost server regardless of restrictions via manipulating the RelayState</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41443 | Guest user can discover active public channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41443</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to properly validate guest user permissions when accessing channel information which allows guest users to discover active public channels and their metadata via the `/api/v4/teams/{team_id}/channels/ids` endpoint</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41018 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41018</link><description>SQL injection in Sergestec's Exito v8.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases through the 'cat' parameter in '/public.php'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41019 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41019</link><description>SQL injection in Sergestec's SISTICK v7.2. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases through the 'id' parameter in '/index.php?view=ticket_detail'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41020 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41020</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Sergestec's Exito v8.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access data belonging to other customers through the 'id' parameter in '/admin/ticket_a4.php'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41021 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41021</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Sergestec's Exito v8.0, consisting of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the 'obs' parameter in '/admin/index.php?action=product_update'. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55091 | Potential out of bound read in _nx_ip_packet_receive()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55091</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ip_packet_receive() function when received an Ethernet with type set as IP but no IP data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10706 | Classified Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10706</link><description>The Classified Pro theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check in the 'cwp_addons_update_plugin_cb' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Note: The required nonce for the vulnerability is in the CubeWP Framework plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10742 | Truelysell Core &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10742</link><description>The Truelysell Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change in versions up to, and including, 1.8.6. This is due to the plugin providing user-controlled access to objects, letting a user bypass authorization and access system resources. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts. Note: This can only be exploited unauthenticated if the attacker knows which page contains the 'truelysell_edit_staff' shortcode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10849 | Felan Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Activation/Deactivation via process_plugin_actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10849</link><description>The Felan Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'process_plugin_actions' function called via an AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to activate or deactivate arbitrary plugins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10850 | Felan Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Hardcoded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10850</link><description>The Felan Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to improper authentication in versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This is due to the hardcoded password in the 'fb_ajax_login_or_register' function and in the 'google_ajax_login_or_register' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, if they registered with facebook or google social login and did not change their password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62583 | Whale Browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to escape the iframe sandbox in a dual-tab environment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62583</link><description>Whale Browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to escape the iframe sandbox in a dual-tab environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62584 | Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Same-Origin Policy in a dual-tab environment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62584</link><description>Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Same-Origin Policy in a dual-tab environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62585 | Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Content Security Policy via a specific scheme in a dual-tab environment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62585</link><description>Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Content Security Policy via a specific scheme in a dual-tab environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55090 | Potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive()  in NetX Duo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55090</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() function when received an Ethernet frame with less than 4 bytes of IP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55084 | Out of bound read in _nx_secure_tls_proc_clienthello_supported_versions_extension()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55084</link><description>In NetX Duo version before 6.4.4, the component of Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was an incorrect bound check in_nx_secure_tls_proc_clienthello_supported_versions_extension() in the extension version field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55089 | Eclipse ThreadX FileX RAM disk driver buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55089</link><description>In FileX before 6.4.2, the file support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a possible buffer overflow in the FileX RAM disk driver. It could cause a remote execurtion after receiving a crafted sequence of packets</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58778 | Multiple versions of RG-EST300 provided by Ruijie Networks provide SSH server functionality. It is not documented in the manual, and enabled...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58778</link><description>Multiple versions of RG-EST300 provided by Ruijie Networks provide SSH server functionality. It is not documented in the manual, and enabled in the initial configuration. Anyone with the knowledge of the related credentials can log in to the affected device, leading to information disclosure, altering the system configurations, or causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0275 | HCL BigFix Mobile 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0275</link><description>HCL BigFix Mobile 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control.  Unauthorized users can access a small subset of endpoint actions, potentially allowing access to select internal functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0274 | HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0274</link><description>HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control.  Unauthorized users can access a small subset of endpoint actions, potentially allowing access to select internal functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11814 | Ultimate Addons for WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt; 3.21.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11814</link><description>The Ultimate Addons for WPBakery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to 3.21.1 (exclusive) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 04:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10700 | Ally - Web Accessibility &amp;amp; Usability &amp;lt;= 3.8.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10700</link><description>The Ally – Web Accessibility &amp; Usability plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the enable_unfiltered_files_upload function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable unfiltered file upload and add svg files to the upload list via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62579 | ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62579</link><description>ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62580 | ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62580</link><description>ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11683 | YAML::Syck versions before 1.36 for Perl has missing Null-Terminators which causes Out-of-Bounds Read and potential Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11683</link><description>YAML::Syck versions before 1.36 for Perl has missing null-terminators which causes out-of-bounds read and potential information disclosure

Missing null terminators in token.c leads to but-of-bounds read which allows adjacent variable to be read

The issue is seen with complex YAML files with a hash of all keys and empty values.  There is no indication that the issue leads to accessing memory outside that allocated to the module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 01:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43280 | The issue was resolved by not loading remote images This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Forwarding an email could display remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43280</link><description>The issue was resolved by not loading remote images This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Forwarding an email could display remote images in Mail in Lockdown Mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43281 | The issue was addressed with improved authentication. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A local attacker may be able to elevate the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43281</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved authentication. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43282 | A double free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43282</link><description>A double free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, watchOS 11.6, tvOS 18.6, visionOS 2.6, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, iPadOS 17.7.9. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43313 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43313</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11619 | Improper certificate validation when connecting to gateways in Devolutions Server 2025.3.2 and earlier allows attackers in MitM position to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11619</link><description>Improper certificate validation when connecting to gateways in Devolutions Server 2025.3.2 and earlier allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11568 | Luksmeta: data corruption when handling luks1 partitions with luksmeta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11568</link><description>A data corruption vulnerability has been identified in the luksmeta utility when used with the LUKS1 disk encryption format. An attacker with the necessary permissions can exploit this flaw by writing a large amount of metadata to an encrypted device. The utility fails to correctly validate the available space, causing the metadata to overwrite and corrupt the user's encrypted data. This action leads to a permanent loss of the stored information. Devices using the LUKS formats other than LUKS1 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62375 | go-witness Improper Verification of AWS EC2 Identity Documents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62375</link><description>go-witness and witness are Go modules for generating attestations. In go-witness versions 0.8.6 and earlier and witness versions 0.9.2 and earlier the AWS attestor improperly verifies AWS EC2 instance identity documents. Verification can incorrectly succeed when a signature is not present or is empty, and when RSA signature verification fails. The attestor also embeds a single legacy global AWS public certificate and does not account for newer region specific certificates issued in 2024, making detection of forged documents difficult without additional trusted region data. An attacker able to supply or intercept instance identity document data (such as through Instance Metadata Service impersonation) can cause a forged identity document to be accepted, leading to incorrect trust decisions based on the attestation. This is fixed in go-witness 0.9.1 and witness 0.10.1. As a workaround, manually verify the included identity document, signature, and public key with standard tools (for example openssl) following AWS’s verification guidance, or disable use of the AWS attestor until upgraded.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11832 | APIs Lack Rate Limiting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11832</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Azure Access Technology BLU-IC2, Azure Access Technology BLU-IC4 allows Flooding.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62371 | OpenSearch Data Prepper plugins trusts all SSL certificates by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62371</link><description>OpenSearch Data Prepper as an open source data collector for observability data. In versions prior to 2.12.2, the OpenSearch sink and source plugins in Data Prepper trust all SSL certificates by default when no certificate path is provided. Prior to this fix, the OpenSearch sink and source plugins would automatically use a trust all SSL strategy when connecting to OpenSearch clusters if no certificate path was explicitly configured. This behavior bypasses SSL certificate validation, potentially allowing attackers to intercept and modify data in transit through man-in-the-middle attacks. The vulnerability affects connections to OpenSearch when the cert parameter is not explicitly provided. This issue has been patched in version 2.12.2. As a workaround, users can add the cert parameter to their OpenSearch sink or source configuration with the path to the cluster's CA certificate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62410 | --disallow-code-generation-from-strings is not sufficient for isolating untrusted JavaScript in happy-dom</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62410</link><description>In versions before 20.0.2, it was found that --disallow-code-generation-from-strings is not sufficient for isolating untrusted JavaScript in happy-dom. The untrusted script and the rest of the application still run in the same Isolate/process, so attackers can deploy prototype pollution payloads to hijack important references like "process" in the example below, or to hijack control flow via flipping checks of undefined property. This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2025-61927. The vulnerability is fixed in 20.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62381 | sveltekit-superforms Prototype Pollution in `parseFormData` function of `formData.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62381</link><description>sveltekit-superforms makes SvelteKit forms a pleasure to use. sveltekit-superforms v2.27.3 and prior are susceptible to a prototype pollution vulnerability within the parseFormData function of formData.js. An attacker can inject string and array properties into Object.prototype, leading to denial of service, type confusion, and potential remote code execution in downstream applications that rely on polluted objects. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.27.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62382 | Frigate Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read via Export Thumbnail &amp;quot;image_path&amp;quot; parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62382</link><description>Frigate is a network video recorder (NVR) with realtime local object detection for IP cameras. Prior to 0.16.2, Frigate's export workflow allows an authenticated operator to nominate any filesystem location as the thumbnail source for a video export. Because that path is copied verbatim into the publicly served clips directory, the feature can be abused to read arbitrary files that reside on the host running Frigate. In practice, a low-privilege user with API access can pivot from viewing camera footage to exfiltrating sensitive configuration files, secrets, or user data from the appliance itself. This behavior violates the principle of least privilege for the export subsystem and turns a convenience feature into a direct information disclosure vector, with exploitation hinging on a short race window while the background exporter copies the chosen file into place before cleanup runs. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.16.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62378 | CommandKit exposes incorrect command name in context object for message command aliases</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62378</link><description>CommandKit is the discord.js meta-framework for building Discord bots. In versions 1.2.0-rc.1 through 1.2.0-rc.11, a logic flaw exists in the message command handler that affects how the commandName property is exposed to both middleware functions and command execution contexts when handling command aliases. When a message command is invoked using an alias, the ctx.commandName value reflects the alias rather than the canonical command name. This occurs in both middleware functions and within the command's own run function. Although not explicitly documented, CommandKit's examples and guidance around middleware usage implicitly convey that ctx.commandName represents the canonical command identifier. Middleware examples in the documentation consistently use ctx.commandName to reference the command being executed. Developers who assume ctx.commandName is canonical may introduce unintended behavior when relying on it for logic such as permission checks, rate limiting, or audit logging. This could allow unauthorized command execution or inaccurate access control decisions. Slash commands and context menu commands are not affected. This issue has been patched in version 1.2.0-rc.12, where ctx.commandName now consistently returns the actual canonical command name regardless of the alias used to invoke it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10576 | Sound Research SECOMNService Escalation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10576</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the audio package for certain HP PC products using the Sound Research SECOMN64 driver, which might allow escalation of privilege. HP is releasing updated audio packages to mitigate the potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10577 | Sound Research SECOMNService Escalation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10577</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the audio package for certain HP PC products using the Sound Research SECOMN64 driver, which might allow escalation of privilege. HP is releasing updated audio packages to mitigate the potential vulnerabilities</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62380 | Mailgen has HTML Injection and XSS Filter Bypass in Plaintext Emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62380</link><description>mailgen is a Node.js package that generates responsive HTML e-mails for sending transactional mail. Mailgen versions through 2.0.31 contain an HTML injection vulnerability in plaintext emails generated with the generatePlaintext method when user generated content is supplied. The plaintext generation code attempts to strip HTML tags using a regular expression and then decodes HTML entities, but tags that include certain Unicode line separator characters are not matched and removed. These encoded tags are later decoded into valid HTML content, allowing unexpected HTML to remain in output intended to be plaintext. Projects are affected if they call Mailgen.generatePlaintext with untrusted input and then render or otherwise process the returned string in a context where HTML is interpreted. This can lead to execution of attacker supplied script in the victim’s browser. Version 2.0.32 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54271 | Creative Cloud Desktop | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition (CWE-367)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54271</link><description>Creative Cloud Desktop versions 6.7.0.278 and earlier are affected by a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system write. A low-privileged attacker could exploit the timing between the check and use of a resource, potentially allowing unauthorized modifications to files. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20329 | Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint and RoomOS Software Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20329</link><description>A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information in clear text on an affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative&amp;nbsp;credentials.

This vulnerability exists because certain unencrypted credentials are stored when SIP media component logging is enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the audit logs on an affected system and obtaining credentials to which they may not normally have access. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to use those credentials to access confidential information, some of which may contain personally identifiable information (PII).
Note: To access the logs that are stored in the Webex Cloud or stored on the device itself, an attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20350 | Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Video Phone 8875 with SIP Firmware Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20350</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, Cisco IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Cisco Video Phone 8875 running Cisco SIP Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to a buffer overflow when an affected device processes HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP input to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
Note: To exploit this vulnerability, the phone must be registered to Cisco Unified Communications Manager and have Web Access enabled. Web Access is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20351 | Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Video Phone 8875 with SIP Firmware Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20351</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, Cisco IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Cisco Video Phone 8875 running Cisco SIP Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct XSS attacks against a user of the web UI.

This vulnerability exists because the web UI of an affected device does not sufficiently validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.
Note: To exploit this vulnerability, the phone must be registered to Cisco Unified Communications Manager and have Web Access enabled. Web Access is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20359 | Multiple Cisco Products Snort 3 MIME Information Disclosure or Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20359</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort 3 HTTP Decoder that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the disclosure of possible sensitive data or cause the Snort 3 Detection Engine to crash.

This vulnerability is due to an error in the logic of buffer handling when the MIME fields of the HTTP header are parsed. This can result in a buffer under-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an established connection that is parsed by Snort 3. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to induce one of two possible outcomes: the unexpected restarting of the Snort 3 Detection Engine, which could cause a denial of service (DoS) condition, or information disclosure of sensitive information in the Snort 3 data stream. Due to the under-read condition, it is possible that sensitive information that is not valid connection data could be returned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20360 | Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort 3 HTTP Decoder that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20360</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort 3 HTTP Decoder that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 Detection Engine to restart.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of complete error checking when the MIME fields of the HTTP header are parsed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an established connection to be parsed by Snort 3. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the Snort 3 Detection Engine unexpectedly restarts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58132 | Zoom Clients for Windows - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58132</link><description>Command injection in some Zoom Clients for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58133 | Zoom Rooms Clients - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58133</link><description>Authentication bypass in some Zoom Rooms Clients before version 6.5.1 may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62379 | Open Redirect in reflex-dev/reflex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62379</link><description>Reflex is a library to build full-stack web apps in pure Python. In versions 0.5.4 through 0.8.14, the /auth-codespace endpoint automatically assigns the redirect_to query parameter value directly to client-side links without any validation and triggers automatic clicks when the page loads in a GitHub Codespaces environment. This allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs. The vulnerable route is only registered when a Codespaces environment is detected, and the detection is controlled by environment variables. The same behavior can be activated in production if the GITHUB_CODESPACES_PORT_FORWARDING_DOMAIN environment variable is set. The vulnerability occurs because the code assigns the redirect_to query parameter directly to a.href without any validation and immediately triggers a click (automatic navigation), allowing users to be sent to arbitrary external domains. The execution condition is based on the presence of a sessionStorage flag, meaning it triggers immediately on first visits or in incognito/private browsing windows, with no server-side origin/scheme whitelist or internal path enforcement defenses in place. This issue has been patched in version 0.8.15. As a workaround, users can ensure that GITHUB_CODESPACES_PORT_FORWARDING_DOMAIN is not set in a production environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59419 | Netty netty-codec-smtp SMTP Command Injection Vulnerability Allowing Email Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59419</link><description>Netty is an asynchronous, event-driven network application framework. In versions prior to 4.1.128.Final and 4.2.7.Final, the SMTP codec in Netty contains an SMTP command injection vulnerability due to insufficient input validation for Carriage Return (\r) and Line Feed (\n) characters in user-supplied parameters. The vulnerability exists in io.netty.handler.codec.smtp.DefaultSmtpRequest, where parameters are directly concatenated into the SMTP command string without sanitization. When methods such as SmtpRequests.rcpt(recipient) are called with a malicious string containing CRLF sequences, attackers can inject arbitrary SMTP commands. Because the injected commands are sent from the server's trusted IP address, resulting emails will likely pass SPF and DKIM authentication checks, making them appear legitimate. This allows remote attackers who can control SMTP command parameters (such as email recipients) to forge arbitrary emails from the trusted server, potentially impersonating executives and forging high-stakes corporate communications. This issue has been patched in versions 4.1.129.Final and 4.2.8.Final. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2529 | IBM Terracotta denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2529</link><description>Applications using affected versions of Ehcache 3.x can experience degraded cache-write performance if the application using Ehcache utilizes keys sourced from (malicious) external parties in an unfiltered/unsalted way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62370 | Alloy Core has a DoS vulnerability on `alloy_dyn_abi::TypedData` hashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62370</link><description>Alloy Core libraries at the root of the Rust Ethereum ecosystem. Prior to 0.8.26 and 1.4.1, an uncaught panic triggered by malformed input to alloy_dyn_abi::TypedData could lead to a denial-of-service (DoS) via eip712_signing_hash(). Software with high availability requirements such as network services may be particularly impacted. If in use, external auto-restarting mechanisms can partially mitigate the availability issues unless repeated attacks are possible. The vulnerability was patched by adding a check to ensure the element is not empty before accessing its first element; an error is returned if it is empty. The fix is included in version v1.4.1 and backported to v0.8.26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57780 | F5OS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57780</link><description>A vulnerability exists in F5OS-A and F5OS-C system that may allow an authenticated attacker with local access to escalate their privileges.  A successful exploit may allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58071 | BIG-IP IPSec vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58071</link><description>When IPsec is configured on the BIG-IP system, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61933 | BIG-IP APM cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61933</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of BIG-IP APM that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the targeted logged-out user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61935 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61935</link><description>When a BIG IP Advanced WAF or ASM security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the bd process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61990 | TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61990</link><description>When using a multi-bladed platform with more than one blade, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53860 | F5OS-A FIPS HSM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53860</link><description>A vulnerability exists in F5OS-A software that allows a highly privileged authenticated attacker to access sensitive FIPS hardware security module (HSM) information on F5 rSeries systems.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10581 | A potential DLL hijacking vulnerability was discovered in the Lenovo PC Manager during an internal security assessment that could allow a lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10581</link><description>A potential DLL hijacking vulnerability was discovered in the Lenovo PC Manager during an internal security assessment that could allow a local authenticated user to execute code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10699 | A vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo LeCloud client application that, under certain conditions, could allow information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10699</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo LeCloud client application that, under certain conditions, could allow information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56749 | Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 6.14 uses a hardcoded default JWT secret for token signing. This predictable secret allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56749</link><description>Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 6.14 uses a hardcoded default JWT secret for token signing. This predictable secret allows attackers to forge valid JWT tokens, leading to authentication bypass and unauthorized access to any user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6026 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Universal Device Client (UDC) that could allow a user capable of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6026</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Universal Device Client (UDC) that could allow a user capable of intercepting network traffic to obtain encrypted application metadata, including device information, geolocation, and telemetry data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8486 | A potential vulnerability was reported in PC Manager that could allow a local authenticated user to execute code with elevated privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8486</link><description>A potential vulnerability was reported in PC Manager that could allow a local authenticated user to execute code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9548 | A potential null pointer dereference vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Power Management Driver that could allow a local authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9548</link><description>A potential null pointer dereference vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Power Management Driver that could allow a local authenticated user to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55083 | Broken bounds check in Broken bounds check in _nx_secure_tls_process_clienthello_psk_extension()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55083</link><description>In NetX Duo version before 6.4.4, the component of Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was an incorrect bound check resulting it out by two out of bound read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56748 | Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 5.13 uses predictable password reset tokens based on Base64 encoded templates without rate limi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56748</link><description>Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 5.13 uses predictable password reset tokens based on Base64 encoded templates without rate limiting, allowing brute force attacks to guess valid reset tokens and compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56746 | Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 5.13 does not regenerate session IDs upon successful authentication, enabling session fixation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56746</link><description>Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 5.13 does not regenerate session IDs upon successful authentication, enabling session fixation attacks where attackers can hijack user sessions by predetermining session identifiers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41430 | BIG-IP SSL Orchestrator vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41430</link><description>When BIG-IP SSL Orchestrator is enabled, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46706 | BIG-IP iRules vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46706</link><description>When an iRule containing the HTTP::respond command is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47148 | BIG-IP APM and SSL Orchestrator vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47148</link><description>When the BIG-IP system is configured as both a Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) service provider (SP) and Identity Provider (IdP), with single logout (SLO) enabled on an access policy, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47150 | F5OS SNMP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47150</link><description>When SNMP is configured on F5OS Appliance and Chassis systems, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in SNMP memory resource utilization.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48008 | BIG-IP MPTCP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48008</link><description>When a TCP profile with Multipath TCP (MPTCP) enabled is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic along with conditions beyond the attacker's control can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53474 | BIG-IP iRules vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53474</link><description>When an iRule using an ILX::call command is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53521 | BigIP APM Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53521</link><description>When a BIG-IP APM Access Policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause TMM to terminate.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53856 | TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53856</link><description>When a virtual server, network address translation (NAT) object, or secure network address translation (SNAT) object uses the embedded Packet Velocity Acceleration (ePVA) feature, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  To determine which BIG-IP platforms have an ePVA chip refer to  K12837: Overview of the ePVA feature https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K12837 .  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53868 | BIG-IP SCP and SFTP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53868</link><description>When running in Appliance mode, a highly privileged authenticated attacker with access to SCP and SFTP may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions using undisclosed commands.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54479 | BIG-IP PEM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54479</link><description>When a classification profile is configured on a virtual server without an HTTP or HTTP/2 profile, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54755 | BIG-IP Configuration utility vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54755</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in TMUI that allows an authenticated attacker to access files which are not limited to the intended files.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54805 | TMM Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54805</link><description>When an iRule is configured on a virtual server via the declarative API, upon re-instantiation, the cleanup process can cause an increase in the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) memory resource utilization.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54854 | BigIP APM Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54854</link><description>When a BIG-IP APM OAuth access profile (Resource Server or Resource Client) is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the apmd process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54858 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54858</link><description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF or BIG-IP ASM Security Policy is configured with a JSON content profile that has a malformed JSON schema, and the security policy is applied to a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the bd process to terminate.

 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55036 | BIG-IP SSL Orchestrator vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55036</link><description>When BIG-IP SSL Orchestrator explicit forward proxy is configured on a virtual server and the proxy connect feature is enabled, undisclosed traffic may cause memory corruption.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55669 | BIG-IP HTTP/2 vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55669</link><description>When the BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM security policy and a server-side HTTP/2 profile are configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55670 | BIG-IP Next (CNF, SPK, and Kubernetes) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55670</link><description>On BIG-IP Next CNF, BIG-IP Next SPK, and BIG-IP Next for Kubernetes systems, repeated undisclosed API calls can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58096 | BIG-IP TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58096</link><description>When the database variable tm.tcpudptxchecksum is configured as non-default value Software-only on a BIG-IP system, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58120 | BIG-IP Next (CNF, SPK, and Kubernetes) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58120</link><description>When HTTP/2 Ingress is configured, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58153 | BIG-IP HSB vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58153</link><description>Under undisclosed traffic conditions along with conditions beyond the attacker's control, hardware systems with a High-Speed Bridge (HSB) may experience a lockup of the HSB.

 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58424 | BIG-IP TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58424</link><description>On BIG-IP systems, undisclosed traffic can cause data corruption and unauthorized data modification in protocols which do not have message integrity protection.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58474 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM and NGINX App Protect DNS lookup vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58474</link><description>When BIG-IP Advanced WAF is configured on a virtual server with Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) protection or when an NGINX server is configured with App Protect Bot Defense, undisclosed requests can disrupt new client requests.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59268 | BIG-IP Configuration utility vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59268</link><description>On the BIG-IP system, undisclosed endpoints that contain static non-sensitive information are accessible to an unauthenticated remote attacker through the Configuration utility.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59269 | BIG-IP Configuration utility XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59269</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59478 | BIG-IP AFM DoS protection profile vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59478</link><description>When a BIG-IP AFM denial-of-service (DoS) protection profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59481 | BIG-IP iControl REST and tmsh vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59481</link><description>A vulnerability exists in an undisclosed iControl REST and BIG-IP TMOS Shell (tmsh) command that may allow an authenticated attacker with at least resource administrator role to execute arbitrary system commands with higher privileges.  A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59483 | BIG-IP Configuration utility and tmsh vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59483</link><description>A validation vulnerability exists in an undisclosed URL in the Configuration utility.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59778 | VELOS partition container network vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59778</link><description>When the Allowed IP Addresses feature is configured on the F5OS-C partition control plane, undisclosed traffic can cause multiple containers to terminate.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59781 | BIG-IP DNS cache vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59781</link><description>When DNS cache is configured on a BIG-IP or BIG-IP Next CNF virtual server, undisclosed DNS queries can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.   Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60013 | F5OS-A FIPS HSM password vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60013</link><description>When a user attempts to initialize the rSeries FIPS module using a password with special shell metacharacters, the FIPS hardware security module (HSM) may fail to initialize.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60015 | F5OS out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60015</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in F5OS-A and F5OS-C that could lead to memory corruption. 

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60016 | BIG-IP SSL/TLS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60016</link><description>When Diffie-Hellman (DH) group Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) Brainpool curves are configured in an SSL profile's Cipher Rule or Cipher Group, and that profile is applied to a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61938 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM bd process vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61938</link><description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF or ASM security policy is configured with a URL greater than 1024 characters in length for the Data Guard Protection Enforcement setting, either manually or through the automatic Policy Builder, the bd process can terminate repeatedly.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61951 | BIG-IP DTLS 1.2 Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61951</link><description>Undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  This issue may occur when a Datagram Transport Layer Security (DTLS) 1.2 virtual server is enabled with a Server SSL profile that is configured with a certificate, key, and the SSL Sign Hash set to ANY, and the backend server is enabled with DTLS 1.2 and client authentication.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61955 | F5OS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61955</link><description>A vulnerability exists in F5OS-A and F5OS-C systems that may allow an authenticated attacker with local access to escalate their privileges.  A successful exploit may allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61958 | BIG-IP TMSH vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61958</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the iHealth command that may allow an authenticated attacker with at least a resource administrator role to bypass tmsh restrictions and gain access to a bash shell.  For BIG-IP systems running in Appliance mode, a successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61960 | BIG-IP APM portal access vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61960</link><description>When a per-request policy is configured on a BIG-IP APM portal access virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61974 | BIG-IP SSL/TLS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61974</link><description>When a client SSL profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10869 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Oct8ne Chatbot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10869</link><description>Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Oct8ne Chatbot v2.3. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by injecting a malicious payload through the creation of a transcript that is sent by email. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9640 | Samba: vfs_streams_xattr uninitialized memory write possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9640</link><description>A flaw was found in Samba, in the vfs_streams_xattr module, where uninitialized heap memory could be written into alternate data streams. This allows an authenticated user to read residual memory content that may include sensitive data, resulting in an information disclosure vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55082 | Potential out of bound read and info leak in_nx_secure_tls_psk_identity_find()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55082</link><description>In NetX Duo version before 6.4.4, the component of Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read in _nx_secure_tls_process_clienthello() because of a missing validation of PSK length provided in the user message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55081 | Potential out of bound read in _nx_secure_tls_process_clienthello()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55081</link><description>In Eclipse Foundation NextX Duo before 6.4.4, a module of ThreadX, the _nx_secure_tls_process_clienthello() function was missing length verification of 
certain SSL/TLS client hello message: the ciphersuite length and 
compression method length. In case of an attacker-crafted message with 
values outside of the expected range, it could cause an out-of-bound 
read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10038 | Binary MLM Plan &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Unauthenticated Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10038</link><description>The Binary MLM Plan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to bmp_user role granting all users with the manage_bmp capability by default upon registration through the plugin's form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register and manage the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10041 | Flex QR Code Generator &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10041</link><description>The Flex QR Code Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in thesave_qr_code_to_db() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10045 | onOffice for WP-Websites &amp;lt;= 5.7 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10045</link><description>The onOffice for WP-Websites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10051 | Demo Import Kit &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10051</link><description>The Demo Import Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 via the import functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10056 | Task Scheduler &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10056</link><description>The Task Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 via the “Check Website” task. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10132 | Dhivehi Text &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10132</link><description>The Dhivehi Text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'dhivehi' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10133 | URLYar &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10133</link><description>The URLYar URL Shortner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'urlyar_shortlink' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10135 | WP ViewSTL &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10135</link><description>The WP ViewSTL plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'viewstl' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10139 | WP BookWidgets &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10139</link><description>The WP BookWidgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bw_link' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10140 | Quick Social Login &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10140</link><description>The Quick Social Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'quick-login' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10141 | Digiseller &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10141</link><description>The Digiseller plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ds' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10186 | WhyDonate – FREE Donate button – Crowdfunding – Fundraising &amp;lt;= 4.0.14 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated wp_wdplugin_style Rww Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10186</link><description>The WhyDonate – FREE Donate button – Crowdfunding – Fundraising plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the remove_row function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete rows from the wp_wdplugin_style table.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10194 | Shortcode Button &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10194</link><description>The Shortcode Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10293 | Keyy Two Factor Authentication (like Clef) &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10293</link><description>The Keyy Two Factor Authentication (like Clef) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity associated with a token generated. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to generate valid auth tokens and leverage that to auto-login as other accounts, including administrators, as long as the administrator has the 2FA set up.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10294 | OwnID Passwordless Login &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10294</link><description>The OwnID Passwordless Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4. This is due to the plugin not properly checking if the ownid_shared_secret value is empty prior to authenticating a user via JWT. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as other users, including administrators, on instances where the plugin has not been fully configured yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10299 | WPBifröst – Instant Passwordless Temporary Login Links &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10299</link><description>The WPBifröst – Instant Passwordless Temporary Login Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the ctl_create_link AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new administrative user accounts and subsequently log in as those.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10300 | TopBar &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10300</link><description>The TopBar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the fme_nb_topbar_save_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10301 | FunKItools &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10301</link><description>The FunKItools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the saveFields() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10303 | Library Management System &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10303</link><description>The Library Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the owt7_library_management_ajax_handler() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update and manipulate several of the plugin's settings and features.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10310 | Rich Snippet Site Report &amp;lt;= 2.0.0105 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10310</link><description>The Rich Snippet Site Report plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to  SQL Injection via the 'last' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0105 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This can also be exploited via CSRF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10312 | Theme Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10312</link><description>The Theme Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation when processing form submissions in the theme-importer.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger arbitrary file downloads and potentially execute malicious operations via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10313 | Find And Replace content for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10313</link><description>The Find And Replace content for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Stored Cross-Site Scripting and Arbitrary Content Replacement due to a missing capability check on the far_admin_ajax_fun() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts into pages that can make privilege escalation and malicious redirects possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10486 | Content Writer &amp;lt;= 3.6.8 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10486</link><description>The Content Writer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.8 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10575 | WP jQuery Pager &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10575</link><description>The WP jQuery Pager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'ids' shortcode attribute parameter handled by the WPJqueryPaged::get_gallery_page_imgs() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10648 | Login with YourMembership - YM SSO Login &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;moym_display_test_attributes&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10648</link><description>The YourMembership Single Sign On – YM SSO Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'moym_display_test_attributes' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the profile data of the latest SSO login.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10660 | WP Dashboard Chat &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10660</link><description>The WP Dashboard Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10682 | TARIFFUXX &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via tariffuxx_configurator Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10682</link><description>The TARIFFUXX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to insufficient neutralization of user-supplied input used directly in SQL queries. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject additional SQL into queries and extract sensitive information from the database via a crafted id attribute in the 'tariffuxx_configurator' shortcode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10730 | Wp tabber widget &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10730</link><description>The Wp tabber widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'wp-tabber-widget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10743 | Outdoor &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10743</link><description>The Outdoor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit' action in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10754 | DocoDoco Store Locator &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Editor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10754</link><description>The DocoDoco Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the zip upload functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11177 | External Login &amp;lt;= 1.11.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11177</link><description>The External Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'log' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database when a PostgreSQL or MSSQL database is configured as the external authentication database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11196 | External Login &amp;lt;= 1.11.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Data Exposure via Test Connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11196</link><description>The External Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.2 due to the 'exlog_test_connection' AJAX action lacking capability checks or nonce validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to query the configured external database and retrieve truncated usernames, email addresses, and password hashes via the diagnostic test results view.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11365 | WP Google Map Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11365</link><description>The WP Google Map Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the 'google_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11692 | Zip Attachments &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Missing Authorization to Limited File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11692</link><description>The Zip Attachments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing authorization and capability checks on the download.php file in all versions up to, and including, 1.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files from the current wp_upload_dir directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11701 | Zip Attachments &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Private And Password-Protected Posts Attachment Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11701</link><description>The Zip Attachments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check as well as missing post status validation in the za_create_zip_callback function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download attachments from private and password-protected posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11722 | Category and Products Accordion Panel &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11722</link><description>The Woocommerce Category and Products Accordion Panel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via the 'categoryaccordionpanel' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11728 | Oceanpayment CreditCard Gateway &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Order Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11728</link><description>The Oceanpayment CreditCard Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated and unauthorized modification of data due to missing authentication and capability checks on the 'return_payment' and 'notice_payment' functions in all versions up to, and including, 6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update WooCommerce orders to 'failed' status, and update transaction IDs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9967 | Orion SMS OTP Verification &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9967</link><description>The Orion SMS OTP Verification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's password to a one-time password if the attacker knows the user's phone number</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39991 | wifi: ath11k: fix NULL dereference in ath11k_qmi_m3_load()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39991</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath11k: fix NULL dereference in ath11k_qmi_m3_load()

If ab-&gt;fw.m3_data points to data, then fw pointer remains null.
Further, if m3_mem is not allocated, then fw is dereferenced to be
passed to ath11k_err function.

Replace fw-&gt;size by m3_len.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39992 | mm: swap: check for stable address space before operating on the VMA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39992</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: swap: check for stable address space before operating on the VMA

It is possible to hit a zero entry while traversing the vmas in unuse_mm()
called from swapoff path and accessing it causes the OOPS:

Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address
0000000000000446--&gt; Loading the memory from offset 0x40 on the
XA_ZERO_ENTRY as address.
Mem abort info:
  ESR = 0x0000000096000005
  EC = 0x25: DABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
  SET = 0, FnV = 0
  EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
  FSC = 0x05: level 1 translation fault

The issue is manifested from the below race between the fork() on a
process and swapoff:
fork(dup_mmap())			swapoff(unuse_mm)
---------------                         -----------------
1) Identical mtree is built using
   __mt_dup().

2) copy_pte_range()--&gt;
	copy_nonpresent_pte():
       The dst mm is added into the
    mmlist to be visible to the
    swapoff operation.

3) Fatal signal is sent to the parent
process(which is the current during the
fork) thus skip the duplication of the
vmas and mark the vma range with
XA_ZERO_ENTRY as a marker for this process
that helps during exit_mmap().

				     4) swapoff is tried on the
					'mm' added to the 'mmlist' as
					part of the 2.

				     5) unuse_mm(), that iterates
					through the vma's of this 'mm'
					will hit the non-NULL zero entry
					and operating on this zero entry
					as a vma is resulting into the
					oops.

The proper fix would be around not exposing this partially-valid tree to
others when droping the mmap lock, which is being solved with [1].  A
simpler solution would be checking for MMF_UNSTABLE, as it is set if
mm_struct is not fully initialized in dup_mmap().

Thanks to Liam/Lorenzo/David for all the suggestions in fixing this
issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39993 | media: rc: fix races with imon_disconnect()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39993</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: rc: fix races with imon_disconnect()

Syzbot reports a KASAN issue as below:
BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in __create_pipe include/linux/usb.h:1945 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in send_packet+0xa2d/0xbc0 drivers/media/rc/imon.c:627
Read of size 4 at addr ffff8880256fb000 by task syz-executor314/4465

CPU: 2 PID: 4465 Comm: syz-executor314 Not tainted 6.0.0-rc1-syzkaller #0
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.14.0-2 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
__dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:88 [inline]
dump_stack_lvl+0xcd/0x134 lib/dump_stack.c:106
print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:317 [inline]
print_report.cold+0x2ba/0x6e9 mm/kasan/report.c:433
kasan_report+0xb1/0x1e0 mm/kasan/report.c:495
__create_pipe include/linux/usb.h:1945 [inline]
send_packet+0xa2d/0xbc0 drivers/media/rc/imon.c:627
vfd_write+0x2d9/0x550 drivers/media/rc/imon.c:991
vfs_write+0x2d7/0xdd0 fs/read_write.c:576
ksys_write+0x127/0x250 fs/read_write.c:631
do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:50 [inline]
do_syscall_64+0x35/0xb0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:80
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

The iMON driver improperly releases the usb_device reference in
imon_disconnect without coordinating with active users of the
device.

Specifically, the fields usbdev_intf0 and usbdev_intf1 are not
protected by the users counter (ictx-&gt;users). During probe,
imon_init_intf0 or imon_init_intf1 increments the usb_device
reference count depending on the interface. However, during
disconnect, usb_put_dev is called unconditionally, regardless of
actual usage.

As a result, if vfd_write or other operations are still in
progress after disconnect, this can lead to a use-after-free of
the usb_device pointer.

Thread 1 vfd_write                      Thread 2 imon_disconnect
                                        ...
                                        if
                                          usb_put_dev(ictx-&gt;usbdev_intf0)
                                        else
                                          usb_put_dev(ictx-&gt;usbdev_intf1)
...
while
  send_packet
    if
      pipe = usb_sndintpipe(
        ictx-&gt;usbdev_intf0) UAF
    else
      pipe = usb_sndctrlpipe(
        ictx-&gt;usbdev_intf0, 0) UAF

Guard access to usbdev_intf0 and usbdev_intf1 after disconnect by
checking ictx-&gt;disconnected in all writer paths. Add early return
with -ENODEV in send_packet(), vfd_write(), lcd_write() and
display_open() if the device is no longer present.

Set and read ictx-&gt;disconnected under ictx-&gt;lock to ensure memory
synchronization. Acquire the lock in imon_disconnect() before setting
the flag to synchronize with any ongoing operations.

Ensure writers exit early and safely after disconnect before the USB
core proceeds with cleanup.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with Syzkaller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39994 | media: tuner: xc5000: Fix use-after-free in xc5000_release</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39994</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: tuner: xc5000: Fix use-after-free in xc5000_release

The original code uses cancel_delayed_work() in xc5000_release(), which
does not guarantee that the delayed work item timer_sleep has fully
completed if it was already running. This leads to use-after-free scenarios
where xc5000_release() may free the xc5000_priv while timer_sleep is still
active and attempts to dereference the xc5000_priv.

A typical race condition is illustrated below:

CPU 0 (release thread)                 | CPU 1 (delayed work callback)
xc5000_release()                       | xc5000_do_timer_sleep()
  cancel_delayed_work()                |
  hybrid_tuner_release_state(priv)     |
    kfree(priv)                        |
                                       |   priv = container_of() // UAF

Replace cancel_delayed_work() with cancel_delayed_work_sync() to ensure
that the timer_sleep is properly canceled before the xc5000_priv memory
is deallocated.

A deadlock concern was considered: xc5000_release() is called in a process
context and is not holding any locks that the timer_sleep work item might
also need. Therefore, the use of the _sync() variant is safe here.

This bug was initially identified through static analysis.

[hverkuil: fix typo in Subject: tunner -&gt; tuner]</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39995 | media: i2c: tc358743: Fix use-after-free bugs caused by orphan timer in probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39995</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: i2c: tc358743: Fix use-after-free bugs caused by orphan timer in probe

The state-&gt;timer is a cyclic timer that schedules work_i2c_poll and
delayed_work_enable_hotplug, while rearming itself. Using timer_delete()
fails to guarantee the timer isn't still running when destroyed, similarly
cancel_delayed_work() cannot ensure delayed_work_enable_hotplug has
terminated if already executing. During probe failure after timer
initialization, these may continue running as orphans and reference the
already-freed tc358743_state object through tc358743_irq_poll_timer.

The following is the trace captured by KASAN.

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
Write of size 8 at addr ffff88800ded83c8 by task swapper/1/0
...
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x55/0x70
 print_report+0xcf/0x610
 ? __pfx_sched_balance_find_src_group+0x10/0x10
 ? __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
 kasan_report+0xb8/0xf0
 ? __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
 __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
 ? rcu_sched_clock_irq+0xb06/0x27d0
 ? __pfx___run_timer_base.part.0+0x10/0x10
 ? try_to_wake_up+0xb15/0x1960
 ? tmigr_update_events+0x280/0x740
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irq+0x80/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irq+0x10/0x10
 tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x603/0x7e0
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x10/0x10
 ? sched_balance_trigger+0x98/0x9f0
 ? sched_tick+0x221/0x5a0
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irq+0x80/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irq+0x10/0x10
 ? tick_nohz_handler+0x339/0x440
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x10/0x10
 __walk_groups.isra.0+0x42/0x150
 tmigr_handle_remote+0x1f4/0x2e0
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote+0x10/0x10
 ? ktime_get+0x60/0x140
 ? lapic_next_event+0x11/0x20
 ? clockevents_program_event+0x1d4/0x2a0
 ? hrtimer_interrupt+0x322/0x780
 handle_softirqs+0x16a/0x550
 irq_exit_rcu+0xaf/0xe0
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x70/0x80
 
...

Allocated by task 141:
 kasan_save_stack+0x24/0x50
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x7f/0x90
 __kmalloc_node_track_caller_noprof+0x198/0x430
 devm_kmalloc+0x7b/0x1e0
 tc358743_probe+0xb7/0x610  i2c_device_probe+0x51d/0x880
 really_probe+0x1ca/0x5c0
 __driver_probe_device+0x248/0x310
 driver_probe_device+0x44/0x120
 __device_attach_driver+0x174/0x220
 bus_for_each_drv+0x100/0x190
 __device_attach+0x206/0x370
 bus_probe_device+0x123/0x170
 device_add+0xd25/0x1470
 i2c_new_client_device+0x7a0/0xcd0
 do_one_initcall+0x89/0x300
 do_init_module+0x29d/0x7f0
 load_module+0x4f48/0x69e0
 init_module_from_file+0xe4/0x150
 idempotent_init_module+0x320/0x670
 __x64_sys_finit_module+0xbd/0x120
 do_syscall_64+0xac/0x280
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Freed by task 141:
 kasan_save_stack+0x24/0x50
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30
 kasan_save_free_info+0x3a/0x60
 __kasan_slab_free+0x3f/0x50
 kfree+0x137/0x370
 release_nodes+0xa4/0x100
 devres_release_group+0x1b2/0x380
 i2c_device_probe+0x694/0x880
 really_probe+0x1ca/0x5c0
 __driver_probe_device+0x248/0x310
 driver_probe_device+0x44/0x120
 __device_attach_driver+0x174/0x220
 bus_for_each_drv+0x100/0x190
 __device_attach+0x206/0x370
 bus_probe_device+0x123/0x170
 device_add+0xd25/0x1470
 i2c_new_client_device+0x7a0/0xcd0
 do_one_initcall+0x89/0x300
 do_init_module+0x29d/0x7f0
 load_module+0x4f48/0x69e0
 init_module_from_file+0xe4/0x150
 idempotent_init_module+0x320/0x670
 __x64_sys_finit_module+0xbd/0x120
 do_syscall_64+0xac/0x280
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
...

Replace timer_delete() with timer_delete_sync() and cancel_delayed_work()
with cancel_delayed_work_sync() to ensure proper termination of timer and
work items before resource cleanup.

This bug was initially identified through static analysis. For reproduction
and testing, I created a functional emulation of the tc358743 device via a
kernel module and introduced faults through the debugfs interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39996 | media: b2c2: Fix use-after-free causing by irq_check_work in flexcop_pci_remove</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39996</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: b2c2: Fix use-after-free causing by irq_check_work in flexcop_pci_remove

The original code uses cancel_delayed_work() in flexcop_pci_remove(), which
does not guarantee that the delayed work item irq_check_work has fully
completed if it was already running. This leads to use-after-free scenarios
where flexcop_pci_remove() may free the flexcop_device while irq_check_work
is still active and attempts to dereference the device.

A typical race condition is illustrated below:

CPU 0 (remove)                         | CPU 1 (delayed work callback)
flexcop_pci_remove()                   | flexcop_pci_irq_check_work()
  cancel_delayed_work()                |
  flexcop_device_kfree(fc_pci-&gt;fc_dev) |
                                       |   fc = fc_pci-&gt;fc_dev; // UAF

This is confirmed by a KASAN report:

==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
Write of size 8 at addr ffff8880093aa8c8 by task bash/135
...
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x55/0x70
 print_report+0xcf/0x610
 ? __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
 kasan_report+0xb8/0xf0
 ? __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
 __run_timer_base.part.0+0x7d7/0x8c0
 ? __pfx___run_timer_base.part.0+0x10/0x10
 ? __pfx_read_tsc+0x10/0x10
 ? ktime_get+0x60/0x140
 ? lapic_next_event+0x11/0x20
 ? clockevents_program_event+0x1d4/0x2a0
 run_timer_softirq+0xd1/0x190
 handle_softirqs+0x16a/0x550
 irq_exit_rcu+0xaf/0xe0
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x70/0x80
 
...

Allocated by task 1:
 kasan_save_stack+0x24/0x50
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x7f/0x90
 __kmalloc_noprof+0x1be/0x460
 flexcop_device_kmalloc+0x54/0xe0
 flexcop_pci_probe+0x1f/0x9d0
 local_pci_probe+0xdc/0x190
 pci_device_probe+0x2fe/0x470
 really_probe+0x1ca/0x5c0
 __driver_probe_device+0x248/0x310
 driver_probe_device+0x44/0x120
 __driver_attach+0xd2/0x310
 bus_for_each_dev+0xed/0x170
 bus_add_driver+0x208/0x500
 driver_register+0x132/0x460
 do_one_initcall+0x89/0x300
 kernel_init_freeable+0x40d/0x720
 kernel_init+0x1a/0x150
 ret_from_fork+0x10c/0x1a0
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30

Freed by task 135:
 kasan_save_stack+0x24/0x50
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30
 kasan_save_free_info+0x3a/0x60
 __kasan_slab_free+0x3f/0x50
 kfree+0x137/0x370
 flexcop_device_kfree+0x32/0x50
 pci_device_remove+0xa6/0x1d0
 device_release_driver_internal+0xf8/0x210
 pci_stop_bus_device+0x105/0x150
 pci_stop_and_remove_bus_device_locked+0x15/0x30
 remove_store+0xcc/0xe0
 kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x2c3/0x440
 vfs_write+0x871/0xd70
 ksys_write+0xee/0x1c0
 do_syscall_64+0xac/0x280
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
...

Replace cancel_delayed_work() with cancel_delayed_work_sync() to ensure
that the delayed work item is properly canceled and any executing delayed
work has finished before the device memory is deallocated.

This bug was initially identified through static analysis. To reproduce
and test it, I simulated the B2C2 FlexCop PCI device in QEMU and introduced
artificial delays within the flexcop_pci_irq_check_work() function to
increase the likelihood of triggering the bug.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39997 | ALSA: usb-audio: fix race condition to UAF in snd_usbmidi_free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39997</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: usb-audio: fix race condition to UAF in snd_usbmidi_free

The previous commit 0718a78f6a9f ("ALSA: usb-audio: Kill timer properly at
removal") patched a UAF issue caused by the error timer.

However, because the error timer kill added in this patch occurs after the
endpoint delete, a race condition to UAF still occurs, albeit rarely.

Additionally, since kill-cleanup for urb is also missing, freed memory can
be accessed in interrupt context related to urb, which can cause UAF.

Therefore, to prevent this, error timer and urb must be killed before
freeing the heap memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39998 | scsi: target: target_core_configfs: Add length check to avoid buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39998</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: target: target_core_configfs: Add length check to avoid buffer overflow

A buffer overflow arises from the usage of snprintf to write into the
buffer "buf" in target_lu_gp_members_show function located in
/drivers/target/target_core_configfs.c. This buffer is allocated with
size LU_GROUP_NAME_BUF (256 bytes).

snprintf(...) formats multiple strings into buf with the HBA name
(hba-&gt;hba_group.cg_item), a slash character, a devicename (dev-&gt;
dev_group.cg_item) and a newline character, the total formatted string
length may exceed the buffer size of 256 bytes.

Since snprintf() returns the total number of bytes that would have been
written (the length of %s/%sn ), this value may exceed the buffer length
(256 bytes) passed to memcpy(), this will ultimately cause function
memcpy reporting a buffer overflow error.

An additional check of the return value of snprintf() can avoid this
buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39999 | blk-mq: fix blk_mq_tags double free while nr_requests grown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39999</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-mq: fix blk_mq_tags double free while nr_requests grown

In the case user trigger tags grow by queue sysfs attribute nr_requests,
hctx-&gt;sched_tags will be freed directly and replaced with a new
allocated tags, see blk_mq_tag_update_depth().

The problem is that hctx-&gt;sched_tags is from elevator-&gt;et-&gt;tags, while
et-&gt;tags is still the freed tags, hence later elevator exit will try to
free the tags again, causing kernel panic.

Fix this problem by replacing et-&gt;tags with new allocated tags as well.

Noted there are still some long term problems that will require some
refactor to be fixed thoroughly[1].

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/all/20250815080216.410665-1-yukuai1@huaweicloud.com/</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40000 | wifi: rtw89: fix use-after-free in rtw89_core_tx_kick_off_and_wait()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40000</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: rtw89: fix use-after-free in rtw89_core_tx_kick_off_and_wait()

There is a bug observed when rtw89_core_tx_kick_off_and_wait() tries to
access already freed skb_data:

 BUG: KFENCE: use-after-free write in rtw89_core_tx_kick_off_and_wait drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/core.c:1110

 CPU: 6 UID: 0 PID: 41377 Comm: kworker/u64:24 Not tainted  6.17.0-rc1+ #1 PREEMPT(lazy)
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS edk2-20250523-14.fc42 05/23/2025
 Workqueue: events_unbound cfg80211_wiphy_work [cfg80211]

 Use-after-free write at 0x0000000020309d9d (in kfence-#251):
 rtw89_core_tx_kick_off_and_wait drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/core.c:1110
 rtw89_core_scan_complete drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/core.c:5338
 rtw89_hw_scan_complete_cb drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/fw.c:7979
 rtw89_chanctx_proceed_cb drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/chan.c:3165
 rtw89_chanctx_proceed drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/chan.h:141
 rtw89_hw_scan_complete drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/fw.c:8012
 rtw89_mac_c2h_scanofld_rsp drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/mac.c:5059
 rtw89_fw_c2h_work drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/fw.c:6758
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3241
 worker_thread kernel/workqueue.c:3400
 kthread kernel/kthread.c:463
 ret_from_fork arch/x86/kernel/process.c:154
 ret_from_fork_asm arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:258

 kfence-#251: 0x0000000056e2393d-0x000000009943cb62, size=232, cache=skbuff_head_cache

 allocated by task 41377 on cpu 6 at 77869.159548s (0.009551s ago):
 __alloc_skb net/core/skbuff.c:659
 __netdev_alloc_skb net/core/skbuff.c:734
 ieee80211_nullfunc_get net/mac80211/tx.c:5844
 rtw89_core_send_nullfunc drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/core.c:3431
 rtw89_core_scan_complete drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/core.c:5338
 rtw89_hw_scan_complete_cb drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/fw.c:7979
 rtw89_chanctx_proceed_cb drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/chan.c:3165
 rtw89_chanctx_proceed drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/chan.c:3194
 rtw89_hw_scan_complete drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/fw.c:8012
 rtw89_mac_c2h_scanofld_rsp drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/mac.c:5059
 rtw89_fw_c2h_work drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/fw.c:6758
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3241
 worker_thread kernel/workqueue.c:3400
 kthread kernel/kthread.c:463
 ret_from_fork arch/x86/kernel/process.c:154
 ret_from_fork_asm arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:258

 freed by task 1045 on cpu 9 at 77869.168393s (0.001557s ago):
 ieee80211_tx_status_skb net/mac80211/status.c:1117
 rtw89_pci_release_txwd_skb drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/pci.c:564
 rtw89_pci_release_tx_skbs.isra.0 drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/pci.c:651
 rtw89_pci_release_tx drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/pci.c:676
 rtw89_pci_napi_poll drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/pci.c:4238
 __napi_poll net/core/dev.c:7495
 net_rx_action net/core/dev.c:7557 net/core/dev.c:7684
 handle_softirqs kernel/softirq.c:580
 do_softirq.part.0 kernel/softirq.c:480
 __local_bh_enable_ip kernel/softirq.c:407
 rtw89_pci_interrupt_threadfn drivers/net/wireless/realtek/rtw89/pci.c:927
 irq_thread_fn kernel/irq/manage.c:1133
 irq_thread kernel/irq/manage.c:1257
 kthread kernel/kthread.c:463
 ret_from_fork arch/x86/kernel/process.c:154
 ret_from_fork_asm arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:258

It is a consequence of a race between the waiting and the signaling side
of the completion:

            Waiting thread                            Completing thread

rtw89_core_tx_kick_off_and_wait()
  rcu_assign_pointer(skb_data-&gt;wait, wait)
  /* start waiting */
  wait_for_completion_timeout()
                                                rtw89_pci_tx_status()
                                                  rtw89_core_tx_wait_complete()
                                                    rcu_read_lock()
                                                    /* signals completion and
   
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39966 | iommufd: Fix race during abort for file descriptors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39966</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommufd: Fix race during abort for file descriptors

fput() doesn't actually call file_operations release() synchronously, it
puts the file on a work queue and it will be released eventually.

This is normally fine, except for iommufd the file and the iommufd_object
are tied to gether. The file has the object as it's private_data and holds
a users refcount, while the object is expected to remain alive as long as
the file is.

When the allocation of a new object aborts before installing the file it
will fput() the file and then go on to immediately kfree() the obj. This
causes a UAF once the workqueue completes the fput() and tries to
decrement the users refcount.

Fix this by putting the core code in charge of the file lifetime, and call
__fput_sync() during abort to ensure that release() is called before
kfree. __fput_sync() is a bit too tricky to open code in all the object
implementations. Instead the objects tell the core code where the file
pointer is and the core will take care of the life cycle.

If the object is successfully allocated then the file will hold a users
refcount and the iommufd_object cannot be destroyed.

It is worth noting that close(); ioctl(IOMMU_DESTROY); doesn't have an
issue because close() is already using a synchronous version of fput().

The UAF looks like this:

    BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in iommufd_eventq_fops_release+0x45/0xc0 drivers/iommu/iommufd/eventq.c:376
    Write of size 4 at addr ffff888059c97804 by task syz.0.46/6164

    CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 6164 Comm: syz.0.46 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
    Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 08/18/2025
    Call Trace:
     
     __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
     dump_stack_lvl+0x116/0x1f0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
     print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
     print_report+0xcd/0x630 mm/kasan/report.c:482
     kasan_report+0xe0/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:595
     check_region_inline mm/kasan/generic.c:183 [inline]
     kasan_check_range+0x100/0x1b0 mm/kasan/generic.c:189
     instrument_atomic_read_write include/linux/instrumented.h:96 [inline]
     atomic_fetch_sub_release include/linux/atomic/atomic-instrumented.h:400 [inline]
     __refcount_dec include/linux/refcount.h:455 [inline]
     refcount_dec include/linux/refcount.h:476 [inline]
     iommufd_eventq_fops_release+0x45/0xc0 drivers/iommu/iommufd/eventq.c:376
     __fput+0x402/0xb70 fs/file_table.c:468
     task_work_run+0x14d/0x240 kernel/task_work.c:227
     resume_user_mode_work include/linux/resume_user_mode.h:50 [inline]
     exit_to_user_mode_loop+0xeb/0x110 kernel/entry/common.c:43
     exit_to_user_mode_prepare include/linux/irq-entry-common.h:225 [inline]
     syscall_exit_to_user_mode_work include/linux/entry-common.h:175 [inline]
     syscall_exit_to_user_mode include/linux/entry-common.h:210 [inline]
     do_syscall_64+0x41c/0x4c0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:100
     entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39967 | fbcon: fix integer overflow in fbcon_do_set_font</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39967</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fbcon: fix integer overflow in fbcon_do_set_font

Fix integer overflow vulnerabilities in fbcon_do_set_font() where font
size calculations could overflow when handling user-controlled font
parameters.

The vulnerabilities occur when:
1. CALC_FONTSZ(h, pitch, charcount) performs h * pith * charcount
   multiplication with user-controlled values that can overflow.
2. FONT_EXTRA_WORDS * sizeof(int) + size addition can also overflow
3. This results in smaller allocations than expected, leading to buffer
   overflows during font data copying.

Add explicit overflow checking using check_mul_overflow() and
check_add_overflow() kernel helpers to safety validate all size
calculations before allocation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39968 | i40e: add max boundary check for VF filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39968</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: add max boundary check for VF filters

There is no check for max filters that VF can request. Add it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39969 | i40e: fix validation of VF state in get resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39969</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: fix validation of VF state in get resources

VF state I40E_VF_STATE_ACTIVE is not the only state in which
VF is actually active so it should not be used to determine
if a VF is allowed to obtain resources.

Use I40E_VF_STATE_RESOURCES_LOADED that is set only in
i40e_vc_get_vf_resources_msg() and cleared during reset.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39970 | i40e: fix input validation logic for action_meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39970</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: fix input validation logic for action_meta

Fix condition to check 'greater or equal' to prevent OOB dereference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39971 | i40e: fix idx validation in config queues msg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39971</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: fix idx validation in config queues msg

Ensure idx is within range of active/initialized TCs when iterating over
vf-&gt;ch[idx] in i40e_vc_config_queues_msg().</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39972 | i40e: fix idx validation in i40e_validate_queue_map</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39972</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: fix idx validation in i40e_validate_queue_map

Ensure idx is within range of active/initialized TCs when iterating over
vf-&gt;ch[idx] in i40e_validate_queue_map().</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39973 | i40e: add validation for ring_len param</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39973</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: add validation for ring_len param

The `ring_len` parameter provided by the virtual function (VF)
is assigned directly to the hardware memory context (HMC) without
any validation.

To address this, introduce an upper boundary check for both Tx and Rx
queue lengths. The maximum number of descriptors supported by the
hardware is 8k-32.
Additionally, enforce alignment constraints: Tx rings must be a multiple
of 8, and Rx rings must be a multiple of 32.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39974 | tracing/osnoise: Fix slab-out-of-bounds in _parse_integer_limit()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39974</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tracing/osnoise: Fix slab-out-of-bounds in _parse_integer_limit()

When config osnoise cpus by write() syscall, the following KASAN splat may
be observed:

BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in _parse_integer_limit+0x103/0x130
Read of size 1 at addr ffff88810121e3a1 by task test/447
CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 447 Comm: test Not tainted 6.17.0-rc6-dirty #288 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x55/0x70
 print_report+0xcb/0x610
 kasan_report+0xb8/0xf0
 _parse_integer_limit+0x103/0x130
 bitmap_parselist+0x16d/0x6f0
 osnoise_cpus_write+0x116/0x2d0
 vfs_write+0x21e/0xcc0
 ksys_write+0xee/0x1c0
 do_syscall_64+0xa8/0x2a0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
 

This issue can be reproduced by below code:

const char *cpulist = "1";
int fd=open("/sys/kernel/debug/tracing/osnoise/cpus", O_WRONLY);
write(fd, cpulist, strlen(cpulist));

Function bitmap_parselist() was called to parse cpulist, it require that
the parameter 'buf' must be terminated with a '\0' or '\n'. Fix this issue
by adding a '\0' to 'buf' in osnoise_cpus_write().</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39975 | smb: client: fix wrong index reference in smb2_compound_op()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39975</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb: client: fix wrong index reference in smb2_compound_op()

In smb2_compound_op(), the loop that processes each command's response
uses wrong indices when accessing response bufferes.

This incorrect indexing leads to improper handling of command results.
Also, if incorrectly computed index is greather than or equal to
MAX_COMPOUND, it can cause out-of-bounds accesses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39976 | futex: Use correct exit on failure from futex_hash_allocate_default()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39976</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

futex: Use correct exit on failure from futex_hash_allocate_default()

copy_process() uses the wrong error exit path from futex_hash_allocate_default().
After exiting from futex_hash_allocate_default(), neither tasklist_lock
nor siglock has been acquired. The exit label bad_fork_core_free unlocks
both of these locks which is wrong.

The next exit label, bad_fork_cancel_cgroup, is the correct exit.
sched_cgroup_fork() did not allocate any resources that need to freed.

Use bad_fork_cancel_cgroup on error exit from futex_hash_allocate_default().</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39977 | futex: Prevent use-after-free during requeue-PI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39977</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

futex: Prevent use-after-free during requeue-PI

syzbot managed to trigger the following race:

   T1                               T2

 futex_wait_requeue_pi()
   futex_do_wait()
     schedule()
                               futex_requeue()
                                 futex_proxy_trylock_atomic()
                                   futex_requeue_pi_prepare()
                                   requeue_pi_wake_futex()
                                     futex_requeue_pi_complete()
                                      /* preempt */

         * timeout/ signal wakes T1 *

   futex_requeue_pi_wakeup_sync() // Q_REQUEUE_PI_LOCKED
   futex_hash_put()
  // back to userland, on stack futex_q is garbage

                                      /* back */
                                     wake_up_state(q-&gt;task, TASK_NORMAL);

In this scenario futex_wait_requeue_pi() is able to leave without using
futex_q::lock_ptr for synchronization.

This can be prevented by reading futex_q::task before updating the
futex_q::requeue_state. A reference on the task_struct is not needed
because requeue_pi_wake_futex() is invoked with a spinlock_t held which
implies a RCU read section.

Even if T1 terminates immediately after, the task_struct will remain valid
during T2's wake_up_state().  A READ_ONCE on futex_q::task before
futex_requeue_pi_complete() is enough because it ensures that the variable
is read before the state is updated.

Read futex_q::task before updating the requeue state, use it for the
following wakeup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39978 | octeontx2-pf: Fix potential use after free in otx2_tc_add_flow()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39978</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

octeontx2-pf: Fix potential use after free in otx2_tc_add_flow()

This code calls kfree_rcu(new_node, rcu) and then dereferences "new_node"
and then dereferences it on the next line.  Two lines later, we take
a mutex so I don't think this is an RCU safe region.  Re-order it to do
the dereferences before queuing up the free.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39979 | net/mlx5: fs, fix UAF in flow counter release</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39979</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5: fs, fix UAF in flow counter release

Fix a kernel trace [1] caused by releasing an HWS action of a local flow
counter in mlx5_cmd_hws_delete_fte(), where the HWS action refcount and
mutex were not initialized and the counter struct could already be freed
when deleting the rule.

Fix it by adding the missing initializations and adding refcount for the
local flow counter struct.

[1] Kernel log:
 Call Trace:
  
  dump_stack_lvl+0x34/0x48
  mlx5_fs_put_hws_action.part.0.cold+0x21/0x94 [mlx5_core]
  mlx5_fc_put_hws_action+0x96/0xad [mlx5_core]
  mlx5_fs_destroy_fs_actions+0x8b/0x152 [mlx5_core]
  mlx5_cmd_hws_delete_fte+0x5a/0xa0 [mlx5_core]
  del_hw_fte+0x1ce/0x260 [mlx5_core]
  mlx5_del_flow_rules+0x12d/0x240 [mlx5_core]
  ? ttwu_queue_wakelist+0xf4/0x110
  mlx5_ib_destroy_flow+0x103/0x1b0 [mlx5_ib]
  uverbs_free_flow+0x20/0x50 [ib_uverbs]
  destroy_hw_idr_uobject+0x1b/0x50 [ib_uverbs]
  uverbs_destroy_uobject+0x34/0x1a0 [ib_uverbs]
  uobj_destroy+0x3c/0x80 [ib_uverbs]
  ib_uverbs_run_method+0x23e/0x360 [ib_uverbs]
  ? uverbs_finalize_object+0x60/0x60 [ib_uverbs]
  ib_uverbs_cmd_verbs+0x14f/0x2c0 [ib_uverbs]
  ? do_tty_write+0x1a9/0x270
  ? file_tty_write.constprop.0+0x98/0xc0
  ? new_sync_write+0xfc/0x190
  ib_uverbs_ioctl+0xd7/0x160 [ib_uverbs]
  __x64_sys_ioctl+0x87/0xc0
  do_syscall_64+0x59/0x90</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39980 | nexthop: Forbid FDB status change while nexthop is in a group</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39980</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nexthop: Forbid FDB status change while nexthop is in a group

The kernel forbids the creation of non-FDB nexthop groups with FDB
nexthops:

 # ip nexthop add id 1 via 192.0.2.1 fdb
 # ip nexthop add id 2 group 1
 Error: Non FDB nexthop group cannot have fdb nexthops.

And vice versa:

 # ip nexthop add id 3 via 192.0.2.2 dev dummy1
 # ip nexthop add id 4 group 3 fdb
 Error: FDB nexthop group can only have fdb nexthops.

However, as long as no routes are pointing to a non-FDB nexthop group,
the kernel allows changing the type of a nexthop from FDB to non-FDB and
vice versa:

 # ip nexthop add id 5 via 192.0.2.2 dev dummy1
 # ip nexthop add id 6 group 5
 # ip nexthop replace id 5 via 192.0.2.2 fdb
 # echo $?
 0

This configuration is invalid and can result in a NPD [1] since FDB
nexthops are not associated with a nexthop device:

 # ip route add 198.51.100.1/32 nhid 6
 # ping 198.51.100.1

Fix by preventing nexthop FDB status change while the nexthop is in a
group:

 # ip nexthop add id 7 via 192.0.2.2 dev dummy1
 # ip nexthop add id 8 group 7
 # ip nexthop replace id 7 via 192.0.2.2 fdb
 Error: Cannot change nexthop FDB status while in a group.

[1]
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 00000000000003c0
[...]
Oops: Oops: 0000 [#1] SMP
CPU: 6 UID: 0 PID: 367 Comm: ping Not tainted 6.17.0-rc6-virtme-gb65678cacc03 #1 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.17.0-4.fc41 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:fib_lookup_good_nhc+0x1e/0x80
[...]
Call Trace:
 
 fib_table_lookup+0x541/0x650
 ip_route_output_key_hash_rcu+0x2ea/0x970
 ip_route_output_key_hash+0x55/0x80
 __ip4_datagram_connect+0x250/0x330
 udp_connect+0x2b/0x60
 __sys_connect+0x9c/0xd0
 __x64_sys_connect+0x18/0x20
 do_syscall_64+0xa4/0x2a0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39981 | Bluetooth: MGMT: Fix possible UAFs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39981</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: MGMT: Fix possible UAFs

This attemps to fix possible UAFs caused by struct mgmt_pending being
freed while still being processed like in the following trace, in order
to fix mgmt_pending_valid is introduce and use to check if the
mgmt_pending hasn't been removed from the pending list, on the complete
callbacks it is used to check and in addtion remove the cmd from the list
while holding mgmt_pending_lock to avoid TOCTOU problems since if the cmd
is left on the list it can still be accessed and freed.

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in mgmt_add_adv_patterns_monitor_sync+0x35/0x50 net/bluetooth/mgmt.c:5223
Read of size 8 at addr ffff8880709d4dc0 by task kworker/u11:0/55

CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 55 Comm: kworker/u11:0 Not tainted 6.16.4 #2 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.10.2-1ubuntu1 04/01/2014
Workqueue: hci0 hci_cmd_sync_work
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x189/0x250 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0xca/0x240 mm/kasan/report.c:482
 kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:595
 mgmt_add_adv_patterns_monitor_sync+0x35/0x50 net/bluetooth/mgmt.c:5223
 hci_cmd_sync_work+0x210/0x3a0 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:332
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3238 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xade/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3321
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x711/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x3fc/0x770 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 home/kwqcheii/source/fuzzing/kernel/kasan/linux-6.16.4/arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:245
 

Allocated by task 12210:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:377 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x93/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:394
 kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:260 [inline]
 __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x230/0x3d0 mm/slub.c:4364
 kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:905 [inline]
 kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1039 [inline]
 mgmt_pending_new+0x65/0x1e0 net/bluetooth/mgmt_util.c:269
 mgmt_pending_add+0x35/0x140 net/bluetooth/mgmt_util.c:296
 __add_adv_patterns_monitor+0x130/0x200 net/bluetooth/mgmt.c:5247
 add_adv_patterns_monitor+0x214/0x360 net/bluetooth/mgmt.c:5364
 hci_mgmt_cmd+0x9c9/0xef0 net/bluetooth/hci_sock.c:1719
 hci_sock_sendmsg+0x6ca/0xef0 net/bluetooth/hci_sock.c:1839
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:714 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0x219/0x270 net/socket.c:729
 sock_write_iter+0x258/0x330 net/socket.c:1133
 new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
 vfs_write+0x5c9/0xb30 fs/read_write.c:686
 ksys_write+0x145/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xfa/0x3b0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Freed by task 12221:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 kasan_save_free_info+0x46/0x50 mm/kasan/generic.c:576
 poison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:247 [inline]
 __kasan_slab_free+0x62/0x70 mm/kasan/common.c:264
 kasan_slab_free include/linux/kasan.h:233 [inline]
 slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:2381 [inline]
 slab_free mm/slub.c:4648 [inline]
 kfree+0x18e/0x440 mm/slub.c:4847
 mgmt_pending_free net/bluetooth/mgmt_util.c:311 [inline]
 mgmt_pending_foreach+0x30d/0x380 net/bluetooth/mgmt_util.c:257
 __mgmt_power_off+0x169/0x350 net/bluetooth/mgmt.c:9444
 hci_dev_close_sync+0x754/0x1330 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:5290
 hci_dev_do_close net/bluetooth/hci_core.c:501 [inline]
 hci_dev_close+0x108/0x200 net/bluetooth/hci_core.c:526
 sock_do_ioctl+0xd9/0x300 net/socket.c:1192
 sock_ioctl+0x576/0x790 net/socket.c:1313
 vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
 __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:907 [inline]
 __se_sys_ioctl+0xf9/0x170 fs/ioctl.c:893
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xf
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39982 | Bluetooth: hci_event: Fix UAF in hci_acl_create_conn_sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39982</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: hci_event: Fix UAF in hci_acl_create_conn_sync

This fixes the following UFA in hci_acl_create_conn_sync where a
connection still pending is command submission (conn-&gt;state == BT_OPEN)
maybe freed, also since this also can happen with the likes of
hci_le_create_conn_sync fix it as well:

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in hci_acl_create_conn_sync+0x5ef/0x790 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:6861
Write of size 2 at addr ffff88805ffcc038 by task kworker/u11:2/9541

CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 9541 Comm: kworker/u11:2 Not tainted 6.16.0-rc7 #3 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.10.2-1ubuntu1 04/01/2014
Workqueue: hci3 hci_cmd_sync_work
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x189/0x250 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0xca/0x230 mm/kasan/report.c:480
 kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:593
 hci_acl_create_conn_sync+0x5ef/0x790 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:6861
 hci_cmd_sync_work+0x210/0x3a0 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:332
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3238 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xae1/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3321
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x70e/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x3fc/0x770 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 home/kwqcheii/source/fuzzing/kernel/kasan/linux-6.16-rc7/arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:245
 

Allocated by task 123736:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:377 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x93/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:394
 kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:260 [inline]
 __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x230/0x3d0 mm/slub.c:4359
 kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:905 [inline]
 kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1039 [inline]
 __hci_conn_add+0x233/0x1b30 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:939
 hci_conn_add_unset net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:1051 [inline]
 hci_connect_acl+0x16c/0x4e0 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:1634
 pair_device+0x418/0xa70 net/bluetooth/mgmt.c:3556
 hci_mgmt_cmd+0x9c9/0xef0 net/bluetooth/hci_sock.c:1719
 hci_sock_sendmsg+0x6ca/0xef0 net/bluetooth/hci_sock.c:1839
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:712 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0x219/0x270 net/socket.c:727
 sock_write_iter+0x258/0x330 net/socket.c:1131
 new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
 vfs_write+0x54b/0xa90 fs/read_write.c:686
 ksys_write+0x145/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xfa/0x3b0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Freed by task 103680:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 kasan_save_free_info+0x46/0x50 mm/kasan/generic.c:576
 poison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:247 [inline]
 __kasan_slab_free+0x62/0x70 mm/kasan/common.c:264
 kasan_slab_free include/linux/kasan.h:233 [inline]
 slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:2381 [inline]
 slab_free mm/slub.c:4643 [inline]
 kfree+0x18e/0x440 mm/slub.c:4842
 device_release+0x9c/0x1c0
 kobject_cleanup lib/kobject.c:689 [inline]
 kobject_release lib/kobject.c:720 [inline]
 kref_put include/linux/kref.h:65 [inline]
 kobject_put+0x22b/0x480 lib/kobject.c:737
 hci_conn_cleanup net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:175 [inline]
 hci_conn_del+0x8ff/0xcb0 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:1173
 hci_conn_complete_evt+0x3c7/0x1040 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:3199
 hci_event_func net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7477 [inline]
 hci_event_packet+0x7e0/0x1200 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7531
 hci_rx_work+0x46a/0xe80 net/bluetooth/hci_core.c:4070
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3238 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xae1/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3321
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x70e/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x3fc/0x770 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 home/kwqcheii/sour
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39983 | Bluetooth: hci_event: Fix UAF in hci_conn_tx_dequeue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39983</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: hci_event: Fix UAF in hci_conn_tx_dequeue

This fixes the following UAF caused by not properly locking hdev when
processing HCI_EV_NUM_COMP_PKTS:

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in hci_conn_tx_dequeue+0x1be/0x220 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:3036
Read of size 4 at addr ffff8880740f0940 by task kworker/u11:0/54

CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 54 Comm: kworker/u11:0 Not tainted 6.16.0-rc7 #3 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.10.2-1ubuntu1 04/01/2014
Workqueue: hci1 hci_rx_work
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x189/0x250 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0xca/0x230 mm/kasan/report.c:480
 kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:593
 hci_conn_tx_dequeue+0x1be/0x220 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:3036
 hci_num_comp_pkts_evt+0x1c8/0xa50 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:4404
 hci_event_func net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7477 [inline]
 hci_event_packet+0x7e0/0x1200 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7531
 hci_rx_work+0x46a/0xe80 net/bluetooth/hci_core.c:4070
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3238 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xae1/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3321
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x70e/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x3fc/0x770 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 home/kwqcheii/source/fuzzing/kernel/kasan/linux-6.16-rc7/arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:245
 

Allocated by task 54:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:377 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x93/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:394
 kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:260 [inline]
 __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x230/0x3d0 mm/slub.c:4359
 kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:905 [inline]
 kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1039 [inline]
 __hci_conn_add+0x233/0x1b30 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:939
 le_conn_complete_evt+0x3d6/0x1220 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:5628
 hci_le_enh_conn_complete_evt+0x189/0x470 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:5794
 hci_event_func net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7474 [inline]
 hci_event_packet+0x78c/0x1200 net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7531
 hci_rx_work+0x46a/0xe80 net/bluetooth/hci_core.c:4070
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3238 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xae1/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3321
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x70e/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x3fc/0x770 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 home/kwqcheii/source/fuzzing/kernel/kasan/linux-6.16-rc7/arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:245

Freed by task 9572:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 kasan_save_free_info+0x46/0x50 mm/kasan/generic.c:576
 poison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:247 [inline]
 __kasan_slab_free+0x62/0x70 mm/kasan/common.c:264
 kasan_slab_free include/linux/kasan.h:233 [inline]
 slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:2381 [inline]
 slab_free mm/slub.c:4643 [inline]
 kfree+0x18e/0x440 mm/slub.c:4842
 device_release+0x9c/0x1c0
 kobject_cleanup lib/kobject.c:689 [inline]
 kobject_release lib/kobject.c:720 [inline]
 kref_put include/linux/kref.h:65 [inline]
 kobject_put+0x22b/0x480 lib/kobject.c:737
 hci_conn_cleanup net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:175 [inline]
 hci_conn_del+0x8ff/0xcb0 net/bluetooth/hci_conn.c:1173
 hci_abort_conn_sync+0x5d1/0xdf0 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:5689
 hci_cmd_sync_work+0x210/0x3a0 net/bluetooth/hci_sync.c:332
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3238 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xae1/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3321
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x70e/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x3fc/0x770 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 home/kwqcheii/source/fuzzing/kernel/kasan/linux-6.16-rc7/arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:245</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39984 | net: tun: Update napi-&amp;gt;skb after XDP process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39984</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: tun: Update napi-&gt;skb after XDP process

The syzbot report a UAF issue:

  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in skb_reset_mac_header include/linux/skbuff.h:3150 [inline]
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in napi_frags_skb net/core/gro.c:723 [inline]
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in napi_gro_frags+0x6e/0x1030 net/core/gro.c:758
  Read of size 8 at addr ffff88802ef22c18 by task syz.0.17/6079
  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 6079 Comm: syz.0.17 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
  Call Trace:
   
   dump_stack_lvl+0x189/0x250 lib/dump_stack.c:120
   print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
   print_report+0xca/0x240 mm/kasan/report.c:482
   kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:595
   skb_reset_mac_header include/linux/skbuff.h:3150 [inline]
   napi_frags_skb net/core/gro.c:723 [inline]
   napi_gro_frags+0x6e/0x1030 net/core/gro.c:758
   tun_get_user+0x28cb/0x3e20 drivers/net/tun.c:1920
   tun_chr_write_iter+0x113/0x200 drivers/net/tun.c:1996
   new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
   vfs_write+0x5c9/0xb30 fs/read_write.c:686
   ksys_write+0x145/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xfa/0x3b0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
   

  Allocated by task 6079:
   kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
   kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
   unpoison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:330 [inline]
   __kasan_mempool_unpoison_object+0xa0/0x170 mm/kasan/common.c:558
   kasan_mempool_unpoison_object include/linux/kasan.h:388 [inline]
   napi_skb_cache_get+0x37b/0x6d0 net/core/skbuff.c:295
   __alloc_skb+0x11e/0x2d0 net/core/skbuff.c:657
   napi_alloc_skb+0x84/0x7d0 net/core/skbuff.c:811
   napi_get_frags+0x69/0x140 net/core/gro.c:673
   tun_napi_alloc_frags drivers/net/tun.c:1404 [inline]
   tun_get_user+0x77c/0x3e20 drivers/net/tun.c:1784
   tun_chr_write_iter+0x113/0x200 drivers/net/tun.c:1996
   new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
   vfs_write+0x5c9/0xb30 fs/read_write.c:686
   ksys_write+0x145/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xfa/0x3b0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

  Freed by task 6079:
   kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
   kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
   kasan_save_free_info+0x46/0x50 mm/kasan/generic.c:576
   poison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:243 [inline]
   __kasan_slab_free+0x5b/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:275
   kasan_slab_free include/linux/kasan.h:233 [inline]
   slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:2422 [inline]
   slab_free mm/slub.c:4695 [inline]
   kmem_cache_free+0x18f/0x400 mm/slub.c:4797
   skb_pp_cow_data+0xdd8/0x13e0 net/core/skbuff.c:969
   netif_skb_check_for_xdp net/core/dev.c:5390 [inline]
   netif_receive_generic_xdp net/core/dev.c:5431 [inline]
   do_xdp_generic+0x699/0x11a0 net/core/dev.c:5499
   tun_get_user+0x2523/0x3e20 drivers/net/tun.c:1872
   tun_chr_write_iter+0x113/0x200 drivers/net/tun.c:1996
   new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
   vfs_write+0x5c9/0xb30 fs/read_write.c:686
   ksys_write+0x145/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xfa/0x3b0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

After commit e6d5dbdd20aa ("xdp: add multi-buff support for xdp running in
generic mode"), the original skb may be freed in skb_pp_cow_data() when
XDP program was attached, which was allocated in tun_napi_alloc_frags().
However, the napi-&gt;skb still point to the original skb, update it after
XDP process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39985 | can: mcba_usb: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39985</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: mcba_usb: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow

Sending an PF_PACKET allows to bypass the CAN framework logic and to
directly reach the xmit() function of a CAN driver. The only check
which is performed by the PF_PACKET framework is to make sure that
skb-&gt;len fits the interface's MTU.

Unfortunately, because the mcba_usb driver does not populate its
net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu(), it is possible for an attacker to
configure an invalid MTU by doing, for example:

  $ ip link set can0 mtu 9999

After doing so, the attacker could open a PF_PACKET socket using the
ETH_P_CANXL protocol:

	socket(PF_PACKET, SOCK_RAW, htons(ETH_P_CANXL))

to inject a malicious CAN XL frames. For example:

	struct canxl_frame frame = {
		.flags = 0xff,
		.len = 2048,
	};

The CAN drivers' xmit() function are calling can_dev_dropped_skb() to
check that the skb is valid, unfortunately under above conditions, the
malicious packet is able to go through can_dev_dropped_skb() checks:

  1. the skb-&gt;protocol is set to ETH_P_CANXL which is valid (the
     function does not check the actual device capabilities).

  2. the length is a valid CAN XL length.

And so, mcba_usb_start_xmit() receives a CAN XL frame which it is not
able to correctly handle and will thus misinterpret it as a CAN frame.

This can result in a buffer overflow. The driver will consume cf-&gt;len
as-is with no further checks on these lines:

	usb_msg.dlc = cf-&gt;len;

	memcpy(usb_msg.data, cf-&gt;data, usb_msg.dlc);

Here, cf-&gt;len corresponds to the flags field of the CAN XL frame. In
our previous example, we set canxl_frame-&gt;flags to 0xff. Because the
maximum expected length is 8, a buffer overflow of 247 bytes occurs!

Populate net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu() to ensure that the
interface's MTU can not be set to anything bigger than CAN_MTU. By
fixing the root cause, this prevents the buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39986 | can: sun4i_can: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39986</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: sun4i_can: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow

Sending an PF_PACKET allows to bypass the CAN framework logic and to
directly reach the xmit() function of a CAN driver. The only check
which is performed by the PF_PACKET framework is to make sure that
skb-&gt;len fits the interface's MTU.

Unfortunately, because the sun4i_can driver does not populate its
net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu(), it is possible for an attacker to
configure an invalid MTU by doing, for example:

  $ ip link set can0 mtu 9999

After doing so, the attacker could open a PF_PACKET socket using the
ETH_P_CANXL protocol:

	socket(PF_PACKET, SOCK_RAW, htons(ETH_P_CANXL))

to inject a malicious CAN XL frames. For example:

	struct canxl_frame frame = {
		.flags = 0xff,
		.len = 2048,
	};

The CAN drivers' xmit() function are calling can_dev_dropped_skb() to
check that the skb is valid, unfortunately under above conditions, the
malicious packet is able to go through can_dev_dropped_skb() checks:

  1. the skb-&gt;protocol is set to ETH_P_CANXL which is valid (the
     function does not check the actual device capabilities).

  2. the length is a valid CAN XL length.

And so, sun4ican_start_xmit() receives a CAN XL frame which it is not
able to correctly handle and will thus misinterpret it as a CAN frame.

This can result in a buffer overflow. The driver will consume cf-&gt;len
as-is with no further checks on this line:

	dlc = cf-&gt;len;

Here, cf-&gt;len corresponds to the flags field of the CAN XL frame. In
our previous example, we set canxl_frame-&gt;flags to 0xff. Because the
maximum expected length is 8, a buffer overflow of 247 bytes occurs a
couple line below when doing:

	for (i = 0; i &lt; dlc; i++)
		writel(cf-&gt;data[i], priv-&gt;base + (dreg + i * 4));

Populate net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu() to ensure that the
interface's MTU can not be set to anything bigger than CAN_MTU. By
fixing the root cause, this prevents the buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39987 | can: hi311x: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39987</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: hi311x: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow

Sending an PF_PACKET allows to bypass the CAN framework logic and to
directly reach the xmit() function of a CAN driver. The only check
which is performed by the PF_PACKET framework is to make sure that
skb-&gt;len fits the interface's MTU.

Unfortunately, because the sun4i_can driver does not populate its
net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu(), it is possible for an attacker to
configure an invalid MTU by doing, for example:

  $ ip link set can0 mtu 9999

After doing so, the attacker could open a PF_PACKET socket using the
ETH_P_CANXL protocol:

	socket(PF_PACKET, SOCK_RAW, htons(ETH_P_CANXL))

to inject a malicious CAN XL frames. For example:

	struct canxl_frame frame = {
		.flags = 0xff,
		.len = 2048,
	};

The CAN drivers' xmit() function are calling can_dev_dropped_skb() to
check that the skb is valid, unfortunately under above conditions, the
malicious packet is able to go through can_dev_dropped_skb() checks:

  1. the skb-&gt;protocol is set to ETH_P_CANXL which is valid (the
     function does not check the actual device capabilities).

  2. the length is a valid CAN XL length.

And so, hi3110_hard_start_xmit() receives a CAN XL frame which it is
not able to correctly handle and will thus misinterpret it as a CAN
frame. The driver will consume frame-&gt;len as-is with no further
checks.

This can result in a buffer overflow later on in hi3110_hw_tx() on
this line:

	memcpy(buf + HI3110_FIFO_EXT_DATA_OFF,
	       frame-&gt;data, frame-&gt;len);

Here, frame-&gt;len corresponds to the flags field of the CAN XL frame.
In our previous example, we set canxl_frame-&gt;flags to 0xff. Because
the maximum expected length is 8, a buffer overflow of 247 bytes
occurs!

Populate net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu() to ensure that the
interface's MTU can not be set to anything bigger than CAN_MTU. By
fixing the root cause, this prevents the buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39988 | can: etas_es58x: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39988</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: etas_es58x: populate ndo_change_mtu() to prevent buffer overflow

Sending an PF_PACKET allows to bypass the CAN framework logic and to
directly reach the xmit() function of a CAN driver. The only check
which is performed by the PF_PACKET framework is to make sure that
skb-&gt;len fits the interface's MTU.

Unfortunately, because the etas_es58x driver does not populate its
net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu(), it is possible for an attacker to
configure an invalid MTU by doing, for example:

  $ ip link set can0 mtu 9999

After doing so, the attacker could open a PF_PACKET socket using the
ETH_P_CANXL protocol:

	socket(PF_PACKET, SOCK_RAW, htons(ETH_P_CANXL));

to inject a malicious CAN XL frames. For example:

	struct canxl_frame frame = {
		.flags = 0xff,
		.len = 2048,
	};

The CAN drivers' xmit() function are calling can_dev_dropped_skb() to
check that the skb is valid, unfortunately under above conditions, the
malicious packet is able to go through can_dev_dropped_skb() checks:

  1. the skb-&gt;protocol is set to ETH_P_CANXL which is valid (the
     function does not check the actual device capabilities).

  2. the length is a valid CAN XL length.

And so, es58x_start_xmit() receives a CAN XL frame which it is not
able to correctly handle and will thus misinterpret it as a CAN(FD)
frame.

This can result in a buffer overflow. For example, using the es581.4
variant, the frame will be dispatched to es581_4_tx_can_msg(), go
through the last check at the beginning of this function:

	if (can_is_canfd_skb(skb))
		return -EMSGSIZE;

and reach this line:

	memcpy(tx_can_msg-&gt;data, cf-&gt;data, cf-&gt;len);

Here, cf-&gt;len corresponds to the flags field of the CAN XL frame. In
our previous example, we set canxl_frame-&gt;flags to 0xff. Because the
maximum expected length is 8, a buffer overflow of 247 bytes occurs!

Populate net_device_ops-&gt;ndo_change_mtu() to ensure that the
interface's MTU can not be set to anything bigger than CAN_MTU or
CANFD_MTU (depending on the device capabilities). By fixing the root
cause, this prevents the buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39990 | bpf: Check the helper function is valid in get_helper_proto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39990</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Check the helper function is valid in get_helper_proto

kernel test robot reported verifier bug [1] where the helper func
pointer could be NULL due to disabled config option.

As Alexei suggested we could check on that in get_helper_proto
directly. Marking tail_call helper func with BPF_PTR_POISON,
because it is unused by design.

  [1] https://lore.kernel.org/oe-lkp/202507160818.68358831-lkp@intel.com</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 08:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11501 | Dynamically Display Posts &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11501</link><description>The Dynamically Display Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'tax_query' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61941 | A path traversal issue exists in WXR9300BE6P series firmware versions prior to Ver.1.10. Arbitrary file may be altered by an administrative ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61941</link><description>A path traversal issue exists in WXR9300BE6P series firmware versions prior to Ver.1.10. Arbitrary file may be altered by an administrative user who logs in to the affected product. Moreover, arbitrary OS command may be executed via some file alteration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55039 | Apache Spark, Apache Spark: RPC encryption defaults to unauthenticated AES-CTR mode, enabling man-in-the-middle ciphertext modification attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55039</link><description>This issue affects Apache Spark versions before  3.4.4, 3.5.2 and 4.0.0.



Apache Spark versions before 4.0.0, 3.5.2 and 3.4.4 use an insecure default network encryption cipher for RPC communication between nodes.

When spark.network.crypto.enabled is set to true (it is set to false by default), but spark.network.crypto.cipher is not explicitly configured, Spark defaults to AES in CTR mode (AES/CTR/NoPadding), which provides encryption without authentication.

This vulnerability allows a man-in-the-middle attacker to modify encrypted RPC traffic undetected by flipping bits in ciphertext, potentially compromising heartbeat messages or application data and affecting the integrity of Spark workflows.


To mitigate this issue, users should either configure spark.network.crypto.cipher to AES/GCM/NoPadding to enable authenticated encryption or

enable SSL encryption by setting spark.ssl.enabled to true, which provides stronger transport security.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11160 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.6.1 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom JS Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11160</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom JS module in all versions up to, and including, 8.6.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping of user-supplied JavaScript code in the Custom JS module. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page via the WPBakery Page Builder Custom JS module granted they have access to the WPBakery editor for post types.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11161 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.6.1 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting via vc_custom_heading Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11161</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the vc_custom_heading shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.6.1. This is due to insufficient restriction of allowed HTML tags and improper sanitization of user-supplied attributes in the font_container parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in posts that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page via the vc_custom_heading shortcode with malicious tag and text attributes granted they have access to use WPBakery shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10406 | BlindMatrix e-Commerce &amp;lt; 3.1 - Contributor+ LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10406</link><description>The BlindMatrix e-Commerce WordPress plugin before 3.1 does not validate some shortcode attributes before using them to generate paths passed to include function/s, allowing any authenticated users, such as contributors, to perform LFI attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26859 | RemoteView PC Application Console versions prior to 6.0.2 contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. If a crafted DLL is pla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26859</link><description>RemoteView PC Application Console versions prior to 6.0.2 contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. If a crafted DLL is placed in the same folder with the affected product, it may cause an arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26860 | RemoteCall Remote Support Program (for Operator) versions prior to 5.1.0 contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. If a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26860</link><description>RemoteCall Remote Support Program (for Operator) versions prior to 5.1.0 contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. If a crafted DLL is placed in the same folder with the affected product, it may cause an arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26861 | RemoteCall Remote Support Program (for Operator) versions prior to 5.3.0 contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. If a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26861</link><description>RemoteCall Remote Support Program (for Operator) versions prior to 5.3.0 contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. If a crafted DLL is placed in the same folder with the affected product, it may cause an arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31702 | A vulnerability exists in certain Dahua embedded products. Third-party malicious attacker with obtained normal user credentials could exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31702</link><description>A vulnerability exists in certain Dahua embedded products. Third-party malicious attacker with obtained normal user credentials could exploit the vulnerability to access certain data which are restricted to admin privileges, such as system-sensitive files through specific HTTP request. This may cause tampering with admin password, leading to privilege escalation. Systems with only admin account are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 06:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55080 | Improper Parameter Check in ThreadX Syscall Implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55080</link><description>In Eclipse ThreadX before 6.4.3, when memory protection is enabled, syscall parameters verification wasn't enough, allowing an attacker to obtain an arbitrary memory read/write.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 05:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11176 | Quick Featured Images &amp;lt;= 13.7.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Image Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11176</link><description>The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 13.7.2 via the qfi_set_thumbnail and qfi_delete_thumbnail AJAX actions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to change or remove featured images of other user's posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6042 | Lisfinity Core - Lisfinity Core plugin used for pebas® Lisfinity WordPress theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation to Editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6042</link><description>The Lisfinity Core - Lisfinity Core plugin used for pebas® Lisfinity WordPress theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0. This is due to the plugin assigning the editor role by default. While limitations with respect to capabilities are put in place, use of the API is not restricted. This vulnerability can be leveraged together with CVE-2025-6038 to obtain admin privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8561 | Ova Advent &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8561</link><description>The Ova Advent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 05:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55079 | Missing check for thread priority</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55079</link><description>In Eclipse ThreadX before version 6.4.3, the thread module has a setting of maximum priority. In some cases the check of that maximum priority wasn't performed, allowing, as a result, to obtain a thread with higher priority than expected and causing a possible denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 04:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11746 | XStore | Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 9.5.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11746</link><description>The XStore theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 9.5.4 via theet_ajax_required_plugins_popup() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 03:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10033 | WordPress Plugin is-human &amp;lt;= v1.4.2 Eval Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10033</link><description>The WordPress plugin is-human &lt;= v1.4.2 contains an eval injection vulnerability in /is-human/engine.php that can be triggered via the 'type' parameter when the 'action' parameter is set to 'log-reset'. The root cause is unsafe use of eval() on user-controlled input, which can lead to execution of attacker-supplied PHP and OS commands. This may result in arbitrary code execution as the webserver user, site compromise, or data exfiltration. The is-human plugin was made defunct in June 2008 and is no longer available for download. This vulnerability was exploited in the wild in March 2012.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20204 | DBLTek GoIP Telnet Admin Interface Undocumented Backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20204</link><description>DBLTek GoIP devices (models GoIP 1, 4, 8, 16, and 32) contain an undocumented vendor backdoor in the Telnet administrative interface that allows remote authentication as an undocumented user via a proprietary challenge–response scheme which is fundamentally flawed. Because the challenge response can be computed from the challenge itself, a remote attacker can authenticate without knowledge of a secret and obtain a root shell on the device. This can lead to persistent remote code execution, full device compromise, and arbitrary control of the device and any managed services. The firmware used within these devices was updated in December 2016 to make this vulnerability more complex to exploit. However, it is unknown if DBLTek has taken steps to fully mitigate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20205 | Valve Source SDK Stack-Based Buffer Overflow RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20205</link><description>Valve's Source SDK (source-sdk-2013)'s ragdoll model parsing logic contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability.The tokenizer function `nexttoken` copies characters from an input string into a fixed-size stack buffer without performing bounds checks. When `ParseKeyValue` processes a collisionpair rule longer than the destination buffer (256 bytes), an overflow of the stack buffer `szToken` can occur and overwrite the function return address. A remote attacker can trigger the vulnerable code by supplying a specially crafted ragdoll model which causes the oversized collisionpair rule to be parsed, resulting in remote code execution on affected clients or servers. Valve has addressed this issue in many of their Source games, but independently-developed games must manually apply patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25117 | VestaCP Debian Installer Malicious Backdoor Supply Chain Compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25117</link><description>VestaCP commit a3f0fa1 (2018-05-31) up to commit ee03eff (2018-06-13) contain embedded malicious code that resulted in a supply-chain compromise. New installations created from the compromised installer since at least May 2018 were subject to installation of Linux/ChachaDDoS, a multi-stage DDoS bot that uses Lua for second- and third-stage components. The compromise leaked administrative credentials (base64-encoded admin password and server domain) to an external URL during installation and/or resulted in the installer dropping and executing a DDoS malware payload under local system privileges. Compromised servers were subsequently observed participating in large-scale DDoS activity. Vesta acknowledged exploitation in the wild in October 2018.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7304 | Ruijie RG-UAC nmc_sync.php Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7304</link><description>Ruijie RG-UAC Application Management Gateway contains a command injection vulnerability via the 'nmc_sync.php' interface. An unauthenticated attacker able to reach the affected endpoint can inject shell commands via crafted request data, causing the application to execute arbitrary commands on the host. Successful exploitation can yield full control of the application process and may lead to system-level access depending on the service privileges. VulnCheck has observed this vulnerability being targeted by the Rondo botnet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7305 | SmartBI RMIServlet Unrestricted File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7305</link><description>SmartBI V8, V9, and V10 contain an unrestricted file upload vulnerability via the RMIServlet request handling logic. Under certain configurations or usage patterns, attackers can send specially crafted requests that cause the application to perform sensitive operations or execute arbitrary code on the host. The vendor released a fix in July 2023 to address the underlying flaw. VulnCheck has observed this vulnerability being targeted by the Rondo botnet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7311 | BYTEVALUE Intelligent Flow Control Router Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7311</link><description>BYTEVALUE Intelligent Flow Control Router contains a command injection vulnerability via the /goform/webRead/open endpoint. The `path` parameter is not properly validated and is echoed into a shell context, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands on the device. Successful exploitation can lead to writing backdoors, privilege escalation on the host, and full compromise of the router and its management functions. VulnCheck has observed this vulnerability being targeted by the Rondo botnet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13991 | Huijietong Cloud Video Platform fileDownload Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13991</link><description>Huijietong Cloud Video Platform contains a path traversal vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker can supply arbitrary file paths to the `fullPath` parameter of the `/fileDownload?action=downloadBackupFile` endpoint and retrieve files from the server filesystem. VulnCheck has observed this vulnerability being targeted by the Rondo botnet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54268 | Bridge | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54268</link><description>Bridge versions 14.1.8, 15.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54278 | Bridge | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54278</link><description>Bridge versions 14.1.8, 15.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information stored in memory. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54269 | Animate | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54269</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.13, 24.0.10 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information stored in memory. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54270 | Animate | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54270</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.13, 24.0.10 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive memory information. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54279 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54279</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.13, 24.0.10 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61804 | Animate | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61804</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.13, 24.0.10 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>