<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-40685 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40685</link><description>Management Central as part of IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Navigator contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with command line access to the operating system can exploit this vulnerability to elevate privileges to gain root access to the operating system.  IBM X-Force ID:  264116.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40686 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40686</link><description>Management Central as part of IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Navigator contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with command line access to the operating system can exploit this vulnerability to elevate privileges to gain component access to the operating system.  IBM X-Force ID:  264114.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43041 | IBM QRadar information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43041</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to information exposure allowing a delegated Admin tenant user with a specific domain security profile assigned to see data from other domains.  This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-34352.  IBM X-Force ID:  266808.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46858 | Moodle 4.3 allows /grade/report/grader/index.php?searchvalue= reflected XSS when logged in as a teacher. NOTE: the Moodle Security FAQ link ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46858</link><description>Moodle 4.3 allows /grade/report/grader/index.php?searchvalue= reflected XSS when logged in as a teacher. NOTE: the Moodle Security FAQ link states "Some forms of rich content [are] used by teachers to enhance their courses ... admins and teachers can post XSS-capable content, but students can not."</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5838 | Insufficient Session Expiration in linkstackorg/linkstack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5838</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository linkstackorg/linkstack prior to v4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5839 | Privilege Chaining in hestiacp/hestiacp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5839</link><description>Privilege Chaining in GitHub repository hestiacp/hestiacp prior to 1.8.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5840 | Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password in linkstackorg/linkstack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5840</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password in GitHub repository linkstackorg/linkstack prior to v4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46854 | Proxmox proxmox-widget-toolkit before 4.0.9, as used in multiple Proxmox products, allows XSS via the edit notes feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46854</link><description>Proxmox proxmox-widget-toolkit before 4.0.9, as used in multiple Proxmox products, allows XSS via the edit notes feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 21:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5837 | AlexanderLivanov FotosCMS2 Cookie profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5837</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in AlexanderLivanov FotosCMS2 up to 2.4.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file profile.php of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243802 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 21:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5836 | SourceCodester Task Reminder System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Reminder System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file classes/Users.php?f=delete. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243800.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 21:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45897 | exfatprogs before 1.2.2 allows out-of-bounds memory access, such as in read_file_dentry_set.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45897</link><description>exfatprogs before 1.2.2 allows out-of-bounds memory access, such as in read_file_dentry_set.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5835 | hu60t hu60wap6 ubbparser.php markdown cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5835</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in hu60t hu60wap6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function markdown of the file src/class/ubbparser.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named a1cd9f12d7687243bfcb7ce295665acb83b9174e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243775.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5425 | The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5425</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pmdm_wp_change_user_meta and pmdm_wp_change_post_meta functions in versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to gain elevated (e.g., administrator) privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 11:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5426 | The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5426</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pmdm_wp_delete_user_meta,  pmdm_wp_delete_term_meta, and pmdm_wp_ajax_delete_meta functions in versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete user, term, and post meta belonging to arbitrary users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 11:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46215 | Apache Airflow Celery provider, Apache Airflow: Sensitive information logged as clear text when rediss, amqp, rpc protocols are used as Celery result backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46215</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Apache Airflow Celery provider, Apache Airflow.

Sensitive information logged as clear text when rediss, amqp, rpc protocols are used as Celery result backend
Note: the vulnerability is about the information exposed in the logs not about accessing the logs.

This issue affects Apache Airflow Celery provider: from 3.3.0 through 3.4.0; Apache Airflow: from 1.10.0 through 2.6.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade Airflow Celery provider to version 3.4.1 and Apache Airlfow to version 2.7.0 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 07:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46569 | An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32_fpu function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46569</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32_fpu function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46570 | An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32 function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46570</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32 function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43322 | ZPE Systems, Inc Nodegrid OS v5.0.0 to v5.0.17, v5.2.0 to v5.2.19, v5.4.0 to v5.4.16, v5.6.0 to v5.6.13, v5.8.0 to v5.8.10, and v5.10.0 to v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43322</link><description>ZPE Systems, Inc Nodegrid OS v5.0.0 to v5.0.17, v5.2.0 to v5.2.19, v5.4.0 to v5.4.16, v5.6.0 to v5.6.13, v5.8.0 to v5.8.10, and v5.10.0 to v5.10.3 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the endpoint /v1/system/toolkit/files/.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46468 | An issue in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the custom plugin function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46468</link><description>An issue in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the custom plugin function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46467 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46467</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the username parameter of the registration page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46587 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in XnView Classic v.2.51.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted TIF file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46587</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in XnView Classic v.2.51.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted TIF file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 23:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46490 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Cacti v1.2.25 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the form_actions() function in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46490</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Cacti v1.2.25 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the form_actions() function in the managers.php function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5834 | Vagrant’s Windows Installer Allowed Directory Junction Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5834</link><description>HashiCorp Vagrant's Windows installer targeted a custom location with a non-protected path that could be junctioned, introducing potential for unauthorized file system writes. Fixed in Vagrant 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34832 | An issue was discovered in VERMEG AgileReporter 21.3. XXE can occur via an XML document to the Analysis component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34832</link><description>An issue was discovered in VERMEG AgileReporter 21.3. XXE can occur via an XML document to the Analysis component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34833 | An issue was discovered in VERMEG AgileReporter 21.3. An admin can enter an XSS payload in the Analysis component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34833</link><description>An issue was discovered in VERMEG AgileReporter 21.3. An admin can enter an XSS payload in the Analysis component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34834 | An issue was discovered in VERMEG AgileReporter 21.3. Attackers can gain privileges via an XSS payload in an Add Comment action to the Activ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34834</link><description>An issue was discovered in VERMEG AgileReporter 21.3. Attackers can gain privileges via an XSS payload in an Add Comment action to the Activity log.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44480 | Leave Management System Project v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44480</link><description>Leave Management System Project v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'setcasualleave' parameter of the admin/setleaves.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46209 | WordPress Grid Plus Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46209</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in G5Theme Grid Plus – Unlimited grid plugin &lt;= 1.3.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46509 | An issue in Contec SolarView Compact v.6.0 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the texteditor.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46509</link><description>An issue in Contec SolarView Compact v.6.0 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the texteditor.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46510 | An issue in ZIONCOM (Hong Kong) Technology Limited A7000R v.4.1cu.4154 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the cig-bin/cstecgi....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46510</link><description>An issue in ZIONCOM (Hong Kong) Technology Limited A7000R v.4.1cu.4154 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the cig-bin/cstecgi.cgi to the settings/setPasswordCfg function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35794 | An issue was discovered in Cassia Access Controller 2.1.1.2303271039. The Web SSH terminal endpoint (spawned console) can be accessed withou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35794</link><description>An issue was discovered in Cassia Access Controller 2.1.1.2303271039. The Web SSH terminal endpoint (spawned console) can be accessed without authentication. Specifically, there is no session cookie validation on the Access Controller; instead, there is only Basic Authentication to the SSH console.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5830 | ColumbiaSoft Document Locator WebTools login improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5830</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ColumbiaSoft Document Locator. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/authentication/login of the component WebTools. The manipulation of the argument Server leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 7.2 SP4 and 2021.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-243729 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46208 | WordPress Motors – Car Dealer &amp;amp; Classified Ads Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46208</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in StylemixThemes Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp; Listing plugin &lt;= 1.4.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40116 | In onTaskAppeared of PipTaskOrganizer.java, there is a possible way to bypass background activity launch restrictions due to a logic error i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40116</link><description>In onTaskAppeared of PipTaskOrganizer.java, there is a possible way to bypass background activity launch restrictions due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40117 | In resetSettingsLocked of SettingsProvider.java, there is a possible lockscreen bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40117</link><description>In resetSettingsLocked of SettingsProvider.java, there is a possible lockscreen bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40120 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to bypass user notification of foreground services due to improper input validation. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40120</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to bypass user notification of foreground services due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40121 | In appendEscapedSQLString of DatabaseUtils.java, there is a possible SQL injection due to unsafe deserialization. This could lead to local i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40121</link><description>In appendEscapedSQLString of DatabaseUtils.java, there is a possible SQL injection due to unsafe deserialization. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40123 | In updateActionViews of PipMenuView.java, there is a possible bypass of a multi user security boundary due to a confused deputy. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40123</link><description>In updateActionViews of PipMenuView.java, there is a possible bypass of a multi user security boundary due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40125 | In onCreate of ApnEditor.java, there is a possible way for a Guest user to change the APN due to a permission bypass. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40125</link><description>In onCreate of ApnEditor.java, there is a possible way for a Guest user to change the APN due to a permission bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40127 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to access screenshots due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40127</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to access screenshots due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40128 | In several functions of xmlregexp.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40128</link><description>In several functions of xmlregexp.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40129 | In build_read_multi_rsp of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40129</link><description>In build_read_multi_rsp of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40130 | In onBindingDied of CallRedirectionProcessor.java, there is a possible permission bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40130</link><description>In onBindingDied of CallRedirectionProcessor.java, there is a possible permission bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege and background activity launch with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40131 | In GpuService of GpuService.cpp, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40131</link><description>In GpuService of GpuService.cpp, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40133 | In multiple locations of DialogFillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40133</link><description>In multiple locations of DialogFillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40134 | In isFullScreen of FillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40134</link><description>In isFullScreen of FillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40135 | In applyCustomDescription of SaveUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40135</link><description>In applyCustomDescription of SaveUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40136 | In setHeader of DialogFillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40136</link><description>In setHeader of DialogFillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40137 | In multiple functions of DialogFillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40137</link><description>In multiple functions of DialogFillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40138 | In FillUi of FillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40138</link><description>In FillUi of FillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40139 | In FillUi of FillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40139</link><description>In FillUi of FillUi.java, there is a possible way to view another user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40140 | In android_view_InputDevice_create of android_view_InputDevice.cpp, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after fre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40140</link><description>In android_view_InputDevice_create of android_view_InputDevice.cpp, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46211 | WordPress Ultimate Addons for WPBakery Page Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19.14 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46211</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Ultimate Addons for WPBakery Page Builder plugin &lt;= 3.19.14 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32738 | WordPress Eonet Manual User Approve Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32738</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Alkaweb Eonet Manual User Approve plugin &lt;= 2.1.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46200 | WordPress Smart App Banner Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46200</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Stephen Darlington, Wandle Software Limited Smart App Banner plugin &lt;= 1.1.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5829 | code-projects Admission Management System student_avatar.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5829</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Admission Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file student_avatar.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243728.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3701 | A privilege elevation vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Vantage SystemUpdate plugin version 2.0.0.212 and earlier that could allow a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3701</link><description>A privilege elevation vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Vantage SystemUpdate plugin version 2.0.0.212 and earlier that could allow a local attacker to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3702 | A denial of service vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Vantage HardwareScan Plugin version 1.3.0.5 and earlier that could allow a local at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3702</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Vantage HardwareScan Plugin version 1.3.0.5 and earlier that could allow a local attacker to delete contents of an arbitrary directory under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3700 | A Time of Check Time of Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Vantage SystemUpdate Plugin version 2.0.0.212 and earlier that...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3700</link><description>A Time of Check Time of Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Vantage SystemUpdate Plugin version 2.0.0.212 and earlier that could allow a local attacker to delete arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29009 | basercms XSS Vulnerability via Favorites Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29009</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework with WebAPI that runs on PHP8 and CakePHP4. There is a XSS Vulnerability in Favorites Feature to baserCMS. This issue has been patched in version 4.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5828 | Nanning Ontall Longxing Industrial Development Zone Project Construction and Installation Management System login.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5828</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nanning Ontall Longxing Industrial Development Zone Project Construction and Installation Management System up to 20231026. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.aspx. The manipulation of the argument tbxUserName leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243727.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3681 | A vulnerability has been identified in the MR2600 router v1.0.18 and earlier that could allow an attacker within range of the wireless netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3681</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the MR2600 router v1.0.18 and earlier that could allow an attacker within range of the wireless network to successfully brute force the WPS pin, potentially allowing them unauthorized access to a wireless network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3611 | An information disclosure vulnerability has been identified in the Lenovo App Store which may allow some applications to gain unauthorized a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3611</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability has been identified in the Lenovo App Store which may allow some applications to gain unauthorized access to sensitive user data used by other unrelated applications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46407 | FFmpeg prior to commit bf814 was discovered to contain an out of bounds read via the dist-&gt;alphabet_size variable in the read_vlc_prefix() f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46407</link><description>FFmpeg prior to commit bf814 was discovered to contain an out of bounds read via the dist-&gt;alphabet_size variable in the read_vlc_prefix() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46852 | In Memcached before 1.6.22, a buffer overflow exists when processing multiget requests in proxy mode, if there are many spaces after the "ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46852</link><description>In Memcached before 1.6.22, a buffer overflow exists when processing multiget requests in proxy mode, if there are many spaces after the "get" substring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46853 | In Memcached before 1.6.22, an off-by-one error exists when processing proxy requests in proxy mode, if \n is used instead of \r\n.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46853</link><description>In Memcached before 1.6.22, an off-by-one error exists when processing proxy requests in proxy mode, if \n is used instead of \r\n.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3429 | A denial-of-service vulnerability was found in the firmware used in Lenovo printers, where users send illegal or malformed strings to an ope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3429</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was found in the firmware used in Lenovo printers, where users send illegal or malformed strings to an open port, triggering a denial of service that causes a display error and prevents the printer from functioning properly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27858 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Simulation Uninitialized Pointer Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27858</link><description>Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation contains an arbitrary code execution vulnerability that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized code to the software by using an uninitialized pointer in the application.  The threat-actor could then execute malicious code on the system affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product.  The user would need to open a malicious file provided to them by the attacker for the code to execute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27854 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Simulation Out of Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27854</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability was reported to Rockwell Automation in Arena Simulation that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized arbitrary code to the software by using a memory buffer overflow.  The threat-actor could then execute malicious code on the system affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product.  The user would need to open a malicious file provided to them by the attacker for the code to execute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34887 | Standard users can directly operate and set printer configuration information , such as IP, in some Lenovo Printers without having to authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34887</link><description>Standard users can directly operate and set printer configuration information , such as IP, in some Lenovo Printers without having to authenticate with the administrator password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34886 | A remote code execution vulnerability was found in the firmware used in some Lenovo printers, which can be caused by a remote user pushing a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34886</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability was found in the firmware used in some Lenovo printers, which can be caused by a remote user pushing an illegal string to the server-side interface via a script, resulting in a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46246 | Integer Overflow in :history command in Vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46246</link><description>Vim is an improved version of the good old UNIX editor Vi. Heap-use-after-free in memory allocated in the function `ga_grow_inner` in in the file `src/alloc.c` at line 748, which is freed in the file `src/ex_docmd.c` in the function `do_cmdline` at line 1010 and then used again in `src/cmdhist.c` at line 759. When using the `:history` command, it's possible that the provided argument overflows the accepted value. Causing an Integer Overflow and potentially later an use-after-free. This vulnerability has been patched in version 9.0.2068.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46289 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View Site Edition Vulnerable to Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46289</link><description>Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk View Site Edition insufficiently validates user input, which could potentially allow threat actors to send malicious data bringing the product offline. If exploited, the product would become unavailable and require a restart to recover resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46290 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Services Platform Elevated Privileges Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46290</link><description>Due to inadequate code logic, a previously unauthenticated threat actor could potentially obtain a local Windows OS user token through the FactoryTalk® Services Platform web service and then use the token to log in into FactoryTalk® Services Platform . This vulnerability can only be exploited if the authorized user did not previously log in into the FactoryTalk® Services Platform web service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4967 | Denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4967</link><description>Denial of Service in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when configured as a Gateway (VPN virtual server, ICA Proxy, CVPN, RDP Proxy) or AAA Virtual Server</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5826 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway list_onlineuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5826</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/list_onlineuser.php. The manipulation of the argument SessionId leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243716. NOTE: We tried to contact the vendor early about the disclosure but the official mail address was not working properly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 17:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5827 | Shanghai CTI Navigation CTI Monitoring and Early Warning System UserEdit.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5827</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shanghai CTI Navigation CTI Monitoring and Early Warning System 2.2. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /Web/SysManage/UserEdit.aspx. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-243717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 17:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46604 | Apache ActiveMQ, Apache ActiveMQ Legacy OpenWire Module: Unbounded deserialization causes ActiveMQ to be vulnerable to a remote code execution (RCE) attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46604</link><description>Apache ActiveMQ is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution.The vulnerability may allow a remote attacker with network access to a broker to run arbitrary shell commands by manipulating serialized class types in the OpenWire protocol to cause the broker to instantiate any class on the classpath. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 5.15.16, 5.16.7, 5.17.6, or 5.18.3, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 15:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46393 | gougucms v4.08.18 was discovered to contain a password reset poisoning vulnerability which allows attackers to arbitrarily reset users' pass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46393</link><description>gougucms v4.08.18 was discovered to contain a password reset poisoning vulnerability which allows attackers to arbitrarily reset users' passwords via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46394 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /home/user/edit_submit of gougucms v4.08.18 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46394</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /home/user/edit_submit of gougucms v4.08.18 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the headimgurl parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5443 | User Enumeration in EDM Informatic&amp;#x27;s E-Invoice Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5443</link><description>Improper Protection for Outbound Error Messages and Alert Signals vulnerability in EDM Informatics E-invoice allows Account Footprinting.This issue affects E-invoice: before 2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5807 | SQLi in TRtek Software&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5807</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TRtek Software Education Portal allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Education Portal: before 3.2023.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44376 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44376</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'add2' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44377 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44377</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'add3' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5570 | User Enumeration in Inohom&amp;#x27;s Home Manager Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5570</link><description>Improper Protection for Outbound Error Messages and Alert Signals vulnerability in Inohom Home Manager Gateway allows Account Footprinting.This issue affects Home Manager Gateway: before v.1.27.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5705 | The VK Filter Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vk_filter_search' shortcode in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5705</link><description>The VK Filter Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vk_filter_search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5820 | The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5820</link><description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the addedit functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5821 | The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing nonce ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5821</link><description>The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the deleteselected function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete sliders in bulk via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5774 | The Animated Counters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5774</link><description>The Animated Counters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5817 | The Neon text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's neontext_box shortcode in all versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5817</link><description>The Neon text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's neontext_box shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes (color). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46199 | WordPress Triberr Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46199</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Triberr plugin &lt;= 4.1.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44220 | SonicWall NetExtender Windows (32-bit and 64-bit) client 10.2.336 and earlier versions have a DLL Search Order Hijacking vulnerability in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44220</link><description>SonicWall NetExtender Windows (32-bit and 64-bit) client 10.2.336 and earlier versions have a DLL Search Order Hijacking vulnerability in the start-up DLL component. Successful exploitation via a local attacker could result in command execution in the target system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46192 | WordPress Internal Link Building Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46192</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Internet Marketing Ninjas Internal Link Building plugin &lt;= 1.2.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46194 | WordPress Archivist – Custom Archive Templates Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46194</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Eric Teubert Archivist – Custom Archive Templates plugin &lt;= 1.7.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46093 | WordPress Webmaster Tools Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46093</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LionScripts.Com Webmaster Tools plugin &lt;= 2.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46153 | WordPress User Feedback Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46153</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in UserFeedback Team User Feedback plugin &lt;= 1.0.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44219 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability in SonicWall Directory Services Connector Windows MSI client 4.1.21 and earlier versions allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44219</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability in SonicWall Directory Services Connector Windows MSI client 4.1.21 and earlier versions allows a local low-privileged user to gain system privileges through running the recovery feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46091 | WordPress Category SEO Meta Tags Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46091</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bala Krishna, Sergey Yakovlev Category SEO Meta Tags plugin &lt;= 2.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34059 | open-vm-tools contains a file descriptor hijack vulnerability in the vmware-user-suid-wrapper. A malicious actor with non-root privileges ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34059</link><description>open-vm-tools contains a file descriptor hijack vulnerability in the vmware-user-suid-wrapper. A malicious actor with non-root privileges may be able to hijack the 
/dev/uinput file descriptor allowing them to simulate user inputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34057 | VMware Tools contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with local user access to a guest virtual machine may el...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34057</link><description>VMware Tools contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with local user access to a guest virtual machine may elevate privileges within the virtual machine.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34058 | VMware Tools contains a SAML token signature bypass vulnerability. A malicious actor that has been granted  Guest Operation Privileges https...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34058</link><description>VMware Tools contains a SAML token signature bypass vulnerability. A malicious actor that has been granted  Guest Operation Privileges https://docs.vmware.com/en/VMware-vSphere/8.0/vsphere-security/GUID-6A952214-0E5E-4CCF-9D2A-90948FF643EC.html  in a target virtual machine may be able to elevate their privileges if that target virtual machine has been assigned a more privileged  Guest Alias https://vdc-download.vmware.com/vmwb-repository/dcr-public/d1902b0e-d479-46bf-8ac9-cee0e31e8ec0/07ce8dbd-db48-4261-9b8f-c6d3ad8ba472/vim.vm.guest.AliasManager.html .</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46815 | An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. An Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability has been identified in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46815</link><description>An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. An Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability has been identified in the Notes module. By using a crafted request, custom PHP code can be injected via the Notes module because of missing input validation. An attacker with regular user privileges can exploit this.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46816 | An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. A Server Site Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability has been id...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46816</link><description>An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. A Server Site Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability has been identified in the GecControl action. By using a crafted request, custom PHP code can be injected via the GetControl action because of missing input validation. An attacker with regular user privileges can exploit this.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46818 | An issue was discovered in ISPConfig before 3.2.11p1. PHP code injection can be achieved in the language file editor by an admin if admin_al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46818</link><description>An issue was discovered in ISPConfig before 3.2.11p1. PHP code injection can be achieved in the language file editor by an admin if admin_allow_langedit is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5051 | The CallRail Phone Call Tracking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'callrail_form' shortcode in vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5051</link><description>The CallRail Phone Call Tracking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'callrail_form' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 0.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'form_id' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46503 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the reader manag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46503</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the reader management and book input modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46504 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46504</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via the library name function in the general settings component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45498 | VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45498</link><description>VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45499 | VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45499</link><description>VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46813 | An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel before 6.5.9, exploitable by local users with userspace access to MMIO registers. Incorrect acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46813</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel before 6.5.9, exploitable by local users with userspace access to MMIO registers. Incorrect access checking in the #VC handler and instruction emulation of the SEV-ES emulation of MMIO accesses could lead to arbitrary write access to kernel memory (and thus privilege escalation). This depends on a race condition through which userspace can replace an instruction before the #VC handler reads it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44375 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44375</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'add1' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44162 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44162</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'contact' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43738 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43738</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'email' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5814 | SourceCodester Task Reminder System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5814</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Reminder System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_reminder. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-243645 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5812 | flusity CMS upload.php handleFileUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5812</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in flusity CMS and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function handleFileUpload of the file core/tools/upload.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243643.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5813 | SourceCodester Task Reminder System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5813</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Reminder System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_reminder. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243644.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46376 | Zentao Biz version 8.7 and before is vulnerable to Information Disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46376</link><description>Zentao Biz version 8.7 and before is vulnerable to Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46375 | ZenTao Biz version 4.1.3 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46375</link><description>ZenTao Biz version 4.1.3 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5810 | flusity CMS posts.php loadPostAddForm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5810</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in flusity CMS. This issue affects the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_post_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-243641 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5811 | flusity CMS posts.php loadPostAddForm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5811</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in flusity CMS. Affected is the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument menu_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-243642 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46505 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in FanCMS v.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the content1 parameter in the demo.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46505</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in FanCMS v.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the content1 parameter in the demo.php file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>