<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-64435 | KubeVirt VMI Denial-of-Service (DoS) Using Pod Impersonation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64435</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Prior to 1.7.0-beta.0, a logic flaw in the virt-controller allows an attacker to disrupt the control over a running VMI by creating a pod with the same labels as the legitimate virt-launcher pod associated with the VMI. This can mislead the virt-controller into associating the fake pod with the VMI, resulting in incorrect status updates and potentially causing a DoS (Denial-of-Service). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.7.0-beta.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64436 | KubeVirt Excessive Role Permissions Could Enable Unauthorized VMI Migrations Between Nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64436</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. In 1.5.0 and earlier, the permissions granted to the virt-handler service account, such as the ability to update VMI and patch nodes, could be abused to force a VMI migration to an attacker-controlled node. This vulnerability could otherwise allow an attacker to mark all nodes as unschedulable, potentially forcing the migration or creation of privileged pods onto a compromised node.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64434 | KubeVirt Improper TLS Certificate Management Handling Allows API Identity Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64434</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Prior to 1.5.3 and 1.6.1, due to the peer verification logic in virt-handler (via verifyPeerCert), an attacker who compromises a virt-handler instance, could exploit these shared credentials to impersonate virt-api and execute privileged operations against other virt-handler instances potentially compromising the integrity and availability of the VM managed by it. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.3 and 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37736 | Elastic Cloud Enterprise Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37736</link><description>Improper Authorization in Elastic Cloud Enterprise can lead to Privilege Escalation where the built-in readonly user can call APIs that should not be allowed. The list of APIs that are affected by this issue is:





post:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts
delete:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}
patch:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}
post:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}/keys
delete:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}/keys/{api_key_id}
patch:/user
post:/users
post:/users/auth/keys
delete:/users/auth/keys
delete:/users/auth/keys/_all
delete:/users/auth/keys/{api_key_id}
delete:/users/{user_id}/auth/keys
delete:/users/{user_id}/auth/keys/{api_key_id}
delete:/users/{user_name}
patch:/users/{user_name}</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36870 | Ruijie Gateway EG &amp;amp; NBR Models v11.1(6)B9P1 - 11.9(4)B12P1 RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36870</link><description>Various Ruijie Gateway EG and NBR models firmware versions 11.1(6)B9P1 &lt; 11.9(4)B12P1 contain a code execution vulnerability in the EWEB management system that can be abused via front-end functionality. Attackers can exploit front-end code when features such as guest authentication, local server authentication, or screen mirroring are enabled to gain access or execute commands on affected devices. Exploitation evidence was first observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-06-07 UTC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12418 | Potential Denial of Service in Supported Versions of Revenera InstallShield</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12418</link><description>Potential Denial of Service issue in all supported versions of Revenera InstallShield version 2025 R1, 2024 R2, 2023 R2, and prior. When e.g., a local administrator performs an uninstall, a symlink may get followed on removal of a user writeable configuration directory and induce a Denial of Service as a result. The issue is resolved through the hotfixes InstallShield2025R1-CVE-2025-12418-SecurityPatch, InstallShield2024R2-CVE-2025-12418-SecurityPatch, and InstallShield2023R2-CVE-2025-12418-SecurityPatch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60574 | A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been identified in tQuadra CMS 4.2.1117. The issue exists in the "/styles/" path, which fails...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60574</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been identified in tQuadra CMS 4.2.1117. The issue exists in the "/styles/" path, which fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input. An attacker can exploit this by sending a crafted GET request to retrieve arbitrary files from the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63420 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CrushFTP 11.3.7_50 Admin Panel (Reports / 'Who Created Folder') allows authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63420</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CrushFTP 11.3.7_50 Admin Panel (Reports / 'Who Created Folder') allows authenticated attackers with permissions to create folders to inject malicious HTML/JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12863 | Libxml2: namespace use-after-free in xmlsettreedoc() function of libxml2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12863</link><description>A flaw was found in the xmlSetTreeDoc() function of the libxml2 XML parsing library. This function is responsible for updating document pointers when XML nodes are moved between documents. Due to improper handling of namespace references, a namespace pointer may remain linked to a freed memory region when the original document is destroyed. As a result, subsequent operations that access the namespace can lead to a use-after-free condition, causing an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12875 | mruby array.c ary_fill_exec out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12875</link><description>A weakness has been identified in mruby 3.4.0. This vulnerability affects the function ary_fill_exec of the file mrbgems/mruby-array-ext/src/array.c. Executing manipulation of the argument start/length can lead to out-of-bounds write. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This patch is called 93619f06dd378db6766666b30c08978311c7ec94. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63544 | TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /order_notes via the id parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63544</link><description>TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /order_notes via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64442 | HumHub is vulnerable to XSS through its Meta Search component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64442</link><description>HumHub is an Open Source Enterprise Social Network. Versions below 1.17.4 have a XSS vulnerability in the Meta-Search feature which allows malicious input to be executed in search previews. This issue is fixed in version 1.17.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64481 | Open redirect endpoint in Datasette</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64481</link><description>Datasette is an open source multi-tool for exploring and publishing data. In versions 0.65.1 and below and 1.0a0 through 1.0a19, deployed instances of Datasette include an open redirect vulnerability. Hits to the path //example.com/foo/bar/ (the trailing slash is required) will redirect the user to https://example.com/foo/bar. This problem has been patched in both Datasette 0.65.2 and 1.0a21. To workaround this issue, if Datasette is running behind a proxy, that proxy could be configured to replace // with / in incoming request URLs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12896 | Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12896</link><description>Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authorized access to a locked storage device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12902 | Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12902</link><description>Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authorized access to a locked Storage Device or create a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63543 | TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /search_results endpoint via the q parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63543</link><description>TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /search_results endpoint via the q parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64439 | LangGraph Checkpoint affected by RCE in &amp;quot;json&amp;quot; mode of JsonPlusSerializer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64439</link><description>LangGraph SQLite Checkpoint is an implementation of LangGraph CheckpointSaver that uses SQLite DB (both sync and async, via aiosqlite). In versions 2.1.2 and below, the JsonPlusSerializer (used as the default serialization protocol for all checkpointing) contains a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability when deserializing payloads saved in the "json" serialization mode. By default, the serializer attempts to use "msgpack" for serialization. However, prior to version 3.0 of the checkpointer library, if illegal Unicode surrogate values caused serialization to fail, it would fall back to using the "json" mode. This issue is fixed in version 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63639 | The chat feature in the application Sourcecodester FAQ Bot with AI Assistant v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) due to imprope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63639</link><description>The chat feature in the application Sourcecodester FAQ Bot with AI Assistant v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) due to improper handling of user-supplied input. An attacker can inject malicious HTML or JavaScript into chat messages, which executes in the browser of any user viewing the conversation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63640 | Sourcecodester Medicine Reminder App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Medicine Name" and "Notes (Optional)" fields w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63640</link><description>Sourcecodester Medicine Reminder App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Medicine Name" and "Notes (Optional)" fields when creating an "Upcoming Reminder", allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary potentially malicious HTML/JavaScript code that executes in the victim's browser upon clicking the "Save Reminder" button.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63638 | Sourcecodester AI-Powered To-Do List App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Task Title" and "Description (Optional)" f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63638</link><description>Sourcecodester AI-Powered To-Do List App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Task Title" and "Description (Optional)" fields when creating a Task, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary potentially malicious HTML/JavaScript code that executes in the victim's browser upon clicking the "Add Task" button.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10230 | Samba: command injection in wins server hook script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10230</link><description>A flaw was found in Samba, in the front-end WINS hook handling: NetBIOS names from registration packets are passed to a shell without proper validation or escaping. Unsanitized NetBIOS name data from WINS registration packets are inserted into a shell command and executed by the Samba Active Directory Domain Controller’s wins hook, allowing an unauthenticated network attacker to achieve remote command execution as the Samba process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36006 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36006</link><description>IBM Db2 10.5.0 through 10.5.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial due to the improper release of resources after use.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36008 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36008</link><description>IBM Db2 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to improper allocation of resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7700 | Ffmpeg: null pointer dereference in ffmpeg als decoder (libavcodec/alsdec.c)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7700</link><description>A flaw was found in FFmpeg’s ALS audio decoder, where it does not properly check for memory allocation failures. This can cause the application to crash when processing certain malformed audio files. While it does not lead to data theft or system control, it can be used to disrupt services and cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36131 | IBM Db2 information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36131</link><description>IBM Db2 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) clpplus command exposes user credentials to the terminal which could be obtained by a third party with physical access to the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12890 | Bluetooth: peripheral: Invalid handling of malformed connection request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12890</link><description>Improper handling of  malformed Connection Request with the interval set to be 1 (which supposed to be illegal) and the chM 0x7CFFFFFFFF triggers a crash. The peripheral will not be connectable after it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36136 | IBM denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36136</link><description>IBM Db2 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to the database monitor script incorrectly detecting that the instance is still starting under specific conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36185 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36185</link><description>IBM Db2 12.1.0 through 12.1.2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to improper neutralization of special elements in data query logic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2534 | IBM Db2  denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2534</link><description>IBM Db2 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33012 | IBM Db2 improper account lockout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33012</link><description>IBM Db2 10.5.0 through 10.5.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux could allow an authenticated user to regain access after account lockout due to password use after expiration date.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36186 | IBM Db2 privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36186</link><description>IBM Db2 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) under specific configurations could allow a local user to execute malicious code that escalate their privileges to root due to execution of unnecessary privileges operated at a higher than minimum level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64432 | KubeVirt Affected by an Authentication Bypass in Kubernetes Aggregation Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64432</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Versions 1.5.3 and below, and 1.6.0 contained a flawed implementation of the Kubernetes aggregation layer's authentication flow which could enable bypass of RBAC controls. It was discovered that the virt-api component fails to correctly authenticate the client when receiving API requests over mTLS. In particular, it fails to validate the CN (Common Name) field in the received client TLS certificates against the set of allowed values defined in the extension-apiserver-authentication configmap. Failre to validate certain fields in the client TLS certificate may allow an attacker to bypass existing RBAC controls by directly communicating with the aggregated API server, impersonating the Kubernetes API server and its aggregator component. This issue is fixed in versions 1.5.3 and 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47118 | IBM Db2 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47118</link><description>IBM Db2 10.5.0 through 10.5.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36135 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway are Vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36135</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_1, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_1, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61261 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CKeditor v46.1.0 &amp; Angular v18.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61261</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CKeditor v46.1.0 &amp; Angular v18.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63717 | The change password functionality at /pet_grooming/admin/change_pass.php in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 is vulnerabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63717</link><description>The change password functionality at /pet_grooming/admin/change_pass.php in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks. The application does not implement adequate anti-CSRF tokens or same-site cookie restrictions, allowing attackers to trick authenticated users into unknowingly changing their passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64431 | IDOR Vulnerabilities in ZITADEL&amp;#x27;s Organization API allows Cross-Tenant Data Tempering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64431</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management platform. Versions 4.0.0-rc.1 through 4.6.2 are vulnerable to secure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) attacks through its V2Beta API, allowing authenticated users with specific administrator roles within one organization to access and modify data belonging to other organizations. Note that this vulnerability is limited to organization-level data (name, domains, metadata). No other related data (such as users, projects, applications, etc.) is affected. This issue is fixed in version 4.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12829 | An uninitialized stack read issue exists in Amazon Ion-C versions &lt;v1.1.4 that may allow a threat actor to craft data and serialize it to Io...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12829</link><description>An uninitialized stack read issue exists in Amazon Ion-C versions &lt;v1.1.4 that may allow a threat actor to craft data and serialize it to Ion text in such a way that sensitive data in memory could be exposed through UTF-8 escape sequences. To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version v1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12873 | Campcodes School File Management update_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12873</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes School File Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update_user.php. Performing manipulation of the argument user_id results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63716 | The SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks that allow unauthorized state-changing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63716</link><description>The SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks that allow unauthorized state-changing operations. The application lacks CSRF protection mechanisms such as anti-CSRF tokens or same-origin verification for critical endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9458 | PRT File Parsing Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9458</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63713 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester "MatchMaster" 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63713</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester "MatchMaster" 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via crafted input in the custom test creation feature. The vulnerability exists because the application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in test titles and matching pair items before rendering them in the DOM during test execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63718 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the SourceCodester PQMS (Patient Queue Management System) 1.0 in the api_patient_schedule.php endpoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63718</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the SourceCodester PQMS (Patient Queue Management System) 1.0 in the api_patient_schedule.php endpoint. The appointmentID parameter is not properly sanitized, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64430 | Parse Server Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in File Upload via URI Format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64430</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. In versions 4.2.0 through 7.5.3, and 8.0.0 through 8.3.1-alpha.1, there is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the file upload functionality when trying to upload a Parse.File with uri parameter, allowing execution of an arbitrary URI. The vulnerability stems from a file upload feature in which Parse Server retrieves the file data from a URI that is provided in the request. A request to the provided URI is executed, but the response is not stored in Parse Server's file storage as the server crashes upon receiving the response. This issue is fixed in versions 7.5.4 and 8.4.0-alpha.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57697 | AstrBot Project v3.5.22 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in function _encode_image_bs64. Since the _encode_image_bs64 function defin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57697</link><description>AstrBot Project v3.5.22 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in function _encode_image_bs64. Since the _encode_image_bs64 function defined in entities.py opens the image specified by the user in the request body and returns the image content as a base64-encoded string without checking the legitimacy of the image path, attackers can construct a series of malicious URLs to read any specified file, resulting in sensitive data leakage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63714 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester User Account Generator 1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63714</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester User Account Generator 1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the user's browser session via crafted input in the Username Prefix field. The vulnerability exists due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input when rendering generated account data to the DOM, allowing persistent injection of malicious HTML elements that execute when clicked by users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64347 | Apollo Router Improperly Enforces Renamed Access Control Directives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64347</link><description>Apollo Router Core is a configurable Rust graph router written to run a federated supergraph using Apollo Federation 2. Versions 1.61.12-rc.0 and below and 2.8.1-rc.0 allow unauthorized access to protected data through schema elements with access control directives (@authenticated, @requiresScopes, and @policy) that were renamed via @link imports. Router did not enforce renamed access control directives on schema elements (e.g. fields and types), allowing queries to bypass those element-level access controls. This issue is fixed in versions 1.61.12 and 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57698 | AstrBot Project v3.5.22 contains a directory traversal vulnerability. The handler function install_plugin_upload of the interface '/plugin/i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57698</link><description>AstrBot Project v3.5.22 contains a directory traversal vulnerability. The handler function install_plugin_upload of the interface '/plugin/install-upload' parses the filename from the request body provided by the user, and directly uses the filename to assign to file_path without checking the validity of the filename. The variable file_path is then passed as a parameter to the function `file.save`, so that the file in the request body can be saved to any location in the file system through directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12862 | projectworlds Online Notes Sharing Platform userprofile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12862</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in projectworlds Online Notes Sharing Platform 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/userprofile.php. Such manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3222 | Smallworld SWMFS Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3222</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in GE Vernova Smallworld on Windows, Linux allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Smallworld: 5.3.3 and prior versions for Linux, and 5.3.4. and prior versions for Windows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63785 | A DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the text editor feature of the Onlook web application 0.2.32. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63785</link><description>A DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the text editor feature of the Onlook web application 0.2.32. This vulnerability occurs because user-supplied input is not properly sanitized before being directly injected into the DOM via innerHTML when editing a text element. An attacker can exploit this to inject malicious HTML and script code, which is then executed within the context of the preview iframe, allowing for the execution of arbitrary scripts in the user's session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7719 | Smallworld SWMFS Arbitrary File Ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7719</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in GE Vernova Smallworld on Windows, Linux allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Smallworld: 5.3.5. and previous versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63784 | An Open Redirect vulnerability exists in the OAuth callback handler in file onlook/apps/web/client/src/app/auth/callback/route.ts in Onlook ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63784</link><description>An Open Redirect vulnerability exists in the OAuth callback handler in file onlook/apps/web/client/src/app/auth/callback/route.ts in Onlook web application 0.2.32. The vulnerability occurs because the application trusts the X-Forwarded-Host header value without proper validation when constructing a redirect URL. A remote attacker can send a manipulated X-Forwarded-Host header to redirect an authenticated user to an arbitrary external website under their control, which can be exploited for phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12861 | DedeBIZ spec_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12861</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/spec_add.php. This manipulation of the argument flags[] causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63783 | A Broken Object Level Authorization (BOLA) vulnerability was discovered in the tRPC project mutation APIs (update, delete, add/remove tag) o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63783</link><description>A Broken Object Level Authorization (BOLA) vulnerability was discovered in the tRPC project mutation APIs (update, delete, add/remove tag) of the Onlook web application 0.2.32. The vulnerability exists because the API fails to verify the ownership or membership of the currently authenticated user for the requested project ID. An authenticated attacker can send a malicious request containing another user's project ID to unlawfully modify, delete, or manipulate tags on that project, which can severely compromise data integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63686 | There is an arbitrary file download vulnerability in GuoMinJim PersonManage thru commit 5a02b1ab208feacf3a34fc123c9381162afbaa95 (2020-11-23...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63686</link><description>There is an arbitrary file download vulnerability in GuoMinJim PersonManage thru commit 5a02b1ab208feacf3a34fc123c9381162afbaa95 (2020-11-23) in the document query function under the Download Center menu in the PersonManage system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63687 | An issue was discovered in rymcu forest thru commit f782e85 (2025-09-04) in function doBefore in file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/core/se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63687</link><description>An issue was discovered in rymcu forest thru commit f782e85 (2025-09-04) in function doBefore in file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/core/service/security/AuthorshipAspect.java, allowing authorized attackers to delete arbitrary users posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63689 | Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilitites in ycf1998 money-pos system before commit 11f276bd20a41f089298d804e43cb1c39d041e59 (2025-09-14) allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63689</link><description>Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilitites in ycf1998 money-pos system before commit 11f276bd20a41f089298d804e43cb1c39d041e59 (2025-09-14) allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the orderby parameter</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47207 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47207</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several product versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52425 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52425</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. A remote attacker can exploit the vulnerability to execute unauthorized code or commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuMagie 2.7.0 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52865 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52865</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53408 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53408</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63690 | In pig-mesh Pig versions 3.8.2 and below, when setting up scheduled tasks in the Quartz management function under the system management modu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63690</link><description>In pig-mesh Pig versions 3.8.2 and below, when setting up scheduled tasks in the Quartz management function under the system management module, it is possible to execute any Java class with a parameterless constructor and its methods with parameter type String through reflection. At this time, the eval method in Tomcat's built-in class jakarta.el.ELProcessor can be used to execute commands, leading to a remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63691 | In pig-mesh In Pig version 3.8.2 and below, within the Token Management function under the System Management module, the token query interfa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63691</link><description>In pig-mesh In Pig version 3.8.2 and below, within the Token Management function under the System Management module, the token query interface (/api/admin/sys-token/page) has an improper permission verification issue, which leads to information leakage. This interface can be called by any user who has completed login authentication, and it returns the plaintext authentication Tokens of all users currently logged in to the system. As a result, ordinary users can obtain the administrator's authentication Token through this interface, thereby forging an administrator account, gaining the system's management permissions, and taking over the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53409 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53409</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53410 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53410</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53411 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53411</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53412 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53412</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53413 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53413</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54167 | Notification Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54167</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Notification Center. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Notification Center 2.1.0.3443 and later
Notification Center 1.9.2.3163 and later
Notification Center 3.0.0.3466 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54168 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54168</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuLog Center. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuLog Center 1.8.2.923 ( 2025/08/27 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57706 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57706</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57712 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57712</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 5.0.0.3 ( 2025/08/28 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58463 | Download Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58463</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Download Station. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Download Station 5.10.0.305 ( 2025/09/16 ) and later
Download Station 5.10.0.304 ( 2025/09/08 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58464 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58464</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If a remote attacker, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.7.3 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58465 | Download Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58465</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Download Station. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Download Station 5.10.0.305 ( 2025/09/16 ) and later
Download Station 5.10.0.304 ( 2025/09/08 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58469 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58469</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuLog Center. The remote attackers can then exploit the vulnerability to gain privileges or hijack user identities.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuLog Center 1.8.2.927 ( 2025/09/17 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12859 | DedeBIZ templets_one_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12859</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/templets_one_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12860 | DedeBIZ freelist_main.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12860</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/freelist_main.php. The manipulation of the argument orderby results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12857 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site roombook.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12857</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/roombook.php. Such manipulation of the argument rid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34299 | Monsta FTP &amp;lt;= 2.11 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34299</link><description>Monsta FTP versions 2.11 and earlier contain a vulnerability that allows unauthenticated arbitrary file uploads. This flaw enables attackers to execute arbitrary code by uploading a specially crafted file from a malicious (S)FTP server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12855 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site newsletterdel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12855</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/newsletterdel.php. The manipulation of the argument eid results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12856 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site reservation.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12856</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/reservation.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10968 | SQLi in GG Soft&amp;#x27;s PaperWork</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10968</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection'), CWE - 564 - SQL Injection: Hibernate vulnerability in GG Soft Software Services Inc. PaperWork allows Blind SQL Injection, SQL Injection.This issue affects PaperWork: from 6.1.0.9390 before 6.1.0.9398.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12853 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php delete_house sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12853</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects the function delete_house of the file /admin_class.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12854 | newbee-mall-plus seckillExecution executeSeckill authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12854</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in newbee-mall-plus up to 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects the function executeSeckill of the file /seckillExecution/. The manipulation of the argument userid leads to authorization bypass. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10870 | SQL injection in DIAL&amp;#x27;s CentrosNet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10870</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in DIAL's CentrosNet v2.64. Allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases by sending POST and GET requests with the 'ultralogin' parameter in '/centrosnet/ultralogin.php'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 09:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46413 | Use of password hash with insufficient computational effort issue exists in BUFFALO Wi-Fi router 'WSR-1800AX4 series'. When WPS is enabled, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46413</link><description>Use of password hash with insufficient computational effort issue exists in BUFFALO Wi-Fi router 'WSR-1800AX4 series'. When WPS is enabled, PIN code and/or Wi-Fi password may be obtained by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 09:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10966 | missing SFTP host verification with wolfSSH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10966</link><description>curl's code for managing SSH connections when SFTP was done using the wolfSSH
powered backend was flawed and missed host verification mechanisms.

This prevents curl from detecting MITM attackers and more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12520 | WP Airbnb Review Slider &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12520</link><description>The WP Airbnb Review Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.2 due to insufficient URL validation that allows users to pull in a malicious HTML file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12527 | Page &amp;amp; Post Notes &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Note Update/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12527</link><description>The Page &amp; Post Notes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of notes due to a missing capability check on the 'yydev_notes_save_dashboard_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify notes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64346 | archives: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64346</link><description>archives is a Go library for extracting archives (tar, zip, etc.). Version 1.0.0 does not prevent a malicious user to feed a specially crafted archive to the library causing RCE, modification of files or other malignancies in the context of whatever the user is running this library as, through the program that imports it. Severity depends on user permissions, environment and how arbitrary archives are passed. This issue is fixed in version 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64343 | (conda) Constructor: Excessive permissions during and after installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64343</link><description>(conda) Constructor is a tool that enables users to create installers for conda package collections. In versions 3.12.2 and below, the  installation directory inherits permissions from its parent directory. Outside of restricted directories, the permissions are very permissive and often allow write access by authenticated users. Any logged in user can make modifications during the installation for both single-user and all-user installations. This constitutes a local attack vector if the installation is in a directory local users have access to. For single-user installations in a shared directory, these permissions persist after the installation. This issue is fixed in version 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64339 | ClipBucket v5: Stored XSS Vulnerability in Manage Playlists</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64339</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. In versions 5.5.2-#146 and below, the Manage Playlists feature is vulnerable to stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS),specifically in the Playlist Name field. An authenticated low-privileged user can create a playlist with a malicious name containing HTML/JavaScript code, which is rendered unescaped on playlist detail and listing pages. This results in arbitrary JavaScript execution in every viewer’s browser, including administrators. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2-#147.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12352 | Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 2.9.20 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;copy_post_image&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12352</link><description>The Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the copy_post_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.20. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This only impacts sites that have allow_url_fopen set to `On`, the post creation form enabled along with a file upload field for the post</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4519 | IDonate 2.1.5 - 2.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via idonate_donor_password Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4519</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the idonate_donor_password() function in versions 2.1.5 to 2.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to initiate a password reset for any user (including administrators) and elevate their privileges for full site takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4522 | IDonate 2.0.0 - 2.1.9 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary User Deletion via admin_post_donor_delete Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4522</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference via the admin_post_donor_delete() function in versions 2.0.0 to 2.1.9. By supplying an arbitrary user_id parameter value to the wp_delete_user() function, authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above could delete arbitrary user accounts, including those of administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64336 | ClipBucket v5&amp;#x27;s Manage Photo Feature is Vulnerable to Stored XSS Attack via Photo Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64336</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. In versions 5.5.2-#146 and below, the Manage Photos feature is vulnerable to stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS). An authenticated regular user can upload a photo with a malicious Photo Title containing HTML/JavaScript code. While the payload does not execute in the user-facing photo gallery or detail pages, it is rendered unsafely in the Admin → Manage Photos section, resulting in JavaScript execution in the administrator’s browser. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2-#147.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64329 | containerd CRI server: Host memory exhaustion through Attach goroutine leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64329</link><description>containerd is an open-source container runtime. Versions 1.7.28 and below, 2.0.0-beta.0 through 2.0.6, 2.1.0-beta.0 through 2.1.4, and 2.2.0-beta.0 through 2.2.0-rc.1 contain a bug in the CRI Attach implementation where a user can exhaust memory on the host due to goroutine leaks. This issue is fixed in versions 1.7.29, 2.0.7, 2.1.5 and 2.2.0. To workaround this vulnerability, users can set up an admission controller to control accesses to pods/attach resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5483 | LC Wizard 1.2.10 - 1.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5483</link><description>The LC Wizard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check in the ghl-wizard/inc/wp_user.php file in versions 1.2.10 to 1.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new user accounts with the administrator role when the PRO functionality is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64328 | FreePBX Administration GUI is Vulnerable to Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64328</link><description>FreePBX Endpoint Manager is a module for managing telephony endpoints in FreePBX systems. In versions 17.0.2.36 and above before 17.0.3, the filestore module within the Administrative interface is vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection by an authenticated known user via the testconnection -&gt; check_ssh_connect() function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to obtain remote access to the system as an asterisk user. This issue is fixed in version 17.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64180 | Manager-io/Manager: Complete Bypass of SSRF Protection via Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64180</link><description>Manager-io/Manager is accounting software. In Manager Desktop and Server versions 25.11.1.3085 and below, a critical vulnerability permits unauthorized access to internal network resources. The flaw lies in the fundamental design of the DNS validation mechanism. A Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) condition that allows attackers to bypass network isolation and access internal services, cloud metadata endpoints, and protected network segments. The Desktop edition requires no authentication; the Server edition requires only standard authentication. This issue is fixed in version 25.11.1.3086.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64184 | Dosage vulnerable to Directory Traversal through crafted HTTP responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64184</link><description>Dosage is a comic strip downloader and archiver. When downloading comic images in versions 3.1 and below, Dosage constructs target file names from different aspects of the remote comic (page URL, image URL, page content, etc.). While the basename is properly stripped of directory-traversing characters, the file extension is taken from the HTTP Content-Type header. This allows a remote attacker (or a Man-in-the-Middle, if the comic is served over HTTP) to write arbitrary files outside the target directory (if additional conditions are met). This issue is fixed in version 3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64187 | OctoPrint is vulnerable to XSS through Action Command Notifications and Prompts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64187</link><description>OctoPrint provides a web interface for controlling consumer 3D printers. Versions 1.11.3 and below are affected by a vulnerability that allows injection of arbitrary HTML and JavaScript into Action Command notifications and prompts popups generated by the printer. An attacker who successfully convinces a victim to print a specially crafted file could exploit this issue to disrupt ongoing prints, extract information (including sensitive configuration settings, if the targeted user has the necessary permissions for that), or perform other actions on behalf of the targeted user within the OctoPrint instance. This issue is fixed in version 1.11.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64323 | kgateway is missing xDS authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64323</link><description>kgateway is a Cloud-Native API and AI Gateway. Versions 2.0.4 and below and 2.1.0-agw-cel-rbac through 2.1.0-rc.2 lack authentication, allowing any client with unrestricted network access to the xDS port to retrieve potentially sensitive configuration data including certificate data, backend service information, routing rules, and cluster metadata. This issue is solved in versions 2.0.5 and 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11546 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver.9.5 to Ver.10.7, from Ver.10.8.21 to Ver.10.8.36, from Ver.10.9.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11546</link><description>Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver.9.5 to Ver.10.7, from Ver.10.8.21 to Ver.10.8.36, from Ver.10.9.11 to Ver.10.9.24, from Ver.10.10.21 to Ver.10.10.31, Ver.10.11.6 and UNIVERGE IX-R/IX-V Ver1.3.16, Ver1.3.21 allows an attacker sends specially crafted network packets to the product, arbitrary OS commands may be executed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48985 | A vulnerability in Vercel’s AI SDK has been fixed in versions 5.0.52, 5.1.0-beta.9, and 6.0.0-beta. This issue may have allowed users to byp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48985</link><description>A vulnerability in Vercel’s AI SDK has been fixed in versions 5.0.52, 5.1.0-beta.9, and 6.0.0-beta. This issue may have allowed users to bypass filetype whitelists when uploading files. All users are encouraged to upgrade.

More details: https://vercel.com/changelog/cve-2025-48985-input-validation-bypass-on-ai-sdk</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52662 | A vulnerability in Nuxt DevTools has been fixed in version **2.6.4***. This issue may have allowed Nuxt auth token extraction via XSS under ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52662</link><description>A vulnerability in Nuxt DevTools has been fixed in version **2.6.4***. This issue may have allowed Nuxt auth token extraction via XSS under certain configurations. All users are encouraged to upgrade.

More details: https://vercel.com/changelog/cve-2025-52662-xss-on-nuxt-devtools</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12789 | Rhsso: open redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12789</link><description>A flaw was found in Red Hat Single Sign-On. This issue is an Open Redirect vulnerability that occurs during the logout process. The redirect_uri parameter associated with the openid-connect logout protocol does not properly validate the provided URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 23:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11458 | Heap buffer overflow in Sync in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.65 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11458</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Sync in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.65 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11460 | Use after free in Storage in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.65 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted video fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11460</link><description>Use after free in Storage in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.65 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted video file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11756 | Use after free in Safe Browsing in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.107 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11756</link><description>Use after free in Safe Browsing in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.107 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12036 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.122 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12036</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.122 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58423 | Advantech DeviceOn/iEdge Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58423</link><description>Due to insufficient sanitization, an attacker can upload a specially 
crafted configuration file to cause a denial-of-service condition, 
traverse directories, or read/write files, within the context of the 
local system account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59171 | Advantech DeviceOn/iEdge Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59171</link><description>Due to insufficient sanitization, an attacker can upload a specially 
crafted configuration file to traverse directories and achieve remote 
code execution with system-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62630 | Advantech DeviceOn/iEdge Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62630</link><description>Due to insufficient sanitization, an attacker can upload a specially 
crafted configuration file to traverse directories and achieve remote 
code execution with system-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64302 | Advantech DeviceOn/iEdge Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64302</link><description>Insufficient input sanitization in the dashboard label or path can allow
 an attacker to trigger a device error causing information disclosure or
 data manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12636 | Ubia Ubox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12636</link><description>The Ubia camera ecosystem fails to adequately secure API credentials, 
potentially enabling an attacker to connect to backend services. The 
attacker would then be able to gain unauthorized access to available 
cameras, enabling the viewing of live feeds or modification of settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11205 | Heap buffer overflow in WebGPU in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11205</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in WebGPU in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11206 | Heap buffer overflow in Video in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11206</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Video in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11207 | Side-channel information leakage in Storage in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/writ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11207</link><description>Side-channel information leakage in Storage in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11208 | Inappropriate implementation in Media in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11208</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Media in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11209 | Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11209</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11210 | Side-channel information leakage in Tab in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11210</link><description>Side-channel information leakage in Tab in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11211 | Out of bounds read in Media in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11211</link><description>Out of bounds read in Media in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11212 | Inappropriate implementation in Media in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11212</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Media in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform domain spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11213 | Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11213</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform domain spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11215 | Off by one error in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11215</link><description>Off by one error in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11216 | Inappropriate implementation in Storage in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11216</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Storage in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted video file. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11219 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11219</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 141.0.7390.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64179 | lakeFS: Unauthenticated access to API usage metrics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64179</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms object storage into a Git-like repositories. In versions 1.69.0 and below, missing authentication in the /api/v1/usage-report/summary endpoint allows anyone to retrieve aggregate API usage counts. While no sensitive data is disclosed, the endpoint may reveal information about service activity or uptime. This issue is fixed in version 1.71.0 . To workaround the vulnerability, use a load-balancer or application level firewall in order to block the request route /api/v1/usage-report/summary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12125 | 3scale-porta: readonly fields not validated server-side</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12125</link><description>A flaw was found in the 3scale developer portal. This issue can allow account creation or updates passed through hidden or read-only fields, the contents of which may be altered. This flaw allows an attacker to access or modify restricted information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64178 | Jellysweep uses uncontrolled data in image cache API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64178</link><description>Jellysweep is a cleanup tool for the Jellyfin media server. In versions 0.12.1 and below, /api/images/cache, used to download media posters from the server, accepted a URL parameter that was directly passed to the cache package, which downloaded the poster from this URL. This URL parameter can be used to make the Jellysweep server download arbitrary content. The API endpoint can only be used by authenticated users. This issue is fixed in version 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64177 | ThinkDashboard: Stored XSS in Dashboard via Malicious Bookmark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64177</link><description>ThinkDashboard is a self-hosted bookmark dashboard built with Go and vanilla JavaScript. In versions 0.6.7 and below, there is a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the dashboard, which can exploited when a user clicks on a malicious bookmark, made vulnerable by the lack of scheme filtering. This is fixed in version 0.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64176 | ThinkDashboard: Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability in the Backup Import Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64176</link><description>ThinkDashboard is a self-hosted bookmark dashboard built with Go and vanilla JavaScript. In versions 0.6.7 and below, an attacker can upload any file they wish to the /data directory of the web application via the backup import feature. When importing a backup, an attacker can first choose a .zip file to bypass the client-side file-type verification. This could lead to stored XSS, or be used for other nefarious purposes such as malware distribution. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12790 | Rubygem-mqtt: rubygem-mqtt hostname validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12790</link><description>A flaw was found in Rubygem MQTT. By default, the package used to not have hostname validation, resulting in possible Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64327 | ThinkDashboard: Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in /api/ping Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64327</link><description>ThinkDashboard is a self-hosted bookmark dashboard built with Go and vanilla JavaScript. Versions 0.6.7 and below contain a Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, in its `/api/ping?url= endpoint`. This allows an attacker to make arbitrary requests to internal or external hosts. This can include discovering ports open on the local machine, hosts on the local network, and ports open on the hosts on the internal network. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64326 | Weblate leaks the IP of project members inviting users to assume reviewer roles in Audit log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64326</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. In versions 5.14 and below,  Weblate leaks the IP address of the project member inviting the user to the project in the audit log. The audit log includes IP addresses from admin-triggered actions, which can be viewed by invited users. This issue is fixed in version 5.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33110 | IBM OpenPages Vulnerable to HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33110</link><description>IBM OpenPages 9.1, and 9.0 with Watson is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64173 | Apollo Router Core: Access Control Bypass on Polymorphic Types</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64173</link><description>Apollo Router Core is a configurable graph router written in Rust to run a federated supergraph using Apollo Federation 2. In versions 1.61.11 below, as well as 2.0.0-alpha.0 through 2.8.1-rc.0, a vulnerability allowed for unauthenticated queries to access data that required additional access controls. Router incorrectly handled access control directives on interface types/fields and their implementing object types/fields, applying them to interface types/fields while ignoring directives on their implementing object types/fields when all implementations had the same requirements. Apollo Router customers defining @authenticated, @requiresScopes, or @policy directives inconsistently on polymorphic types (i.e., object types that implement interface types) are impacted. This issue is fixed in versions 1.61.12 and 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64174 | OpenMage is vulnerable to XSS in Admin Notifications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64174</link><description>Magento-lts is a long-term support alternative to Magento Community Edition (CE). Versions 20.15.0 and below are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an admin with direct database access or the admin notification feed source to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable fields. Unescaped translation strings and URLs are printed into contexts inside app/code/core/Mage/Adminhtml/Block/Notification/Grid/Renderer/Actions.php. A malicious translation or polluted data can inject script. This issue is fixed in version 20.16.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52881 | runc: LSM labels can be bypassed with malicious config using dummy procfs files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52881</link><description>runc is a CLI tool for spawning and running containers according to the OCI specification. In versions 1.2.7, 1.3.2 and 1.4.0-rc.2, an attacker can trick runc into misdirecting writes to /proc to other procfs files through the use of a racing container with shared mounts (we have also verified this attack is possible to exploit using a standard Dockerfile with docker buildx build as that also permits triggering parallel execution of containers with custom shared mounts configured). This redirect could be through symbolic links in a tmpfs or theoretically other methods such as regular bind-mounts. While similar, the mitigation applied for the related CVE, CVE-2019-19921, was fairly limited and effectively only caused runc to verify that when LSM labels are written they are actually procfs files. This issue is fixed in versions 1.2.8, 1.3.3, and 1.4.0-rc.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12486 | Heimdall Data Database Proxy Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12486</link><description>Heimdall Data Database Proxy Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Heimdall Data Database Proxy. Minimal user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the database event logs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to interact with the application in the context of the target user. Was ZDI-CAN-24755.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12487 | oobabooga text-generation-webui trust_remote_code Reliance on Untrusted Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12487</link><description>oobabooga text-generation-webui trust_remote_code Reliance on Untrusted Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oobabooga text-generation-webui. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the trust_remote_code parameter provided to the join endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied argument before using it to load a model. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-26681.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12488 | oobabooga text-generation-webui trust_remote_code Reliance on Untrusted Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12488</link><description>oobabooga text-generation-webui trust_remote_code Reliance on Untrusted Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oobabooga text-generation-webui. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the trust_remote_code parameter provided to the load endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied argument before using it to load a model. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account.
. Was ZDI-CAN-26680.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12489 | evernote-mcp-server openBrowser Command Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12489</link><description>evernote-mcp-server openBrowser Command Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of evernote-mcp-server. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the openBrowser function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-27913.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12490 | Netgate pfSense CE Suricata Path Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12490</link><description>Netgate pfSense CE Suricata Path Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Netgate pfSense. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Suricata package. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create files in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-28085.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52565 | container escape due to /dev/console mount and related races</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52565</link><description>runc is a CLI tool for spawning and running containers according to the OCI specification. Versions 1.0.0-rc3 through 1.2.7, 1.3.0-rc.1 through 1.3.2, and 1.4.0-rc.1 through 1.4.0-rc.2, due to insufficient checks when bind-mounting `/dev/pts/$n` to `/dev/console` inside the container, an attacker can trick runc into bind-mounting paths which would normally be made read-only or be masked onto a path that the attacker can write to. This attack is very similar in concept and application to CVE-2025-31133, except that it attacks a similar vulnerability in a different target (namely, the bind-mount of `/dev/pts/$n` to `/dev/console` as configured for all containers that allocate a console). This happens after `pivot_root(2)`, so this cannot be used to write to host files directly -- however, as with CVE-2025-31133, this can load to denial of service of the host or a container breakout by providing the attacker with a writable copy of `/proc/sysrq-trigger` or `/proc/sys/kernel/core_pattern` (respectively). This issue is fixed in versions 1.2.8, 1.3.3 and 1.4.0-rc.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50589 | SuiteCRM &amp;lt; 7.12.6 SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;export&amp;#x27; Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50589</link><description>SuiteCRM versions prior to 7.12.6 contain a SQL injection vulnerability within the processing of the ‘uid’ parameter within the ‘export’ functionality. Successful exploitation allows remote unauthenticated attackers to ultimately execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50590 | SuiteCRM &amp;lt; 7.12.6 Type Confusion via &amp;#x27;deleteAttachment&amp;#x27; Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50590</link><description>SuiteCRM versions prior to 7.12.6 contain a type confusion vulnerability within the processing of the ‘module’ parameter within the ‘deleteAttachment’ functionality. Successful exploitation allows remote unauthenticated attackers to alter database objects including changing the email address of the administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50591 | Advantech iView &amp;lt; v5.7.04 Build 6425 ztp_config_id Parameter SQL Injection Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50591</link><description>Advantech iView versions prior to v5.7.04 build 6425 contain a vulnerability within the SNMP management tool that allows for remote attackers to bypass authentication checks and reach a SQL injection vulnerability within the ‘ztp_config_id’ parameter to the ‘NetworkServlet’ endpoint. Successful exploitation allows for the exfiltration of user data, included clear text passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50592 | Advantech iView &amp;lt; v5.7.04 Build 6425 getInventoryReportData Parameter SQL Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50592</link><description>Advantech iView versions prior to v5.7.04 build 6425 contain a vulnerability within the SNMP management tool that allows for remote attackers to bypass authentication checks and reach a SQL injection vulnerability within the ‘getInventoryReportData’ parameter to the ‘NetworkServlet’ endpoint. Successful exploitation allows for remote code execution with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50593 | Advantech iView &amp;lt; v5.7.04 Build 6425 search_term Parameter SQL Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50593</link><description>Advantech iView versions prior to v5.7.04 build 6425 contain a vulnerability within the SNMP management tool that allows for remote attackers to bypass authentication checks and reach a SQL injection vulnerability within the ‘search_term’ parameter to the ‘NetworkServlet’ endpoint. Successful exploitation allows for remote code execution with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50594 | Advantech iView &amp;lt; v5.7.04 Build 6425 data Parameter SQL Injection Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50594</link><description>Advantech iView versions prior to v5.7.04 build 6425 contain a vulnerability within the SNMP management tool that allows for remote attackers to bypass authentication checks and reach a SQL injection vulnerability within the ‘data’ parameter to the ‘NetworkServlet’ endpoint. Successful exploitation allows for the exfiltration of user data, included clear text passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50595 | Advantech iView &amp;lt; v5.7.04 Build 6425 ztp_search_value Parameter SQL Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50595</link><description>Advantech iView versions prior to v5.7.04 build 6425 contain a vulnerability within the SNMP management tool that allows for remote attackers to bypass authentication checks and reach a SQL injection vulnerability within the ‘ztp_search_value’ parameter to the ‘NetworkServlet’ endpoint. Successful exploitation allows for remote code execution with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50596 | D-Link DIR-1260 &amp;lt;= v1.20B05 GetDeviceSettings Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50596</link><description>D-Link DIR-1260 Wi-Fi router firmware versions up to and including v1.20B05 contain a command injection vulnerability within the web management interface that allows for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the device with root privileges. The flaw specifically exists within the SetDest/Dest/Target arguments to the GetDeviceSettings form. The management interface is accessible over HTTP and HTTPS on the local and Wi-Fi networks and optionally from the Internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34247 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via NetworksController.addNetworkAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34247</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in NetworksController.addNetworkAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34239 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 Command Injection in AppManagementController.appUpgradeAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34239</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a command injection vulnerability in AppManagementController.appUpgradeAction() that allows an authenticated system administrator to execute arbitrary commands as the web server user (www-data) by supplying a crafted uploaded filename.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34240 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AppManagementController.appUpgradeAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34240</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AppManagementController.appUpgradeAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34241 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AjaxDeviceController.ajaxDeviceAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34241</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AjaxDeviceController.ajaxDeviceAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34242 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AjaxNetworkController.ajaxAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34242</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AjaxNetworkController.ajaxAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34243 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AjaxFwRulesController.ajaxNetworkFwRulesAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34243</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AjaxFwRulesController.ajaxNetworkFwRulesAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34244 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AjaxFwRulesController.ajaxDeviceFwRulesAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34244</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AjaxFwRulesController.ajaxDeviceFwRulesAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34245 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AjaxStandaloneVpnClientsController.ajaxAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34245</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AjaxStandaloneVpnClientsController.ajaxAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34246 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 SQL Injection via AjaxPrevalidationController.ajaxAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34246</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in AjaxPrevalidationController.ajaxAction() that allows an authenticated low-privileged observer user to inject SQL via datatable search parameters, leading to disclosure of database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34236 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 Stored XSS via NetworksController.addNetworkAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34236</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via NetworksController.addNetworkAction(). Insufficient validation or escaping of user-supplied input may allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary script in the context of a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34237 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 Stored XSS via StandaloneVpnClientsController.addStandaloneVpnClientAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34237</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via StandaloneVpnClientsController.addStandaloneVpnClientAction(). Insufficient validation or escaping of user-supplied input may allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary script in the context of a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34238 | Advantech WebAccess/VPN &amp;lt; 1.1.5 Path Traversal via AjaxStandaloneVpnClientsController.ajaxDownloadRoadWarriorConfigFileAction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34238</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/VPN versions prior to 1.1.5 contain an absolute path traversal via AjaxStandaloneVpnClientsController.ajaxDownloadRoadWarriorConfigFileAction() that allows an authenticated network administrator to cause the application to read and return the contents of arbitrary files the web user (www-data) can access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22397 | Dell Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller 9, 14G versions prior to 7.00.00.181, 15G and 16G versions 6.10.80.00 through 7.20.10.50 and D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22397</link><description>Dell Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller 9, 14G versions prior to 7.00.00.181, 15G and 16G versions 6.10.80.00 through 7.20.10.50 and Dell Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller 10, 17G versions prior to 1.20.25.00, contain an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31133 | runc container escape via &amp;quot;masked path&amp;quot; abuse due to mount race conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31133</link><description>runc is a CLI tool for spawning and running containers according to the OCI specification. In versions 1.2.7 and below, 1.3.0-rc.1 through 1.3.1, 1.4.0-rc.1 and 1.4.0-rc.2 files, runc would not perform sufficient verification that the source of the bind-mount (i.e., the container's /dev/null) was actually a real /dev/null inode when using the container's /dev/null to mask. This exposes two methods of attack:  an arbitrary mount gadget, leading to host information disclosure, host denial of service, container escape, or a bypassing of maskedPaths. This issue is fixed in versions 1.2.8, 1.3.3 and 1.4.0-rc.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25621 | containerd affected by a local privilege escalation via wide permissions on CRI directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25621</link><description>containerd is an open-source container runtime. Versions 0.1.0 through 1.7.28, 2.0.0-beta.0 through 2.0.6, 2.1.0-beta.0 through 2.1.4 and 2.2.0-beta.0 through 2.2.0-rc.1 have an overly broad default permission vulnerability. Directory paths `/var/lib/containerd`, `/run/containerd/io.containerd.grpc.v1.cri` and `/run/containerd/io.containerd.sandbox.controller.v1.shim` were all created with incorrect permissions. This issue is fixed in versions 1.7.29, 2.0.7, 2.1.5 and 2.2.0. Workarounds include updating system administrator permissions so the host can manually chmod the directories to not have group or world accessible permissions, or to run containerd in rootless mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60541 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the /api/proxy/ component of linshenkx prompt-optimizer v1.3.0 to v1.4.2 allows attackers to scan in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60541</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the /api/proxy/ component of linshenkx prompt-optimizer v1.3.0 to v1.4.2 allows attackers to scan internal resources via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63551 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, achievable through an XML External Entity (XXE) injection, exists in MetInfo Content Man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63551</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, achievable through an XML External Entity (XXE) injection, exists in MetInfo Content Management System (CMS) thru 8.1. This flaw stems from a defect in the XML parsing logic, which allows an attacker to construct a malicious XML entity that forces the server to initiate an HTTP request to an arbitrary internal or external network address. Successful exploitation could lead to internal network reconnaissance, port scanning, or the retrieval of sensitive information. The vulnerability may be present in the backend API called by or associated with the path `/admin/#/webset/?head_tab_active=0`, where user-provided XML data is processed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12815 | An ownership verification issue in the Virtual Desktop preview page in the Research and Engineering Studio (RES) on AWS before version 2025....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12815</link><description>An ownership verification issue in the Virtual Desktop preview page in the Research and Engineering Studio (RES) on AWS before version 2025.09 may allow an authenticated remote user to view another user's active desktop session metadata, including periodical desktop preview screenshots. 

To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version 2025.09 or above.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27916 | An issue was discovered in AnyDesk through 9.0.4. When the connection between two clients is established via an IP address, it is possible t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27916</link><description>An issue was discovered in AnyDesk through 9.0.4. When the connection between two clients is established via an IP address, it is possible to manipulate the data and spoof the AnyDesk ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27917 | An issue was discovered in AnyDesk through 9.0.4. Remote Denial of Service can occur because of incorrect deserialization that results in fa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27917</link><description>An issue was discovered in AnyDesk through 9.0.4. Remote Denial of Service can occur because of incorrect deserialization that results in failed memory allocation and a NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27918 | An issue was discovered in AnyDesk before 9.0.0. It has an integer overflow and resultant heap-based buffer overflow via a UDP packet during...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27918</link><description>An issue was discovered in AnyDesk before 9.0.0. It has an integer overflow and resultant heap-based buffer overflow via a UDP packet during processing of an Identity user image within the Discovery feature, or when establishing a connection between any two clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27919 | An issue was discovered in AnyDesk through 9.0.4. A remotely connected user with the "Control my device" permission can manipulate remote An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27919</link><description>An issue was discovered in AnyDesk through 9.0.4. A remotely connected user with the "Control my device" permission can manipulate remote AnyDesk settings and create a password for the Full Access profile without needing confirmation from the counterparty. Consequently, the attacker can later connect without this counterparty confirmation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10885 | Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10885</link><description>A maliciously crafted file, when executed on the victim's machine, can lead to privilege escalation to NT AUTHORITY/SYSTEM due to an insufficient validation of loaded binaries. An attacker with local and low-privilege access could exploit this to execute code as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12485 | Improper privilege management during pre-MFA cookie handling in Devolutions Server 2025.3.5.0 and earlier allows a low-privileged authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12485</link><description>Improper privilege management during pre-MFA cookie handling in Devolutions Server 2025.3.5.0 and earlier allows a low-privileged authenticated user to impersonate another account by replaying the pre-MFA cookie.This does not bypass the target account MFA verification step.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63560 | An issue in KiloView Dual Channel 4k HDMI &amp; 3G-SDI HEVC Video Encoder Firmware v.1.20.0006 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63560</link><description>An issue in KiloView Dual Channel 4k HDMI &amp; 3G-SDI HEVC Video Encoder Firmware v.1.20.0006 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the systemctrl API System/reFactory component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12808 | Improper access control in Devolutions Server 2025.3.5.0 and earlier allows a View-only user to retrieve sensitive third-level nested fields...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12808</link><description>Improper access control in Devolutions Server 2025.3.5.0 and earlier allows a View-only user to retrieve sensitive third-level nested fields, such as password lists custom values, resulting in password disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59396 | The default configuration of WatchGuard Firebox devices through 2025-09-10 allows administrative access via SSH on port 4118 with the readwr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59396</link><description>The default configuration of WatchGuard Firebox devices through 2025-09-10 allows administrative access via SSH on port 4118 with the readwrite password for the admin account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63588 | An unauthenticated reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the query handling of CMSimpleXH allows remote attackers to inject and ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63588</link><description>An unauthenticated reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the query handling of CMSimpleXH allows remote attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's browser via a crafted request (e.g., a maliciously crafted POST login). Successful exploitation may lead to theft of session cookies, credential disclosure, or other client-side impacts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63589 | A reflected XSS vulnerability exists in CMSimple_XH 1.8's index.php router when attacker-controlled path segments are not sanitized or encod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63589</link><description>A reflected XSS vulnerability exists in CMSimple_XH 1.8's index.php router when attacker-controlled path segments are not sanitized or encoded before being inserted into the generated HTML (navigation links, breadcrumbs, search form action, footer links). An attacker-controlled string placed in the URL path is reflected into multiple HTML elements, allowing execution of arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers visiting a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63307 | alexusmai laravel-file-manager 3.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The application permits user-controlled upload, create, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63307</link><description>alexusmai laravel-file-manager 3.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The application permits user-controlled upload, create, and rename of files to HTML and SVG types and serves those files inline without adequate content-type validation or output sanitization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48290 | WordPress Kinsley theme &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48290</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in bslthemes Kinsley kinsley allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Kinsley: from n/a through &lt;= 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48330 | WordPress Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48330</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Daman Jeet Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms real-time-validation-for-gravity-forms allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49372 | WordPress HAPPY plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49372</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in VillaTheme HAPPY happy-helpdesk-support-ticket-system allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects HAPPY: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49386 | WordPress Preserve Code Formatting Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49386</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Scott Reilly Preserve Code Formatting preserve-code-formatting allows Object Injection.This issue affects Preserve Code Formatting: from n/a through &lt;= 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49390 | WordPress Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Consent plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49390</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in christophrado Cookie Notice &amp; Consent cookie-notice-consent allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cookie Notice &amp; Consent: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49393 | WordPress Sign-up Sheets Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49393</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Fetch Designs Sign-up Sheets sign-up-sheets allows Object Injection.This issue affects Sign-up Sheets: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49394 | WordPress Image Gallery block – Create and display photo gallery/photo album. plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49394</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Image Gallery block – Create and display photo gallery/photo album. 3d-image-gallery allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Image Gallery block – Create and display photo gallery/photo album.: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49398 | WordPress Easy Appointments plugin &amp;lt;= 3.12.14 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49398</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Easy Appointments Easy Appointments easy-appointments allows Code Injection.This issue affects Easy Appointments: from n/a through &lt;= 3.12.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49900 | WordPress Advanced scrollbar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49900</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in bPlugins Advanced scrollbar advanced-scrollbar allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Advanced scrollbar: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49904 | WordPress Booking and Rental Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49904</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in magepeopleteam Booking and Rental Manager booking-and-rental-manager-for-woocommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Booking and Rental Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49905 | WordPress Range Slider Addon for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49905</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PluginsCafe Range Slider Addon for Gravity Forms range-slider-addon-for-gravity-forms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Range Slider Addon for Gravity Forms: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49909 | WordPress Penci Bookmark &amp;amp; Follow plugin &amp;lt; 2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49909</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PenciDesign Penci Bookmark &amp; Follow penci-bookmark-follow allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Penci Bookmark &amp; Follow: from n/a through &lt; 2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52764 | WordPress flexoslider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0004 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52764</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in marielav flexoslider flexoslider allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects flexoslider: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0004.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52773 | WordPress HieCOR Payment Gateway plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.11 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52773</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in hiecor HieCOR Payment Gateway Plugin hcv4-payment-gateway allows SQL Injection.This issue affects HieCOR Payment Gateway Plugin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53214 | WordPress Sertifier Certificate &amp;amp; Badge Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53214</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sertifier Sertifier Certificate &amp; Badge Maker sertifier-certificates-open-badges allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sertifier Certificate &amp; Badge Maker: from n/a through &lt;= 1.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53239 | WordPress User Registration Aide Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bnovotny User Registration Aide user-registration-aide allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects User Registration Aide: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53242 | WordPress Seil Theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53242</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in VictorThemes Seil seil allows Object Injection.This issue affects Seil: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53245 | WordPress WP Logo Changer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Afzal Multani WP Logo Changer am-login-logo allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Logo Changer: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53246 | WordPress Backup and Move Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53246</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gaurav Aggarwal Backup and Move backup-and-move allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Backup and Move: from n/a through &lt;= 0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53252 | WordPress Zegen Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53252</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in zozothemes Zegen zegen allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Zegen: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53283 | WordPress Drop Uploader for CF7 - Drag&amp;amp;Drop File Uploader Addon Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53283</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in borisolhor Drop Uploader for CF7 - Drag&amp;amp;Drop File Uploader Addon drop-uploader-for-contact-form-7-dragdrop-file-uploader-addon allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Drop Uploader for CF7 - Drag&amp;amp;Drop File Uploader Addon: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53286 | WordPress Dropify Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jhainey Milevis Dropify wc-dropi-integration allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Dropify: from n/a through &lt;= 4.6.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53316 | WordPress WP GDPR Cookie Consent plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53316</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shahjahan Jewel WP GDPR Cookie Consent wp-gdpr-cookie-consent allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP GDPR Cookie Consent: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53324 | WordPress Gutenify Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeYatri Gutenify gutenify allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gutenify: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53349 | WordPress Kalium Theme &amp;lt;= 3.18.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Laborator Kalium kalium allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kalium: from n/a through &lt;= 3.18.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53573 | WordPress Epic Review Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jegtheme Epic Review epic-review allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Epic Review: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53574 | WordPress Doliconnect Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ptibogxiv Doliconnect doliconnect allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Doliconnect: from n/a through &lt;= 9.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53585 | WordPress WeMusic theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53585</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NooTheme WeMusic noo-wemusic allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WeMusic: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53586 | WordPress WeMusic Theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53586</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NooTheme WeMusic noo-wemusic allows Object Injection.This issue affects WeMusic: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54711 | WordPress Info Cards Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54711</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Info Cards info-cards allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Info Cards: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54718 | WordPress Yogi - Health Beauty &amp;amp; Yoga theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54718</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NooTheme Yogi - Health Beauty &amp; Yoga noo-yogi allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Yogi - Health Beauty &amp; Yoga: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54719 | WordPress Yogi - Health Beauty &amp;amp; Yoga Theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54719</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NooTheme Yogi - Health Beauty &amp; Yoga noo-yogi allows Object Injection.This issue affects Yogi - Health Beauty &amp; Yoga: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54721 | WordPress Resca theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54721</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThimPress Resca resca allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Resca: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54722 | WordPress WooTour plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54722</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ex-Themes WooTour woo-tour allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooTour: from n/a through &lt;= 3.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54737 | WordPress Jobmonster theme &amp;lt;= 4.7.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54737</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NooTheme Jobmonster noo-jobmonster allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Jobmonster: from n/a through &lt;= 4.7.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58207 | WordPress Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58207</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Messiah Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP ai-image-alt-text-generator-for-wp allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58243 | WordPress imEvent Theme &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58243</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jthemes imEvent imevent allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects imEvent: from n/a through &lt;= 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58592 | WordPress TranslatePress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.2 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58592</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Cozmoslabs TranslatePress translatepress-multilingual allows Object Injection.This issue affects TranslatePress: from n/a through &lt;= 2.10.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58595 | WordPress All In One Login plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58595</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Saad Iqbal All In One Login change-wp-admin-login allows Identity Spoofing.This issue affects All In One Login: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58619 | WordPress Falang multilanguage Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.65 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58619</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in sbouey Falang multilanguage falang allows Object Injection.This issue affects Falang multilanguage: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.65.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58627 | WordPress Miraculous Core Plugin plugin &amp;lt; 2.0.9 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58627</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in kamleshyadav Miraculous Core Plugin miraculouscore allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Miraculous Core Plugin: from n/a through &lt; 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58629 | WordPress Miraculous theme &amp;lt; 2.0.9 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58629</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in kamleshyadav Miraculous miraculous allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Miraculous: from n/a through &lt; 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58636 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Keap/Infusionsoft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58636</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Keap/Infusionsoft gf-infusionsoft allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Keap/Infusionsoft: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58638 | WordPress Institutions Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in e-plugins Institutions Directory institutions-directory allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Institutions Directory: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58964 | WordPress Enzy theme &amp;lt; 1.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58964</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in skygroup Enzy enzy allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Enzy: from n/a through &lt; 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58972 | WordPress Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp;amp; Order Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.4 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58972</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Dmitry V. (CEO of "UKR Solution") Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager barcode-scanner-lite-pos-to-manage-products-inventory-and-orders allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 1.10.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58986 | WordPress Jock On Air Now (JOAN) plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58986</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ganddser Jock On Air Now (JOAN) joan allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Jock On Air Now (JOAN): from n/a through &lt;= 6.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58994 | WordPress Greenify theme &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58994</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in designervily Greenify greenify allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Greenify: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58995 | WordPress Leblix Theme &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58995</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Creatives_Planet Leblix leblix allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Leblix: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58996 | WordPress Advanced Settings Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58996</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Helmut Wandl Advanced Settings advanced-settings allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Advanced Settings: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58998 | WordPress s2Member Plugin &amp;lt;= 250701 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58998</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Cristián Lávaque s2Member s2member allows Object Injection.This issue affects s2Member: from n/a through &lt;= 250701.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59392 | On Elspec G5 devices through 1.2.2.19, a person with physical access to the device can reset the Admin password by inserting a USB drive (co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59392</link><description>On Elspec G5 devices through 1.2.2.19, a person with physical access to the device can reset the Admin password by inserting a USB drive (containing a publicly documented reset string) into a USB port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59556 | WordPress GoStore theme &amp;lt; 1.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59556</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in skygroup GoStore gostore allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects GoStore: from n/a through &lt; 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5803 | WordPress VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp;amp; PMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5803</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in e4jvikwp VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS vikbooking.This issue affects VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60073 | WordPress Responsive Sidebar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60073</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Processby Responsive Sidebar responsive-sidebar allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Responsive Sidebar: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60074 | WordPress Lazy Load Optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60074</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Processby Lazy Load Optimizer lazy-load-optimizer allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Lazy Load Optimizer: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60187 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60187</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Vito Peleg Atarim atarim-visual-collaboration allows Using Malicious Files.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60188 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60188</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Vito Peleg Atarim atarim-visual-collaboration allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60189 | WordPress PoloPag – Pix Automático para Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60189</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in PoloPag PoloPag &amp;#8211; Pix Automático para Woocommerce wc-polo-payments allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PoloPag &amp;#8211; Pix Automático para Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60190 | WordPress Immocaster WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60190</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Hinnerk Altenburg Immocaster WordPress Plugin immocaster allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Immocaster WordPress Plugin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60191 | WordPress Premmerce Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60191</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce Wishlist for WooCommerce premmerce-woocommerce-wishlist allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Premmerce Wishlist for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60192 | WordPress Premmerce Wholesale Pricing for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60192</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce Wholesale Pricing for WooCommerce premmerce-woocommerce-wholesale-pricing allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Premmerce Wholesale Pricing for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60193 | WordPress Premmerce User Roles plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60193</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce User Roles premmerce-user-roles allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Premmerce User Roles: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60194 | WordPress Premmerce Product Search for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60194</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce Product Search for WooCommerce premmerce-search allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Premmerce Product Search for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60195 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60195</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Vito Peleg Atarim atarim-visual-collaboration allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60196 | WordPress Clearblue® Ovulation Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60196</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Clearblue Clearblue® Ovulation Calculator clearblue-ovulation-calculator allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Clearblue® Ovulation Calculator: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60197 | WordPress Simple Contact Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60197</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in owenr88 Simple Contact Forms simple-contact-forms allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Simple Contact Forms: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60198 | WordPress Saxon - Viral Content Blog &amp;amp; Magazine Marketing WordPress Theme theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60198</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in dedalx Saxon - Viral Content Blog &amp; Magazine Marketing WordPress Theme saxon allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Saxon - Viral Content Blog &amp; Magazine Marketing WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60199 | WordPress InHype - Blog &amp;amp; Magazine WordPress Theme theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60199</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in dedalx InHype - Blog &amp; Magazine WordPress Theme inhype allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects InHype - Blog &amp; Magazine WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60200 | WordPress LearnPress Export Import plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60200</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress Export Import learnpress-import-export allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects LearnPress Export Import: from n/a through &lt;= 4.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60201 | WordPress WP Customer Area plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60201</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in aguilatechnologies WP Customer Area customer-area allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WP Customer Area: from n/a through &lt;= 8.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60202 | WordPress Favorites plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60202</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Kyle Phillips Favorites favorites allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Favorites: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60203 | WordPress Store Exporter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60203</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Josh Kohlbach Store Exporter woocommerce-exporter allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Store Exporter: from n/a through &lt;= 2.7.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60204 | WordPress WooCommerce Store Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60204</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Josh Kohlbach WooCommerce Store Toolkit woocommerce-store-toolkit allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WooCommerce Store Toolkit: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60207 | WordPress Custom User Registration Fields for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60207</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Addify Custom User Registration Fields for WooCommerce user-registration-plugin-for-woocommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Custom User Registration Fields for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60235 | WordPress Helpdesk Support Ticket System for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60235</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Plugify Helpdesk Support Ticket System for WooCommerce support-ticket-system-for-woocommerce allows Using Malicious Files.This issue affects Helpdesk Support Ticket System for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60239 | WordPress CoSchool LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Codexpert, Inc CoSchool LMS coschool allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects CoSchool LMS: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60240 | WordPress AnyComment plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60240</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Alexander AnyComment anycomment allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects AnyComment: from n/a through &lt;= 0.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60241 | WordPress Premmerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60241</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce premmerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Premmerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60242 | WordPress Download Counter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60242</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Anatoly Download Counter download-counter allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Download Counter: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60243 | WordPress Selling Commander for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.46 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60243</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Holest Engineering Selling Commander for WooCommerce selling-commander-connector allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Selling Commander for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.46.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60244 | WordPress TableOn plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4.2 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in RealMag777 TableOn posts-table-filterable allows Code Injection.This issue affects TableOn: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60245 | WordPress WP User Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.12 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60245</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WP User Manager WP User Manager wp-user-manager allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP User Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60247 | WordPress Bux Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60247</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bux Bux Woocommerce bux-woocommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Bux Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60248 | WordPress WPC Product Options for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60248</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPClever WPC Product Options for WooCommerce wpc-product-options allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WPC Product Options for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62010 | WordPress Famita theme &amp;lt;= 1.54 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62010</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Famita famita allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Famita: from n/a through &lt;= 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62011 | WordPress TheGem theme &amp;lt;= 5.10.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62011</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem thegem.This issue affects TheGem: from n/a through &lt;= 5.10.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62012 | WordPress TheGem (Elementor) theme &amp;lt;= 5.10.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62012</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem (Elementor) thegem-elementor.This issue affects TheGem (Elementor): from n/a through &lt;= 5.10.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62014 | WordPress ITok theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.42 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62014</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme ITok itok.This issue affects ITok: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.42.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62016 | WordPress Kallyas theme &amp;lt;= 4.22.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62016</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in hogash Kallyas kallyas.This issue affects Kallyas: from n/a through &lt;= 4.22.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62017 | WordPress Kallyas theme &amp;lt;= 4.22.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62017</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in hogash Kallyas kallyas.This issue affects Kallyas: from n/a through &lt;= 4.22.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62018 | WordPress Kallyas theme &amp;lt;= 4.22.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62018</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in hogash Kallyas kallyas.This issue affects Kallyas: from n/a through &lt;= 4.22.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62028 | WordPress Salient theme &amp;lt; 17.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62028</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeNectar Salient salient.This issue affects Salient: from n/a through &lt; 17.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62030 | WordPress tagDiv Composer plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62030</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tagDiv tagDiv Composer td-composer.This issue affects tagDiv Composer: from n/a through &lt;= 5.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62031 | WordPress tagDiv Composer plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62031</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tagDiv tagDiv Composer td-composer.This issue affects tagDiv Composer: from n/a through &lt;= 5.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62032 | WordPress tagDiv Cloud Library plugin &amp;lt; 3.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62032</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tagDiv tagDiv Cloud Library td-cloud-library allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects tagDiv Cloud Library: from n/a through &lt; 3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62033 | WordPress Togo theme &amp;lt; 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62033</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in uxper Togo togo.This issue affects Togo: from n/a through &lt; 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62034 | WordPress Togo theme &amp;lt; 1.0.4 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62034</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in uxper Togo togo.This issue affects Togo: from n/a through &lt; 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62035 | WordPress Togo theme &amp;lt; 1.0.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62035</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in uxper Togo togo.This issue affects Togo: from n/a through &lt; 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62036 | WordPress Togo theme &amp;lt; 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62036</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uxper Togo togo.This issue affects Togo: from n/a through &lt; 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62037 | WordPress Togo theme &amp;lt; 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62037</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in uxper Togo togo.This issue affects Togo: from n/a through &lt; 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62038 | WordPress MeetingHub plugin &amp;lt;= 1.23.9 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62038</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Sovlix MeetingHub meetinghub allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects MeetingHub: from n/a through &lt;= 1.23.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62039 | WordPress AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62039</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Ays Pro AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS ays-chatgpt-assistant allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS: from n/a through &lt;= 2.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62040 | WordPress YOP Poll plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.37 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62040</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in YOP YOP Poll yop-poll.This issue affects YOP Poll: from n/a through &lt;= 6.5.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62041 | WordPress TheGem (Elementor) theme &amp;lt;= 5.10.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62041</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem (Elementor) thegem-elementor.This issue affects TheGem (Elementor): from n/a through &lt;= 5.10.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62044 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62044</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery) thegem-elements.This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery): from n/a through &lt;= 5.10.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62045 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.5.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62045</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery) thegem-elements.This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery): from n/a through &lt;= 5.10.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62046 | WordPress TheGem Demo Import (for WPBakery) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.5 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62046</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Demo Import (for WPBakery) thegem-importer.This issue affects TheGem Demo Import (for WPBakery): from n/a through &lt;= 5.10.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62047 | WordPress Case Addons plugin &amp;lt; 1.3.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62047</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Case-Themes Case Addons case-addons.This issue affects Case Addons: from n/a through &lt; 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62049 | WordPress Cost Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.32 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62049</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stylemix Cost Calculator Builder cost-calculator-builder.This issue affects Cost Calculator Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 3.5.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62051 | WordPress UDesign Core plugin &amp;lt;= 4.14.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62051</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AndonDesign UDesign Core u-design-core.This issue affects UDesign Core: from n/a through &lt;= 4.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62053 | WordPress Houzez theme &amp;lt; 4.2.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62053</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez houzez.This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through &lt; 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62055 | WordPress Academist theme &amp;lt; 1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62055</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Elated-Themes Academist academist.This issue affects Academist: from n/a through &lt; 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62057 | WordPress Houzez Theme - Functionality plugin &amp;lt; 4.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez Theme - Functionality houzez-theme-functionality.This issue affects Houzez Theme - Functionality: from n/a through &lt; 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62059 | WordPress SureRank plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62059</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force SureRank surerank.This issue affects SureRank: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62064 | WordPress Search &amp;amp; Go theme &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62064</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Elated-Themes Search &amp; Go search-and-go allows Password Recovery Exploitation.This issue affects Search &amp; Go: from n/a through &lt;= 2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62065 | WordPress RTMKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62065</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Rometheme RTMKit rometheme-for-elementor.This issue affects RTMKit: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62066 | WordPress Revolution theme &amp;lt; 2.5.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62066</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in fuelthemes Revolution revolution.This issue affects Revolution: from n/a through &lt; 2.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62067 | WordPress Savory theme &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62067</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Elated-Themes Savory savory.This issue affects Savory: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62074 | WordPress WPMobile.App plugin &amp;lt;= 11.71 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62074</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Amauri WPMobile.App wpappninja.This issue affects WPMobile.App: from n/a through &lt;= 11.71.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62075 | WordPress Simple Payment plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62075</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Ido Kobelkowsky Simple Payment simple-payment.This issue affects Simple Payment: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62076 | WordPress Simple Payment plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62076</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ido Kobelkowsky Simple Payment simple-payment.This issue affects Simple Payment: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62914 | WordPress Effect Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62914</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in anibalwainstein Effect Maker effect-maker allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Effect Maker: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62950 | WordPress Contest Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 28.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62950</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wasiliy Strecker / ContestGallery developer Contest Gallery contest-gallery allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Contest Gallery: from n/a through &lt;= 28.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64196 | WordPress Booster for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64196</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pluggabl Booster for WooCommerce woocommerce-jetpack allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Booster for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 7.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64198 | WordPress Easy Social Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt; 10.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64198</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in appscreo Easy Social Share Buttons easy-social-share-buttons3 allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Easy Social Share Buttons: from n/a through &lt; 10.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64224 | WordPress Grand Conference Theme Custom Post Type plugin &amp;lt; 2.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGoods Grand Conference Theme Custom Post Type grandconference-custom-post allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Grand Conference Theme Custom Post Type: from n/a through &lt; 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64232 | WordPress Import from YML plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64232</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in icopydoc Import from YML import-from-yml allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Import from YML: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64287 | WordPress Alloggio - Hotel Booking Theme theme &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64287</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Edge-Themes Alloggio - Hotel Booking alloggio allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Alloggio - Hotel Booking: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6325 | WordPress King Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 51.1.36 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6325</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in KingAddons.com King Addons for Elementor king-addons allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects King Addons for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 51.1.36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6327 | WordPress King Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 51.1.36 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6327</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in KingAddons.com King Addons for Elementor king-addons allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects King Addons for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 51.1.36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22288 | WordPress Smush Image Compression and Optimization plugin &amp;lt;= 3.17.0 - Directory Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22288</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in WPMU DEV - Your All-in-One WordPress Platform Smush Image Compression and Optimization wp-smushit allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Smush Image Compression and Optimization: from n/a through &lt;= 3.17.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28953 | WordPress smart SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28953</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in axiomthemes smart SEO smartSEO allows SQL Injection.This issue affects smart SEO: from n/a through &lt;= 4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31029 | WordPress replyMail plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31029</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bingu replyMail replymail allows Stored XSS.This issue affects replyMail: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32222 | WordPress Widget Logic &amp;lt;= 6.0.5 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32222</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Widgetlogic.org Widget Logic widget-logic allows Code Injection.This issue affects Widget Logic: from n/a through &lt;= 6.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39463 | WordPress Dessau theme &amp;lt; 1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39463</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Select-Themes Dessau dessau allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dessau: from n/a through &lt; 1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39465 | WordPress Advanced Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39465</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in flippercode Advanced Google Maps wp-google-map-gold allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced Google Maps: from n/a through &lt;= 5.8.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39466 | WordPress Dør theme &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39466</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Dør dor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dør: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39467 | WordPress Wanderland theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39467</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Wanderland wanderland allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Wanderland: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39468 | WordPress Modal Survey plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39468</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in pantherius Modal Survey modal-survey.This issue affects Modal Survey: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47588 | WordPress Dynamic Pricing With Discount Rules for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.9 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47588</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in acowebs Dynamic Pricing With Discount Rules for WooCommerce aco-woo-dynamic-pricing allows Code Injection.This issue affects Dynamic Pricing With Discount Rules for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 4.5.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48077 | WordPress Block Country plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48077</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nitinmaurya12 Block Country block-country allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Block Country: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48078 | WordPress Slick Google Map plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48078</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Norbert Slick Google Map slick-google-map allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Slick Google Map: from n/a through &lt;= 0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48083 | WordPress wpNamedUsers plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48083</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in andriassundskard wpNamedUsers wpnamedusers allows Stored XSS.This issue affects wpNamedUsers: from n/a through &lt;= 0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48085 | WordPress Simple Stripe plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.17 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48085</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ZIPANG Simple Stripe simple-stripe allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Stripe: from n/a through &lt;= 0.9.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48086 | WordPress Ajax Search Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 4.13.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48086</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in wpdreams Ajax Search Lite ajax-search-lite allows Object Injection.This issue affects Ajax Search Lite: from n/a through &lt;= 4.13.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48089 | WordPress Education WordPress Theme | HiStudy theme &amp;lt; 3.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48089</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Rainbow-Themes Education WordPress Theme | HiStudy histudy allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Education WordPress Theme | HiStudy: from n/a through &lt; 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48090 | WordPress Blanka - One Page WordPress Theme Theme &amp;lt; 1.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48090</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in CocoBasic Blanka - One Page WordPress Theme blanka-wp allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Blanka - One Page WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt; 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12556 | IDIS ICM Viewer Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12556</link><description>An argument injection vulnerability exists in the affected product that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code within the context of the host machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11956 | XSS in Proliz&amp;#x27;s OBS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11956</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Proliz Software Ltd. Co. OBS (Student Affairs Information System) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects OBS (Student Affairs Information System): before 25.0401.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10955 | HTML Injection in Netcad Software&amp;#x27;s Netigma</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10955</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Netcad Software Inc. Netigma allows XSS Through HTTP Query Strings.This issue affects Netigma: through 28102025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37735 | Improper preservation of permissions in Elastic Defend on Windows hosts can lead to arbitrary files on the system being deleted by the Defen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37735</link><description>Improper preservation of permissions in Elastic Defend on Windows hosts can lead to arbitrary files on the system being deleted by the Defend service running as SYSTEM. In some cases, this could result in local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36054 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability affect IBM Business Automation Workflow Process Federation Server -</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36054</link><description>IBM Business Automation Workflow containers 24.0.0 through 24.0.0-IF006, 24.0.1 through 24.0.1-IF004, 25.0.0 through 25.0.0-IF001 and IBM Business Automation Workflow traditional with Process Federation Server 24.0.0 through 24.0.1 and 25.0.0 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11268 | Strong Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.2.16 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11268</link><description>The Strong Testimonials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.16. This is due to the software allowing users to submit a testimonial in which a value is not properly validated or sanitized prior to being passed to a do_shortcode call. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes if an administrator previews or publishes a crafted testimonial.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 08:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12360 | Better Find and Replace &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12360</link><description>The Better Find and Replace – AI-Powered Suggestions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized API usage due to a missing capability check on the rtafar_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access, to trigger OpenAI API key usage resulting in quota consumption potentially incurring cost.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 07:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10259 | Denial-of-Service(DoS) Vulnerability in TCP Communication Function on MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10259</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in TCP Communication Function on Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote attacker to disconnect the connection by sending specially crafted TCP packets to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the products. There is no impact on connections other than the attacked one.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 07:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12471 | Hubbub Lite &amp;lt;= 1.36.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12471</link><description>The Hubbub Lite – Fast, free social sharing and follow buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'dpsp_list_attention_search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.36.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9338 | A improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer exists in AsIO3.sys driver. This vulnerability can be triggered by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9338</link><description>A improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer exists in AsIO3.sys driver. This vulnerability can be triggered by manually executing a specially crafted process, potentially leading to local privilage escalation.
For additional information, please refer to the 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' section of the ASUS Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 06:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12560 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 8.6.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via post_url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12560</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 8.6.0 via the getFullContent() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 05:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11271 | Easy Digital Download &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Insufficient Verification to Order Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11271</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Order Manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to an order verification bypass. The verification is unconditionally skipped when the POST body includes verification_override=1. Because this value is attacker-supplied, an unauthenticated actor can submit a forged IPN and have it treated as verified, even on production sites and with verification otherwise enabled. A valid PayPal transaction id is needed, restricting order manipulation to orders placed by the attacker.  This, in turn, requires them to have a customer account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12563 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 8.6.0 - Incorrect Authorization to Video File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12563</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited file upload due to an incorrect capability check on theuploadVideo() function in all versions up to, and including, 8.6.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload mp4 files to the 'wp-content/uploads///' directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61994 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GROWI prior to v7.2.10. If a malicious user creates a page containing crafted contents, an arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61994</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GROWI prior to v7.2.10. If a malicious user creates a page containing crafted contents, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of a victim user who accesses the page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10691 | Easy Email Subscription &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Subscriber Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10691</link><description>The Easy Email Subscription plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the show_editsub_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary subscribers via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10683 | Easy Email Subscription &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via uid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10683</link><description>The Easy Email Subscription plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'uid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 03:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64164 | DataEase is vulnerable to Oracle JNDI Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64164</link><description>Dataease is an open source data visualization analysis tool. In versions 2.10.14 and below, DataEase did not properly filter when establishing JDBC connections to Oracle, resulting in a risk of JNDI injection (Java Naming and Directory Interface injection). This issue is fixed in version 2.10.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64171 | MARIN3R: Cross-Namespace Vulnerability in the Operator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64171</link><description>MARIN3R is a lightweight, CRD based envoy control plane for kubernetes. In versions 0.13.3 and below, there is a cross-namespace secret access vulnerability in the project's DiscoveryServiceCertificate which allows users to bypass RBAC and access secrets in unauthorized namespaces. This issue is fixed in version 0.13.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64163 | DataEase&amp;#x27;s DB2 is vulnerable to SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64163</link><description>DataEase is an open source data visualization analysis tool. In versions 2.10.14 and below, the vendor added a blacklist to filter ldap:// and ldaps://. However, omission of protection for the dns:// protocol results in an SSRF vulnerability. This issue is fixed in version 2.10.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64114 | ClipBucket v5: SQL Injection possible through ClipBucket Custom Fields plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64114</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Versions 5.5.2 - #151 and below allow authenticated administrators with plugin management privileges to execute arbitrary SQL commands against the database through its ClipBucket Custom Fields plugin. The vulnerabilities require the Custom Fields plugin to be installed and accessible, and can only be exploited by users with administrative access to the plugin interface. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2 - #.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 23:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62161 | youki container escape via &amp;quot;masked path&amp;quot; abuse due to mount race conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62161</link><description>Youki is a container runtime written in Rust. In versions 0.5.6 and below, the initial validation of the source /dev/null is insufficient, allowing container escape when youki utilizes bind mounting the container's /dev/null as a file mask. This issue is fixed in version 0.5.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 23:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62596 | youki container escape and denial of service due to arbitrary write gadgets and procfs write redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62596</link><description>Youki is a container runtime written in Rust. In versions 0.5.6 and below, youki’s apparmor handling performs insufficiently strict write-target validation, and when combined with path substitution during pathname resolution, can allow writes to unintended procfs locations. While resolving a path component-by-component, a shared-mount race can substitute intermediate components and redirect the final target. This issue is fixed in version 0.5.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 23:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55278 | HCL DevOps Loop is susceptible to an improper authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55278</link><description>Improper authentication in the API authentication middleware of HCL DevOps Loop allows authentication tokens to be accepted without proper validation of their expiration and cryptographic signature.  As a result, an attacker could potentially use expired or tampered tokens to gain unauthorized access to sensitive resources and perform actions with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 22:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12779 | Improper handling of the authentication token in the Amazon WorkSpaces client for Linux, versions 2023.0 through 2024.8, may expose the auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12779</link><description>Improper handling of the authentication token in the Amazon WorkSpaces client for Linux, versions 2023.0 through 2024.8, may expose the authentication token for DCV-based WorkSpaces to other local users on the same client machine. Under certain circumstances, a local user may be able to extract another local user's authentication token from the shared client machine and access their WorkSpace.

To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to the Amazon WorkSpaces client for Linux version 2025.0 or later.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60784 | A vulnerability in the XiaozhangBang Voluntary Like System V8.8 allows remote attackers to manipulate the zhekou parameter in the /topfirst....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60784</link><description>A vulnerability in the XiaozhangBang Voluntary Like System V8.8 allows remote attackers to manipulate the zhekou parameter in the /topfirst.php Pay module, enabling unauthorized discounts. By sending a crafted HTTP POST request with zhekou set to an abnormally low value, an attacker can purchase votes at a reduced cost. Furthermore, by modifying the zid parameter, attackers can influence purchases made by other users, amplifying the impact. This issue stems from insufficient server-side validation of these parameters, potentially leading to economic loss and unfair manipulation of vote counts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63585 | OSSN (Open Source Social Network) 8.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /action/rtcomments/status via the timestamp parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63585</link><description>OSSN (Open Source Social Network) 8.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /action/rtcomments/status via the timestamp parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63334 | PocketVJ CP PocketVJ-CP-v3 pvj version 3.9.1 contains an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the submit_opacity.php compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63334</link><description>PocketVJ CP PocketVJ-CP-v3 pvj version 3.9.1 contains an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the submit_opacity.php component. The application fails to sanitize user input in the opacityValue POST parameter before passing it to a shell command, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10853 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Management Console of Multiple WSO2 Products Due to Improper Output Encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10853</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the management console of multiple WSO2 products due to improper output encoding. By tampering with specific parameters, a malicious actor can inject arbitrary JavaScript into the response, leading to reflected XSS.

Successful exploitation could result in UI manipulation, redirection to malicious websites, or data theft from the browser. However, session-related sensitive cookies are protected with the httpOnly flag, which mitigates the risk of session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5770 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Authentication Endpoints of Multiple WSO2 Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5770</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the authentication endpoints of multiple WSO2 products due to a lack of output encoding. A malicious actor can inject arbitrary JavaScript payloads into the authentication endpoint, which are reflected back in the response, enabling browser-based attacks.

Exploitation may result in redirection to malicious websites, UI manipulation, or unauthorized data access from the victim’s browser. However, session-related cookies are protected with the httpOnly flag, which mitigates session hijacking via this vector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55343 | Quipux 4.0.1 through e1774ac allows authenticated users to conduct SQL injection attacks via busqueda/busqueda.php txt_depe_codi, busqueda/b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55343</link><description>Quipux 4.0.1 through e1774ac allows authenticated users to conduct SQL injection attacks via busqueda/busqueda.php txt_depe_codi, busqueda/busqueda.php txt_usua_codi, anexos_lista.php radi_temp, Administracion/listas/formArea_ajax.php codDepe, Administracion/listas/formDepeHijo_ajax.php codDepe, Administracion/listas/formDepePadre_ajax.php codInst, asociar_documentos/asociar_borrar_referencia.php radi_nume, asociar_documentos/asociar_documento_buscar_query.php radi_nume, asociar_documentos/asociar_documento_grabar.php txt_radi_nume, asociar_documentos/asociar_documento radi_nume, radicacion/buscar_usuario.php buscar_tipo, radicacion/formArea_ajax.php codDepe, radicacion/formDepeHijo_ajax.php codDepe, radicacion/formDepePadre_ajax.php codInst, radicacion/ver_datos_usuario.php destinatorio, reportes/reporte_TraspasoDocFisico.php verrad, tx/datos_imprimir_sobre.php txt_usua_codi, tx/datos_imprimir_sobre.php nume_radi_temp, tx/revertir_firma_digital_grabar.php txt_radi_nume, tx/tx_borrar_opcion_imp.php codigo_opc, tx/tx_realizar_tx.php txt_radicados, tx/tx_seguridad_documentos.php txt_radicados, or uploadFiles/cargar_doc_digitalizado_paginador.php txt_depe_codi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55341 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Quipux 4.0.1 through e1774ac allows anexos/anexos_nuevo.php asocImgRad.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55341</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Quipux 4.0.1 through e1774ac allows anexos/anexos_nuevo.php asocImgRad.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55342 | Quipux 4.0.1 through e1774ac allows enumeration of usernames, and accessing the Ecuadorean identification number for all registered users vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55342</link><description>Quipux 4.0.1 through e1774ac allows enumeration of usernames, and accessing the Ecuadorean identification number for all registered users via the Administracion/usuarios/cambiar_password_olvido_validar.php txt_login parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63417 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the chat functionality of the SelfBest platform 2023.3 allows authenticated attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63417</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the chat functionality of the SelfBest platform 2023.3 allows authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts or HTML via the chat message input field. This malicious content is stored and then executed in the context of other users' browsers when they view the malicious message, potentially leading to session hijacking, account takeover, or other client-side attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63418 | A DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SelfBest platform 2023.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63418</link><description>A DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SelfBest platform 2023.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a logged-in user's session by injecting payloads via the browser's developer console. The vulnerability arises from the application's client-side code being susceptible to direct DOM manipulation without adequate sanitization or a Content Security Policy (CSP), potentially leading to account takeover and data theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43000 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.5, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43000</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.5, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, Safari 16.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11093 | Arbitrary Code Execution with higher privileged users in Multiple WSO2 Products via Script Mediator Engines (GraalJS and NashornJS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11093</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to insufficient restrictions in the GraalJS and NashornJS Script Mediator engines. Authenticated users with elevated privileges can execute arbitrary code within the integration runtime environment.

By default, access to these scripting engines is limited to administrators in WSO2 Micro Integrator and WSO2 Enterprise Integrator, while in WSO2 API Manager, access extends to both administrators and API creators. This may allow trusted-but-privileged users to perform unauthorized actions or compromise the execution environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12745 | QuickJS quickjs.c js_array_buffer_slice buffer over-read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12745</link><description>A weakness has been identified in QuickJS up to eb2c89087def1829ed99630cb14b549d7a98408c. This affects the function js_array_buffer_slice of the file quickjs.c. This manipulation causes buffer over-read. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery Patch name: c6fe5a98fd3ef3b7064e6e0145dfebfe12449fea. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43418 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2. An attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43418</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63416 | ** exclusively-hosted-service ** A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the chat functionality of the SelfBest platform 2023.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63416</link><description>** exclusively-hosted-service ** A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the chat functionality of the SelfBest platform 2023.3 allows authenticated low-privileged attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of other users' sessions. This can be exploited to access administrative data and functions, leading to privilege escalation and full compromise of sensitive user data, as demonstrated by the ability to fetch and exfiltrate the contents of the /admin/users endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31954 | HCL iAutomate is susceptible to a sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31954</link><description>HCL iAutomate v6.5.1 and v6.5.2 is susceptible to a sensitive information disclosure.  An HTTP GET method is used to process a request and includes sensitive information in the query string of that request.  An attacker could potentially access information or resources they were not intended to see.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56232 | GOG Galaxy 2.0.0.2 suffers from Missing SSL Certificate Validation. An attacker who controls the local network, DNS, or a proxy can perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56232</link><description>GOG Galaxy 2.0.0.2 suffers from Missing SSL Certificate Validation. An attacker who controls the local network, DNS, or a proxy can perform a man-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to intercept update requests and replace installer or update packages with malicious files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10907 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload in Multiple WSO2 Products via SOAP Admin Services Leading to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10907</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to insufficient validation of uploaded content and destination in SOAP admin services. A malicious actor with administrative privileges can upload a specially crafted file to a user-controlled location within the deployment.

Successful exploitation may lead to remote code execution (RCE) on the server, depending on how the uploaded file is processed. By default, this vulnerability is only exploitable by users with administrative access to the affected SOAP services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56231 | Tonec Internet Download Manager 6.42.41.1 and earlier suffers from Missing SSL Certificate Validation, which allows attackers to bypass upda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56231</link><description>Tonec Internet Download Manager 6.42.41.1 and earlier suffers from Missing SSL Certificate Validation, which allows attackers to bypass update protections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10713 | XML External Entity (XXE) Vulnerability in Multiple WSO2 Products Due to Improper XML Parser Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10713</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to improper configuration of the XML parser. The application parses user-supplied XML without applying sufficient restrictions, allowing resolution of external entities.

A successful attack could enable a remote, unauthenticated attacker to read sensitive files from the server's filesystem or perform denial-of-service (DoS) attacks that render affected services unavailable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43990 | Dell Command Monitor (DCM), versions prior to 10.12.3.28, contains an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43990</link><description>Dell Command Monitor (DCM), versions prior to 10.12.3.28, contains an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46366 | Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.1.1, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user may exploit and gain parallel privilege escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46366</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.1.1, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user may exploit and gain parallel privilege escalation or access to the database to obtain confidential information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46365 | Dell CloudLink, versions prior 8.1.1, contain a Command Injection vulnerability which can be exploited by an Authenticated attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46365</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions prior 8.1.1, contain a Command Injection vulnerability which can be exploited by an Authenticated attacker to cause Command Injection on an affected Dell CloudLink.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46424 | Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.2, contain use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A high privileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46424</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.2, contain use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59716 | ownCloud Guests before 0.12.5 allows unauthenticated user enumeration via the /apps/guests/register/{email}/{token} endpoint. Because of ins...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59716</link><description>ownCloud Guests before 0.12.5 allows unauthenticated user enumeration via the /apps/guests/register/{email}/{token} endpoint. Because of insufficient validation of the supplied token in showPasswordForm, the server responds differently when an e-mail address corresponds to a valid pending guest user rather than a non-existent user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:02:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20289 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20289</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected XSS attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20303 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20303</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected XSS attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20304 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20304</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected XSS attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20305 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20305</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain files lack proper data protection mechanisms. An attacker with read-only Administrator privileges could exploit this vulnerability by performing actions where the results should only be viewable to a high-privileged user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view passwords that are normally not visible to read-only administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20343 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Radius Suppression Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20343</link><description>A vulnerability in the RADIUS setting Reject RADIUS requests from clients with repeated failures on Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause Cisco ISE to restart unexpectedly.

This vulnerability is due to a logic error when processing a RADIUS access request for a MAC address that is already a rejected endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specific sequence of multiple crafted RADIUS access request messages to Cisco ISE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition when Cisco ISE restarts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20354 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20354</link><description>A vulnerability in the Java Remote Method Invocation (RMI) process of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files and execute arbitrary commands with root permissions on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to improper authentication mechanisms that are associated to specific Cisco Unified CCX features. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted file to an affected system through the Java RMI process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20358 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Editor Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20358</link><description>A vulnerability in the Contact Center Express (CCX) Editor application of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and obtain administrative permissions pertaining to script creation and execution.

This vulnerability is due to improper authentication mechanisms in the communication between the CCX Editor and an affected Unified CCX server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by redirecting the authentication flow to a malicious server and tricking the CCX Editor into believing the authentication was successful. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create and execute arbitrary scripts on the underlying operating system of an affected Unified CCX server, as an internal non-root user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20374 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20374</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a directory traversal and access arbitrary resources.

This vulnerability is due to an insufficient input validation associated to specific UI features. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain read access to arbitrary files on the underlying operating system.&amp;nbsp;To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20375 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20375</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload and execute arbitrary files.

This vulnerability is due to an insufficient input validation associated to specific UI features. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted file to the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload arbitrary files to a vulnerable system and execute them, gaining access to the underlying operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20376 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20376</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload and execute arbitrary files.

This vulnerability is due to an insufficient input validation associated to file upload mechanisms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to the web UI and executing it. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20377 | Cisco Unified Intelligence Center API Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20377</link><description>A vulnerability in the API subsystem of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of requests to certain API endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a valid request to a specific API endpoint within the affected system. A successful exploit could allow a low-privileged user to view sensitive information on the affected system that should be restricted. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid user credentials on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30479 | Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.2, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user with known password can run command injection to gain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30479</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.2, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user with known password can run command injection to gain control of system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45379 | Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.2, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user with known password can run command injection from co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45379</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.2, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user with known password can run command injection from console to gain shell access of system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46364 | Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.1.1, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user with known password can run CLI Escape Vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46364</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions prior to 8.1.1, contain a vulnerability where a privileged user with known password can run CLI Escape Vulnerability to gain control of system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57244 | OpenKM Community Edition 6.3.12 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in the user account creation interface. The Name field ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57244</link><description>OpenKM Community Edition 6.3.12 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in the user account creation interface. The Name field accepts script tags and the Email field is vulnerable when the POST request is modified to include encoded script tags, by passing frontend validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45378 | Dell CloudLink, versions 8.0 through 8.1.2, contain vulnerability on restricted shell. A Privileged user with known password can break into ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45378</link><description>Dell CloudLink, versions 8.0 through 8.1.2, contain vulnerability on restricted shell. A Privileged user with known password can break into command shell of CloudLink server and gain access of shell and escalate privilege, gain unauthorized access of system.

If ssh is enabled with web credentials of server, attack is possible through network with known privileged user/password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63248 | DWSurvey 6.14.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. When deleting a questionnaire, replacing the questionnaire ID with the ID of anot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63248</link><description>DWSurvey 6.14.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. When deleting a questionnaire, replacing the questionnaire ID with the ID of another questionnaire can enable the deletion of other questionnaires.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57130 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in the user management component of ZwiiCMS up to v13.6.07 allows a remote, authenticated attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57130</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in the user management component of ZwiiCMS up to v13.6.07 allows a remote, authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges. By sending a specially crafted HTTP request, a low-privilege user can access and modify the profile data of any other user, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63601 | Snipe-IT before version 8.3.3 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to upload a malicious bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63601</link><description>Snipe-IT before version 8.3.3 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to upload a malicious backup file containing arbitrary files and execute system commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60753 | An issue was discovered in libarchive bsdtar before version 3.8.1 in function apply_substitution in file tar/subst.c when processing crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60753</link><description>An issue was discovered in libarchive bsdtar before version 3.8.1 in function apply_substitution in file tar/subst.c when processing crafted -s substitution rules. This can cause unbounded memory allocation and lead to denial of service (Out-of-Memory crash).</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61304 | OS command injection vulnerability in Dynatrace ActiveGate ping extension up to 1.016 via crafted ip address.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61304</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability in Dynatrace ActiveGate ping extension up to 1.016 via crafted ip address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64458 | Potential denial-of-service vulnerability in HttpResponseRedirect and HttpResponsePermanentRedirect on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64458</link><description>An issue was discovered in 5.1 before 5.1.14, 4.2 before 4.2.26, and 5.2 before 5.2.8.
NFKC normalization in Python is slow on Windows. As a consequence, `django.http.HttpResponseRedirect`, `django.http.HttpResponsePermanentRedirect`, and the shortcut `django.shortcuts.redirect`  were subject to a potential  denial-of-service attack via certain inputs with a very large number of Unicode characters.
Earlier, unsupported Django series (such as 5.0.x, 4.1.x, and 3.2.x) were not evaluated and may also be affected.
Django would like to thank Seokchan Yoon for reporting this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64459 | Potential SQL injection via _connector keyword argument in QuerySet and Q objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64459</link><description>An issue was discovered in 5.1 before 5.1.14, 4.2 before 4.2.26, and 5.2 before 5.2.8.
The methods `QuerySet.filter()`, `QuerySet.exclude()`, and `QuerySet.get()`, and the class `Q()`, are subject to SQL injection when using a suitably crafted dictionary, with dictionary expansion, as the `_connector` argument.
Earlier, unsupported Django series (such as 5.0.x, 4.1.x, and 3.2.x) were not evaluated and may also be affected.
Django would like to thank cyberstan for reporting this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46404 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the lasso_provider_verify_saml_signature functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46404</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the lasso_provider_verify_saml_signature functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1. A specially crafted SAML response can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a malformed SAML response to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46705 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the g_assert_not_reached functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1 and 2.8.2. A specially cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46705</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the g_assert_not_reached functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1 and 2.8.2. A specially crafted SAML assertion response can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a malformed SAML response to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46784 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the lasso_node_init_from_message_with_format functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46784</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the lasso_node_init_from_message_with_format functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1. A specially crafted SAML response can lead to a memory depletion, resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a malformed SAML response to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47151 | A type confusion vulnerability exists in the lasso_node_impl_init_from_xml functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1 and 2.8.2. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47151</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in the lasso_node_impl_init_from_xml functionality of Entr'ouvert Lasso 2.5.1 and 2.8.2. A specially crafted SAML response can lead to an arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a malformed SAML response to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3125 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload in Multiple WSO2 Products via CarbonAppUploader Admin Service Leading to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3125</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to improper input validation in the CarbonAppUploader admin service endpoint. An authenticated attacker with appropriate privileges can upload a malicious file to a user-controlled location on the server, potentially leading to remote code execution (RCE).

This functionality is restricted by default to admin users; therefore, successful exploitation requires valid credentials with administrative permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52602 | HCL BigFix Query is affected by a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability in the WebUI Query application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52602</link><description>HCL BigFix Query is affected by a sensitive information disclosure in the WebUI Query application.  An HTTP GET endpoint request returns discoverable responses that may disclose: group names, active user names (or IDs).   An attacker can use that information to target individuals with phishing or other social-engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61084 | MDaemon Mail Server 23.5.2 validates SPF, DKIM, and DMARC using the email enclosed in angle brackets (&lt;&gt;) in the From: header of SMTP DATA. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61084</link><description>MDaemon Mail Server 23.5.2 validates SPF, DKIM, and DMARC using the email enclosed in angle brackets () in the From: header of SMTP DATA. An attacker can craft a From: header with multiple invisible Unicode thin spaces to display a spoofed sender while passing validation, allowing email spoofing even when anti-spoofing protections are in place.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11745 | Ad Inserter &amp;lt;= 2.8.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11745</link><description>The Ad Inserter – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense Ads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom field through the plugin's 'adinserter' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12497 | Premium Portfolio Features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.10 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion via args[extra_template_path]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12497</link><description>The Premium Portfolio Features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.10 via the 'args[extra_template_path]' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11820 | Graphina – Elementor Charts and Graphs &amp;lt;= 3.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Chart Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11820</link><description>The Graphina – Elementor Charts and Graphs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple chart widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on data attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability affects multiple chart widgets including Area Chart, Line Chart, Column Chart, Donut Chart, Heatmap Chart, Radar Chart, Polar Chart, Pie Chart, Radial Chart, and Advance Data Table widgets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11987 | Visual Link Preview &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via visual-link-preview Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11987</link><description>The Visual Link Preview plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's visual-link-preview shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12192 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.15.9 - Sysinfo Key Incorrect Comparison to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12192</link><description>The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in versions up to, and including, 6.15.9. The sysinfo REST endpoint compares the provided key to the stored opt-in key using a loose comparison, allowing unauthenticated attackers to send a boolean value and obtain the full system report whenever "Yes, automatically share my system information with The Events Calendar support team" setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12468 | FunnelKit Automations – Email Marketing Automation and CRM for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.6.4.1 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12468</link><description>The FunnelKit Automations – Email Marketing Automation and CRM for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4.1 via the '/wc-coupons/' REST API endpoint. This is due to the endpoint being marked as a public API (`public_api = true`), which results in the endpoint being registered with `permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true'`, bypassing all authentication and capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including all WooCommerce coupon codes, coupon IDs, and expiration status.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12469 | FunnelKit Automations – Email Marketing Automation and CRM for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.6.4.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12469</link><description>The FunnelKit Automations – Email Marketing Automation and CRM for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform administrative actions in the `bwfan_test_email` AJAX handler. The nonce used for verification is publicly exposed to all visitors (including unauthenticated users) via the frontend JavaScript localization, and the `check_nonce()` function accepts low-privilege authenticated users who possess this nonce. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to send arbitrary emails from the site with attacker-controlled subject and body content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58337 | Apache Doris-MCP-Server: Improper Access Control results in bypassing a &amp;quot;read-only&amp;quot; mode for doris-mcp-server MCP Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58337</link><description>An attacker with a valid read-only account can bypass Doris MCP Server’s read-only mode due to improper access control, allowing modifications that should have been prevented by read-only restrictions.


Impact:

Bypasses read-only mode; attackers with read-only access may perform unauthorized modifications.




Recommended action for operators: Upgrade to version 0.6.0 as soon as possible (this release contains the fix).</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55108 | BMC Control-M/Agent default configuration does not enforce SSL/TLS allowing unauthorized actions and remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55108</link><description>The Control-M/Agent is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution, arbitrary file read and write and similar unauthorized actions when mutual SSL/TLS authentication is not enabled (i.e. in the default configuration).


NOTE: The vendor believes that this vulnerability only occurs when documented security best practices are not followed. BMC has always strongly recommended to use security best practices such as configuring SSL/TLS between Control-M Server and Agent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10622 | Foreman: os command injection via ct_location and fcct_location parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10622</link><description>A flaw was found in Red Hat Satellite (Foreman component). This vulnerability allows an authenticated user with edit_settings permissions to achieve arbitrary command execution on the underlying operating system via insufficient server-side validation of command whitelisting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12674 | KiotViet Sync &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12674</link><description>The KiotViet Sync plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the create_media() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12675 | KiotViet Sync &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12675</link><description>The KiotViet Sync plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the saveConfig() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's config.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12676 | KiotViet Sync &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Use of Hard-coded Password to Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12676</link><description>The KiotViet Sync plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorizarion bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5. This is due to the plugin using a hardcoded password for authentication in the QueryControllerAdmin::authenticated function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create and sync products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12677 | KiotViet Sync &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Unauthenticated Webhook Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12677</link><description>The KiotViet Sync plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via the register_api_route() function in kiotvietsync/includes/public_actions/WebHookAction.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract the webhook token value when configured.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11373 | Popup and Slider Builder by Depicter – Add Email collecting Popup, Popup Modal, Coupon Popup, Image Slider, Carousel Slider, Post Slider Carousel &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Safe File Type Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11373</link><description>The Popup and Slider Builder by Depicter – Add Email collecting Popup, Popup Modal, Coupon Popup, Image Slider, Carousel Slider, Post Slider Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability checks in the "depicter-media-upload" AJAX route in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload limited files on the affected site's server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11917 | WPeMatico RSS Feed Fetcher &amp;lt;= 2.8.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery via wpematico_test_feed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11917</link><description>The WPeMatico RSS Feed Fetcher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.11 via the wpematico_test_feed() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12139 | File Manager for Google Drive – Integrate Google Drive with WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12139</link><description>The File Manager for Google Drive – Integrate Google Drive with WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 via the "get_localize_data" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including Google OAuth credentials (client_id and client_secret) and Google account email addresses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12384 | Document Embedder – Embed PDFs, Word, Excel, and Other Files &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Document Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12384</link><description>The Document Embedder – Embed PDFs, Word, Excel, and Other Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access/modification/loss of data in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the "bplde_save_document_library", "bplde_get_all", "bplde_get_single", and "bplde_delete_document_library" functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create, read, update, and delete arbitrary document_library posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12388 | B Carousel Block – Responsive Image and Content Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12388</link><description>The B Carousel Block – Responsive Image and Content Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.1.5. This is due to the plugin not validating user-supplied URLs before passing them to the wp_remote_request() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62225 | Optical Disc Archive Software provided by Sony Corporation registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62225</link><description>Optical Disc Archive Software provided by Sony Corporation registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64151 | Multiple Roboticsware products provided by Roboticsware PTE. LTD. register Windows services with unquoted file paths. A user with the write ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64151</link><description>Multiple Roboticsware products provided by Roboticsware PTE. LTD. register Windows services with unquoted file paths. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10567 | FunnelKit &amp;lt; 3.12.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10567</link><description>The FunnelKit  WordPress plugin before 3.12.0.1 does not sanitize user input before echoing it back in some of its checkout-related AJAX actions, allowing attackers to conduct reflected XSS attacks against logged-in users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10873 | Elementinvader Addons for Elementor &amp;lt; 1.4.1 – Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10873</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor WordPress plugin before 1.4.1 allows unauthenticated user to send arbitrary e-mails to arbitrary addresses due to missing authorization on the elementinvader_addons_for_elementor_forms_send_form action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11072 | Download Counter Button &amp;lt;= 1.8.6.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11072</link><description>The MelAbu WP Download Counter Button WordPress plugin through 1.8.6.7 does not validate the path of files to be downloaded, which could allow unauthenticated attacker to read/download arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6027 | Ace User Management &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Subscriber+ Authentication Bypass via Password Rest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6027</link><description>The Ace User Management WordPress plugin through 2.0.3 does not properly validate that a password reset token is associated with the user who requested it, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to reset the password of arbitrary accounts, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21071 | Out-of-bounds write in handling opcode in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write ou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21071</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in handling opcode in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21073 | Insecure default configuration in USB connection mode prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows privileged physical attackers to access user da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21073</link><description>Insecure default configuration in USB connection mode prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows privileged physical attackers to access user data. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21074 | Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21074</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21075 | Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21075</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21076 | Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.00.18 allows local attackers to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21076</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.00.18 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Account. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21077 | Improper input validation in Samsung Email prior to version 6.2.06.0 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Email ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21077</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Email prior to version 6.2.06.0 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Email privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21078 | Use of insufficiently random value of secretKey in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.68.6 allows adjacent attackers to access backup data fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21078</link><description>Use of insufficiently random value of secretKey in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.68.6 allows adjacent attackers to access backup data from applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21079 | Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.5.01.3 allows remote attackers to connect arbitrary URL and launch arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21079</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.5.01.3 allows remote attackers to connect arbitrary URL and launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Members privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11749 | AI Engine &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11749</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3 via the /mcp/v1/ REST API endpoint that exposes the 'Bearer Token' value when 'No-Auth URL' is enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract the bearer token, which can be used to gain access to a valid session and perform many actions like creating a new administrator account, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11162 | Spectra &amp;lt;= 2.19.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom CSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11162</link><description>The Spectra Gutenberg Blocks – Website Builder for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom CSS in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12197 | The Events Calendar 6.15.1.1 - 6.15.9 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via s</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12197</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the 's' parameter in versions 6.15.1.1 to 6.15.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11835 | Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Member Subscription Auto Renewal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11835</link><description>The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability and validation check on the PMS_AJAX_Checkout_Handler::process_payment() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger stored auto-renew charges for arbitrary members.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12580 | SMS for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12580</link><description>The SMS for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'paged' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12582 | Features &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Option Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12582</link><description>The Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'features_revert_option AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to revert options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8871 | Everest Forms (Pro) &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via PHAR Deserialization in Form Signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8871</link><description>The Everest Forms (Pro) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.7 via deserialization of untrusted input in the mime_content_type() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. This vulnerability may be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when a form is present on the site with a non-required signature form field along with an image upload field. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. This vulnerability is only exploitable in PHP versions prior to 8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12735 | CVE-2025-12735</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12735</link><description>The expr-eval library is a JavaScript expression parser and evaluator designed to safely evaluate mathematical expressions with user-defined variables. However, due to insufficient input validation, an attacker can pass a crafted variables object into the evaluate() function and trigger arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>