<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:57:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-43288 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able to bypass Priva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43288</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43309 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An attacker with physical access to an iOS de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43309</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An attacker with physical access to an iOS device may be able to view notification contents from the Lock Screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43322 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43322</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43323 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26, tvOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, watchOS 26. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43323</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26, tvOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, watchOS 26. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43334 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43334</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43335 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43335</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43336 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43336</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app with root privileges may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43338 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43338</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43345 | A correctness issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, macOS Sonoma 14.8, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43345</link><description>A correctness issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, macOS Sonoma 14.8, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, macOS Sequoia 15.7, visionOS 26, iOS 18.7 and iPadOS 18.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43348 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may bypass Ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43348</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may bypass Gatekeeper checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43350 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43350</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43360 | The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Password fields may be unintentionally revealed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43360</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Password fields may be unintentionally revealed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43361 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, macOS S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43361</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS 26. A malicious app may be able to read kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43364 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8, macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43364</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8, macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43365 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An unprivileged process...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43365</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An unprivileged process may be able to terminate a root processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43373 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43373</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43376 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, vis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43376</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, visionOS 26. A remote attacker may be able to view leaked DNS queries with Private Relay turned on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43377 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43377</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43378 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43378</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43379 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43379</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43380 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43380</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43382 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43382</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43383 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43383</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43384 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43384</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43385 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43385</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43386 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43386</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43387 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A malicious app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43387</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43389 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43389</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43390 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43390</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43391 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43391</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43392 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43392</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. A website may exfiltrate image data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43394 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43394</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43395 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43395</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43396 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A sandboxed app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43396</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A sandboxed app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43397 | A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43397</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43398 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43398</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43399 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43399</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43401 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43401</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43405 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43405</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43407 | This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43407</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43408 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43408</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An attacker with physical access may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43409 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43409</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43411 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43411</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43412 | A file quarantine bypass was addressed with additional checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43412</link><description>A file quarantine bypass was addressed with additional checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43413 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43413</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. A sandboxed app may be able to observe system-wide network connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43414 | A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A shortcut may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43414</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A shortcut may be able to access files that are normally inaccessible to the Shortcuts app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43419 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, visionOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43419</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, visionOS 26. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43420 | A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43420</link><description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43421 | Multiple issues were addressed by disabling array allocation sinking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43421</link><description>Multiple issues were addressed by disabling array allocation sinking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43422 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43422</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a device may be able to disable Stolen Device Protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43423 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43423</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to an unlocked device paired with a Mac may be able to view sensitive user information in system logging.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43424 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious HID device may cause an un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43424</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious HID device may cause an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43425 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43425</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43426 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to access se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43426</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43427 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43427</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43429 | A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43429</link><description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43430 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43430</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43431 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43431</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43432 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43432</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43433 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43433</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43434 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43434</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43435 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43435</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43436 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43436</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43438 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43438</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43439 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43439</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43440 | This issue was addressed with improved checks This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43440</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43441 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43441</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43442 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to ident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43442</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to identify what other apps a user has installed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43443 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43443</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43444 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43444</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43445 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43445</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43446 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43446</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43447 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43447</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43448 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43448</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43449 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious app may be able to tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43449</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious app may be able to track users between installs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43450 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to learn information a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43450</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to learn information about the current camera view before being granted camera access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43452 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. Keyboard sugges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43452</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. Keyboard suggestions may display sensitive information on the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43454 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A device may persistently fail ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43454</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A device may persistently fail to lock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43455 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. A maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43455</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. A malicious app may be able to take a screenshot of sensitive information in embedded views.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43457 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43457</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43458 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43458</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43459 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43459</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a locked Apple Watch may be able to view Live Voicemail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43460 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43460</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43462 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43462</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43468 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43468</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43469 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43469</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43472 | A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43472</link><description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43474 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43474</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or read kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43476 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43476</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43477 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43477</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43478 | A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43478</link><description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43479 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43479</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43480 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43480</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. A malicious website may exfiltrate data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43481 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43481</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43493 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Visiting a malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43493</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43495 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to monitor keystrokes with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43495</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to monitor keystrokes without user permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43496 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, vis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43496</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS 26.1. Remote content may be loaded even when the 'Load Remote Images' setting is turned off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43498 | An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43498</link><description>An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43499 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43499</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43500 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of user preferences. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, vis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43500</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of user preferences. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43502 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43502</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43503 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43503</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to user interface spoofing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43504 | A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. A user in a privileged network position ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43504</link><description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. A user in a privileged network position may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43505 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. Processing a maliciously craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43505</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43507 | A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43507</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35021 | Abilis CPX Fallback Shell Connection Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35021</link><description>By failing to authenticate three times to an unconfigured Abilis CPX device via SSH, an attacker can login to a restricted shell on the fourth attempt, and from there, relay connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46556 | MantisBT is Vulnerable to Denial-of-Service (DoS) attack via Excessive Note Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46556</link><description>Mantis Bug Tracker (MantisBT) is an open source issue tracker. Versions 2.27.1 and below allow attackers to permanently corrupt issue activity logs by submitting extremely long notes (tested with 4,788,761 characters) due to a lack of server-side validation of note length. Once such a note is added, the activity stream UI fails to render; therefore, new notes cannot be displayed, effectively breaking all future collaboration on the issue. This issue is fixed in version 2.27.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15054 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 5.4.0 XSS via jQuery Migrate Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15054</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to5.4.0 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) via the jQuery Migrate library. Insufficient validation or escaping of user-supplied input may allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary script in the context of a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47698 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 5.8.7 XSS in Core UI Views URL handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47698</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to5.8.7using embedded Nagios Core are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) viathe Core UIs Views URL handling. Insufficient validation or escaping of user-supplied input may allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary script in the context of a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13997 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 2024R1.1.3 Privilege Escalation via Migrate Server Feature to Root on Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13997</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to2024R1.1.3contain a privilege escalation vulnerability inwhich an authenticated administrator could leverage the Migrate Server feature to obtain root privileges on the underlying XI host. By abusing the migration workflow, an admin-level attacker could execute actions outside the intended security scope of the application, resulting in full control of the operating system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34501 | Shuffle Master Deck Mate 2 Hard-coded Credentials &amp;amp; Exposed Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34501</link><description>Deck Mate 2 is distributed with static, hard-coded credentials for the root shell and web user interface, while multiple management services (SSH, HTTP, Telnet, SMB, X11) are enabled by default. If an attacker can reach these interfaces - most often through local or near-local access such as connecting to the USB or Ethernet ports beneath the table - the built-in credentials permit administrative login and full control of the system. Once authenticated, an attacker can access firmware utilities, modify controller software, and establish persistent compromise. Remote attack paths via network, cellular, or telemetry links may exist in specific configurations but generally require additional capabilities or operator error. The vendor reports that USB access has been disabled in current firmware builds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13998 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 2024R1.1.3 API Keys &amp;amp; Hashed Passwords Authenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13998</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to2024R1.1.3, under certain circumstances, disclose sensitive user account information (including API keys and hashed passwords) to authenticated users who should not have access to that data. Exposure of API keys or password hashes could lead to account compromise, abuse of API privileges, or offline cracking attempts.CVE-2024-13995 addresses a similar vulnerability with a potentially incomplete fix for the underlying problem in earlier versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11193 | A potential vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Tablets that could allow a local authenticated user or application to gain access to s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11193</link><description>A potential vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Tablets that could allow a local authenticated user or application to gain access to sensitive device specific information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36172 | Multiple security vulnerabilities are addressed with IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation iFixes for 24.0.0-IF007, 24.0.1-IF005 and 25.0.0-IF002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36172</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 25.0.0 through 25.0.0 Interim Fix 001, 24.0.1 through 24.0.1 Interim Fix 004, 24.0.0 through 24.0.0 Interim Fix 006, and earlier unsupported releases IBM Business Automation Workflow is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12657 | Malformed KMIP response may result in access violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12657</link><description>The KMIP response parser built into mongo binaries is overly tolerant of certain malformed packets, and may parse them into invalid objects. Later reads of this object can result in read access violations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63293 | FairSketch Rise Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. A remote authenticated user can append comments ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63293</link><description>FairSketch Rise Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. A remote authenticated user can append comments or upload attachments to tickets for which they lack view or edit authorization, due to missing authorization checks in the ticketing/commenting API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50735 | Directory traversal vulnerability in NextChat thru 2.16.0 due to the WebDAV proxy failing to canonicalize or reject dot path segments in its...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50735</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in NextChat thru 2.16.0 due to the WebDAV proxy failing to canonicalize or reject dot path segments in its catch-all route, allowing attackers to gain sensitive information via authenticated or anonymous WebDAV endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12531 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server is affected by an XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12531</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7.0.0 through 11.7.1.6 is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12642 | HTTP Header Smuggling via Trailer Merge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12642</link><description>lighttpd1.4.80 incorrectly merged trailer fields into headersafter http request parsing. This behavior can be exploited to conduct HTTP Header Smuggling attacks.

Successful exploitation may allow an attacker to:

  *  Bypass access control rules
  *  Inject unsafe input into backend logic that trusts request headers
  *  Execute HTTP Request Smuggling attacks under some conditions


This issue affects lighttpd1.4.80</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63593 | Grav CMS1.7.49.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63593</link><description>Grav CMS1.7.49.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8558 | Insider Threat Management (ITM) Serverversions prior to 7.17.2contain an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8558</link><description>Insider Threat Management (ITM) Serverversions prior to 7.17.2contain an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated users on an adjacent network to perform agent unregistration when the number of registered agents exceeds the licensed limit. Successful exploitation prevents the server from receiving new events from affected agents, resulting in a partial loss of integrity and availability with no impact to confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12463 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection in Guetebruck G-Cam Series Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12463</link><description>An unauthenticated SQL Injection was discovered within the Geutebruck G-Cam E-Series Cameras through the `Group` parameter in the `/uapi-cgi/viewer/Param.cgi` script. This has been confirmed on the EFD-2130 camera running firmware version 1.12.0.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10280 | Incorrect Content Type Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10280</link><description>IdentityIQ
8.5, IdentityIQ 8.4 and all 8.4 patch levels prior to 8.4p4, IdentityIQ 8.3 and
all 8.3 patch levels prior to 8.3p6, and all prior versions allows some
IdentityIQ web services that provide non-HTML content to be accessed via a URL
path that will set the Content-Type to HTML allowing a requesting browser to
interpret content not properly escaped to prevent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11953 | Command injection in React Native CLI allows remote attackers to perform remote code execution by sending HTTP requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11953</link><description>The Metro Development Server, which is opened by the React Native CLI, binds to external interfaces by default. The server exposes an endpoint that is vulnerable to OS command injection. This allows unauthenticated network attackers to send a POST request to the server and run arbitrary executables. On Windows, the attackers can also execute arbitrary shell commands with fully controlled arguments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50363 | Phpgurukul Maid Hiring Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /maid-hiring.php va the name field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50363</link><description>Phpgurukul Maid Hiring Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /maid-hiring.php va the name field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63441 | Open Source Social Network (OSSN) 8.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the parameter param` at endpoint u/administrator/frien...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63441</link><description>Open Source Social Network (OSSN) 8.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the parameter param` at endpoint u/administrator/friends.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60785 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Postgres Drivers component of iceScrum v7.54 Pro On-prem allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60785</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Postgres Drivers component of iceScrum v7.54 Pro On-prem allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60503 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the administrative interface of ultimatefosters UltimatePOS 4.8 where input submitted i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60503</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the administrative interface of ultimatefosters UltimatePOS 4.8 where input submitted in the purchase functionality is reflected without proper escaping in the admin log panel page in the 'reference No.' field. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of an administrator's browser session, which could lead to session hijacking or other malicious actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36093 | security vulnerabilities are addressed with IBM Business Automation Insights iFixes for October 2025.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36093</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak For Business Automation 25.0.0, 24.0.1, and 24.0.0 could allow an attacker to access unauthorized content or perform unauthorized actions using man in the middle techniques due to improper access controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63453 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/contact.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63453</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/contact.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63452 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/forgot-pass.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63452</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/forgot-pass.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63450 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /carlux/booking.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63450</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /carlux/booking.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63451 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/sign-in.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63451</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/sign-in.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63449 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /orders.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63449</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /orders.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11761 | HP Client Management Script Library  Security Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11761</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Client Management Script Library software, which might allow escalation of privilege during the installation process. HP is releasing software updates to mitigate the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36091 | IBM Business Automation Insights unverified ownership</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36091</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak For Business Automation 25.0.0, 24.0.1, and 24.0.0 could allow an authenticated user to cause dashboards to become inaccessible to legitimate users due to invalid ownership assignment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36092 | IBM Business Automation Insights improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36092</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak For Business Automation 25.0.0, 24.0.1, and 24.0.0 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to the improper validation of input length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63446 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_vendor.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63446</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_vendor.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63447 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_customer.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63447</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_customer.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63448 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit_product.php?id=1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63448</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit_product.php?id=1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63442 | Simple User Management System with PHP-MySQL v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the Profile Section. The system fails to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63442</link><description>Simple User Management System with PHP-MySQL v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the Profile Section. The system fails to properly sanitize user input, allowing attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript when the input is displayed in the browser</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63443 | School Management System PHP v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php via the password parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63443</link><description>School Management System PHP v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php via the password parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45663 | An issue in NetSurf v3.11 causes the application to read uninitialized heap memory when creating a dom_event structure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45663</link><description>An issue in NetSurf v3.11 causes the application to read uninitialized heap memory when creating a dom_event structure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51317 | An issue in NetSurf v.3.11 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dom_node_normalize function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51317</link><description>An issue in NetSurf v.3.11 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dom_node_normalize function</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29699 | NetSurf 3.11 is vulnerable to Use After Free in dom_node_set_text_content function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29699</link><description>NetSurf 3.11 is vulnerable to Use After Free in dom_node_set_text_content function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60892 | An issue in Raspberry Pi Imager version 1.9.6 for Windows, affecting its OS customization feature. The imager's 'public-key authentication' ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60892</link><description>An issue in Raspberry Pi Imager version 1.9.6 for Windows, affecting its OS customization feature. The imager's 'public-key authentication' setting unintentionally re-adds a user's id_rsa.pub key from their local Windows machine to the authorized_keys file on the Raspberry Pi, even after the user explicitly deletes the key from the user interface. This creates an unintended attack surface, as it could allow an attacker to use a different key than the intended one to login to the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8900 | Doccure Core &amp;lt; 1.5.4 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8900</link><description>The Doccure Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and excluding, 1.5.4. This is due to the plugin allowing users who are registering new accounts to set their own role or by supplying 'user_type' field. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain elevated privileges by creating an account with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64294 | WordPress WP Snow Effect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.15 - Broken Access Control to Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64294</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in d3wp WP Snow Effect allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Snow Effect: from n/a through 1.1.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12626 | jeecgboot jeewx-boot WxActGoldeneggsPrizesController.java getImgUrl path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12626</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in jeecgboot jeewx-boot up to 641ab52c3e1845fec39996d7794c33fb40dad1dd. This affects the function getImgUrl of the file WxActGoldeneggsPrizesController.java. Performing manipulation of the argument imgurl results in path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The root cause was initially fixed but can be evaded with additional encoding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40107 | can: hi311x: fix null pointer dereference when resuming from sleep before interface was enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40107</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: hi311x: fix null pointer dereference when resuming from sleep before interface was enabled

This issue is similar to the vulnerability in the `mcp251x` driver,
which was fixed in commit 03c427147b2d ("can: mcp251x: fix resume from
sleep before interface was brought up").

In the `hi311x` driver, when the device resumes from sleep, the driver
schedules `priv-&gt;restart_work`. However, if the network interface was
not previously enabled, the `priv-&gt;wq` (workqueue) is not allocated and
initialized, leading to a null pointer dereference.

To fix this, we move the allocation and initialization of the workqueue
from the `hi3110_open` function to the `hi3110_can_probe` function.
This ensures that the workqueue is properly initialized before it is
used during device resume. And added logic to destroy the workqueue
in the error handling paths of `hi3110_can_probe` and in the
`hi3110_can_remove` function to prevent resource leaks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0987 | IDOR in CB Project&amp;#x27;s CVLand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0987</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in CB Project Ltd. Co. CVLand allows Parameter Injection.This issue affects CVLand: from 2.1.0 through 20251103.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48397 | The privileged user could log in without sufficient credentials after enabling an application protocol.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48397</link><description>The privileged user could log in without sufficient credentials after enabling an application protocol.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12623 | fushengqian fuint Authentication Token ClientSignController.java authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12623</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in fushengqian fuint up to 41e26be8a2c609413a0feaa69bdad33a71ae8032. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file fuint-application/src/main/java/com/fuint/module/clientApi/controller/ClientSignController.java of the component Authentication Token Handler. Such manipulation leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be launched remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48396 | Arbitrary code executionis possible due to improper validation of the file upload functionality in Eaton BLSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48396</link><description>Arbitrary code executionis possible due to improper validation of the file upload functionality in Eaton BLSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12622 | Tenda AC10 SysRunCmd formSysRunCmd buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12622</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSysRunCmd of the file /goform/SysRunCmd. This manipulation of the argument getui causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12619 | Tenda A15 openNetworkGateway fromSetWirelessRepeat buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12619</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. Affected is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat of the file /goform/openNetworkGateway. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto2_4g results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 07:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12503 | DigiwinEasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12503</link><description>EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet developed by Digiwin has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12618 | Tenda AC8 DatabaseIniSet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12618</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/DatabaseIniSet. The manipulation of the argument Time leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12617 | itsourcecode Billing System login_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12617</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/app/login_crud.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Password can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12616 | PHPGurukul News Portal settings.py insertion of sensitive information into debugging code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12616</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /onps/settings.py. Performing manipulation results in insertion of sensitive information into debugging code. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12615 | PHPGurukul News Portal settings.py hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12615</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /onps/settings.py. Such manipulation of the argument SECRET_KEY leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack may be performed from remote. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12614 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php delete_payment sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12614</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Impacted is the function delete_payment of the file /admin_class.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12611 | Tenda AC21 SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12611</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This vulnerability affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument startIp leads to buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12612 | Campcodes School Fees Payment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12612</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes School Fees Payment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12610 | CodeAstro Gym Management System view-progress-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12610</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-progress-report.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12609 | CodeAstro Gym Management System update-progress.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12609</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-progress.php. Performing manipulation of the argument id/ini_weight results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12608 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12608</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /manage_user.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12607 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12607</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /manage_payment.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12606 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_borrower.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12606</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /manage_borrower.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12605 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_loan.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12605</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_loan.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12604 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System load_fields.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12604</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /load_fields.php. The manipulation of the argument loan_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12598 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php save_tenant sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12598</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function save_tenant of the file /admin_class.php. Executing manipulation of the argument firstname can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 12:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12597 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php save_category sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12597</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_category of the file /admin_class.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12596 | Tenda AC23 saveParentControlInfo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12596</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. Affected is the function saveParentControlInfo of the file /goform/saveParentControlInfo. Such manipulation of the argument Time leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12595 | Tenda AC23 SetVirtualServerCfg formSetVirtualSer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12595</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This impacts the function formSetVirtualSer of the file /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This manipulation of the argument list causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12594 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System add_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12594</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 2.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 08:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12593 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System Photo edit_room.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12593</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 2.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_room.php of the component Photo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>