<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:28:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-28741 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in EginDemirbilek NorthStar C2 v1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28741</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in EginDemirbilek NorthStar C2 v1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27620 | An issue in Ladder v.0.0.1 thru v.0.0.21 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27620</link><description>An issue in Ladder v.0.0.1 thru v.0.0.21 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the API.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0406 | Mholt/archiver: path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0406</link><description>A flaw was discovered in the mholt/archiver package. This flaw allows an attacker to create a specially crafted tar file, which, when unpacked, may allow access to restricted files or directories. This issue can allow the creation or overwriting of files with the user's or application's privileges using the library.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3156 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3156</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3158 | Use after free in Bookmarks in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3158</link><description>Use after free in Bookmarks in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3159 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3159</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3378 | iboss Secure Web Gateway Login Portal login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3378</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in iboss Secure Web Gateway up to 10.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login of the component Login Portal. The manipulation of the argument redirectUrl leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 10.2.0.160 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-259501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3377 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3377</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/SystemSettings.php?f=update_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259498 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24746 | Apache NimBLE: Denial of service in NimBLE Bluetooth stack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24746</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache NimBLE. 

Specially crafted GATT operation can cause infinite loop in GATT server leading to denial of service in Bluetooth stack or device.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.6.0.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25029 | IBM Personal Communications code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25029</link><description>IBM Personal Communications 14.0.6 through 15.0.1 includes a Windows service that is vulnerable to remote code execution (RCE) and local privilege escalation (LPE). The vulnerability allows any unprivileged user with network access to a target computer to run commands with full privileges in the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. This allows for a low privileged attacker to move laterally to affected systems and to escalate their privileges.  IBM X-Force ID:  281619.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22328 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22328</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10 and 8.11 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  279950.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3376 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System config.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3376</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file config.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259497 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3369 | code-projects Car Rental add-vehicle.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3369</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Car Rental 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument Upload Image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3366 | Xuxueli xxl-job Template JdkSerializeTool.java deserialize injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3366</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Xuxueli xxl-job up to 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects the function deserialize of the file com/xxl/job/core/util/JdkSerializeTool.java of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259480.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 10:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3365 | SourceCodester Online Library System controller.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/users/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259469 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3364 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3364</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/books/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259468.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2132 | The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Widget in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2132</link><description>The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2296 | The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2296</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3363 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3363</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/borrowed/index.php. The manipulation of the argument BookPublisher/BookTitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259467.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0837 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0837</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the image URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1428 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1428</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘element_pack_wrapper_link’ attribute of the Trailer Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2458 | The Powerkit – Supercharge your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2458</link><description>The Powerkit – Supercharge your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2949 | The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel – Image Carousel &amp; Photo Gallery, Post Carousel &amp; Post Grid, Product Carousel &amp; Product Grid fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2949</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel – Image Carousel &amp; Photo Gallery, Post Carousel &amp; Post Grid, Product Carousel &amp; Product Grid for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3362 | SourceCodester Online Library System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3362</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/books/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument IBSN leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259466 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 06:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2471 | The FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image attachment fields (such as 'Title', 'Alt Text', '...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2471</link><description>The FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image attachment fields (such as 'Title', 'Alt Text', 'Custom URL', 'Custom Class', and 'Override Type') in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3361 | SourceCodester Online Library System deweydecimal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3361</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/books/deweydecimal.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259465 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21506 | Versions of the package pymongo before 4.6.3 are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read in the bson module. Using the crafted payload the attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21506</link><description>Versions of the package pymongo before 4.6.3 are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read in the bson module. Using the crafted payload the attacker could force the parser to deserialize unmanaged memory. The parser tries to interpret bytes next to buffer and throws an exception with string. If the following bytes are not printable UTF-8 the parser throws an exception with a single byte.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2444 | Inline Related Posts &amp;lt; 3.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2444</link><description>The Inline Related Posts WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3360 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3360</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/books/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259464.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3359 | SourceCodester Online Library System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3359</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259463.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3358 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3358</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument to leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259462 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1385 | The WP-Stateless – Google Cloud Storage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1385</link><description>The WP-Stateless – Google Cloud Storage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the dismiss_notices() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary option values to the current time, which may completely take a site offline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2656 | The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2656</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a CSV import in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2950 | The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2950</link><description>The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.14 via meta information (og:description) This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the first 130 characters of a password protected post which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3216 | The WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modificat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3216</link><description>The WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wt_pklist_reset_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset all of the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3245 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3245</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Youtube block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1994 | The Image Watermark plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the waterma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1994</link><description>The Image Watermark plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the watermark_action_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to apply and remove watermarks from images.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3357 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3357</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/mod_reports/index.php. The manipulation of the argument end leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259461 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3356 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/mod_settings/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument type leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259460.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30977 | An issue in Secnet Security Network Intelligent AC Management System v.1.02.040 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the passw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30977</link><description>An issue in Secnet Security Network Intelligent AC Management System v.1.02.040 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the password component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25493 | A potential vulnerability was reported in the BIOS update tool driver for some Desktop, Smart Edge, Smart Office, and ThinkStation products ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25493</link><description>A potential vulnerability was reported in the BIOS update tool driver for some Desktop, Smart Edge, Smart Office, and ThinkStation products that could allow a local user with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25494 | A potential vulnerability were reported in the BIOS of some Desktop, Smart Edge, and ThinkStation products that could allow a local attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25494</link><description>A potential vulnerability were reported in the BIOS of some Desktop, Smart Edge, and ThinkStation products that could allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to write to NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4605 | A valid authenticated Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) user can potentially leverage an unauthenticated API endpoint to retrieve system ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4605</link><description>A valid authenticated Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) user can potentially leverage an unauthenticated API endpoint to retrieve system event information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5912 | A potential memory leakage vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Notebook products that may allow a local attacker with elevated privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5912</link><description>A potential memory leakage vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Notebook products that may allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to write to NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23592 | An authentication bypass vulnerability was reported in Lenovo devices with Synaptics fingerprint readers that could allow an attacker with p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23592</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was reported in Lenovo devices with Synaptics fingerprint readers that could allow an attacker with physical access to replay fingerprints and bypass Windows Hello authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27908 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27908</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27909 | A denial of service vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in a system reboot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27909</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in a system reboot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27910 | A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to reboot the printer without authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27910</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to reboot the printer without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27911 | A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the administrator password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27911</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the administrator password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27912 | A denial of service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an attacker to cause the device to crash by sending ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27912</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an attacker to cause the device to crash by sending crafted LPD packets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3355 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/mod_users/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259459.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27231 | In tmu_get_tr_stats of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27231</link><description>In tmu_get_tr_stats of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27232 | In asn1_ec_pkey_parse of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27232</link><description>In asn1_ec_pkey_parse of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29738 | In gov_init, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29738</link><description>In gov_init, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29739 | In tmu_get_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29739</link><description>In tmu_get_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29740 | In tmu_set_table of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29740</link><description>In tmu_set_table of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29741 | In pblS2mpuResume of s2mpu.c, there is a possible mitigation bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29741</link><description>In pblS2mpuResume of s2mpu.c, there is a possible mitigation bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29742 | In apply_minlock_constraint of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29742</link><description>In apply_minlock_constraint of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29743 | In tmu_set_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29743</link><description>In tmu_set_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29744 | In tmu_get_gov_time_windows, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29744</link><description>In tmu_get_gov_time_windows, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29745 | there is a possible Information Disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29745</link><description>there is a possible Information Disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29746 | In lpm_req_handler of lpm.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29746</link><description>In lpm_req_handler of lpm.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29747 | In _dvfs_get_lv of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29747</link><description>In _dvfs_get_lv of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29748 | there is a possible way to bypass  due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29748</link><description>there is a possible way to bypass  due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29749 | In tmu_set_tr_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29749</link><description>In tmu_set_tr_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29750 | In km_exp_did_inner of kmv.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29750</link><description>In km_exp_did_inner of kmv.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29751 | In asn1_ec_pkey_parse_p384 of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB Read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29751</link><description>In asn1_ec_pkey_parse_p384 of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB Read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29752 | In tmu_set_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29752</link><description>In tmu_set_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29753 | In tmu_set_control_temp_step of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29753</link><description>In tmu_set_control_temp_step of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29754 | In TMU_IPC_GET_TABLE, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29754</link><description>In TMU_IPC_GET_TABLE, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29755 | In tmu_get_pi of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29755</link><description>In tmu_get_pi of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29756 | In afe_callback of q6afe.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29756</link><description>In afe_callback of q6afe.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29757 | there is a possible permission bypass due to Debug certs being allowlisted. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29757</link><description>there is a possible permission bypass due to Debug certs being allowlisted. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29782 | In tmu_get_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29782</link><description>In tmu_get_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29783 | In tmu_get_tr_thresholds, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29783</link><description>In tmu_get_tr_thresholds, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3354 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3354</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/mod_users/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2312 | GRUB2 does not call the module fini functions on exit, leading to Debian/Ubuntu's peimage GRUB2 module leaving UEFI system table hooks after...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2312</link><description>GRUB2 does not call the module fini functions on exit, leading to Debian/Ubuntu's peimage GRUB2 module leaving UEFI system table hooks after exit. This lead to a use-after-free condition, and could possibly lead to secure boot bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3353 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3353</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/mod_reports/index.php. The manipulation of the argument categ/end leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259457 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3352 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3352</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/mod_comments/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259456.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0081 | NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0081</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without limits or throttling. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a server-side denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22004 | Unchecked length in Trusted Application on Google Nest Wifi Pro, leading to out of bounds read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22004</link><description>Due to length check, an attacker with privilege access on a Linux Nonsecure operating system can trigger a vulnerability and leak the secure memory from the Trusted Application</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3351 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3351</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/mod_roomtype/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259455.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28065 | In Unify CP IP Phone firmware 1.10.4.3, files are not encrypted and contain sensitive information such as the root password hash.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28065</link><description>In Unify CP IP Phone firmware 1.10.4.3, files are not encrypted and contain sensitive information such as the root password hash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0076 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0076</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0080 | NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0080</link><description>NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31028 | NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31028</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0072 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0072</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31851 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Sync &lt; 23.4.8843 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31851</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Sync &lt; 23.4.8843 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information and perform limited actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31848 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData API Server &lt; 23.4.8844 when running using the embedded Jetty server, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31848</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData API Server &lt; 23.4.8844 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain complete administrative access to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31849 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Connect &lt; 23.4.8846 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31849</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Connect &lt; 23.4.8846 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain complete administrative access to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31850 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Arc &lt; 23.4.8839 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31850</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Arc &lt; 23.4.8839 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information and perform limited actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3350 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3350</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/mod_room/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3349 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3349</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259453 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3348 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3348</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file booking/index.php. The manipulation of the argument log_email/log_pword leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259452.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3347 | SourceCodester Airline Ticket Reservation System activate_jet_details_form_handler.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Airline Ticket Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file activate_jet_details_form_handler.php. The manipulation of the argument jet_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259451.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3346 | Byzro Smart S80 webmailattach.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3346</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Byzro Smart S80 up to 20240328. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /log/webmailattach.php. The manipulation of the argument mail_file_path leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48426 | Chromecast Bootloader &amp;amp; Kernel-level code-execution including compromise of user-data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48426</link><description>u-boot bug that allows for u-boot shell and interrupt over UART</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31220 | Sunshine vulnerable to remote unauthenticated arbitrary file read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31220</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Starting in version 0.16.0 and prior to version 0.18.0, an attacker may be able to remotely read arbitrary files without authentication due to a path traversal vulnerability. Users who exposed the Sunshine configuration web user interface outside of localhost may be affected, depending on firewall configuration. To exploit vulnerability, attacker could make an http/s request to the `node_modules` endpoint if user exposed Sunshine config web server to internet or attacker is on the LAN. Version 0.18.0 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, one may block access to Sunshine via firewall.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31213 | InstantCMS Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31213</link><description>InstantCMS is a free and open source content management system. An open redirect was found in the ICMS2 application version 2.16.2 when being redirected after modifying one's own user profile. An attacker could trick a victim into visiting their web application, thinking they are still present on the ICMS2 application. They could then host a website stating "To update your profile, please enter your password," upon which the user may type their password and send it to the attacker. As of time of publication, a patched version is not available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31218 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Webhood backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31218</link><description>Webhood is a self-hosted URL scanner used analyzing phishing and malicious sites. Webhood's backend container images in versions 0.9.0 and earlier are subject to Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to send a HTTP request to the database (Pocketbase) admin API to create an admin account. The Pocketbase admin API does not check for authentication/authorization when creating an admin account when no admin accounts have been added. In its default deployment, Webhood does not create a database admin account. Therefore, unless users have manually created an admin account in the database, an admin account will not exist in the deployment and the deployment is vulnerable. Versions starting from 0.9.1 are patched. The patch creates a randomly generated admin account if admin accounts have not already been created i.e. the vulnerability is exploitable in the deployment. As a workaround, users can disable access to URL path starting with `/api/admins` entirely. With this workaround, the vulnerability is not exploitable via network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31852 | LLVM before 18.1.3 generates code in which the LR register can be overwritten without data being saved to the stack, and thus there can some...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31852</link><description>LLVM before 18.1.3 generates code in which the LR register can be overwritten without data being saved to the stack, and thus there can sometimes be an exploitable error in the flow of control. This affects the ARM backend and can be demonstrated with Clang. NOTE: the vendor perspective is "we don't have strong objections for a CVE to be created ... It does seem that the likelihood of this miscompile enabling an exploit remains very low, because the miscompile resulting in this JOP gadget is such that the function is most likely to crash on most valid inputs to the function. So, if this function is covered by any testing, the miscompile is most likely to be discovered before the binary is shipped to production."</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49965 | SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router Gen 2 before 2023.48.0 allows XSS via the ssid and password parameters on the Setup Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49965</link><description>SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router Gen 2 before 2023.48.0 allows XSS via the ssid and password parameters on the Setup Page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2380 | XSS in graph rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2380</link><description>Stored XSS in graph rendering in Checkmk &lt;2.3.0b4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5692 | WordPress Core is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including,  6.4.3 via the redirect_guess_404_permalink...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5692</link><description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including,  6.4.3 via the redirect_guess_404_permalink function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to expose the slug of a custom post whose 'publicly_queryable' post status has been set to 'false'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2499 | The Squelch Tabs and Accordions Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'accordions' s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2499</link><description>The Squelch Tabs and Accordions Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'accordions' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31083 | Xorg-x11-server: user-after-free in procrenderaddglyphs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31083</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6522 | Information Disclosure in ExtremePacs&amp;#x27;s Extreme XDS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6522</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ExtremePacs Extreme XDS allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects Extreme XDS: before 3914.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6523 | IDOR in ExtremePacs&amp;#x27;s Extreme XDS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6523</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ExtremePacs Extreme XDS allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Extreme XDS: before 3914.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2447 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.11, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, and 9.5.x before 9.5.2 fail to authenticate the source of c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2447</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.11, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, and 9.5.x before 9.5.2 fail to authenticate the source of certain types of post actions, allowing an authenticated attacker to create posts as other users via a crafted post action.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 09:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26810 | vfio/pci: Lock external INTx masking ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26810</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/pci: Lock external INTx masking ops

Mask operations through config space changes to DisINTx may race INTx
configuration changes via ioctl.  Create wrappers that add locking for
paths outside of the core interrupt code.

In particular, irq_type is updated holding igate, therefore testing
is_intx() requires holding igate.  For example clearing DisINTx from
config space can otherwise race changes of the interrupt configuration.

This aligns interfaces which may trigger the INTx eventfd into two
camps, one side serialized by igate and the other only enabled while
INTx is configured.  A subsequent patch introduces synchronization for
the latter flows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26812 | vfio/pci: Create persistent INTx handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26812</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/pci: Create persistent INTx handler

A vulnerability exists where the eventfd for INTx signaling can be
deconfigured, which unregisters the IRQ handler but still allows
eventfds to be signaled with a NULL context through the SET_IRQS ioctl
or through unmask irqfd if the device interrupt is pending.

Ideally this could be solved with some additional locking; the igate
mutex serializes the ioctl and config space accesses, and the interrupt
handler is unregistered relative to the trigger, but the irqfd path
runs asynchronous to those.  The igate mutex cannot be acquired from the
atomic context of the eventfd wake function.  Disabling the irqfd
relative to the eventfd registration is potentially incompatible with
existing userspace.

As a result, the solution implemented here moves configuration of the
INTx interrupt handler to track the lifetime of the INTx context object
and irq_type configuration, rather than registration of a particular
trigger eventfd.  Synchronization is added between the ioctl path and
eventfd_signal() wrapper such that the eventfd trigger can be
dynamically updated relative to in-flight interrupts or irqfd callbacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26813 | vfio/platform: Create persistent IRQ handlers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26813</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/platform: Create persistent IRQ handlers

The vfio-platform SET_IRQS ioctl currently allows loopback triggering of
an interrupt before a signaling eventfd has been configured by the user,
which thereby allows a NULL pointer dereference.

Rather than register the IRQ relative to a valid trigger, register all
IRQs in a disabled state in the device open path.  This allows mask
operations on the IRQ to nest within the overall enable state governed
by a valid eventfd signal.  This decouples @masked, protected by the
@locked spinlock from @trigger, protected via the @igate mutex.

In doing so, it's guaranteed that changes to @trigger cannot race the
IRQ handlers because the IRQ handler is synchronously disabled before
modifying the trigger, and loopback triggering of the IRQ via ioctl is
safe due to serialization with trigger changes via igate.

For compatibility, request_irq() failures are maintained to be local to
the SET_IRQS ioctl rather than a fatal error in the open device path.
This allows, for example, a userspace driver with polling mode support
to continue to work regardless of moving the request_irq() call site.
This necessarily blocks all SET_IRQS access to the failed index.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26814 | vfio/fsl-mc: Block calling interrupt handler without trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26814</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/fsl-mc: Block calling interrupt handler without trigger

The eventfd_ctx trigger pointer of the vfio_fsl_mc_irq object is
initially NULL and may become NULL if the user sets the trigger
eventfd to -1.  The interrupt handler itself is guaranteed that
trigger is always valid between request_irq() and free_irq(), but
the loopback testing mechanisms to invoke the handler function
need to test the trigger.  The triggering and setting ioctl paths
both make use of igate and are therefore mutually exclusive.

The vfio-fsl-mc driver does not make use of irqfds, nor does it
support any sort of masking operations, therefore unlike vfio-pci
and vfio-platform, the flow can remain essentially unchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27437 | vfio/pci: Disable auto-enable of exclusive INTx IRQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27437</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/pci: Disable auto-enable of exclusive INTx IRQ

Currently for devices requiring masking at the irqchip for INTx, ie.
devices without DisINTx support, the IRQ is enabled in request_irq()
and subsequently disabled as necessary to align with the masked status
flag.  This presents a window where the interrupt could fire between
these events, resulting in the IRQ incrementing the disable depth twice.
This would be unrecoverable for a user since the masked flag prevents
nested enables through vfio.

Instead, invert the logic using IRQF_NO_AUTOEN such that exclusive INTx
is never auto-enabled, then unmask as required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21848 | Users maintain access to active call after being removed from a channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21848</link><description>Improper Access Control in Mattermost Server versions 8.1.x before 8.1.11 allows an attacker that is in a channel with an active call to keep participating in the call even if they are removed from the channel</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28949 | DoS via a large number of User Preferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28949</link><description>Mattermost Server versions 9.5.x before 9.5.2, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 8.1.x before 8.1.11 don't limit the number of user preferences which allows an attacker to send a large number of user preferences potentially causing denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29221 | Invite ID available to team admins even without the &amp;quot;Add Members&amp;quot; permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29221</link><description>Improper Access Control in Mattermost Server versions 9.5.x before 9.5.2, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 8.1.x before 8.1.11 lacked proper access control in the `/api/v4/users/me/teams` endpoint allowing a team admin to get the invite ID of their team, thus allowing them to invite users, even if the "Add Members" permission was explicitly removed from team admins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30849 | Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Sourcecodester Complete E-Commerce Site v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30849</link><description>Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Sourcecodester Complete E-Commerce Site v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via filename parameter in admin/products_photo.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2115 | The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2115</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the filter_users functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of a teacher via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3217 | The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value' and 'attribute_id' parameters in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3217</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value' and 'attribute_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30891 | A command injection vulnerability exists in /goform/exeCommand in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05, which allows attackers to construct cmdinput para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30891</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in /goform/exeCommand in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05, which allows attackers to construct cmdinput parameters for arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26329 | Chilkat before v9.5.0.98, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via predictable PRNG in ChilkatRand::randomBytes function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26329</link><description>Chilkat before v9.5.0.98, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via predictable PRNG in ChilkatRand::randomBytes function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29863 | A race condition in the installer executable in Qlik Qlikview before versions May 2022 SR3 (12.70.20300) and May 2023 SR2 (12,80.20200) may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29863</link><description>A race condition in the installer executable in Qlik Qlikview before versions May 2022 SR3 (12.70.20300) and May 2023 SR2 (12,80.20200) may allow an existing lower privileged user to cause code to be executed in the context of a Windows Administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 06:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52235 | SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router GEN 2 before 2023.53.0 and Starlink Dish before 07dd2798-ff15-4722-a9ee-de28928aed34 allow CSRF (e.g., for a re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52235</link><description>SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router GEN 2 before 2023.53.0 and Starlink Dish before 07dd2798-ff15-4722-a9ee-de28928aed34 allow CSRF (e.g., for a reboot) via a DNS Rebinding attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 06:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27448 | MailDev 2 through 2.1.0 allows Remote Code Execution via a crafted Content-ID header for an e-mail attachment, leading to lib/mailserver.js ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27448</link><description>MailDev 2 through 2.1.0 allows Remote Code Execution via a crafted Content-ID header for an e-mail attachment, leading to lib/mailserver.js writing arbitrary code into the routes.js file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 06:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29672 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in zly2006 Reden before v.0.2.514 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DEBUG_RTC_REQ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29672</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in zly2006 Reden before v.0.2.514 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DEBUG_RTC_REQUEST_SYNC_DATA in KeyCallbacks.kt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 05:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22363 | SheetJS Community Edition before 0.20.2 is vulnerable.to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22363</link><description>SheetJS Community Edition before 0.20.2 is vulnerable.to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2509 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt; 3.2.26 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2509</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.2.26 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 05:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5973 | Truncated port name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5973</link><description>Brocade
 Web Interface in Brocade Fabric OS v9.x and before v9.2.0 does not 
properly represent the portName to the user if the portName contains 
reserved characters. This could allow an authenticated user to alter the
 UI of the Brocade Switch and change ports display.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 02:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3321 | SourceCodester eLearning System Maintenance Module cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3321</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester eLearning System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Maintenance Module. The manipulation of the argument Subject Code/Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259389 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3320 | SourceCodester eLearning System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3320</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester eLearning System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259388.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31210 | PHP file upload bypass via Plugin installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31210</link><description>WordPress is an open publishing platform for the Web. It's possible for a file of a type other than a zip file to be submitted as a new plugin by an administrative user on the Plugins -&gt; Add New -&gt; Upload Plugin screen in WordPress. If FTP credentials are requested for installation (in order to move the file into place outside of the `uploads` directory) then the uploaded file remains temporary available in the Media Library despite it not being allowed. If the `DISALLOW_FILE_EDIT` constant is set to `true` on the site _and_ FTP credentials are required when uploading a new theme or plugin, then this technically allows an RCE when the user would otherwise have no means of executing arbitrary PHP code. This issue _only_ affects Administrator level users on single site installations, and Super Admin level users on Multisite installations where it's otherwise expected that the user does not have permission to upload or execute arbitrary PHP code. Lower level users are not affected. Sites where the `DISALLOW_FILE_MODS` constant is set to `true` are not affected. Sites where an administrative user either does not need to enter FTP credentials or they have access to the valid FTP credentials, are not affected. The issue was fixed in WordPress 6.4.3 on January 30, 2024 and backported to versions 6.3.3, 6.2.4, 6.1.5, 6.0.7, 5.9.9, 5.8.9, 5.7.11, 5.6.13, 5.5.14, 5.4.15, 5.3.17, 5.2.20, 5.1.18, 5.0.21, 4.9.25, 2.8.24, 4.7.28, 4.6.28, 4.5.31, 4.4.32, 4.3.33, 4.2.37, and 4.1.40. A workaround is available. If the `DISALLOW_FILE_MODS` constant is defined as `true` then it will not be possible for any user to upload a plugin and therefore this issue will not be exploitable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 23:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31211 | Remote Code Execution in `WP_HTML_Token`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31211</link><description>WordPress is an open publishing platform for the Web. Unserialization of instances of the `WP_HTML_Token` class allows for code execution via its `__destruct()` magic method. This issue was fixed in WordPress 6.4.2 on December 6th, 2023. Versions prior to 6.4.0 are not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 23:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31212 | SQL injection in index_chart_data action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31212</link><description>InstantCMS is a free and open source content management system. A SQL injection vulnerability affects instantcms v2.16.2 in which an attacker with administrative privileges can cause the application to execute unauthorized SQL code. The vulnerability exists in index_chart_data action, which receives an input from user and passes it unsanitized to the core model `filterFunc` function that further embeds this data in an SQL statement. This allows attackers to inject unwanted SQL code into the statement. The `period` should be escaped before inserting it in the query. As of time of publication, a patched version is not available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 23:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21894 | A heap overflow vulnerability in IPSec component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthenticated mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21894</link><description>A heap overflow vulnerability in IPSec component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthenticated malicious user to send specially crafted requests in-order-to crash the service thereby causing a DoS attack. In certain conditions this may lead to execution of arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27981 | A Command Injection vulnerability found in a Self-Hosted UniFi Network Servers (Linux) with UniFi Network Application (Version 8.0.28 and ea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27981</link><description>A Command Injection vulnerability found in a Self-Hosted UniFi Network Servers (Linux) with UniFi Network Application (Version 8.0.28 and earlier) allows a malicious actor with UniFi Network Application Administrator credentials to escalate privileges to root on the host device.&#13;
&#13;
Affected Products:&#13;
UniFi Network Application (Version 8.0.28 and earlier) .&#13;
 &#13;
Mitigation:&#13;
Update UniFi Network Application to Version 8.1.113 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31498 | ykman-gui (aka YubiKey Manager GUI) before 1.2.6 on Windows, when Edge is not used, allows privilege escalation because browser windows can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31498</link><description>ykman-gui (aka YubiKey Manager GUI) before 1.2.6 on Windows, when Edge is not used, allows privilege escalation because browser windows can open as Administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31206 | Use of Unencrypted HTTP Request in dectalk-tts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31206</link><description>dectalk-tts is a Node package to interact with the aeiou Dectalk web API. In `dectalk-tts@1.0.0`, network requests to the third-party API are sent over HTTP, which is unencrypted. Unencrypted traffic can be easily intercepted and modified by attackers. Anyone who uses the package could be the victim of a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack. The network request was upgraded to HTTPS in version `1.0.1`. There are no workarounds, but some precautions include not sending any sensitive information and carefully verifying the API response before saving it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29049 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Webview2 Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29049</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29981 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29981</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3316 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System view_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3316</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/category/view_category.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259387.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3314 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3314</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Users.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-259385 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3315 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3315</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file classes/user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45288 | HTTP/2 CONTINUATION flood in net/http</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45288</link><description>An attacker may cause an HTTP/2 endpoint to read arbitrary amounts of header data by sending an excessive number of CONTINUATION frames. Maintaining HPACK state requires parsing and processing all HEADERS and CONTINUATION frames on a connection. When a request's headers exceed MaxHeaderBytes, no memory is allocated to store the excess headers, but they are still parsed. This permits an attacker to cause an HTTP/2 endpoint to read arbitrary amounts of header data, all associated with a request which is going to be rejected. These headers can include Huffman-encoded data which is significantly more expensive for the receiver to decode than for an attacker to send. The fix sets a limit on the amount of excess header frames we will process before closing a connection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31204 | mailcow Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability via Exception Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31204</link><description>mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. A security vulnerability has been identified in mailcow affecting versions prior to 2024-04. This vulnerability resides in the exception handling mechanism, specifically when not operating in DEV_MODE. The system saves exception details into a session array without proper sanitization or encoding. These details are later rendered into HTML and executed in a JavaScript block within the user's browser, without adequate escaping of HTML entities. This flaw allows for Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks, where attackers can inject malicious scripts into the admin panel by triggering exceptions with controlled input. The exploitation method involves using any function that might throw an exception with user-controllable argument. This issue can lead to session hijacking and unauthorized administrative actions, posing a significant security risk. Version 2024-04 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3311 | Dreamer CMS ThemesController.java ZipUtils.unZipFiles path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3311</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dreamer CMS up to 4.1.3.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ZipUtils.unZipFiles of the file controller/admin/ThemesController.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-259369 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30270 | mailcow Path Traversal and Arbitrary Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30270</link><description>mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. A security vulnerability has been identified in mailcow affecting versions prior to 2024-04. This vulnerability is a combination of path traversal and arbitrary code execution, specifically targeting the `rspamd_maps()` function. It allows authenticated admin users to overwrite any file writable by the www-data user by exploiting improper path validation. The exploit chain can lead to the execution of arbitrary commands on the server. Version 2024-04 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30264 | typebot.io: `GHSL-2024-040`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30264</link><description>Typebot is an open-source chatbot builder. A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) in the sign-in page of typebot.io prior to version 2.24.0 may allow an attacker to hijack a user's account. The sign-in page takes the `redirectPath` parameter from the URL. If a user clicks on a link where the `redirectPath` parameter has a javascript scheme, the attacker that crafted the link may be able to execute arbitrary JavaScript with the privileges  of the user. Version 2.24.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29387 | projeqtor up to 11.2.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /view/print.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29387</link><description>projeqtor up to 11.2.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /view/print.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29386 | projeqtor up to 11.2.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /view/criticalResourceExport.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29386</link><description>projeqtor up to 11.2.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /view/criticalResourceExport.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22023 | An XML entity expansion or XEE vulnerability in SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22023</link><description>An XML entity expansion or XEE vulnerability in SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthenticated attacker to send specially crafted XML requests in-order-to temporarily cause resource exhaustion thereby resulting in a limited-time DoS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22052 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in IPSec component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22052</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in IPSec component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthenticated malicious user to send specially crafted requests in-order-to crash the service thereby causing a DoS attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22053 | A heap overflow vulnerability in IPSec component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x
 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthenticated mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22053</link><description>A heap overflow vulnerability in IPSec component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x
 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure allows an unauthenticated malicious user to send specially crafted requests in-order-to crash the service thereby causing a DoS attack or in certain conditions read contents from memory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30255 | HTTP/2: CPU exhaustion due to CONTINUATION frame flood</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30255</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. The HTTP/2 protocol stack in Envoy versions prior to 1.29.3, 1.28.2, 1.27.4, and 1.26.8 are vulnerable to CPU exhaustion due to flood of CONTINUATION frames. Envoy's HTTP/2 codec allows the client to send an unlimited number of CONTINUATION frames even after exceeding Envoy's header map limits. This allows an attacker to send a sequence of CONTINUATION frames without the END_HEADERS bit set causing CPU utilization, consuming approximately 1 core per 300Mbit/s of traffic and culminating in denial of service through CPU exhaustion. Users should upgrade to version 1.29.3, 1.28.2, 1.27.4, or 1.26.8 to mitigate the effects of the CONTINUATION flood. As a workaround, disable HTTP/2 protocol for downstream connections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24795 | Apache HTTP Server: HTTP Response Splitting in multiple modules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24795</link><description>HTTP Response splitting in multiple modules in Apache HTTP Server allows an attacker that can inject malicious response headers into backend applications to cause an HTTP desynchronization attack.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.59, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27316 | Apache HTTP Server: HTTP/2 DoS by memory exhaustion on endless continuation frames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27316</link><description>HTTP/2 incoming headers exceeding the limit are temporarily buffered in nghttp2 in order to generate an informative HTTP 413 response. If a client does not stop sending headers, this leads to memory exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38709 | Apache HTTP Server: HTTP response splitting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38709</link><description>Faulty input validation in the core of Apache allows malicious or exploitable backend/content generators to split HTTP responses.

This issue affects Apache HTTP Server: through 2.4.58.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30254 | Directory traversal allowing overwriting arbitrary files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30254</link><description>MesonLSP is an unofficial, unendorsed language server for meson written in C++. A vulnerability in versions prior to 4.1.4 allows overwriting arbitrary files if the attacker can make the victim either run the language server within a specific crafted project or `mesonlsp --full`. Version 4.1.4 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, avoid running `mesonlsp --full` and set the language server option `others.neverDownloadAutomatically` to `true`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30252 | GitHub Security Lab (GHSL) Vulnerability Report, livemarks: `GHSL-2024-015`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30252</link><description>Livemarks is a browser extension that provides RSS feed bookmark folders. Versions of Livemarks prior to 3.7 are vulnerable to cross-site request forgery. A malicious website may be able to coerce the extension to send an authenticated GET request to an arbitrary URL. An authenticated request is a request where the cookies of the browser are sent along with the request. The `subscribe.js` script uses the first parameter from the current URL location as the URL of the RSS feed to subscribe to and checks that the RSS feed is valid XML. `subscribe.js` is accessible by an attacker website due to its use in `subscribe.html`, an HTML page that is declared as a `web_accessible_resource` in `manifest.json`. This issue may lead to `Privilege Escalation`. A CSRF breaks the integrity of servers running on a private network. A user of the browser extension may have a private server with dangerous functionality, which is assumed to be safe due to network segmentation. Upon receiving an authenticated request instantiated from an attacker, this integrity is broken. Version 3.7 fixes this issue by removing subscribe.html from `web_accessible_resources`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30249 | Cloudburst Network DoS in RakNet connection handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30249</link><description>Cloudburst Network provides network components used within Cloudburst projects. A vulnerability in versions prior to `1.0.0.CR1-20240330.101522-15` impacts publicly accessible software depending on the affected versions of Network and allows an attacker to use Network as an amplification vector for a UDP denial of service attack against a third party or as an attempt to trigger service suspension of the host. All consumers of the library should upgrade to at least version `1.0.0.CR1-20240330.101522-15` to receive a fix. There are no known workarounds beyond updating the library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:51:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29193 | GHSL-2023-207 gotortc DOM-based Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29193</link><description>gotortc is a camera streaming application. Versions 1.8.5 and prior are vulnerable to DOM-based cross-site scripting. The index page (`index.html`) shows the available streams by fetching the API (`[0]`) in the client side. Then, it uses `Object.entries` to iterate over the result (`[1]`) whose first item (`name`) gets appended using `innerHTML` (`[2]`). In the event of a victim visiting the server in question, their browser will execute the request against the go2rtc instance. After the request, the browser will be redirected to go2rtc, in which the XSS would be executed in the context of go2rtc’s origin. As of time of publication, no patch is available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25007 | Ericsson Network Manager - Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25007</link><description>Ericsson Network Manager (ENM), versions prior to 23.1, contains a vulnerability in the export function of application log where Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File can lead to code execution or information disclosure. There is limited impact to integrity and availability. The attacker on the adjacent network with administration access can exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29192 | GHSL-2023-206 gotortc Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29192</link><description>gotortc is a camera streaming application. Versions 1.8.5 and prior are vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery. The `/api/config` endpoint allows one to modify the existing configuration with user-supplied values. While the API is only allowing localhost to interact without authentication, an attacker may be able to achieve that depending on how go2rtc is set up on the upstream application, and given that this endpoint is not protected against CSRF, it allows requests from any origin (e.g. a "drive-by" attack) . The `exec` handler allows for any stream to execute arbitrary commands. An attacker may add a custom stream through `api/config`, which may lead to arbitrary command execution. In the event of a victim visiting the server in question, their browser will execute the requests against the go2rtc instance. Commit 8793c3636493c5efdda08f3b5ed5c6e1ea594fd9 adds a warning about secure API access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25690 | HTML injection in ArcGIS Web AppBuilder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25690</link><description>There is an HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 11.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could render arbitrary HTML in the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25692 | BUG-000154722 - Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) issue in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25692</link><description>There is a cross-site-request forgery vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Versions 11.1 and below that may in some cases allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trick an authorized user into executing unwanted actions via a crafted form. The impact to Confidentiality and Integrity vectors is limited and of low severity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25693 | Portal for ArcGIS has a directory traversal vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25693</link><description>There is a path traversal in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions &lt;= 11.2.  Successful exploitation may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to traverse the file system to access files or execute code outside of the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25695 | concatenated errors resulting in cross site scripting and frame injection issues.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25695</link><description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;= 11.2 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to provide input that is not sanitized properly and is rendered in error messages.  The are no privileges required to execute this attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25696 | Stored XSS in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25696</link><description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;=11.0 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when accessing the page editor an image will render in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25697 | Stored XSS in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25697</link><description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;=11.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when opening an authenticated users bio page will render an image in the victims browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are low.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25698 | Reflected XSS in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25698</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the home application in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25699 | Portal for ArcGIS has an invalid authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25699</link><description>There is a difficult to exploit improper authentication issue in the Home application for Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 through 11.2 on Windows and Linux, and ArcGIS Enterprise 11.1 and below on Kubernetes which, under unique circumstances, could potentially allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the software.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25700 | Persistent XSS in URL added to a shared map</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25700</link><description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Enterprise Web App Builder versions &lt;= 11.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link that is stored in a web map link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25703 | Reflected XSS in home/pages/Account/manage_accounts.html via #redirect_uri</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25703</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the home application in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25704 | Persistent XSS in Experience Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25704</link><description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Enterprise Experience Builder versions &lt;= 11.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link that is stored in the Experience Builder Embed widget which when loaded could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25705 | Cross site scripting issue in embed widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25705</link><description>There is a cross site scripting vulnerability in the Esri Portal for ArcGIS Experience Builder 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser. The privileges required to execute this attack are low.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25706 | HTMLi at createFolder Content Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25706</link><description>There is an HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS &lt;=11.0 that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL which, when clicked, could potentially generate a message that may entice an unsuspecting victim to visit an arbitrary website. This could simplify phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25708 | Persistent XSS when creating new application using Web App Builder </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25708</link><description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Enterprise Web App Builder versions 10.8.1 – 10.9.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25709 | Self-XSS style in move item dialog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25709</link><description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 – 1121 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link that can be saved as a new location when moving an existing item which will potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2660 | Vault TLS Cert Auth Method Did Not Correctly Validate OCSP Responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2660</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise TLS certificates auth method did not correctly validate OCSP responses when one or more OCSP sources were configured. Fixed in Vault 1.16.0 and Vault Enterprise 1.16.1, 1.15.7, and 1.14.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28787 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28787</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0 through 10.0.7 and IBM Application Gateway 20.01 through 24.03 could allow a remote attacker to obtain highly sensitive private information or cause a denial of service using a specially crafted HTTP request.  IBM X-Force ID:  286584.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27268 | IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27268</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 18.0.0.2 through 24.0.0.3 is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by sending a specially crafted request. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause the server to consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  284574.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3454 | Remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS after v9.0 and before v9.2.0 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3454</link><description>Remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS after v9.0 and before v9.2.0 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code and use this to gain root access to the Brocade switch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30263 | The PDF Viewer macro can be used to view PDF attachments with restricted access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30263</link><description>macro-pdfviewer is a PDF Viewer Macro for XWiki using Mozilla pdf.js. Users with edit rights can access restricted PDF attachments using the PDF Viewer macro, just by passing the attachment URL as the value of the ``file`` parameter. Users with view rights can access restricted PDF attachments if they are shown on public pages where the PDF Viewer macro is called using the attachment URL instead of its reference. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31209 | OpenID Connect client Atom Exhaustion in provider configuration worker ets table location</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31209</link><description>oidcc is the OpenID Connect client library for Erlang. Denial of Service (DoS) by Atom exhaustion is possible by calling `oidcc_provider_configuration_worker:get_provider_configuration/1` or `oidcc_provider_configuration_worker:get_jwks/1`. This issue has been patched in version(s)`3.1.2` &amp; `3.2.0-beta.3`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31215 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in firebase database check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31215</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is a security research platform for mobile applications in Android, iOS and Windows Mobile.
A SSRF vulnerability in firebase database check logic. The attacker can cause the server to make a connection to internal-only services within the organization’s infrastructure. When a malicious app is uploaded to Static analyzer, it is possible to make internal requests. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31207 | Vite&amp;#x27;s `server.fs.deny` did not deny requests for patterns with directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31207</link><description>Vite (French word for "quick", pronounced /vit/, like "veet") is a frontend build tooling to improve the frontend development experience.`server.fs.deny` does not deny requests for patterns with directories. This vulnerability has been patched in version(s) 5.2.6, 5.1.7, 5.0.13, 4.5.3, 3.2.10 and 2.9.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30266 | Wasmtime vulnerable to panic when using a dropped extenref-typed element segment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30266</link><description>wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. The 19.0.0 release of Wasmtime contains a regression introduced during its development which can lead to a guest WebAssembly module causing a panic in the host runtime. A valid WebAssembly module, when executed at runtime, may cause this panic. This vulnerability has been patched in version 19.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2103 | Inclusion of Undocumented Features</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2103</link><description>Inclusion of undocumented features vulnerability accessible when logged on with a privileged access level on the following Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories relays could allow the relay to behave unpredictably:
SEL-700BT Motor Bus Transfer Relay, SEL-700G Generator Protection Relay, SEL-710-5 Motor Protection Relay, SEL-751 Feeder Protection Relay, SEL-787-2/-3/-4 Transformer Protection Relay, SEL-787Z High-Impedance Differential Relay

. See product instruction manual appendix A dated 20240308 for more details regarding the SEL-751 Feeder Protection Relay. For more information for the other affected products, see their instruction manuals dated 20240329.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30260 | Undici&amp;#x27;s Proxy-Authorization header not cleared on cross-origin redirect for dispatch, request, stream, pipeline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30260</link><description>Undici is an HTTP/1.1 client, written from scratch for Node.js. Undici cleared Authorization and Proxy-Authorization headers for `fetch()`, but did not clear them for `undici.request()`. This vulnerability was patched in version(s) 5.28.4 and 6.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30261 | Undici&amp;#x27;s fetch with integrity option is too lax when algorithm is specified but hash value is in incorrect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30261</link><description>Undici is an HTTP/1.1 client, written from scratch for Node.js. An attacker can alter the `integrity` option passed to `fetch()`, allowing `fetch()` to accept requests as valid even if they have been tampered. This vulnerability was patched in version(s) 5.28.4 and 6.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3298 | Out-Of-Bounds Write and Type Confusion vulnerabilities exist in the DWG and DXF file reading procedure in eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2023 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2024</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3298</link><description>Out-Of-Bounds Write and Type Confusion vulnerabilities exist in the file reading procedure in eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2023 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2024. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted DWG or DXF. NOTE: this vulnerability was SPLIT from CVE-2024-1847.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3299 | Out-Of-Bounds Write, Use of Uninitialized Resource and Use-After-Free vulnerabilities exist in the SLDDRW and SLDPRT file reading procedure in eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2023 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2024</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3299</link><description>Out-Of-Bounds Write, Use of Uninitialized Resource and Use-After-Free vulnerabilities exist in the file reading procedure in eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2023 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2024. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted SLDDRW or SLDPRT file. NOTE: this vulnerability was SPLIT from CVE-2024-1847.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3116 | Remote Code Execution Vulnerability through the validate binary path API in pgAdmin 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3116</link><description>pgAdmin &lt;= 8.4 is affected by a  Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability through the validate binary path API. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server hosting PGAdmin, posing a severe risk to the database management system's integrity and the security of the underlying data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29191 | GHSL-2023-205 gotortc DOM-based Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29191</link><description>gotortc is a camera streaming application. Versions 1.8.5 and prior are vulnerable to DOM-based cross-site scripting. The links page (`links.html`) appends the `src` GET parameter (`[0]`) in all of its links for 1-click previews. The context in which `src` is being appended is `innerHTML` (`[1]`), which will insert the text as HTML. Commit 3b3d5b033aac3a019af64f83dec84f70ed2c8aba contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30250 | In Astro-Shield, setting a correct `integrity` attribute to injected code allows to bypass the allow-lists</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30250</link><description>Astro-Shield is an integration to enhance website security with SubResource Integrity hashes, Content-Security-Policy headers, and other techniques. Versions from 1.2.0 to 1.3.1 of Astro-Shield allow bypass to the allow-lists for cross-origin resources by introducing valid `integrity` attributes to the injected code. This implies that the injected SRI hash would be added to the generated CSP header, which would lead the browser to believe that the injected resource is legit. This vulnerability is patched in version 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:07:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29182 | Collabora Online Stored Cross-Site-Scripting vulnerability via tooltip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29182</link><description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice. A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability was found in Collabora Online. An attacker could create a document with an XSS payload in document text referenced by field which, if hovered over to produce a tooltip, could be executed by the user's browser. Users should upgrade to Collabora Online 23.05.10.1 or higher. Earlier series of Collabora Online, 22.04, 21.11, etc. are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28182 | Reading unbounded number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames to cause excessive CPU usage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28182</link><description>nghttp2 is an implementation of the Hypertext Transfer Protocol version 2 in C. The nghttp2 library prior to version 1.61.0 keeps reading the unbounded number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames even after a stream is reset to keep HPACK context in sync.  This causes excessive CPU usage to decode HPACK stream. nghttp2 v1.61.0 mitigates this vulnerability by limiting the number of CONTINUATION frames it accepts per stream. There is no workaround for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28871 | Excessive CPU used on malformed traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28871</link><description>LibHTP is a security-aware parser for the HTTP protocol and the related bits and pieces. Version 0.5.46 may parse malformed request traffic, leading to excessive CPU usage. Version 0.5.47 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27919 | HTTP/2: memory exhaustion due to CONTINUATION frame flood</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27919</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open-source edge and service proxy. In versions 1.29.0 and 1.29.1, theEnvoy HTTP/2 protocol stack is vulnerable to the flood of CONTINUATION frames. Envoy's HTTP/2 codec does not reset a request when header map limits have been exceeded. This allows an attacker to send an sequence of CONTINUATION frames without the END_HEADERS bit set causing unlimited memory consumption. This can lead to denial of service through memory exhaustion. Users should upgrade to versions 1.29.2 to mitigate the effects of the CONTINUATION flood. Note that this vulnerability is a regression in Envoy version 1.29.0 and 1.29.1 only. As a workaround, downgrade to version 1.28.1 or earlier or disable HTTP/2 protocol for downstream connections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3250 | It was discovered that Canonical's Pebble service manager read-file API and the associated pebble pull command, before v1.10.2, allowed unpr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3250</link><description>It was discovered that Canonical's Pebble service manager read-file API and the associated pebble pull command, before v1.10.2, allowed unprivileged local users to read files with root-equivalent permissions when Pebble was running as root. Fixes are also available as backports to v1.1.1, v1.4.2, and v1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22189 | QUIC&amp;#x27;s Connection ID Mechanism vulnerable to Memory Exhaustion Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22189</link><description>quic-go is an implementation of the QUIC protocol in Go. Prior to version 0.42.0, an attacker can cause its peer to run out of memory sending a large number of `NEW_CONNECTION_ID` frames that retire old connection IDs. The receiver is supposed to respond to each retirement frame with a `RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID` frame. The attacker can prevent the receiver from sending out (the vast majority of) these `RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID` frames by collapsing the peers congestion window (by selectively acknowledging received packets) and by manipulating the peer's RTT estimate. Version 0.42.0 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31080 | Xorg-x11-server: heap buffer overread/data leakage in procxigetselectedevents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31080</link><description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIGetSelectedEvents() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31081 | Xorg-x11-server: heap buffer overread/data leakage in procxipassivegrabdevice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31081</link><description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIPassiveGrabDevice() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31082 | Xorg-x11-server: heap buffer overread/data leakage in procappledricreatepixmap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31082</link><description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcAppleDRICreatePixmap() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3296 | Rust-openssl: timing based side-channel can lead to a bleichenbacher style attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3296</link><description>A timing-based side-channel flaw exists in the rust-openssl package, which could be sufficient to recover a plaintext across a network in a Bleichenbacher-style attack. To achieve successful decryption, an attacker would have to be able to send a large number of trial messages for decryption. The vulnerability affects the legacy PKCS#1v1.5 RSA encryption padding mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2700 | Quarkus-core: leak of local configuration properties into quarkus applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2700</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the quarkus-core component. Quarkus captures the local environment variables from the Quarkus namespace during the application's build. Thus, running the resulting application inherits the values captured at build time. &#13;
&#13;
However, some local environment variables may have been set by the developer / CI environment for testing purposes, such as dropping the database during the application startup or trusting all TLS certificates to accept self-signed certificates. If these properties are configured using environment variables or the .env facility, they are captured into the built application. It leads to dangerous behavior if the application does not override these values.&#13;
&#13;
This behavior only happens for configuration properties from the `quarkus.*` namespace. So, application-specific properties are not captured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2759 | Improper access control in Apaczka plugin for PrestaShop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2759</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Apaczka plugin for PrestaShop allows information gathering from saved templates without authentication.This issue affects Apaczka plugin for PrestaShop from v1 through v4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27575 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in INOTEC Sicherheitstechnik GmbH INOTEC Sicherheitstechnik GmbH WebServer CPS220/64 V.3.3.19 allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27575</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in INOTEC Sicherheitstechnik GmbH INOTEC Sicherheitstechnik GmbH WebServer CPS220/64 V.3.3.19 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /etc/passwd file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26808 | netfilter: nft_chain_filter: handle NETDEV_UNREGISTER for inet/ingress basechain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26808</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_chain_filter: handle NETDEV_UNREGISTER for inet/ingress basechain

Remove netdevice from inet/ingress basechain in case NETDEV_UNREGISTER
event is reported, otherwise a stale reference to netdevice remains in
the hook list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26809 | netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: release elements in clone only from destroy path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26809</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: release elements in clone only from destroy path

Clone already always provides a current view of the lookup table, use it
to destroy the set, otherwise it is possible to destroy elements twice.

This fix requires:

 212ed75dc5fb ("netfilter: nf_tables: integrate pipapo into commit protocol")

which came after:

 9827a0e6e23b ("netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: release elements in clone from abort path").</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3262 | Information exposure vulnerability in Request Tracker (RT)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3262</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in RT software affecting version 4.4.1. This vulnerability allows an attacker with local access to the device to retrieve sensitive information about the application, such as vulnerability tickets, because the application stores the information in the browser cache, leading to information exposure despite session termination.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20800 | DOM XSS in `libs/granite/security/clientlibs/v2/usereditor/js/UserProperties.js` via propertiesform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20800</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.19 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable web pages. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable script. This could result in arbitrary code execution within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36643 | Incorrect Access Control in ITB-GmbH TradePro v9.5, allows remote attackers to receive all orders from the online shop via oordershow compon...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36643</link><description>Incorrect Access Control in ITB-GmbH TradePro v9.5, allows remote attackers to receive all orders from the online shop via oordershow component in customer function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36644 | Incorrect Access Control in ITB-GmbH TradePro v9.5, allows remote attackers to receive all order confirmations from the online shop via the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36644</link><description>Incorrect Access Control in ITB-GmbH TradePro v9.5, allows remote attackers to receive all order confirmations from the online shop via the printmail plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36645 | SQL injection vulnerability in ITB-GmbH TradePro v9.5, allows remote attackers to run SQL queries via oordershow component in customer funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36645</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in ITB-GmbH TradePro v9.5, allows remote attackers to run SQL queries via oordershow component in customer function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26745 | powerpc/pseries/iommu: IOMMU table is not initialized for kdump over SR-IOV</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26745</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

powerpc/pseries/iommu: IOMMU table is not initialized for kdump over SR-IOV

When kdump kernel tries to copy dump data over SR-IOV, LPAR panics due
to NULL pointer exception:

  Kernel attempted to read user page (0) - exploit attempt? (uid: 0)
  BUG: Kernel NULL pointer dereference on read at 0x00000000
  Faulting instruction address: 0xc000000020847ad4
  Oops: Kernel access of bad area, sig: 11 [#1]
  LE PAGE_SIZE=64K MMU=Radix SMP NR_CPUS=2048 NUMA pSeries
  Modules linked in: mlx5_core(+) vmx_crypto pseries_wdt papr_scm libnvdimm mlxfw tls psample sunrpc fuse overlay squashfs loop
  CPU: 12 PID: 315 Comm: systemd-udevd Not tainted 6.4.0-Test102+ #12
  Hardware name: IBM,9080-HEX POWER10 (raw) 0x800200 0xf000006 of:IBM,FW1060.00 (NH1060_008) hv:phyp pSeries
  NIP:  c000000020847ad4 LR: c00000002083b2dc CTR: 00000000006cd18c
  REGS: c000000029162ca0 TRAP: 0300   Not tainted  (6.4.0-Test102+)
  MSR:  800000000280b033 &lt;SF,VEC,VSX,EE,FP,ME,IR,DR,RI,LE&gt;  CR: 48288244  XER: 00000008
  CFAR: c00000002083b2d8 DAR: 0000000000000000 DSISR: 40000000 IRQMASK: 1
  ...
  NIP _find_next_zero_bit+0x24/0x110
  LR  bitmap_find_next_zero_area_off+0x5c/0xe0
  Call Trace:
    dev_printk_emit+0x38/0x48 (unreliable)
    iommu_area_alloc+0xc4/0x180
    iommu_range_alloc+0x1e8/0x580
    iommu_alloc+0x60/0x130
    iommu_alloc_coherent+0x158/0x2b0
    dma_iommu_alloc_coherent+0x3c/0x50
    dma_alloc_attrs+0x170/0x1f0
    mlx5_cmd_init+0xc0/0x760 [mlx5_core]
    mlx5_function_setup+0xf0/0x510 [mlx5_core]
    mlx5_init_one+0x84/0x210 [mlx5_core]
    probe_one+0x118/0x2c0 [mlx5_core]
    local_pci_probe+0x68/0x110
    pci_call_probe+0x68/0x200
    pci_device_probe+0xbc/0x1a0
    really_probe+0x104/0x540
    __driver_probe_device+0xb4/0x230
    driver_probe_device+0x54/0x130
    __driver_attach+0x158/0x2b0
    bus_for_each_dev+0xa8/0x130
    driver_attach+0x34/0x50
    bus_add_driver+0x16c/0x300
    driver_register+0xa4/0x1b0
    __pci_register_driver+0x68/0x80
    mlx5_init+0xb8/0x100 [mlx5_core]
    do_one_initcall+0x60/0x300
    do_init_module+0x7c/0x2b0

At the time of LPAR dump, before kexec hands over control to kdump
kernel, DDWs (Dynamic DMA Windows) are scanned and added to the FDT.
For the SR-IOV case, default DMA window "ibm,dma-window" is removed from
the FDT and DDW added, for the device.

Now, kexec hands over control to the kdump kernel.

When the kdump kernel initializes, PCI busses are scanned and IOMMU
group/tables created, in pci_dma_bus_setup_pSeriesLP(). For the SR-IOV
case, there is no "ibm,dma-window". The original commit: b1fc44eaa9ba,
fixes the path where memory is pre-mapped (direct mapped) to the DDW.
When TCEs are direct mapped, there is no need to initialize IOMMU
tables.

iommu_table_setparms_lpar() only considers "ibm,dma-window" property
when initiallizing IOMMU table. In the scenario where TCEs are
dynamically allocated for SR-IOV, newly created IOMMU table is not
initialized. Later, when the device driver tries to enter TCEs for the
SR-IOV device, NULL pointer execption is thrown from iommu_area_alloc().

The fix is to initialize the IOMMU table with DDW property stored in the
FDT. There are 2 points to remember:

	1. For the dedicated adapter, kdump kernel would encounter both
	   default and DDW in FDT. In this case, DDW property is used to
	   initialize the IOMMU table.

	2. A DDW could be direct or dynamic mapped. kdump kernel would
	   initialize IOMMU table and mark the existing DDW as
	   "dynamic". This works fine since, at the time of table
	   initialization, iommu_table_clear() makes some space in the
	   DDW, for some predefined number of TCEs which are needed for
	   kdump to succeed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26746 | dmaengine: idxd: Ensure safe user copy of completion record</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26746</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dmaengine: idxd: Ensure safe user copy of completion record

If CONFIG_HARDENED_USERCOPY is enabled, copying completion record from
event log cache to user triggers a kernel bug.

[ 1987.159822] usercopy: Kernel memory exposure attempt detected from SLUB object 'dsa0' (offset 74, size 31)!
[ 1987.170845] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[ 1987.176086] kernel BUG at mm/usercopy.c:102!
[ 1987.180946] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
[ 1987.186866] CPU: 17 PID: 528 Comm: kworker/17:1 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc2+ #5
[ 1987.194537] Hardware name: Intel Corporation AvenueCity/AvenueCity, BIOS BHSDCRB1.86B.2492.D03.2307181620 07/18/2023
[ 1987.206405] Workqueue: wq0.0 idxd_evl_fault_work [idxd]
[ 1987.212338] RIP: 0010:usercopy_abort+0x72/0x90
[ 1987.217381] Code: 58 65 9c 50 48 c7 c2 17 85 61 9c 57 48 c7 c7 98 fd 6b 9c 48 0f 44 d6 48 c7 c6 b3 08 62 9c 4c 89 d1 49 0f 44 f3 e8 1e 2e d5 ff &lt;0f&gt; 0b 49 c7 c1 9e 42 61 9c 4c 89 cf 4d 89 c8 eb a9 66 66 2e 0f 1f
[ 1987.238505] RSP: 0018:ff62f5cf20607d60 EFLAGS: 00010246
[ 1987.244423] RAX: 000000000000005f RBX: 000000000000001f RCX: 0000000000000000
[ 1987.252480] RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: ffffffff9c61429e RDI: 00000000ffffffff
[ 1987.260538] RBP: ff62f5cf20607d78 R08: ff2a6a89ef3fffe8 R09: 00000000fffeffff
[ 1987.268595] R10: ff2a6a89eed00000 R11: 0000000000000003 R12: ff2a66934849c89a
[ 1987.276652] R13: 0000000000000001 R14: ff2a66934849c8b9 R15: ff2a66934849c899
[ 1987.284710] FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ff2a66b22fe40000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[ 1987.293850] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[ 1987.300355] CR2: 00007fe291a37000 CR3: 000000010fbd4005 CR4: 0000000000f71ef0
[ 1987.308413] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
[ 1987.316470] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe07f0 DR7: 0000000000000400
[ 1987.324527] PKRU: 55555554
[ 1987.327622] Call Trace:
[ 1987.330424]  &lt;TASK&gt;
[ 1987.332826]  ? show_regs+0x6e/0x80
[ 1987.336703]  ? die+0x3c/0xa0
[ 1987.339988]  ? do_trap+0xd4/0xf0
[ 1987.343662]  ? do_error_trap+0x75/0xa0
[ 1987.347922]  ? usercopy_abort+0x72/0x90
[ 1987.352277]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x57/0x80
[ 1987.356634]  ? usercopy_abort+0x72/0x90
[ 1987.360988]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1f/0x30
[ 1987.365734]  ? usercopy_abort+0x72/0x90
[ 1987.370088]  __check_heap_object+0xb7/0xd0
[ 1987.374739]  __check_object_size+0x175/0x2d0
[ 1987.379588]  idxd_copy_cr+0xa9/0x130 [idxd]
[ 1987.384341]  idxd_evl_fault_work+0x127/0x390 [idxd]
[ 1987.389878]  process_one_work+0x13e/0x300
[ 1987.394435]  ? __pfx_worker_thread+0x10/0x10
[ 1987.399284]  worker_thread+0x2f7/0x420
[ 1987.403544]  ? _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0x2b/0x50
[ 1987.409171]  ? __pfx_worker_thread+0x10/0x10
[ 1987.414019]  kthread+0x107/0x140
[ 1987.417693]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[ 1987.421954]  ret_from_fork+0x3d/0x60
[ 1987.426019]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[ 1987.430281]  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30
[ 1987.434744]  &lt;/TASK&gt;

The issue arises because event log cache is created using
kmem_cache_create() which is not suitable for user copy.

Fix the issue by creating event log cache with
kmem_cache_create_usercopy(), ensuring safe user copy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26750 | af_unix: Drop oob_skb ref before purging queue in GC.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26750</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

af_unix: Drop oob_skb ref before purging queue in GC.

syzbot reported another task hung in __unix_gc().  [0]

The current while loop assumes that all of the left candidates
have oob_skb and calling kfree_skb(oob_skb) releases the remaining
candidates.

However, I missed a case that oob_skb has self-referencing fd and
another fd and the latter sk is placed before the former in the
candidate list.  Then, the while loop never proceeds, resulting
the task hung.

__unix_gc() has the same loop just before purging the collected skb,
so we can call kfree_skb(oob_skb) there and let __skb_queue_purge()
release all inflight sockets.

[0]:
Sending NMI from CPU 0 to CPUs 1:
NMI backtrace for cpu 1
CPU: 1 PID: 2784 Comm: kworker/u4:8 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc4-syzkaller-01028-g71b605d32017 #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/25/2024
Workqueue: events_unbound __unix_gc
RIP: 0010:__sanitizer_cov_trace_pc+0x0/0x70 kernel/kcov.c:200
Code: 89 fb e8 23 00 00 00 48 8b 3d 84 f5 1a 0c 48 89 de 5b e9 43 26 57 00 0f 1f 00 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 &lt;f3&gt; 0f 1e fa 48 8b 04 24 65 48 8b 0d 90 52 70 7e 65 8b 15 91 52 70
RSP: 0018:ffffc9000a17fa78 EFLAGS: 00000287
RAX: ffffffff8a0a6108 RBX: ffff88802b6c2640 RCX: ffff88802c0b3b80
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000002 RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: ffffc9000a17fbf0 R08: ffffffff89383f1d R09: 1ffff1100ee5ff84
R10: dffffc0000000000 R11: ffffed100ee5ff85 R12: 1ffff110056d84ee
R13: ffffc9000a17fae0 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffffffff8f47b840
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8880b9500000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007ffef5687ff8 CR3: 0000000029b34000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 &lt;NMI&gt;
 &lt;/NMI&gt;
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 __unix_gc+0xe69/0xf40 net/unix/garbage.c:343
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:2633 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0x913/0x1420 kernel/workqueue.c:2706
 worker_thread+0xa5f/0x1000 kernel/workqueue.c:2787
 kthread+0x2ef/0x390 kernel/kthread.c:388
 ret_from_fork+0x4b/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:242
 &lt;/TASK&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26780 | af_unix: Fix task hung while purging oob_skb in GC.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26780</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

af_unix: Fix task hung while purging oob_skb in GC.

syzbot reported a task hung; at the same time, GC was looping infinitely
in list_for_each_entry_safe() for OOB skb.  [0]

syzbot demonstrated that the list_for_each_entry_safe() was not actually
safe in this case.

A single skb could have references for multiple sockets.  If we free such
a skb in the list_for_each_entry_safe(), the current and next sockets could
be unlinked in a single iteration.

unix_notinflight() uses list_del_init() to unlink the socket, so the
prefetched next socket forms a loop itself and list_for_each_entry_safe()
never stops.

Here, we must use while() and make sure we always fetch the first socket.

[0]:
Sending NMI from CPU 0 to CPUs 1:
NMI backtrace for cpu 1
CPU: 1 PID: 5065 Comm: syz-executor236 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc3-syzkaller-00136-g1f719a2f3fa6 #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/25/2024
RIP: 0010:preempt_count arch/x86/include/asm/preempt.h:26 [inline]
RIP: 0010:check_kcov_mode kernel/kcov.c:173 [inline]
RIP: 0010:__sanitizer_cov_trace_pc+0xd/0x60 kernel/kcov.c:207
Code: cc cc cc cc 66 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 f3 0f 1e fa 65 48 8b 14 25 40 c2 03 00 &lt;65&gt; 8b 05 b4 7c 78 7e a9 00 01 ff 00 48 8b 34 24 74 0f f6 c4 01 74
RSP: 0018:ffffc900033efa58 EFLAGS: 00000283
RAX: ffff88807b077800 RBX: ffff88807b077800 RCX: 1ffffffff27b1189
RDX: ffff88802a5a3b80 RSI: ffffffff8968488d RDI: ffff88807b077f70
RBP: ffffc900033efbb0 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: fffffbfff27a900c
R10: ffffffff93d48067 R11: ffffffff8ae000eb R12: ffff88807b077800
R13: dffffc0000000000 R14: ffff88807b077e40 R15: 0000000000000001
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8880b9500000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 0000564f4fc1e3a8 CR3: 000000000d57a000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 &lt;NMI&gt;
 &lt;/NMI&gt;
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 unix_gc+0x563/0x13b0 net/unix/garbage.c:319
 unix_release_sock+0xa93/0xf80 net/unix/af_unix.c:683
 unix_release+0x91/0xf0 net/unix/af_unix.c:1064
 __sock_release+0xb0/0x270 net/socket.c:659
 sock_close+0x1c/0x30 net/socket.c:1421
 __fput+0x270/0xb80 fs/file_table.c:376
 task_work_run+0x14f/0x250 kernel/task_work.c:180
 exit_task_work include/linux/task_work.h:38 [inline]
 do_exit+0xa8a/0x2ad0 kernel/exit.c:871
 do_group_exit+0xd4/0x2a0 kernel/exit.c:1020
 __do_sys_exit_group kernel/exit.c:1031 [inline]
 __se_sys_exit_group kernel/exit.c:1029 [inline]
 __x64_sys_exit_group+0x3e/0x50 kernel/exit.c:1029
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xd5/0x270 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6f/0x77
RIP: 0033:0x7f9d6cbdac09
Code: Unable to access opcode bytes at 0x7f9d6cbdabdf.
RSP: 002b:00007fff5952feb8 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 00000000000000e7
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: 00007f9d6cbdac09
RDX: 000000000000003c RSI: 00000000000000e7 RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: 00007f9d6cc552b0 R08: ffffffffffffffb8 R09: 0000000000000006
R10: 0000000000000006 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00007f9d6cc552b0
R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 00007f9d6cc55d00 R15: 00007f9d6cbabe70
 &lt;/TASK&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26781 | mptcp: fix possible deadlock in subflow diag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26781</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: fix possible deadlock in subflow diag

Syzbot and Eric reported a lockdep splat in the subflow diag:

   WARNING: possible circular locking dependency detected
   6.8.0-rc4-syzkaller-00212-g40b9385dd8e6 #0 Not tainted

   syz-executor.2/24141 is trying to acquire lock:
   ffff888045870130 (k-sk_lock-AF_INET6){+.+.}-{0:0}, at:
   tcp_diag_put_ulp net/ipv4/tcp_diag.c:100 [inline]
   ffff888045870130 (k-sk_lock-AF_INET6){+.+.}-{0:0}, at:
   tcp_diag_get_aux+0x738/0x830 net/ipv4/tcp_diag.c:137

   but task is already holding lock:
   ffffc9000135e488 (&amp;h-&gt;lhash2[i].lock){+.+.}-{2:2}, at: spin_lock
   include/linux/spinlock.h:351 [inline]
   ffffc9000135e488 (&amp;h-&gt;lhash2[i].lock){+.+.}-{2:2}, at:
   inet_diag_dump_icsk+0x39f/0x1f80 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1038

   which lock already depends on the new lock.

   the existing dependency chain (in reverse order) is:

   -&gt; #1 (&amp;h-&gt;lhash2[i].lock){+.+.}-{2:2}:
   lock_acquire+0x1e3/0x530 kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5754
   __raw_spin_lock include/linux/spinlock_api_smp.h:133 [inline]
   _raw_spin_lock+0x2e/0x40 kernel/locking/spinlock.c:154
   spin_lock include/linux/spinlock.h:351 [inline]
   __inet_hash+0x335/0xbe0 net/ipv4/inet_hashtables.c:743
   inet_csk_listen_start+0x23a/0x320 net/ipv4/inet_connection_sock.c:1261
   __inet_listen_sk+0x2a2/0x770 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:217
   inet_listen+0xa3/0x110 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:239
   rds_tcp_listen_init+0x3fd/0x5a0 net/rds/tcp_listen.c:316
   rds_tcp_init_net+0x141/0x320 net/rds/tcp.c:577
   ops_init+0x352/0x610 net/core/net_namespace.c:136
   __register_pernet_operations net/core/net_namespace.c:1214 [inline]
   register_pernet_operations+0x2cb/0x660 net/core/net_namespace.c:1283
   register_pernet_device+0x33/0x80 net/core/net_namespace.c:1370
   rds_tcp_init+0x62/0xd0 net/rds/tcp.c:735
   do_one_initcall+0x238/0x830 init/main.c:1236
   do_initcall_level+0x157/0x210 init/main.c:1298
   do_initcalls+0x3f/0x80 init/main.c:1314
   kernel_init_freeable+0x42f/0x5d0 init/main.c:1551
   kernel_init+0x1d/0x2a0 init/main.c:1441
   ret_from_fork+0x4b/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
   ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:242

   -&gt; #0 (k-sk_lock-AF_INET6){+.+.}-{0:0}:
   check_prev_add kernel/locking/lockdep.c:3134 [inline]
   check_prevs_add kernel/locking/lockdep.c:3253 [inline]
   validate_chain+0x18ca/0x58e0 kernel/locking/lockdep.c:3869
   __lock_acquire+0x1345/0x1fd0 kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5137
   lock_acquire+0x1e3/0x530 kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5754
   lock_sock_fast include/net/sock.h:1723 [inline]
   subflow_get_info+0x166/0xd20 net/mptcp/diag.c:28
   tcp_diag_put_ulp net/ipv4/tcp_diag.c:100 [inline]
   tcp_diag_get_aux+0x738/0x830 net/ipv4/tcp_diag.c:137
   inet_sk_diag_fill+0x10ed/0x1e00 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:345
   inet_diag_dump_icsk+0x55b/0x1f80 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1061
   __inet_diag_dump+0x211/0x3a0 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1263
   inet_diag_dump_compat+0x1c1/0x2d0 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1371
   netlink_dump+0x59b/0xc80 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2264
   __netlink_dump_start+0x5df/0x790 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2370
   netlink_dump_start include/linux/netlink.h:338 [inline]
   inet_diag_rcv_msg_compat+0x209/0x4c0 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1405
   sock_diag_rcv_msg+0xe7/0x410
   netlink_rcv_skb+0x1e3/0x430 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2543
   sock_diag_rcv+0x2a/0x40 net/core/sock_diag.c:280
   netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1341 [inline]
   netlink_unicast+0x7ea/0x980 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1367
   netlink_sendmsg+0xa3b/0xd70 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1908
   sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
   __sock_sendmsg+0x221/0x270 net/socket.c:745
   ____sys_sendmsg+0x525/0x7d0 net/socket.c:2584
   ___sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2638 [inline]
   __sys_sendmsg+0x2b0/0x3a0 net/socket.c:2667
   do_syscall_64+0xf9/0x240
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6f/0x77

As noted by Eric we can break the lock dependency chain avoid
dumping 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26782 | mptcp: fix double-free on socket dismantle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26782</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: fix double-free on socket dismantle

when MPTCP server accepts an incoming connection, it clones its listener
socket. However, the pointer to 'inet_opt' for the new socket has the same
value as the original one: as a consequence, on program exit it's possible
to observe the following splat:

  BUG: KASAN: double-free in inet_sock_destruct+0x54f/0x8b0
  Free of addr ffff888485950880 by task swapper/25/0

  CPU: 25 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/25 Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.8.0-rc1+ #609
  Hardware name: Supermicro SYS-6027R-72RF/X9DRH-7TF/7F/iTF/iF, BIOS 3.0  07/26/2013
  Call Trace:
   &lt;IRQ&gt;
   dump_stack_lvl+0x32/0x50
   print_report+0xca/0x620
   kasan_report_invalid_free+0x64/0x90
   __kasan_slab_free+0x1aa/0x1f0
   kfree+0xed/0x2e0
   inet_sock_destruct+0x54f/0x8b0
   __sk_destruct+0x48/0x5b0
   rcu_do_batch+0x34e/0xd90
   rcu_core+0x559/0xac0
   __do_softirq+0x183/0x5a4
   irq_exit_rcu+0x12d/0x170
   sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x6b/0x80
   &lt;/IRQ&gt;
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   asm_sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x16/0x20
  RIP: 0010:cpuidle_enter_state+0x175/0x300
  Code: 30 00 0f 84 1f 01 00 00 83 e8 01 83 f8 ff 75 e5 48 83 c4 18 44 89 e8 5b 5d 41 5c 41 5d 41 5e 41 5f c3 cc cc cc cc fb 45 85 ed &lt;0f&gt; 89 60 ff ff ff 48 c1 e5 06 48 c7 43 18 00 00 00 00 48 83 44 2b
  RSP: 0018:ffff888481cf7d90 EFLAGS: 00000202
  RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff88887facddc8 RCX: 0000000000000000
  RDX: 1ffff1110ff588b1 RSI: 0000000000000019 RDI: ffff88887fac4588
  RBP: 0000000000000004 R08: 0000000000000002 R09: 0000000000043080
  R10: 0009b02ea273363f R11: ffff88887fabf42b R12: ffffffff932592e0
  R13: 0000000000000004 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 00000022c880ec80
   cpuidle_enter+0x4a/0xa0
   do_idle+0x310/0x410
   cpu_startup_entry+0x51/0x60
   start_secondary+0x211/0x270
   secondary_startup_64_no_verify+0x184/0x18b
   &lt;/TASK&gt;

  Allocated by task 6853:
   kasan_save_stack+0x1c/0x40
   kasan_save_track+0x10/0x30
   __kasan_kmalloc+0xa6/0xb0
   __kmalloc+0x1eb/0x450
   cipso_v4_sock_setattr+0x96/0x360
   netlbl_sock_setattr+0x132/0x1f0
   selinux_netlbl_socket_post_create+0x6c/0x110
   selinux_socket_post_create+0x37b/0x7f0
   security_socket_post_create+0x63/0xb0
   __sock_create+0x305/0x450
   __sys_socket_create.part.23+0xbd/0x130
   __sys_socket+0x37/0xb0
   __x64_sys_socket+0x6f/0xb0
   do_syscall_64+0x83/0x160
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76

  Freed by task 6858:
   kasan_save_stack+0x1c/0x40
   kasan_save_track+0x10/0x30
   kasan_save_free_info+0x3b/0x60
   __kasan_slab_free+0x12c/0x1f0
   kfree+0xed/0x2e0
   inet_sock_destruct+0x54f/0x8b0
   __sk_destruct+0x48/0x5b0
   subflow_ulp_release+0x1f0/0x250
   tcp_cleanup_ulp+0x6e/0x110
   tcp_v4_destroy_sock+0x5a/0x3a0
   inet_csk_destroy_sock+0x135/0x390
   tcp_fin+0x416/0x5c0
   tcp_data_queue+0x1bc8/0x4310
   tcp_rcv_state_process+0x15a3/0x47b0
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x2c1/0x990
   tcp_v4_rcv+0x41fb/0x5ed0
   ip_protocol_deliver_rcu+0x6d/0x9f0
   ip_local_deliver_finish+0x278/0x360
   ip_local_deliver+0x182/0x2c0
   ip_rcv+0xb5/0x1c0
   __netif_receive_skb_one_core+0x16e/0x1b0
   process_backlog+0x1e3/0x650
   __napi_poll+0xa6/0x500
   net_rx_action+0x740/0xbb0
   __do_softirq+0x183/0x5a4

  The buggy address belongs to the object at ffff888485950880
   which belongs to the cache kmalloc-64 of size 64
  The buggy address is located 0 bytes inside of
   64-byte region [ffff888485950880, ffff8884859508c0)

  The buggy address belongs to the physical page:
  page:0000000056d1e95e refcount:1 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0xffff888485950700 pfn:0x485950
  flags: 0x57ffffc0000800(slab|node=1|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x1fffff)
  page_type: 0xffffffff()
  raw: 0057ffffc0000800 ffff88810004c640 ffffea00121b8ac0 dead000000000006
  raw: ffff888485950700 0000000000200019 00000001ffffffff 0000000000000000
  page dumped because: kasan: bad access detected

  Memory state around the buggy address:
   ffff888485950780: fa fb fb
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26783 | mm/vmscan: fix a bug calling wakeup_kswapd() with a wrong zone index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26783</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/vmscan: fix a bug calling wakeup_kswapd() with a wrong zone index

With numa balancing on, when a numa system is running where a numa node
doesn't have its local memory so it has no managed zones, the following
oops has been observed.  It's because wakeup_kswapd() is called with a
wrong zone index, -1.  Fixed it by checking the index before calling
wakeup_kswapd().

&gt; BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: 00000000000033f3
&gt; #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
&gt; #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
&gt; PGD 0 P4D 0
&gt; Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
&gt; CPU: 2 PID: 895 Comm: masim Not tainted 6.6.0-dirty #255
&gt; Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS
&gt;    rel-1.16.0-0-gd239552ce722-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
&gt; RIP: 0010:wakeup_kswapd (./linux/mm/vmscan.c:7812)
&gt; Code: (omitted)
&gt; RSP: 0000:ffffc90004257d58 EFLAGS: 00010286
&gt; RAX: ffffffffffffffff RBX: ffff88883fff0480 RCX: 0000000000000003
&gt; RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: ffff88883fff0480
&gt; RBP: ffffffffffffffff R08: ff0003ffffffffff R09: ffffffffffffffff
&gt; R10: ffff888106c95540 R11: 0000000055555554 R12: 0000000000000003
&gt; R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffff88883fff0940
&gt; FS:  00007fc4b8124740(0000) GS:ffff888827c00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
&gt; CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
&gt; CR2: 00000000000033f3 CR3: 000000026cc08004 CR4: 0000000000770ee0
&gt; DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
&gt; DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
&gt; PKRU: 55555554
&gt; Call Trace:
&gt;  &lt;TASK&gt;
&gt; ? __die
&gt; ? page_fault_oops
&gt; ? __pte_offset_map_lock
&gt; ? exc_page_fault
&gt; ? asm_exc_page_fault
&gt; ? wakeup_kswapd
&gt; migrate_misplaced_page
&gt; __handle_mm_fault
&gt; handle_mm_fault
&gt; do_user_addr_fault
&gt; exc_page_fault
&gt; asm_exc_page_fault
&gt; RIP: 0033:0x55b897ba0808
&gt; Code: (omitted)
&gt; RSP: 002b:00007ffeefa821a0 EFLAGS: 00010287
&gt; RAX: 000055b89983acd0 RBX: 00007ffeefa823f8 RCX: 000055b89983acd0
&gt; RDX: 00007fc2f8122010 RSI: 0000000000020000 RDI: 000055b89983acd0
&gt; RBP: 00007ffeefa821a0 R08: 0000000000000037 R09: 0000000000000075
&gt; R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000202 R12: 0000000000000000
&gt; R13: 00007ffeefa82410 R14: 000055b897ba5dd8 R15: 00007fc4b8340000
&gt;  &lt;/TASK&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26784 | pmdomain: arm: Fix NULL dereference on scmi_perf_domain removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26784</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pmdomain: arm: Fix NULL dereference on scmi_perf_domain removal

On unloading of the scmi_perf_domain module got the below splat, when in
the DT provided to the system under test the '#power-domain-cells' property
was missing. Indeed, this particular setup causes the probe to bail out
early without giving any error, which leads to the -&gt;remove() callback gets
to run too, but without all the expected initialized structures in place.

Add a check and bail out early on remove too.

 Call trace:
  scmi_perf_domain_remove+0x28/0x70 [scmi_perf_domain]
  scmi_dev_remove+0x28/0x40 [scmi_core]
  device_remove+0x54/0x90
  device_release_driver_internal+0x1dc/0x240
  driver_detach+0x58/0xa8
  bus_remove_driver+0x78/0x108
  driver_unregister+0x38/0x70
  scmi_driver_unregister+0x28/0x180 [scmi_core]
  scmi_perf_domain_driver_exit+0x18/0xb78 [scmi_perf_domain]
  __arm64_sys_delete_module+0x1a8/0x2c0
  invoke_syscall+0x50/0x128
  el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x48/0xf0
  do_el0_svc+0x24/0x38
  el0_svc+0x34/0xb8
  el0t_64_sync_handler+0x100/0x130
  el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x198
 Code: a90153f3 f9403c14 f9414800 955f8a05 (b9400a80)
 ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26785 | iommufd: Fix protection fault in iommufd_test_syz_conv_iova</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26785</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommufd: Fix protection fault in iommufd_test_syz_conv_iova

Syzkaller reported the following bug:

  general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000038: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN
  KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x00000000000001c0-0x00000000000001c7]
  Call Trace:
   lock_acquire
   lock_acquire+0x1ce/0x4f0
   down_read+0x93/0x4a0
   iommufd_test_syz_conv_iova+0x56/0x1f0
   iommufd_test_access_rw.isra.0+0x2ec/0x390
   iommufd_test+0x1058/0x1e30
   iommufd_fops_ioctl+0x381/0x510
   vfs_ioctl
   __do_sys_ioctl
   __se_sys_ioctl
   __x64_sys_ioctl+0x170/0x1e0
   do_syscall_x64
   do_syscall_64+0x71/0x140

This is because the new iommufd_access_change_ioas() sets access-&gt;ioas to
NULL during its process, so the lock might be gone in a concurrent racing
context.

Fix this by doing the same access-&gt;ioas sanity as iommufd_access_rw() and
iommufd_access_pin_pages() functions do.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26786 | iommufd: Fix iopt_access_list_id overwrite bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26786</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommufd: Fix iopt_access_list_id overwrite bug

Syzkaller reported the following WARN_ON:
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 4738 at drivers/iommu/iommufd/io_pagetable.c:1360

  Call Trace:
   iommufd_access_change_ioas+0x2fe/0x4e0
   iommufd_access_destroy_object+0x50/0xb0
   iommufd_object_remove+0x2a3/0x490
   iommufd_object_destroy_user
   iommufd_access_destroy+0x71/0xb0
   iommufd_test_staccess_release+0x89/0xd0
   __fput+0x272/0xb50
   __fput_sync+0x4b/0x60
   __do_sys_close
   __se_sys_close
   __x64_sys_close+0x8b/0x110
   do_syscall_x64

The mismatch between the access pointer in the list and the passed-in
pointer is resulting from an overwrite of access-&gt;iopt_access_list_id, in
iopt_add_access(). Called from iommufd_access_change_ioas() when
xa_alloc() succeeds but iopt_calculate_iova_alignment() fails.

Add a new_id in iopt_add_access() and only update iopt_access_list_id when
returning successfully.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26787 | mmc: mmci: stm32: fix DMA API overlapping mappings warning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26787</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mmc: mmci: stm32: fix DMA API overlapping mappings warning

Turning on CONFIG_DMA_API_DEBUG_SG results in the following warning:

DMA-API: mmci-pl18x 48220000.mmc: cacheline tracking EEXIST,
overlapping mappings aren't supported
WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 51 at kernel/dma/debug.c:568
add_dma_entry+0x234/0x2f4
Modules linked in:
CPU: 1 PID: 51 Comm: kworker/1:2 Not tainted 6.1.28 #1
Hardware name: STMicroelectronics STM32MP257F-EV1 Evaluation Board (DT)
Workqueue: events_freezable mmc_rescan
Call trace:
add_dma_entry+0x234/0x2f4
debug_dma_map_sg+0x198/0x350
__dma_map_sg_attrs+0xa0/0x110
dma_map_sg_attrs+0x10/0x2c
sdmmc_idma_prep_data+0x80/0xc0
mmci_prep_data+0x38/0x84
mmci_start_data+0x108/0x2dc
mmci_request+0xe4/0x190
__mmc_start_request+0x68/0x140
mmc_start_request+0x94/0xc0
mmc_wait_for_req+0x70/0x100
mmc_send_tuning+0x108/0x1ac
sdmmc_execute_tuning+0x14c/0x210
mmc_execute_tuning+0x48/0xec
mmc_sd_init_uhs_card.part.0+0x208/0x464
mmc_sd_init_card+0x318/0x89c
mmc_attach_sd+0xe4/0x180
mmc_rescan+0x244/0x320

DMA API debug brings to light leaking dma-mappings as dma_map_sg and
dma_unmap_sg are not correctly balanced.

If an error occurs in mmci_cmd_irq function, only mmci_dma_error
function is called and as this API is not managed on stm32 variant,
dma_unmap_sg is never called in this error path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26788 | dmaengine: fsl-qdma: init irq after reg initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26788</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dmaengine: fsl-qdma: init irq after reg initialization

Initialize the qDMA irqs after the registers are configured so that
interrupts that may have been pending from a primary kernel don't get
processed by the irq handler before it is ready to and cause panic with
the following trace:

  Call trace:
   fsl_qdma_queue_handler+0xf8/0x3e8
   __handle_irq_event_percpu+0x78/0x2b0
   handle_irq_event_percpu+0x1c/0x68
   handle_irq_event+0x44/0x78
   handle_fasteoi_irq+0xc8/0x178
   generic_handle_irq+0x24/0x38
   __handle_domain_irq+0x90/0x100
   gic_handle_irq+0x5c/0xb8
   el1_irq+0xb8/0x180
   _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0x14/0x40
   __setup_irq+0x4bc/0x798
   request_threaded_irq+0xd8/0x190
   devm_request_threaded_irq+0x74/0xe8
   fsl_qdma_probe+0x4d4/0xca8
   platform_drv_probe+0x50/0xa0
   really_probe+0xe0/0x3f8
   driver_probe_device+0x64/0x130
   device_driver_attach+0x6c/0x78
   __driver_attach+0xbc/0x158
   bus_for_each_dev+0x5c/0x98
   driver_attach+0x20/0x28
   bus_add_driver+0x158/0x220
   driver_register+0x60/0x110
   __platform_driver_register+0x44/0x50
   fsl_qdma_driver_init+0x18/0x20
   do_one_initcall+0x48/0x258
   kernel_init_freeable+0x1a4/0x23c
   kernel_init+0x10/0xf8
   ret_from_fork+0x10/0x18</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26789 | crypto: arm64/neonbs - fix out-of-bounds access on short input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26789</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: arm64/neonbs - fix out-of-bounds access on short input

The bit-sliced implementation of AES-CTR operates on blocks of 128
bytes, and will fall back to the plain NEON version for tail blocks or
inputs that are shorter than 128 bytes to begin with.

It will call straight into the plain NEON asm helper, which performs all
memory accesses in granules of 16 bytes (the size of a NEON register).
For this reason, the associated plain NEON glue code will copy inputs
shorter than 16 bytes into a temporary buffer, given that this is a rare
occurrence and it is not worth the effort to work around this in the asm
code.

The fallback from the bit-sliced NEON version fails to take this into
account, potentially resulting in out-of-bounds accesses. So clone the
same workaround, and use a temp buffer for short in/outputs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26790 | dmaengine: fsl-qdma: fix SoC may hang on 16 byte unaligned read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26790</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dmaengine: fsl-qdma: fix SoC may hang on 16 byte unaligned read

There is chip (ls1028a) errata:

The SoC may hang on 16 byte unaligned read transactions by QDMA.

Unaligned read transactions initiated by QDMA may stall in the NOC
(Network On-Chip), causing a deadlock condition. Stalled transactions will
trigger completion timeouts in PCIe controller.

Workaround:
Enable prefetch by setting the source descriptor prefetchable bit
( SD[PF] = 1 ).

Implement this workaround.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26791 | btrfs: dev-replace: properly validate device names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26791</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: dev-replace: properly validate device names

There's a syzbot report that device name buffers passed to device
replace are not properly checked for string termination which could lead
to a read out of bounds in getname_kernel().

Add a helper that validates both source and target device name buffers.
For devid as the source initialize the buffer to empty string in case
something tries to read it later.

This was originally analyzed and fixed in a different way by Edward Adam
Davis (see links).</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26792 | btrfs: fix double free of anonymous device after snapshot creation failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26792</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix double free of anonymous device after snapshot creation failure

When creating a snapshot we may do a double free of an anonymous device
in case there's an error committing the transaction. The second free may
result in freeing an anonymous device number that was allocated by some
other subsystem in the kernel or another btrfs filesystem.

The steps that lead to this:

1) At ioctl.c:create_snapshot() we allocate an anonymous device number
   and assign it to pending_snapshot-&gt;anon_dev;

2) Then we call btrfs_commit_transaction() and end up at
   transaction.c:create_pending_snapshot();

3) There we call btrfs_get_new_fs_root() and pass it the anonymous device
   number stored in pending_snapshot-&gt;anon_dev;

4) btrfs_get_new_fs_root() frees that anonymous device number because
   btrfs_lookup_fs_root() returned a root - someone else did a lookup
   of the new root already, which could some task doing backref walking;

5) After that some error happens in the transaction commit path, and at
   ioctl.c:create_snapshot() we jump to the 'fail' label, and after
   that we free again the same anonymous device number, which in the
   meanwhile may have been reallocated somewhere else, because
   pending_snapshot-&gt;anon_dev still has the same value as in step 1.

Recently syzbot ran into this and reported the following trace:

  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  ida_free called for id=51 which is not allocated.
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 31038 at lib/idr.c:525 ida_free+0x370/0x420 lib/idr.c:525
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 1 PID: 31038 Comm: syz-executor.2 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc4-syzkaller-00410-gc02197fc9076 #0
  Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/25/2024
  RIP: 0010:ida_free+0x370/0x420 lib/idr.c:525
  Code: 10 42 80 3c 28 (...)
  RSP: 0018:ffffc90015a67300 EFLAGS: 00010246
  RAX: be5130472f5dd000 RBX: 0000000000000033 RCX: 0000000000040000
  RDX: ffffc90009a7a000 RSI: 000000000003ffff RDI: 0000000000040000
  RBP: ffffc90015a673f0 R08: ffffffff81577992 R09: 1ffff92002b4cdb4
  R10: dffffc0000000000 R11: fffff52002b4cdb5 R12: 0000000000000246
  R13: dffffc0000000000 R14: ffffffff8e256b80 R15: 0000000000000246
  FS:  00007fca3f4b46c0(0000) GS:ffff8880b9500000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: 00007f167a17b978 CR3: 000000001ed26000 CR4: 0000000000350ef0
  Call Trace:
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   btrfs_get_root_ref+0xa48/0xaf0 fs/btrfs/disk-io.c:1346
   create_pending_snapshot+0xff2/0x2bc0 fs/btrfs/transaction.c:1837
   create_pending_snapshots+0x195/0x1d0 fs/btrfs/transaction.c:1931
   btrfs_commit_transaction+0xf1c/0x3740 fs/btrfs/transaction.c:2404
   create_snapshot+0x507/0x880 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:848
   btrfs_mksubvol+0x5d0/0x750 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:998
   btrfs_mksnapshot+0xb5/0xf0 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1044
   __btrfs_ioctl_snap_create+0x387/0x4b0 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1306
   btrfs_ioctl_snap_create_v2+0x1ca/0x400 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1393
   btrfs_ioctl+0xa74/0xd40
   vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
   __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:871 [inline]
   __se_sys_ioctl+0xfe/0x170 fs/ioctl.c:857
   do_syscall_64+0xfb/0x240
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6f/0x77
  RIP: 0033:0x7fca3e67dda9
  Code: 28 00 00 00 (...)
  RSP: 002b:00007fca3f4b40c8 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000010
  RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007fca3e7abf80 RCX: 00007fca3e67dda9
  RDX: 00000000200005c0 RSI: 0000000050009417 RDI: 0000000000000003
  RBP: 00007fca3e6ca47a R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: 000000000000000b R14: 00007fca3e7abf80 R15: 00007fff6bf95658
   &lt;/TASK&gt;

Where we get an explicit message where we attempt to free an anonymous
device number that is not currently allocated. It happens in a different
code path from the example below, at btrfs_get_root_ref(), so this change
may not fix the case triggered by sy
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26793 | gtp: fix use-after-free and null-ptr-deref in gtp_newlink()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26793</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gtp: fix use-after-free and null-ptr-deref in gtp_newlink()

The gtp_link_ops operations structure for the subsystem must be
registered after registering the gtp_net_ops pernet operations structure.

Syzkaller hit 'general protection fault in gtp_genl_dump_pdp' bug:

[ 1010.702740] gtp: GTP module unloaded
[ 1010.715877] general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000001: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN NOPTI
[ 1010.715888] KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000008-0x000000000000000f]
[ 1010.715895] CPU: 1 PID: 128616 Comm: a.out Not tainted 6.8.0-rc6-std-def-alt1 #1
[ 1010.715899] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.0-alt1 04/01/2014
[ 1010.715908] RIP: 0010:gtp_newlink+0x4d7/0x9c0 [gtp]
[ 1010.715915] Code: 80 3c 02 00 0f 85 41 04 00 00 48 8b bb d8 05 00 00 e8 ed f6 ff ff 48 89 c2 48 89 c5 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 48 c1 ea 03 &lt;80&gt; 3c 02 00 0f 85 4f 04 00 00 4c 89 e2 4c 8b 6d 00 48 b8 00 00 00
[ 1010.715920] RSP: 0018:ffff888020fbf180 EFLAGS: 00010203
[ 1010.715929] RAX: dffffc0000000000 RBX: ffff88800399c000 RCX: 0000000000000000
[ 1010.715933] RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: ffffffff84805280 RDI: 0000000000000282
[ 1010.715938] RBP: 000000000000000d R08: 0000000000000001 R09: 0000000000000000
[ 1010.715942] R10: 0000000000000001 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: ffff88800399cc80
[ 1010.715947] R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000400
[ 1010.715953] FS:  00007fd1509ab5c0(0000) GS:ffff88805b300000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[ 1010.715958] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[ 1010.715962] CR2: 0000000000000000 CR3: 000000001c07a000 CR4: 0000000000750ee0
[ 1010.715968] PKRU: 55555554
[ 1010.715972] Call Trace:
[ 1010.715985]  ? __die_body.cold+0x1a/0x1f
[ 1010.715995]  ? die_addr+0x43/0x70
[ 1010.716002]  ? exc_general_protection+0x199/0x2f0
[ 1010.716016]  ? asm_exc_general_protection+0x1e/0x30
[ 1010.716026]  ? gtp_newlink+0x4d7/0x9c0 [gtp]
[ 1010.716034]  ? gtp_net_exit+0x150/0x150 [gtp]
[ 1010.716042]  __rtnl_newlink+0x1063/0x1700
[ 1010.716051]  ? rtnl_setlink+0x3c0/0x3c0
[ 1010.716063]  ? is_bpf_text_address+0xc0/0x1f0
[ 1010.716070]  ? kernel_text_address.part.0+0xbb/0xd0
[ 1010.716076]  ? __kernel_text_address+0x56/0xa0
[ 1010.716084]  ? unwind_get_return_address+0x5a/0xa0
[ 1010.716091]  ? create_prof_cpu_mask+0x30/0x30
[ 1010.716098]  ? arch_stack_walk+0x9e/0xf0
[ 1010.716106]  ? stack_trace_save+0x91/0xd0
[ 1010.716113]  ? stack_trace_consume_entry+0x170/0x170
[ 1010.716121]  ? __lock_acquire+0x15c5/0x5380
[ 1010.716139]  ? mark_held_locks+0x9e/0xe0
[ 1010.716148]  ? kmem_cache_alloc_trace+0x35f/0x3c0
[ 1010.716155]  ? __rtnl_newlink+0x1700/0x1700
[ 1010.716160]  rtnl_newlink+0x69/0xa0
[ 1010.716166]  rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x43b/0xc50
[ 1010.716172]  ? rtnl_fdb_dump+0x9f0/0x9f0
[ 1010.716179]  ? lock_acquire+0x1fe/0x560
[ 1010.716188]  ? netlink_deliver_tap+0x12f/0xd50
[ 1010.716196]  netlink_rcv_skb+0x14d/0x440
[ 1010.716202]  ? rtnl_fdb_dump+0x9f0/0x9f0
[ 1010.716208]  ? netlink_ack+0xab0/0xab0
[ 1010.716213]  ? netlink_deliver_tap+0x202/0xd50
[ 1010.716220]  ? netlink_deliver_tap+0x218/0xd50
[ 1010.716226]  ? __virt_addr_valid+0x30b/0x590
[ 1010.716233]  netlink_unicast+0x54b/0x800
[ 1010.716240]  ? netlink_attachskb+0x870/0x870
[ 1010.716248]  ? __check_object_size+0x2de/0x3b0
[ 1010.716254]  netlink_sendmsg+0x938/0xe40
[ 1010.716261]  ? netlink_unicast+0x800/0x800
[ 1010.716269]  ? __import_iovec+0x292/0x510
[ 1010.716276]  ? netlink_unicast+0x800/0x800
[ 1010.716284]  __sock_sendmsg+0x159/0x190
[ 1010.716290]  ____sys_sendmsg+0x712/0x880
[ 1010.716297]  ? sock_write_iter+0x3d0/0x3d0
[ 1010.716304]  ? __ia32_sys_recvmmsg+0x270/0x270
[ 1010.716309]  ? lock_acquire+0x1fe/0x560
[ 1010.716315]  ? drain_array_locked+0x90/0x90
[ 1010.716324]  ___sys_sendmsg+0xf8/0x170
[ 1010.716331]  ? sendmsg_copy_msghdr+0x170/0x170
[ 1010.716337]  ? lockdep_init_map
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26794 | btrfs: fix race between ordered extent completion and fiemap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26794</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix race between ordered extent completion and fiemap

For fiemap we recently stopped locking the target extent range for the
whole duration of the fiemap call, in order to avoid a deadlock in a
scenario where the fiemap buffer happens to be a memory mapped range of
the same file. This use case is very unlikely to be useful in practice but
it may be triggered by fuzz testing (syzbot, etc).

However by not locking the target extent range for the whole duration of
the fiemap call we can race with an ordered extent. This happens like
this:

1) The fiemap task finishes processing a file extent item that covers
   the file range [512K, 1M[, and that file extent item is the last item
   in the leaf currently being processed;

2) And ordered extent for the file range [768K, 2M[, in COW mode,
   completes (btrfs_finish_one_ordered()) and the file extent item
   covering the range [512K, 1M[ is trimmed to cover the range
   [512K, 768K[ and then a new file extent item for the range [768K, 2M[
   is inserted in the inode's subvolume tree;

3) The fiemap task calls fiemap_next_leaf_item(), which then calls
   btrfs_next_leaf() to find the next leaf / item. This finds that the
   the next key following the one we previously processed (its type is
   BTRFS_EXTENT_DATA_KEY and its offset is 512K), is the key corresponding
   to the new file extent item inserted by the ordered extent, which has
   a type of BTRFS_EXTENT_DATA_KEY and an offset of 768K;

4) Later the fiemap code ends up at emit_fiemap_extent() and triggers
   the warning:

      if (cache-&gt;offset + cache-&gt;len &gt; offset) {
               WARN_ON(1);
               return -EINVAL;
      }

   Since we get 1M &gt; 768K, because the previously emitted entry for the
   old extent covering the file range [512K, 1M[ ends at an offset that
   is greater than the new extent's start offset (768K). This makes fiemap
   fail with -EINVAL besides triggering the warning that produces a stack
   trace like the following:

     [1621.677651] ------------[ cut here ]------------
     [1621.677656] WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 204366 at fs/btrfs/extent_io.c:2492 emit_fiemap_extent+0x84/0x90 [btrfs]
     [1621.677899] Modules linked in: btrfs blake2b_generic (...)
     [1621.677951] CPU: 1 PID: 204366 Comm: pool Not tainted 6.8.0-rc5-btrfs-next-151+ #1
     [1621.677954] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.2-0-gea1b7a073390-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
     [1621.677956] RIP: 0010:emit_fiemap_extent+0x84/0x90 [btrfs]
     [1621.678033] Code: 2b 4c 89 63 (...)
     [1621.678035] RSP: 0018:ffffab16089ffd20 EFLAGS: 00010206
     [1621.678037] RAX: 00000000004fa000 RBX: ffffab16089ffe08 RCX: 0000000000009000
     [1621.678039] RDX: 00000000004f9000 RSI: 00000000004f1000 RDI: ffffab16089ffe90
     [1621.678040] RBP: 00000000004f9000 R08: 0000000000001000 R09: 0000000000000000
     [1621.678041] R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000001000 R12: 0000000041d78000
     [1621.678043] R13: 0000000000001000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffff9434f0b17850
     [1621.678044] FS:  00007fa6e20006c0(0000) GS:ffff943bdfa40000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
     [1621.678046] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
     [1621.678048] CR2: 00007fa6b0801000 CR3: 000000012d404002 CR4: 0000000000370ef0
     [1621.678053] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
     [1621.678055] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
     [1621.678056] Call Trace:
     [1621.678074]  &lt;TASK&gt;
     [1621.678076]  ? __warn+0x80/0x130
     [1621.678082]  ? emit_fiemap_extent+0x84/0x90 [btrfs]
     [1621.678159]  ? report_bug+0x1f4/0x200
     [1621.678164]  ? handle_bug+0x42/0x70
     [1621.678167]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x14/0x70
     [1621.678170]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x16/0x20
     [1621.678178]  ? emit_fiemap_extent+0x84/0x90 [btrfs]
     [1621.678253]  extent_fiemap+0x766
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26795 | riscv: Sparse-Memory/vmemmap out-of-bounds fix</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26795</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: Sparse-Memory/vmemmap out-of-bounds fix

Offset vmemmap so that the first page of vmemmap will be mapped
to the first page of physical memory in order to ensure that
vmemmap’s bounds will be respected during
pfn_to_page()/page_to_pfn() operations.
The conversion macros will produce correct SV39/48/57 addresses
for every possible/valid DRAM_BASE inside the physical memory limits.

v2:Address Alex's comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26796 | drivers: perf: ctr_get_width function for legacy is not defined</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26796</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drivers: perf: ctr_get_width function for legacy is not defined

With parameters CONFIG_RISCV_PMU_LEGACY=y and CONFIG_RISCV_PMU_SBI=n
linux kernel crashes when you try perf record:

$ perf record ls
[ 46.749286] Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 0000000000000000
[ 46.750199] Oops [#1]
[ 46.750342] Modules linked in:
[ 46.750608] CPU: 0 PID: 107 Comm: perf-exec Not tainted 6.6.0 #2
[ 46.750906] Hardware name: riscv-virtio,qemu (DT)
[ 46.751184] epc : 0x0
[ 46.751430] ra : arch_perf_update_userpage+0x54/0x13e
[ 46.751680] epc : 0000000000000000 ra : ffffffff8072ee52 sp : ff2000000022b8f0
[ 46.751958] gp : ffffffff81505988 tp : ff6000000290d400 t0 : ff2000000022b9c0
[ 46.752229] t1 : 0000000000000001 t2 : 0000000000000003 s0 : ff2000000022b930
[ 46.752451] s1 : ff600000028fb000 a0 : 0000000000000000 a1 : ff600000028fb000
[ 46.752673] a2 : 0000000ae2751268 a3 : 00000000004fb708 a4 : 0000000000000004
[ 46.752895] a5 : 0000000000000000 a6 : 000000000017ffe3 a7 : 00000000000000d2
[ 46.753117] s2 : ff600000028fb000 s3 : 0000000ae2751268 s4 : 0000000000000000
[ 46.753338] s5 : ffffffff8153e290 s6 : ff600000863b9000 s7 : ff60000002961078
[ 46.753562] s8 : ff60000002961048 s9 : ff60000002961058 s10: 0000000000000001
[ 46.753783] s11: 0000000000000018 t3 : ffffffffffffffff t4 : ffffffffffffffff
[ 46.754005] t5 : ff6000000292270c t6 : ff2000000022bb30
[ 46.754179] status: 0000000200000100 badaddr: 0000000000000000 cause: 000000000000000c
[ 46.754653] Code: Unable to access instruction at 0xffffffffffffffec.
[ 46.754939] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
[ 46.755131] note: perf-exec[107] exited with irqs disabled
[ 46.755546] note: perf-exec[107] exited with preempt_count 4

This happens because in the legacy case the ctr_get_width function was not
defined, but it is used in arch_perf_update_userpage.

Also remove extra check in riscv_pmu_ctr_get_width_mask</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26797 | drm/amd/display: Prevent potential buffer overflow in map_hw_resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26797</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Prevent potential buffer overflow in map_hw_resources

Adds a check in the map_hw_resources function to prevent a potential
buffer overflow. The function was accessing arrays using an index that
could potentially be greater than the size of the arrays, leading to a
buffer overflow.

Adds a check to ensure that the index is within the bounds of the
arrays. If the index is out of bounds, an error message is printed and
break it will continue execution with just ignoring extra data early to
prevent the buffer overflow.

Reported by smatch:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/../display/dc/dml2/dml2_wrapper.c:79 map_hw_resources() error: buffer overflow 'dml2-&gt;v20.scratch.dml_to_dc_pipe_mapping.disp_cfg_to_stream_id' 6 &lt;= 7
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/../display/dc/dml2/dml2_wrapper.c:81 map_hw_resources() error: buffer overflow 'dml2-&gt;v20.scratch.dml_to_dc_pipe_mapping.disp_cfg_to_plane_id' 6 &lt;= 7</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26798 | fbcon: always restore the old font data in fbcon_do_set_font()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26798</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fbcon: always restore the old font data in fbcon_do_set_font()

Commit a5a923038d70 (fbdev: fbcon: Properly revert changes when
vc_resize() failed) started restoring old font data upon failure (of
vc_resize()). But it performs so only for user fonts. It means that the
"system"/internal fonts are not restored at all. So in result, the very
first call to fbcon_do_set_font() performs no restore at all upon
failing vc_resize().

This can be reproduced by Syzkaller to crash the system on the next
invocation of font_get(). It's rather hard to hit the allocation failure
in vc_resize() on the first font_set(), but not impossible. Esp. if
fault injection is used to aid the execution/failure. It was
demonstrated by Sirius:
  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: fffffffffffffff8
  #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
  PGD cb7b067 P4D cb7b067 PUD cb7d067 PMD 0
  Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN
  CPU: 1 PID: 8007 Comm: poc Not tainted 6.7.0-g9d1694dc91ce #20
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:fbcon_get_font+0x229/0x800 drivers/video/fbdev/core/fbcon.c:2286
  Call Trace:
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   con_font_get drivers/tty/vt/vt.c:4558 [inline]
   con_font_op+0x1fc/0xf20 drivers/tty/vt/vt.c:4673
   vt_k_ioctl drivers/tty/vt/vt_ioctl.c:474 [inline]
   vt_ioctl+0x632/0x2ec0 drivers/tty/vt/vt_ioctl.c:752
   tty_ioctl+0x6f8/0x1570 drivers/tty/tty_io.c:2803
   vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
  ...

So restore the font data in any case, not only for user fonts. Note the
later 'if' is now protected by 'old_userfont' and not 'old_data' as the
latter is always set now. (And it is supposed to be non-NULL. Otherwise
we would see the bug above again.)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26799 | ASoC: qcom: Fix uninitialized pointer dmactl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26799</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: qcom: Fix uninitialized pointer dmactl

In the case where __lpass_get_dmactl_handle is called and the driver
id dai_id is invalid the pointer dmactl is not being assigned a value,
and dmactl contains a garbage value since it has not been initialized
and so the null check may not work. Fix this to initialize dmactl to
NULL. One could argue that modern compilers will set this to zero, but
it is useful to keep this initialized as per the same way in functions
__lpass_platform_codec_intf_init and lpass_cdc_dma_daiops_hw_params.

Cleans up clang scan build warning:
sound/soc/qcom/lpass-cdc-dma.c:275:7: warning: Branch condition
evaluates to a garbage value [core.uninitialized.Branch]</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26800 | tls: fix use-after-free on failed backlog decryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26800</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: fix use-after-free on failed backlog decryption

When the decrypt request goes to the backlog and crypto_aead_decrypt
returns -EBUSY, tls_do_decryption will wait until all async
decryptions have completed. If one of them fails, tls_do_decryption
will return -EBADMSG and tls_decrypt_sg jumps to the error path,
releasing all the pages. But the pages have been passed to the async
callback, and have already been released by tls_decrypt_done.

The only true async case is when crypto_aead_decrypt returns
 -EINPROGRESS. With -EBUSY, we already waited so we can tell
tls_sw_recvmsg that the data is available for immediate copy, but we
need to notify tls_decrypt_sg (via the new -&gt;async_done flag) that the
memory has already been released.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26801 | Bluetooth: Avoid potential use-after-free in hci_error_reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26801</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Avoid potential use-after-free in hci_error_reset

While handling the HCI_EV_HARDWARE_ERROR event, if the underlying
BT controller is not responding, the GPIO reset mechanism would
free the hci_dev and lead to a use-after-free in hci_error_reset.

Here's the call trace observed on a ChromeOS device with Intel AX201:
   queue_work_on+0x3e/0x6c
   __hci_cmd_sync_sk+0x2ee/0x4c0 [bluetooth &lt;HASH:3b4a6&gt;]
   ? init_wait_entry+0x31/0x31
   __hci_cmd_sync+0x16/0x20 [bluetooth &lt;HASH:3b4a 6&gt;]
   hci_error_reset+0x4f/0xa4 [bluetooth &lt;HASH:3b4a 6&gt;]
   process_one_work+0x1d8/0x33f
   worker_thread+0x21b/0x373
   kthread+0x13a/0x152
   ? pr_cont_work+0x54/0x54
   ? kthread_blkcg+0x31/0x31
    ret_from_fork+0x1f/0x30

This patch holds the reference count on the hci_dev while processing
a HCI_EV_HARDWARE_ERROR event to avoid potential crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26802 | stmmac: Clear variable when destroying workqueue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26802</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

stmmac: Clear variable when destroying workqueue

Currently when suspending driver and stopping workqueue it is checked whether
workqueue is not NULL and if so, it is destroyed.
Function destroy_workqueue() does drain queue and does clear variable, but
it does not set workqueue variable to NULL. This can cause kernel/module
panic if code attempts to clear workqueue that was not initialized.

This scenario is possible when resuming suspended driver in stmmac_resume(),
because there is no handling for failed stmmac_hw_setup(),
which can fail and return if DMA engine has failed to initialize,
and workqueue is initialized after DMA engine.
Should DMA engine fail to initialize, resume will proceed normally,
but interface won't work and TX queue will eventually timeout,
causing 'Reset adapter' error.
This then does destroy workqueue during reset process.
And since workqueue is initialized after DMA engine and can be skipped,
it will cause kernel/module panic.

To secure against this possible crash, set workqueue variable to NULL when
destroying workqueue.

Log/backtrace from crash goes as follows:
[88.031977]------------[ cut here ]------------
[88.031985]NETDEV WATCHDOG: eth0 (sxgmac): transmit queue 1 timed out
[88.032017]WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 0 at net/sched/sch_generic.c:477 dev_watchdog+0x390/0x398
           &lt;Skipping backtrace for watchdog timeout&gt;
[88.032251]---[ end trace e70de432e4d5c2c0 ]---
[88.032282]sxgmac 16d88000.ethernet eth0: Reset adapter.
[88.036359]------------[ cut here ]------------
[88.036519]Call trace:
[88.036523] flush_workqueue+0x3e4/0x430
[88.036528] drain_workqueue+0xc4/0x160
[88.036533] destroy_workqueue+0x40/0x270
[88.036537] stmmac_fpe_stop_wq+0x4c/0x70
[88.036541] stmmac_release+0x278/0x280
[88.036546] __dev_close_many+0xcc/0x158
[88.036551] dev_close_many+0xbc/0x190
[88.036555] dev_close.part.0+0x70/0xc0
[88.036560] dev_close+0x24/0x30
[88.036564] stmmac_service_task+0x110/0x140
[88.036569] process_one_work+0x1d8/0x4a0
[88.036573] worker_thread+0x54/0x408
[88.036578] kthread+0x164/0x170
[88.036583] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[88.036588]---[ end trace e70de432e4d5c2c1 ]---
[88.036597]Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 0000000000000004</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26803 | net: veth: clear GRO when clearing XDP even when down</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26803</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: veth: clear GRO when clearing XDP even when down

veth sets NETIF_F_GRO automatically when XDP is enabled,
because both features use the same NAPI machinery.

The logic to clear NETIF_F_GRO sits in veth_disable_xdp() which
is called both on ndo_stop and when XDP is turned off.
To avoid the flag from being cleared when the device is brought
down, the clearing is skipped when IFF_UP is not set.
Bringing the device down should indeed not modify its features.

Unfortunately, this means that clearing is also skipped when
XDP is disabled _while_ the device is down. And there's nothing
on the open path to bring the device features back into sync.
IOW if user enables XDP, disables it and then brings the device
up we'll end up with a stray GRO flag set but no NAPI instances.

We don't depend on the GRO flag on the datapath, so the datapath
won't crash. We will crash (or hang), however, next time features
are sync'ed (either by user via ethtool or peer changing its config).
The GRO flag will go away, and veth will try to disable the NAPIs.
But the open path never created them since XDP was off, the GRO flag
was a stray. If NAPI was initialized before we'll hang in napi_disable().
If it never was we'll crash trying to stop uninitialized hrtimer.

Move the GRO flag updates to the XDP enable / disable paths,
instead of mixing them with the ndo_open / ndo_close paths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26804 | net: ip_tunnel: prevent perpetual headroom growth</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26804</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: ip_tunnel: prevent perpetual headroom growth

syzkaller triggered following kasan splat:
BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in __skb_flow_dissect+0x19d1/0x7a50 net/core/flow_dissector.c:1170
Read of size 1 at addr ffff88812fb4000e by task syz-executor183/5191
[..]
 kasan_report+0xda/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:588
 __skb_flow_dissect+0x19d1/0x7a50 net/core/flow_dissector.c:1170
 skb_flow_dissect_flow_keys include/linux/skbuff.h:1514 [inline]
 ___skb_get_hash net/core/flow_dissector.c:1791 [inline]
 __skb_get_hash+0xc7/0x540 net/core/flow_dissector.c:1856
 skb_get_hash include/linux/skbuff.h:1556 [inline]
 ip_tunnel_xmit+0x1855/0x33c0 net/ipv4/ip_tunnel.c:748
 ipip_tunnel_xmit+0x3cc/0x4e0 net/ipv4/ipip.c:308
 __netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4940 [inline]
 netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4954 [inline]
 xmit_one net/core/dev.c:3548 [inline]
 dev_hard_start_xmit+0x13d/0x6d0 net/core/dev.c:3564
 __dev_queue_xmit+0x7c1/0x3d60 net/core/dev.c:4349
 dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3134 [inline]
 neigh_connected_output+0x42c/0x5d0 net/core/neighbour.c:1592
 ...
 ip_finish_output2+0x833/0x2550 net/ipv4/ip_output.c:235
 ip_finish_output+0x31/0x310 net/ipv4/ip_output.c:323
 ..
 iptunnel_xmit+0x5b4/0x9b0 net/ipv4/ip_tunnel_core.c:82
 ip_tunnel_xmit+0x1dbc/0x33c0 net/ipv4/ip_tunnel.c:831
 ipgre_xmit+0x4a1/0x980 net/ipv4/ip_gre.c:665
 __netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4940 [inline]
 netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4954 [inline]
 xmit_one net/core/dev.c:3548 [inline]
 dev_hard_start_xmit+0x13d/0x6d0 net/core/dev.c:3564
 ...

The splat occurs because skb-&gt;data points past skb-&gt;head allocated area.
This is because neigh layer does:
  __skb_pull(skb, skb_network_offset(skb));

... but skb_network_offset() returns a negative offset and __skb_pull()
arg is unsigned.  IOW, we skb-&gt;data gets "adjusted" by a huge value.

The negative value is returned because skb-&gt;head and skb-&gt;data distance is
more than 64k and skb-&gt;network_header (u16) has wrapped around.

The bug is in the ip_tunnel infrastructure, which can cause
dev-&gt;needed_headroom to increment ad infinitum.

The syzkaller reproducer consists of packets getting routed via a gre
tunnel, and route of gre encapsulated packets pointing at another (ipip)
tunnel.  The ipip encapsulation finds gre0 as next output device.

This results in the following pattern:

1). First packet is to be sent out via gre0.
Route lookup found an output device, ipip0.

2).
ip_tunnel_xmit for gre0 bumps gre0-&gt;needed_headroom based on the future
output device, rt.dev-&gt;needed_headroom (ipip0).

3).
ip output / start_xmit moves skb on to ipip0. which runs the same
code path again (xmit recursion).

4).
Routing step for the post-gre0-encap packet finds gre0 as output device
to use for ipip0 encapsulated packet.

tunl0-&gt;needed_headroom is then incremented based on the (already bumped)
gre0 device headroom.

This repeats for every future packet:

gre0-&gt;needed_headroom gets inflated because previous packets' ipip0 step
incremented rt-&gt;dev (gre0) headroom, and ipip0 incremented because gre0
needed_headroom was increased.

For each subsequent packet, gre/ipip0-&gt;needed_headroom grows until
post-expand-head reallocations result in a skb-&gt;head/data distance of
more than 64k.

Once that happens, skb-&gt;network_header (u16) wraps around when
pskb_expand_head tries to make sure that skb_network_offset() is unchanged
after the headroom expansion/reallocation.

After this skb_network_offset(skb) returns a different (and negative)
result post headroom expansion.

The next trip to neigh layer (or anything else that would __skb_pull the
network header) makes skb-&gt;data point to a memory location outside
skb-&gt;head area.

v2: Cap the needed_headroom update to an arbitarily chosen upperlimit to
prevent perpetual increase instead of dropping the headroom increment
completely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26805 | netlink: Fix kernel-infoleak-after-free in __skb_datagram_iter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26805</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netlink: Fix kernel-infoleak-after-free in __skb_datagram_iter

syzbot reported the following uninit-value access issue [1]:

netlink_to_full_skb() creates a new `skb` and puts the `skb-&gt;data`
passed as a 1st arg of netlink_to_full_skb() onto new `skb`. The data
size is specified as `len` and passed to skb_put_data(). This `len`
is based on `skb-&gt;end` that is not data offset but buffer offset. The
`skb-&gt;end` contains data and tailroom. Since the tailroom is not
initialized when the new `skb` created, KMSAN detects uninitialized
memory area when copying the data.

This patch resolved this issue by correct the len from `skb-&gt;end` to
`skb-&gt;len`, which is the actual data offset.

BUG: KMSAN: kernel-infoleak-after-free in instrument_copy_to_user include/linux/instrumented.h:114 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: kernel-infoleak-after-free in copy_to_user_iter lib/iov_iter.c:24 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: kernel-infoleak-after-free in iterate_ubuf include/linux/iov_iter.h:29 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: kernel-infoleak-after-free in iterate_and_advance2 include/linux/iov_iter.h:245 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: kernel-infoleak-after-free in iterate_and_advance include/linux/iov_iter.h:271 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: kernel-infoleak-after-free in _copy_to_iter+0x364/0x2520 lib/iov_iter.c:186
 instrument_copy_to_user include/linux/instrumented.h:114 [inline]
 copy_to_user_iter lib/iov_iter.c:24 [inline]
 iterate_ubuf include/linux/iov_iter.h:29 [inline]
 iterate_and_advance2 include/linux/iov_iter.h:245 [inline]
 iterate_and_advance include/linux/iov_iter.h:271 [inline]
 _copy_to_iter+0x364/0x2520 lib/iov_iter.c:186
 copy_to_iter include/linux/uio.h:197 [inline]
 simple_copy_to_iter+0x68/0xa0 net/core/datagram.c:532
 __skb_datagram_iter+0x123/0xdc0 net/core/datagram.c:420
 skb_copy_datagram_iter+0x5c/0x200 net/core/datagram.c:546
 skb_copy_datagram_msg include/linux/skbuff.h:3960 [inline]
 packet_recvmsg+0xd9c/0x2000 net/packet/af_packet.c:3482
 sock_recvmsg_nosec net/socket.c:1044 [inline]
 sock_recvmsg net/socket.c:1066 [inline]
 sock_read_iter+0x467/0x580 net/socket.c:1136
 call_read_iter include/linux/fs.h:2014 [inline]
 new_sync_read fs/read_write.c:389 [inline]
 vfs_read+0x8f6/0xe00 fs/read_write.c:470
 ksys_read+0x20f/0x4c0 fs/read_write.c:613
 __do_sys_read fs/read_write.c:623 [inline]
 __se_sys_read fs/read_write.c:621 [inline]
 __x64_sys_read+0x93/0xd0 fs/read_write.c:621
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0x44/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

Uninit was stored to memory at:
 skb_put_data include/linux/skbuff.h:2622 [inline]
 netlink_to_full_skb net/netlink/af_netlink.c:181 [inline]
 __netlink_deliver_tap_skb net/netlink/af_netlink.c:298 [inline]
 __netlink_deliver_tap+0x5be/0xc90 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:325
 netlink_deliver_tap net/netlink/af_netlink.c:338 [inline]
 netlink_deliver_tap_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:347 [inline]
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1341 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x10f1/0x1250 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1368
 netlink_sendmsg+0x1238/0x13d0 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1910
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:745 [inline]
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x9c2/0xd60 net/socket.c:2584
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x28d/0x3c0 net/socket.c:2638
 __sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2667 [inline]
 __do_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2676 [inline]
 __se_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2674 [inline]
 __x64_sys_sendmsg+0x307/0x490 net/socket.c:2674
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0x44/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

Uninit was created at:
 free_pages_prepare mm/page_alloc.c:1087 [inline]
 free_unref_page_prepare+0xb0/0xa40 mm/page_alloc.c:2347
 free_unref_page_list+0xeb/0x1100 mm/page_alloc.c:2533
 release_pages+0x23d3/0x2410 mm/swap.c:1042
 free_pages_and_swap_cache+0xd9/0xf0 mm/swap_state.c:316
 tlb_batch_pages
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26806 | spi: cadence-qspi: remove system-wide suspend helper calls from runtime PM hooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26806</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: cadence-qspi: remove system-wide suspend helper calls from runtime PM hooks

The -&gt;runtime_suspend() and -&gt;runtime_resume() callbacks are not
expected to call spi_controller_suspend() and spi_controller_resume().
Remove calls to those in the cadence-qspi driver.

Those helpers have two roles currently:
 - They stop/start the queue, including dealing with the kworker.
 - They toggle the SPI controller SPI_CONTROLLER_SUSPENDED flag. It
   requires acquiring ctlr-&gt;bus_lock_mutex.

Step one is irrelevant because cadence-qspi is not queued. Step two
however has two implications:
 - A deadlock occurs, because -&gt;runtime_resume() is called in a context
   where the lock is already taken (in the -&gt;exec_op() callback, where
   the usage count is incremented).
 - It would disallow all operations once the device is auto-suspended.

Here is a brief call tree highlighting the mutex deadlock:

spi_mem_exec_op()
        ...
        spi_mem_access_start()
                mutex_lock(&amp;ctlr-&gt;bus_lock_mutex)

        cqspi_exec_mem_op()
                pm_runtime_resume_and_get()
                        cqspi_resume()
                                spi_controller_resume()
                                        mutex_lock(&amp;ctlr-&gt;bus_lock_mutex)
                ...

        spi_mem_access_end()
                mutex_unlock(&amp;ctlr-&gt;bus_lock_mutex)
        ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26807 | spi: cadence-qspi: fix pointer reference in runtime PM hooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26807</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: cadence-qspi: fix pointer reference in runtime PM hooks

dev_get_drvdata() gets used to acquire the pointer to cqspi and the SPI
controller. Neither embed the other; this lead to memory corruption.

On a given platform (Mobileye EyeQ5) the memory corruption is hidden
inside cqspi-&gt;f_pdata. Also, this uninitialised memory is used as a
mutex (ctlr-&gt;bus_lock_mutex) by spi_controller_suspend().</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30565 | An issue was discovered in SeaCMS version 12.9, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via admin notify.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30565</link><description>An issue was discovered in SeaCMS version 12.9, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via admin notify.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29006 | Apache CloudStack: x-forwarded-for HTTP header parsed by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29006</link><description>By default the CloudStack management server honours the x-forwarded-for HTTP header and logs it as the source IP of an API request. This could lead to authentication bypass and other operational problems should an attacker decide to spoof their IP address this way. Users are recommended to upgrade to CloudStack version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29007 | Apache CloudStack: When downloading templates or ISOs, the management server and SSVM follow HTTP redirects with potentially dangerous consequences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29007</link><description>The CloudStack management server and secondary storage VM could be tricked into making requests to restricted or random resources by means of following 301 HTTP redirects presented by external servers when downloading templates or ISOs. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29008 | Apache CloudStack: The extraconfig feature can be abused to load hypervisor resources on a VM instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29008</link><description>A problem has been identified in the CloudStack additional VM configuration (extraconfig) feature which can be misused by anyone who has privilege to deploy a VM instance or configure settings of an already deployed VM instance, to configure additional VM configuration even when the feature is not explicitly enabled by the administrator. In a KVM based CloudStack environment, an attacker can exploit this issue to attach host devices such as storage disks, and PCI and USB devices such as network adapters and GPUs, in a regular VM instance that can be further exploited to gain access to the underlying network and storage infrastructure resources, and access any VM instance disks on the local storage.

Users are advised to upgrade to version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25503 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Advanced REST Client v.17.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25503</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Advanced REST Client v.17.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the edit details parameter of the New Project function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-25730 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ZoneMinder before version 1.34.21, allows remote attackers execute arbitrary code, escalate priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25730</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ZoneMinder before version 1.34.21, allows remote attackers execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via PHP_SELF component in classic/views/download.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25199 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the MT Safeline X-Ray X3310 webserver version NXG 19.05 that enables a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25199</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the MT Safeline X-Ray X3310 webserver version NXG 19.05 that enables a remote attacker to execute JavaScript code and obtain sensitive information in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25200 | An HTML injection vulnerability exists in the MT Safeline X-Ray X3310 webserver version NXG 19.05 that enables a remote attacker to render m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25200</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability exists in the MT Safeline X-Ray X3310 webserver version NXG 19.05 that enables a remote attacker to render malicious HTML and obtain sensitive information in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29375 | CSV Injection vulnerability in Addactis IBNRS v.3.10.3.107 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .ibnrs file to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29375</link><description>CSV Injection vulnerability in Addactis IBNRS v.3.10.3.107 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .ibnrs file to the Project Description, Identifiers, Custom Triangle Name (inside Input Triangles) and Yield Curve Name parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 06:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28520 | File Upload vulnerability in Byzoro Networks Smart multi-service security gateway intelligent management platform version S210, allows an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28520</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Byzoro Networks Smart multi-service security gateway intelligent management platform version S210, allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the uploadfile.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 05:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1418 | The CGC Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1418</link><description>The CGC Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view protected posts via REST API even when maintenance mode is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 05:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31025 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ECshop 4.x allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the file/article.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31025</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ECshop 4.x allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the file/article.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 04:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2008 | The Modal Popup Box – Popup Builder, Show Offers And News in Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2008</link><description>The Modal Popup Box – Popup Builder, Show Offers And News in Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via deserialization of untrusted input in the awl_modal_popup_box_shortcode function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2830 | The WordPress Tag and Category Manager – AI Autotagger plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2830</link><description>The WordPress Tag and Category Manager – AI Autotagger plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'st_tag_cloud' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2919 | The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2919</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown and CountUp Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2803 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2803</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2868 | The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +12 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2868</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +12 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the slitems parameter in the WL Special Day Offer Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3022 | The BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient filename validation in the 'bookingpress_p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3022</link><description>The BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient filename validation in the 'bookingpress_process_upload' function in all versions up to, and including 1.0.87. This allows an authenticated attacker with administrator-level capabilities or higher to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3030 | The Announce from the Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3030</link><description>The Announce from the Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2692 | SiYuan 3.0.3 - RCE via Server Side XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2692</link><description>SiYuan version 3.0.3 allows executing arbitrary commands on the server. This is possible because the application is vulnerable to Server Side XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3274 | D-Link DNS-320L/DNS-320LW/DNS-327L HTTP GET Request info.cgi information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3274</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-320L, DNS-320LW and DNS-327L up to 20240403 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/info.cgi of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259285 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3272 | D-Link DNS-320L/DNS-325/DNS-327L/DNS-340L HTTP GET Request nas_sharing.cgi hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3272</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as very critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-320L, DNS-325, DNS-327L and DNS-340L up to 20240403. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/nas_sharing.cgi of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument user with the input messagebus leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259283. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3273 | D-Link DNS-320L/DNS-325/DNS-327L/DNS-340L HTTP GET Request nas_sharing.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3273</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-320L, DNS-325, DNS-327L and DNS-340L up to 20240403. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/nas_sharing.cgi of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument system leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259284. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25568 | OS command injection vulnerability in WRC-X3200GST3-B v1.25 and earlier, and WRC-G01-W v1.24 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25568</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability in WRC-X3200GST3-B v1.25 and earlier, and WRC-G01-W v1.24 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands by sending a specially crafted request to the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26258 | OS command injection vulnerability in WRC-X3200GST3-B v1.25 and earlier, and WRC-G01-W v1.24 and earlier allows a network-adjacent attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26258</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability in WRC-X3200GST3-B v1.25 and earlier, and WRC-G01-W v1.24 and earlier allows a network-adjacent attacker with credentials to execute arbitrary OS commands by sending a specially crafted request to the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29167 | SVR-116 firmware version 1.6.0.30028871 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to execute arbitrary OS comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29167</link><description>SVR-116 firmware version 1.6.0.30028871 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to execute arbitrary OS commands by sending a specially crafted request to the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29225 | WRC-X3200GST3-B v1.25 and earlier, and WRC-G01-W v1.24 and earlier allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain the configura...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29225</link><description>WRC-X3200GST3-B v1.25 and earlier, and WRC-G01-W v1.24 and earlier allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain the configuration file containing sensitive information by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>