<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:50:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-26279 | IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent improper output encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26279</link><description>IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent 10.0 through 10.1.7 could allow a local user to perform unauthorized actions due to improper encoding.  IBM X-Force ID:  248160.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-39008 | IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39008</link><description>IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent 10.0 through 10.1.7 could allow a privileged user to obtain sensitive information due to missing best practices. IBM X-Force ID: 213551.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49214 | Usedesk before 1.7.57 allows chat template injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49214</link><description>Usedesk before 1.7.57 allows chat template injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49215 | Usedesk before 1.7.57 allows filter reflected XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49215</link><description>Usedesk before 1.7.57 allows filter reflected XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49216 | Usedesk before 1.7.57 allows profile stored XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49216</link><description>Usedesk before 1.7.57 allows profile stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49213 | The API endpoints in Ironman PowerShell Universal 3.0.0 through 4.2.0 allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via crafted HTTP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49213</link><description>The API endpoints in Ironman PowerShell Universal 3.0.0 through 4.2.0 allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via crafted HTTP requests if a param block is used, due to invalid sanitization of input strings. The fixed versions are 3.10.2, 4.1.10, and 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 21:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47244 | WordPress Email Marketing for WooCommerce by Omnisend Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.8 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47244</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Omnisend Email Marketing for WooCommerce by Omnisend.This issue affects Email Marketing for WooCommerce by Omnisend: from n/a through 1.13.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 20:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47529 | WordPress Cloud Templates &amp;amp; Patterns collection Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47529</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in ThemeIsle Cloud Templates &amp; Patterns collection.This issue affects Cloud Templates &amp; Patterns collection: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 20:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49210 | The openssl (aka node-openssl) NPM package through 2.0.0 was characterized as "a nonsense wrapper with no real purpose" by its author, and a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49210</link><description>The openssl (aka node-openssl) NPM package through 2.0.0 was characterized as "a nonsense wrapper with no real purpose" by its author, and accepts an opts argument that contains a verb field (used for command execution). NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 20:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49208 | scheme/webauthn.c in Glewlwyd SSO server before 2.7.6 has a possible buffer overflow during FIDO2 credentials validation in webauthn registr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49208</link><description>scheme/webauthn.c in Glewlwyd SSO server before 2.7.6 has a possible buffer overflow during FIDO2 credentials validation in webauthn registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5972 | Kernel: the nfta_inner_num and nfta_expr_name netlink attributes accessed without checking its presence in nft_inner.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5972</link><description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the nft_inner.c functionality of netfilter in the Linux kernel. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system or escalate their privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44010 | An issue was discovered in ClickHouse before 22.9.1.2603. An attacker could send a crafted HTTP request to the HTTP Endpoint (usually listen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44010</link><description>An issue was discovered in ClickHouse before 22.9.1.2603. An attacker could send a crafted HTTP request to the HTTP Endpoint (usually listening on port 8123 by default), causing a heap-based buffer overflow that crashes the process. This does not require authentication. The fixed versions are 22.9.1.2603, 22.8.2.11, 22.7.4.16, 22.6.6.16, and 22.3.12.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44011 | An issue was discovered in ClickHouse before 22.9.1.2603. An authenticated user (with the ability to load data) could cause a heap buffer ov...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44011</link><description>An issue was discovered in ClickHouse before 22.9.1.2603. An authenticated user (with the ability to load data) could cause a heap buffer overflow and crash the server by inserting a malformed CapnProto object. The fixed versions are 22.9.1.2603, 22.8.2.11, 22.7.4.16, 22.6.6.16, and 22.3.12.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33202 | Bouncy Castle for Java before 1.73 contains a potential Denial of Service (DoS) issue within the Bouncy Castle org.bouncycastle.openssl.PEMP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33202</link><description>Bouncy Castle for Java before 1.73 contains a potential Denial of Service (DoS) issue within the Bouncy Castle org.bouncycastle.openssl.PEMParser class. This class parses OpenSSL PEM encoded streams containing X.509 certificates, PKCS8 encoded keys, and PKCS7 objects. Parsing a file that has crafted ASN.1 data through the PEMParser causes an OutOfMemoryError, which can enable a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41811 | Stored XSS Via Site News Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41811</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allowed Javascript code to be executed in the news section of the web console. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41812 | Uploading executables via the file manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41812</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This vulnerability allowed PHP executable files to be uploaded through the file manager. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41806 | Misassignment of privileges can cause DOS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41806</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Privilege Escalation. This vulnerability causes that a bad privilege assignment could cause a DOS attack that affects the availability of the Pandora FMS server. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41807 | Linux Local Privilege Escalation Via GoTTY Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41807</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Privilege Escalation. This vulnerability allows a user to escalate permissions on the system shell. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41808 | Arbitrary File Read As Root Via GoTTY Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41808</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Privilege Escalation. This vulnerability allows an unauthorised user to escalate and read sensitive files as if they were root. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41810 | Stored XSS Via Dashboard Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41810</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allowed Javascript code to be executed in some Widgets' text box. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41791 | Lack of Authorization and Stored XSS Via Translation Abuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41791</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allowed users with low privileges to introduce Javascript executables via a translation string that could affect the integrity of some configuration files. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41792 | Lack of Authorization and Stored XSS Via SNMP Trap Editor Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41792</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allowed Javascript code to be executed in the SNMP Trap Editor. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41789 | Unauthenticated Admin Account Takeover Via XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41789</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform cookie hijacking and log in as that user without the need for credentials. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41790 | Traversal Path on PHP file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41790</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Leveraging/Manipulating Configuration File Search Paths. This vulnerability allows to access the server configuration file and to compromise the database. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41787 | Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41787</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Leveraging/Manipulating Configuration File Search Paths. This vulnerability allows access to files with sensitive information. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 772.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41788 | Remote Code Execution via File Uploader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41788</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute code via PHP file uploads. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41786 | Database backups availability by low-privileged users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41786</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Pandora FMS on all allows File Discovery. This vulnerability allows users with low privileges to download database backups. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through 772.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6118 | Path Traversal in Neutron IP Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6118</link><description>: Path Traversal: '/../filedir' vulnerability in Neutron IP Camera allows Absolute Path Traversal.This issue affects IP Camera: before b1130.1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4677 | Unauthenticated Admin Account Takeover Via Cron Log File Backups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4677</link><description>Cron log backup files contain administrator session IDs. It is trivial for any attacker who can reach the Pandora FMS Console to scrape the cron logs directory for cron log backups. The contents of these log files can then be abused to authenticate to the application as an administrator. This issue affects Pandora FMS &lt;= 772.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4593 | Path Traversal in BVRP Software SLmail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4593</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability whose exploitation could allow an authenticated remote user to bypass SecurityManager's intended restrictions and list a parent directory via any filename, such as a multiple ..%2F value affecting the 'dodoc' parameter in the /MailAdmin_dll.htm file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 12:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4594 | Cross-site Scripting in BVRP Software SLmail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4594</link><description>Stored XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to store a malicious JavaScript payload via GET and POST methods on multiple parameters in the MailAdmin_dll.htm file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 12:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4595 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory in BVRP Software SLmail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4595</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability has been found, the exploitation of which could allow a remote user to retrieve sensitive information stored on the server such as credential files, configuration files, application files, etc., simply by appending any of the following parameters to the end of the URL: %00 %0a, %20, %2a, %a0, %aa, %c0 and %ca.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 12:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4406 | XSS in KC Group&amp;#x27;s E-Commerce Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4406</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in KC Group E-Commerce Software allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects E-Commerce Software: through 20231123. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43123 | Apache Storm: Local Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Storm-core on Unix-Like systems due temporary files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43123</link><description>On unix-like systems, the temporary directory is shared between all user. As such, writing to this directory using APIs that do not explicitly set the file/directory permissions can lead to information disclosure. Of note, this does not impact modern MacOS Operating Systems.

The method File.createTempFile on unix-like systems creates a file with predefined name (so easily identifiable) and by default will create this file with the permissions -rw-r--r--. Thus, if sensitive information is written to this file, other local users can read this information.

File.createTempFile(String, String) will create a temporary file in the system temporary directory if the 'java.io.tmpdir' system property is not explicitly set. 

This affects the class  https://github.com/apache/storm/blob/master/storm-core/src/jvm/org/apache/storm/utils/TopologySpoutLag.java#L99  and was introduced by  https://issues.apache.org/jira/browse/STORM-3123 

In practice, this has a very limited impact as this class is used only if ui.disable.spout.lag.monitoring

 is set to false, but its value is true by default.
Moreover, the temporary file gets deleted soon after its creation.

The solution is to use  Files.createTempFile https://docs.oracle.com/en/java/javase/11/docs/api/java.base/java/nio/file/Files.html#createTempFile(java.lang.String,java.lang.String,java.nio.file.attribute.FileAttribute...)  instead.

We recommend that all users upgrade to the latest version of Apache Storm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3631 | SQLi in Medart Notification Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Medart Health Services Medart Notification Panel allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Medart Notification Panel: through 20231123. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28813 | An attacker could exploit a vulnerability by sending crafted messages to computers installed with this plug-in to modify plug-in parameters,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28813</link><description>An attacker could exploit a vulnerability by sending crafted messages to computers installed with this plug-in to modify plug-in parameters, which could cause affected computers to download malicious files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28812 | There is a buffer overflow vulnerability in a web browser plug-in could allow an attacker to exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28812</link><description>There is a buffer overflow vulnerability in a web browser plug-in could allow an attacker to exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted messages to computers installed with this plug-in, which could lead to arbitrary code execution or cause process exception of the plug-in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3377 | SQLi in Veribilim&amp;#x27;s Veribase</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3377</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Veribilim Software Computer Veribase allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Veribase: through 20231123. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44290 | Dell Command | Monitor versions prior to 10.10.0, contain an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44290</link><description>Dell Command | Monitor versions prior to 10.10.0, contain an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could potentially exploit this vulnerability while repairing/changing installation, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28811 | There is a buffer overflow in the password recovery feature of Hikvision NVR/DVR models. If exploited, an attacker on the same local area ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28811</link><description>There is a buffer overflow in the password recovery feature of Hikvision NVR/DVR models. If exploited, an attacker on the same local area network (LAN) could cause the device to malfunction by sending specially crafted packets to an unpatched device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44289 | Dell Command | Configure versions prior to 4.11.0, contain an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44289</link><description>Dell Command | Configure versions prior to 4.11.0, contain an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could potentially exploit this vulnerability while repairing/changing installation, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43086 | Dell Command | Configure, versions prior to 4.11.0, contains an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious user could potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43086</link><description>Dell Command | Configure, versions prior to 4.11.0, contains an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious user could potentially modify files inside installation folder during application upgrade, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39253 | Dell OS Recovery Tool, versions 2.2.4013, 2.3.7012.0, and 2.3.7515.0 contain an Improper Access Control Vulnerability. A local authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39253</link><description>Dell OS Recovery Tool, versions 2.2.4013, 2.3.7012.0, and 2.3.7515.0 contain an Improper Access Control Vulnerability. A local authenticated non-administrator user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the elevation of privilege on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41140 | A maliciously crafted PRT file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow. A malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41140</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 04:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41139 | A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to dereference an untrusted pointer. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41139</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to dereference an untrusted pointer. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29076 | A maliciously crafted MODEL, SLDASM, SAT or CATPART file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 could cause memory corruption vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29076</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL, SLDASM, SAT or CATPART file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 could cause memory corruption vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29074 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause an Out-Of-Bounds Write. A malicio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29074</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause an Out-Of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29075 | A maliciously crafted PRT file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause an Out-Of-Bounds Write. A malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29075</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause an Out-Of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29073 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow. A mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29073</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD 2024 and 2023 can be used to cause a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40002 | WordPress Booster for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40002</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Pluggabl LLC Booster for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 7.1.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 02:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47668 | WordPress Restrict Content Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47668</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in StellarWP Membership Plugin – Restrict Content plugin &lt;= 3.2.7 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 02:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23978 | WordPress WP Client Reports Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.16 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23978</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in SwitchWP WP Client Reports plugin &lt;= 1.0.16 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30581 | The use of __proto__ in process.mainModule.__proto__.require() can bypass the policy mechanism and require modules outside of the policy.jso...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30581</link><description>The use of __proto__ in process.mainModule.__proto__.require() can bypass the policy mechanism and require modules outside of the policy.json definition. This vulnerability affects all users using the experimental policy mechanism in all active release lines: v16, v18 and, v20.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the policy is an experimental feature of Node.js</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47790 | WordPress Pz-LinkCard Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47790</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Poporon Pz-LinkCard plugin &lt;= 2.4.8 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47839 | WordPress eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.26 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47839</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in impleCode eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress plugin &lt;= 3.3.26 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47833 | WordPress Theater for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.18.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47833</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeroen Schmit Theater for WordPress plugin &lt;= 0.18.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47834 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master plugin &lt;= 8.1.13 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47835 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.32 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47835</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder plugin &lt;= 1.2.32 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47821 | WordPress Email Encoder Bundle Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47821</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jannis Thuemmig Email Encoder plugin &lt;= 2.1.8 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47829 | WordPress Quick Call Button Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47829</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codez Quick Call Button plugin &lt;= 1.2.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47831 | WordPress DrawIt (draw.io) Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47831</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in assorted[chips] DrawIt (draw.Io) plugin &lt;= 1.1.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47817 | WordPress Daily Prayer Time Plugin &amp;lt;= 2023.10.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47817</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mmrs151 Daily Prayer Time plugin &lt;= 2023.10.13 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47816 | WordPress Charitable Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47816</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Charitable Donations &amp; Fundraising Team Donation Forms by Charitable plugin &lt;= 1.7.0.13 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47815 | WordPress BP Profile Shortcodes Extra Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47815</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Venutius BP Profile Shortcodes Extra plugin &lt;= 2.5.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47813 | WordPress Better RSS Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47813</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in grandslambert Better RSS Widget plugin &lt;= 2.8.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47814 | WordPress BMI Calculator Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47814</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Waterloo Plugins BMI Calculator Plugin plugin &lt;= 1.0.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47812 | WordPress Bamboo Columns Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47812</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bamboo Mcr Bamboo Columns plugin &lt;= 1.6.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47811 | WordPress Anywhere Flash Embed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47811</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Suresh KUMAR Mukhiya Anywhere Flash Embed plugin &lt;= 1.0.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48107 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zlib-ng minizip-ng v.4.0.2 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the mz_path_h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48107</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zlib-ng minizip-ng v.4.0.2 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the mz_path_has_slash function in the mz_os.c file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47809 | WordPress Accordion Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47809</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themepoints Accordion plugin &lt;= 2.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47810 | WordPress Ajax Domain Checker Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47810</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Asdqwe Dev Ajax Domain Checker plugin &lt;= 1.3.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48105 | An heap overflow vulnerability was discovered in Bytecode alliance wasm-micro-runtime v.1.2.3 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48105</link><description>An heap overflow vulnerability was discovered in Bytecode alliance wasm-micro-runtime v.1.2.3 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the wasm_loader_prepare_bytecode function in core/iwasm/interpreter/wasm_loader.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47773 | WordPress Permalinks Customizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47773</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in YAS Global Team Permalinks Customizer plugin &lt;= 2.8.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47786 | WordPress LayerSlider Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47786</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LayerSlider plugin &lt;= 7.7.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47808 | WordPress Add Widgets to Page Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47808</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Christina Uechi Add Widgets to Page plugin &lt;= 1.3.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47767 | WordPress Interactive World Map Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47767</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fla-shop.Com Interactive World Map plugin &lt;= 3.2.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47768 | WordPress Footer Putter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47768</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Russell Jamieson Footer Putter plugin &lt;= 1.17 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48706 | Vim has heap-use-after-free at /src/charset.c:1770:12 in skipwhite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48706</link><description>Vim is a UNIX editor that, prior to version 9.0.2121, has a heap-use-after-free vulnerability. When executing a `:s` command for the very first time and using a sub-replace-special atom inside the substitution part, it is possible that the recursive `:s` call causes free-ing of memory which may later then be accessed by the initial `:s` command. The user must intentionally execute the payload and the whole process is a bit tricky to do since it seems to work only reliably for the very first :s command. It may also cause a crash of Vim. Version 9.0.2121 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47766 | WordPress Post Status Notifier Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47766</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Timo Reith Post Status Notifier Lite plugin &lt;= 1.11.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49146 | DOMSanitizer (aka dom-sanitizer) before 1.0.7 allows XSS via an SVG document because of mishandling of comments and greedy regular expressio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49146</link><description>DOMSanitizer (aka dom-sanitizer) before 1.0.7 allows XSS via an SVG document because of mishandling of comments and greedy regular expressions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49102 | NZBGet 21.1 allows authenticated remote code execution because the unarchive programs (7za and unrar) preserve executable file permissions. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49102</link><description>NZBGet 21.1 allows authenticated remote code execution because the unarchive programs (7za and unrar) preserve executable file permissions. An attacker with the Control capability can execute a file by setting the value of SevenZipCommand or UnrarCmd. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30496 | WordPress Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30496</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MagePeople Team WpBusTicketly plugin &lt;= 5.2.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47759 | WordPress Chaty Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47759</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Premio Chaty plugin &lt;= 3.1.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6265 | DrayTek Vigor2960 mainfunction.cgi dumpSyslog &amp;#x27;option&amp;#x27; directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6265</link><description>Draytek Vigor2960 v1.5.1.4 and v1.5.1.5 are vulnerable to directory traversal via the mainfunction.cgi dumpSyslog 'option' parameter allowing an authenticated attacker with access to the web management interface to delete arbitrary files. Vigor2960 is no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47825 | WordPress WP EXtra Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47825</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in TienCOP WP EXtra plugin &lt;= 6.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47824 | WordPress Legal Pages Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47824</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpWax Legal Pages – Privacy Policy, Terms &amp; Conditions, GDPR, CCPA, and Cookie Notice Generator plugin &lt;= 1.3.8 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25682 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25682</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.8 and 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.1 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  247034.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39925 | WordPress Community by PeepSo Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.6.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39925</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PeepSo Download Community by PeepSo plugin &lt;= 6.1.6.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47819 | WordPress Easy Call Now by ThikShare Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47819</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Dang Ngoc Binh Easy Call Now by ThikShare plugin &lt;= 1.1.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47791 | WordPress Leadster Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47791</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Leadster plugin &lt;= 1.1.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47792 | WordPress Big File Uploads Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47792</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Infinite Uploads Big File Uploads – Increase Maximum File Upload Size plugin &lt;= 2.1.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6264 | Information leak in Content-Security-Policy header in Devolutions Server 2023.3.7.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to list the configure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6264</link><description>Information leak in Content-Security-Policy header in Devolutions Server 2023.3.7.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to list the configured Devolutions Gateways endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47785 | WordPress LayerSlider Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47785</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in LayerSlider plugin &lt;= 7.7.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36777 | IBM Cloud Pak for Security information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36777</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security (CP4S) 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.16.0could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive version information that could aid in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  233665.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47775 | WordPress wpDiscuz Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47775</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in gVectors Team Comments — wpDiscuz plugin &lt;= 7.6.11 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47781 | WordPress Thrive Theme Builder Theme &amp;lt; 3.24.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47781</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Thrive Themes Thrive Theme Builder &lt;= 3.24.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47755 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Carousel Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47755</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AazzTech WooCommerce Product Carousel Slider plugin &lt;= 3.3.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47758 | WordPress Multi Step Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47758</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mondula GmbH Multi Step Form plugin &lt;= 1.7.11 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47765 | WordPress CodeBard&amp;#x27;s Patron Button and Widgets for Patreon Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47765</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CodeBard CodeBard's Patron Button and Widgets for Patreon plugin &lt;= 2.1.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25986 | WordPress PayGreen Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25986</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WattIsIt PayGreen – Ancienne version plugin &lt;= 4.10.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6263 | Server Spoofing Vulnerability in NxCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6263</link><description>An issue was discovered in Network Optix NxCloud before 23.1.0.40440. It was possible to add a fake VMS server to NxCloud by using the exact identification of a legitimate VMS server. As result, it was possible to retrieve authorization headers from legitimate users when the legitimate client connects to the fake VMS server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25987 | WordPress YouTube Channel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.23.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25987</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aleksandar Urošević My YouTube Channel plugin &lt;= 3.23.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48646 | Zoho ManageEngine RecoveryManager Plus before 6070 allows admin users to execute arbitrary commands via proxy settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48646</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine RecoveryManager Plus before 6070 allows admin users to execute arbitrary commands via proxy settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43887 | Libde265 v1.0.12 was discovered to contain multiple buffer overflows via the num_tile_columns and num_tile_row parameters in the function pi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43887</link><description>Libde265 v1.0.12 was discovered to contain multiple buffer overflows via the num_tile_columns and num_tile_row parameters in the function pic_parameter_set::dump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47467 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in jeecg-boot v.3.6.0 allows a remote privileged attacker to obtain sensitive information via the file dir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47467</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in jeecg-boot v.3.6.0 allows a remote privileged attacker to obtain sensitive information via the file directory structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48106 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zlib-ng minizip-ng v.4.0.2 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the mz_path_r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48106</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zlib-ng minizip-ng v.4.0.2 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the mz_path_resolve function in the mz_os.c file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47250 | In mprivacy-tools before 2.0.406g in m-privacy TightGate-Pro Server, broken Access Control on X11 server sockets allows authenticated attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47250</link><description>In mprivacy-tools before 2.0.406g in m-privacy TightGate-Pro Server, broken Access Control on X11 server sockets allows authenticated attackers (with access to a VNC session) to access the X11 desktops of other users by specifying their DISPLAY ID. This allows complete control of their desktop, including the ability to inject keystrokes and perform a keylogging attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47251 | In mprivacy-tools before 2.0.406g in m-privacy TightGate-Pro Server, a Directory Traversal in the print function of the VNC service allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47251</link><description>In mprivacy-tools before 2.0.406g in m-privacy TightGate-Pro Server, a Directory Traversal in the print function of the VNC service allows authenticated attackers (with access to a VNC session) to automatically transfer malicious PDF documents by moving them into the .spool directory, and then sending a signal to the VNC service, which automatically transfers them to the connected VNC client's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46357 | In the module "Cross Selling in Modal Cart" (motivationsale) &lt; 3.5.0 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46357</link><description>In the module "Cross Selling in Modal Cart" (motivationsale) &lt; 3.5.0 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `motivationsaleDataModel::getProductsByIds()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47014 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Sticky Notes App Using PHP with Source Code v.1.0 allows a local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47014</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Sticky Notes App Using PHP with Source Code v.1.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to add-note.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20084 | A vulnerability in the endpoint software of Cisco Secure Endpoint for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to evade endpoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20084</link><description>A vulnerability in the endpoint software of Cisco Secure Endpoint for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to evade endpoint protection within a limited time window. This vulnerability is due to a timing issue that occurs between various software components. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to put a malicious file into a specific folder and then persuading the user to execute the file within a limited time window. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the endpoint software to fail to quarantine the malicious file or kill its process. Note: This vulnerability only applies to deployments that have the Windows Folder Redirection feature enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20240 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Secure Client Software, formerly AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client, could allow an authenticated, local at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20240</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Secure Client Software, formerly AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client, could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. These vulnerabilities are due to an out-of-bounds memory read from Cisco Secure Client Software. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by logging in to an affected device at the same time that another user is accessing Cisco Secure Client on the same system, and then sending crafted packets to a port on that local host. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the VPN Agent service, causing it to be unavailable to all users of the system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on a multi-user system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20241 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Secure Client Software, formerly AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client, could allow an authenticated, local at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20241</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Secure Client Software, formerly AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client, could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due to an out-of-bounds memory read from Cisco Secure Client Software. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by logging in to an affected device at the same time that another user is accessing Cisco Secure Client on the same system, and then sending crafted packets to a port on that local host. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the VPN Agent service, causing it to be unavailable to all users of the system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on a multi-user system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45377 | In the module "Chronopost Official" (chronopost) for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script PHP `cancelSkybill.php` own a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45377</link><description>In the module "Chronopost Official" (chronopost) for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script PHP `cancelSkybill.php` own a sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47315 | Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control due to a hard-coded JWT Secret.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47315</link><description>Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control due to a hard-coded JWT Secret.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47316 | Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The Web panel allows users to gain access to potentially sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47316</link><description>Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The Web panel allows users to gain access to potentially sensitive API calls such as listing users and their data, file management API calls and audit-related API calls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6156 | Livestatus injection in availability timeline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6156</link><description>Improper neutralization of livestatus command delimiters in the availability timeline in Checkmk &lt;= 2.0.0p39, &lt; 2.1.0p37, and &lt; 2.2.0p15 allows arbitrary livestatus command execution for authorized users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6157 | Livestatus injection in ajax_search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6157</link><description>Improper neutralization of livestatus command delimiters in ajax_search in Checkmk &lt;= 2.0.0p39, &lt; 2.1.0p37, and &lt; 2.2.0p15 allows arbitrary livestatus command execution for authorized users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43082 | Dell Unity prior to 5.3 contains a 'man in the middle' vulnerability in the vmadapter component. If a customer has a certificate signed by a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43082</link><description>Dell Unity prior to 5.3 contains a 'man in the middle' vulnerability in the vmadapter component. If a customer has a certificate signed by a third-party public Certificate Authority, the vCenter CA could be spoofed by an attacker who can obtain a CA-signed certificate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47312 | Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control due to Login Credential Leakage via Audit Entries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47312</link><description>Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control due to Login Credential Leakage via Audit Entries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47313 | Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47313</link><description>Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47314 | Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Uncontrolled File Upload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47314</link><description>Headwind MDM Web panel 5.22.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Uncontrolled File Upload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47350 | SwiftyEdit Content Management System prior to v1.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47350</link><description>SwiftyEdit Content Management System prior to v1.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2437 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to insufficient...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2437</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during a Facebook login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email. An attacker can leverage CVE-2023-2448 and CVE-2023-2446 to get the user's email address to successfully exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2438 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.0. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2438</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'userpro_save_userdata' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the user meta and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2440 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2440</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to missing nonce validation in the 'admin_page', 'userpro_verify_user' and 'verifyUnverifyAllUsers' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the role of verified users to elevate verified user privileges to that of any user such as 'administrator' via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2448 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'userpro_shortcode_te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2448</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'userpro_shortcode_template' function in versions up to, and including, 5.1.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrary shortcode execution. An attacker can leverage CVE-2023-2446 to get sensitive information via shortcode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2449 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized password resets in versions up to, and including 5.1.1. This is due to the pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2449</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized password resets in versions up to, and including 5.1.1. This is due to the plugin using native password reset functionality, with insufficient validation on the password reset function (userpro_process_form). The function uses the plaintext value of a password reset key instead of a hashed value which means it can easily be retrieved and subsequently used. An attacker can leverage CVE-2023-2448 and CVE-2023-2446, or another vulnerability like SQL Injection in another plugin or theme installed on the site to successfully exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2497 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.0. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2497</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'import_settings' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to exploit PHP Object Injection due to the use of unserialize() on the user supplied parameter via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2841 | The Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the id parameter in versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2841</link><description>The Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the id parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.5.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with admin-level privileges to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4686 | The WP Customer Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3.6.6 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4686</link><description>The WP Customer Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3.6.6 via the ajax_enabled_posts function. This can allow authenticated attackers to extract sensitive data such as post titles and slugs, including those of protected and trashed posts and pages in addition to other post types such as galleries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4726 | The Ultimate Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4726</link><description>The Ultimate Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and including, 3.7.7. due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5048 | The WDContactFormBuilder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Contact_Form_Builder' shortcode in versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5048</link><description>The WDContactFormBuilder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Contact_Form_Builder' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0.72 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on 'id' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5096 | The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'csvsearch' shortcode...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5096</link><description>The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'csvsearch' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5128 | The TCD Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'map' shortcode in versions up to, and including, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5128</link><description>The TCD Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'map' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5163 | The Weather Atlas Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortcode-weather-atlas' shortcode in versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5163</link><description>The Weather Atlas Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortcode-weather-atlas' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5234 | The Related Products for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'woo-related' shortcode in versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5234</link><description>The Related Products for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'woo-related' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5314 | The WP EXtra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access to restricted functionality due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5314</link><description>The WP EXtra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access to restricted functionality due to a missing capability check on the 'test-email' section of the register() function in versions up to, and including, 6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as a subscriber, to send emails with arbitrary content to arbitrary locations from the affected site's mail server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5338 | The Theme Blvd Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5338</link><description>The Theme Blvd Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5382 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This is due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5382</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the fnsf_delete_posts function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5383 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This is due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5383</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the fnsf_copy_posts function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create copies of arbitrary posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5385 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5385</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_copy_posts function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to create copies of arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5386 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5386</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_delete_posts function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to delete arbitrary posts, including administrator posts, and posts not related to the Funnelforms Free plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5387 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5387</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_af2_trigger_dark_mode function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to enable or disable the dark mode plugin setting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5411 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5411</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_af2_save_post function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to modify certain post values. Note that the extent of modification is limited due to fixed values passed to the wp_update_post function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5415 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5415</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_add_category function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to add new categories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5416 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5416</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_delete_category function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to delete categories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5417 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5417</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_update_category function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to modify the Funnelforms category for a given post ID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5419 | The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5419</link><description>The Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fnsf_af2_test_mail function in versions up to, and including, 3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to send test emails to an arbitrary email address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5465 | The Popup with fancybox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5465</link><description>The Popup with fancybox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5466 | The Wp anything slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.1 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5466</link><description>The Wp anything slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5469 | The Drop Shadow Boxes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'dropshadowbox' shortcode in versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5469</link><description>The Drop Shadow Boxes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'dropshadowbox' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.7.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5537 | The Delete Usermeta plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This is due to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5537</link><description>The Delete Usermeta plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This is due to missing nonce validation on the delumet_options_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to remove user meta for arbitrary users via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5662 | The Sponsors plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sponsors' shortcode in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5662</link><description>The Sponsors plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sponsors' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5664 | The Garden Gnome Package plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ggpkg' shortcode in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5664</link><description>The Garden Gnome Package plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ggpkg' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This was partially patched in version 2.2.7 and fully patched in version 2.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5667 | The Tab Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5667</link><description>The Tab Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5704 | The CPO Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5704</link><description>The CPO Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5706 | The VK Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vk-blocks/ancestor-page-list' block in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5706</link><description>The VK Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vk-blocks/ancestor-page-list' block in all versions up to, and including, 1.63.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5708 | The WP Post Columns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'column' shortcode in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5708</link><description>The WP Post Columns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'column' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5715 | The Website Optimization – Plerdy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's tracking code settings ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5715</link><description>The Website Optimization – Plerdy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's tracking code settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5742 | The EasyRotator for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'easyrotator' shortcode in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5742</link><description>The EasyRotator for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'easyrotator' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5815 | The News &amp; Blog Designer Pack – WordPress Blog Plugin — (Blog Post Grid, Blog Post Slider, Blog Post Carousel, Blog Post Ticker, Blog Post M...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5815</link><description>The News &amp; Blog Designer Pack – WordPress Blog Plugin — (Blog Post Grid, Blog Post Slider, Blog Post Carousel, Blog Post Ticker, Blog Post Masonry) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1 via the bdp_get_more_post function hooked via a nopriv AJAX. This is due to function utilizing an unsafe extract() method to extract values from the POST variable and passing that input to the include() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include arbitrary PHP files and achieve remote code execution. On vulnerable Docker configurations it may be possible for an attacker to create a PHP file and then subsequently include it to achieve RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5822 | The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload - Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads to insufficient file ty...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5822</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload - Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads to insufficient file type validation in the 'dnd_upload_cf7_upload' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This can be exploited if a user authorized to edit form, which means editor privileges or above, has added a 'multiple file upload' form field with '*' acceptable file types.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6007 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, loss of data due to a missing capabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6007</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete user meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6008 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6008</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete user meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6009 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 5.1.4 due to insufficient restricti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6009</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 5.1.4 due to insufficient restriction on the 'userpro_update_user_profile' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as a subscriber, to modify their user role by supplying the 'wp_capabilities' parameter during a profile update.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6160 | The LifterLMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for eLearning plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and includin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6160</link><description>The LifterLMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for eLearning plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and including, 7.4.2 via the maybe_serve_export function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator or LMS manager access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary CSV files on the server, which can contain sensitive information as well as removing those files from the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6164 | The MainWP Dashboard  – WordPress Manager for Multiple Websites Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSS Injection via the ‘new...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6164</link><description>The MainWP Dashboard  – WordPress Manager for Multiple Websites Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSS Injection via the ‘newColor’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary CSS values into the site tags.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48705 | nautobot has XSS potential in custom links, job buttons, and computed fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48705</link><description>Nautobot is a Network Source of Truth and Network Automation Platform built as a web application All users of Nautobot versions earlier than 1.6.6 or 2.0.5 are potentially affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability. Due to incorrect usage of Django's `mark_safe()` API when rendering certain types of user-authored content; including custom links, job buttons, and computed fields; it is possible that users with permission to create or edit these types of content could craft a malicious payload (such as JavaScript code) that would be executed when rendering pages containing this content. The maintainers have fixed the incorrect uses of `mark_safe()` (generally by replacing them with appropriate use of `format_html()` instead) to prevent such malicious data from being executed. Users on Nautobot 1.6.x LTM should upgrade to v1.6.6 and users on Nautobot 2.0.x should upgrade to v2.0.5. Appropriate object permissions can and should be applied to restrict which users are permitted to create or edit the aforementioned types of user-authored content. Other than that, there is no direct workaround available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26542 | WordPress phpinfo() WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26542</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Exeebit phpinfo() WP plugin &lt;= 4.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47380 | Admidio v4.2.12 and below is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47380</link><description>Admidio v4.2.12 and below is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26535 | WordPress Sheets To WP Table Live Sync Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.15 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26535</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPPOOL Sheets To WP Table Live Sync plugin &lt;= 2.12.15 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26532 | WordPress Social Auto Poster Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26532</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AccessPress Themes Social Auto Poster plugin &lt;= 2.1.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27457 | WordPress Add Expires Headers &amp;amp; Optimized Minify Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27457</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Passionate Brains Add Expires Headers &amp; Optimized Minify plugin &lt;= 2.7 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27458 | WordPress WpStream – Live Streaming, Video on Demand, Pay Per View Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27458</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpstream WpStream plugin &lt;= 4.4.10 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27461 | WordPress When Last Login Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27461</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yoohoo Plugins When Last Login plugin &lt;= 1.2.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27451 | WordPress Instant Images Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0.2 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27451</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Darren Cooney Instant Images plugin &lt;= 5.1.0.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27453 | WordPress LWS Tools Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27453</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in LWS LWS Tools plugin &lt;= 2.3.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6252 | Path traversal vulnerability in Chameleon Power products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6252</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in Chalemelon Power framework, affecting the getImage parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to read files located on the server and gain access to sensitive information such as configuration files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2889 | SQLi in Veon Computer&amp;#x27;s Service Tracking Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Veon Computer Service Tracking Software allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Service Tracking Software: through 20231122. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27442 | WordPress Leyka Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.29.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27442</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Teplitsa of social technologies Leyka plugin &lt;= 3.29.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27444 | WordPress DecaLog Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27444</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pierre Lannoy / PerfOps One DecaLog plugin &lt;= 3.7.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27446 | WordPress DeepL Pro API translation Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27446</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Fluenx DeepL API translation plugin &lt;= 2.1.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27633 | WordPress Customify Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27633</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pixelgrade Customify – Intuitive Website Styling plugin &lt;= 2.10.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28747 | WordPress CBX Currency Converter Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28747</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in codeboxr CBX Currency Converter plugin &lt;= 3.0.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28749 | WordPress CM On Demand Search And Replace Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28749</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM On Demand Search And Replace plugin &lt;= 1.3.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43081 | PowerProtect Agent for File System Version 19.14 and prior, contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability in ddfscon component. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43081</link><description>PowerProtect Agent for File System Version 19.14 and prior, contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability in ddfscon component. A low Privileged local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to overwriting of log files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3104 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Unitree Robotics A1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3104</link><description>Lack of authentication vulnerability. An unauthenticated local user is able to see through the cameras using the web server due to the lack of any form of authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5983 | Information Disclosure in Botanik Software Pharmacy Automation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5983</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Botanik Software Pharmacy Automation allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Pharmacy Automation: before 2.1.133.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3103 | Authentication Bypass by Spoofing in Unitree Robotics A1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3103</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability, the exploitation of which could allow a local attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack on the robot's camera video stream. In addition, if a MITM attack is carried out, it is possible to consume the robot's resources, which could lead to a denial-of-service (DOS) condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5047 | SQLi in DRDrive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5047</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in DRD Fleet Leasing DRDrive allows SQL Injection.This issue affects DRDrive: before 20231006.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6253 | Saved Uninstall Key in Digital Guardian Agent Uninstaller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6253</link><description>A saved encryption key in the Uninstaller in Digital Guardian's Agent before version 7.9.4 allows a local attacker to retrieve the uninstall key and remove the software by extracting the uninstaller key from the memory of the uninstaller file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6117 | M-Files REST API allows Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6117</link><description>A possibility of unwanted server memory consumption was detected through the obsolete functionalities in the Rest API methods of the M-Files server

 before 23.11.13156.0 which allows attackers to execute DoS attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 10:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6189 | Improper Permission Handling in M-Files Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6189</link><description>Missing access permissions checks

 in the M-Files server before 23.11.13156.0 allow attackers to perform data write and export

jobs using the M-Files API methods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 10:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46673 | It was identified that malformed scripts used in the script processor of an Ingest Pipeline could cause an Elasticsearch node to crash when ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46673</link><description>It was identified that malformed scripts used in the script processor of an Ingest Pipeline could cause an Elasticsearch node to crash when calling the Simulate Pipeline API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37924 | Apache Submarine: SQL injection from unauthorized login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37924</link><description>Apache Software Foundation Apache Submarine has an SQL injection vulnerability when a user logs in. This issue can result in unauthorized login.
Now we have fixed this issue and now user must have the correct login to access workbench.
This issue affects Apache Submarine: from 0.7.0 before 0.8.0. We recommend that all submarine users with 0.7.0 upgrade to 0.8.0, which not only fixes the issue, supports the oidc authentication mode, but also removes the case of unauthenticated logins.
If using the version lower than 0.8.0 and not want to upgrade, you can try cherry-pick PR  https://github.com/apache/submarine/pull/1037 https://github.com/apache/submarine/pull/1054  and rebuild the submarine-server image to fix this.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6011 | Stored XSS in Geodi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6011</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DECE Software Geodi allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Geodi: before 8.0.0.27396.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5921 | Function Bypass in Geodi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5921</link><description>Improper Enforcement of Behavioral Workflow vulnerability in DECE Software Geodi allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Geodi: before 8.0.0.27396.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2446 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure via the 'userpro' shortcode in versions up to, and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2446</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure via the 'userpro' shortcode in versions up to, and including 5.1.1. This is due to insufficient restriction on sensitive user meta values that can be called via that shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions, and above to retrieve sensitive user meta that can be used to gain access to a high privileged user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2447 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2447</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'export_users' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export the users to a csv file, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41145 | Autodesk users who no longer have an active license for an account can still access cases for that account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41145</link><description>Autodesk users who no longer have an active license for an account can still access cases for that account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41146 | Autodesk Customer Support Portal allows cases created by users under an account to see cases created by other users on the same account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41146</link><description>Autodesk Customer Support Portal allows cases created by users under an account to see cases created by other users on the same account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47392 | An access control issue in Mercedes me IOS APP v1.34.0 and below allows attackers to view the carts of other users via sending a crafted add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47392</link><description>An access control issue in Mercedes me IOS APP v1.34.0 and below allows attackers to view the carts of other users via sending a crafted add order request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47393 | An access control issue in Mercedes me IOS APP v1.34.0 and below allows attackers to view the maintenance orders of other users and access s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47393</link><description>An access control issue in Mercedes me IOS APP v1.34.0 and below allows attackers to view the maintenance orders of other users and access sensitive user information via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29069 | A maliciously crafted DLL file can be forced to install onto a non-default location, and attacker can overwrite parts of the product with ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29069</link><description>A maliciously crafted DLL file can be forced to install onto a non-default location, and attacker can overwrite parts of the product with malicious DLLs. These files may then have elevated privileges leading to a Privilege Escalation vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47016 | radare2 5.8.9 has an out-of-bounds read in r_bin_object_set_items in libr/bin/bobj.c, causing a crash in r_read_le32 in libr/include/r_endia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47016</link><description>radare2 5.8.9 has an out-of-bounds read in r_bin_object_set_items in libr/bin/bobj.c, causing a crash in r_read_le32 in libr/include/r_endian.h.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48161 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in GifLib Project GifLib v.5.2.1 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the DumpSCreen2RG...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48161</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in GifLib Project GifLib v.5.2.1 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the DumpSCreen2RGB function in gif2rgb.c</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46814 | A binary hijacking vulnerability exists within the VideoLAN VLC media player before 3.0.19 on Windows. The uninstaller attempts to execute c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46814</link><description>A binary hijacking vulnerability exists within the VideoLAN VLC media player before 3.0.19 on Windows. The uninstaller attempts to execute code with elevated privileges out of a standard user writable location. Standard users may use this to gain arbitrary code execution as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-35638 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35638</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.8 and 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.1 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  230824.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-37937 | Elasticsearch privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37937</link><description>An issue was found with how API keys are created with the Fleet-Server service account. When an API key is created with a service account, it is possible that the API key could be created with higher privileges than intended. Using this vulnerability, a compromised Fleet-Server service account could escalate themselves to a super-user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22143 | Elastic APM .NET Agent information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22143</link><description>The Elastic APM .NET Agent can leak sensitive HTTP header information when logging the details during an application error. Normally, the APM agent will sanitize sensitive HTTP header details before sending the information to the APM server. During an application error it is possible the headers will not be sanitized before being sent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-37942 | APM Java Agent Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37942</link><description>A local privilege escalation issue was found with the APM Java agent, where a user on the system could attach a malicious plugin to an application running the APM Java agent. By using this vulnerability, an attacker could execute code at a potentially higher level of permissions than their user typically has access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22142 | Kibana Reporting vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22142</link><description>Kibana contains an embedded version of the Chromium browser that the Reporting feature uses to generate the downloadable reports. If a user with permissions to generate reports is able to render arbitrary HTML with this browser, they may be able to leverage known Chromium vulnerabilities to conduct further attacks. Kibana contains a number of protections to prevent this browser from rendering arbitrary content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35127 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35127</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow may occur when Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator parses a specially-crafted input file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22150 | Kibana code execution issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22150</link><description>It was discovered that a user with Fleet admin permissions could upload a malicious package. Due to using an older version of the js-yaml library, this package would be loaded in an insecure manner, allowing an attacker to execute commands on the Kibana server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22151 | Kibana path traversal issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22151</link><description>It was discovered that Kibana was not validating a user supplied path, which would load .pbf files. Because of this, a malicious user could arbitrarily traverse the Kibana host to load internal files ending in the .pbf extension.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40152 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40152</link><description>When Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator parses a specially-crafted input file an out of bounds write may occur.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5299 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator  Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5299</link><description>A user with a standard account in Fuji Electric Tellus Lite may overwrite files in the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48701 | Statamic CMS vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting via uploaded assets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48701</link><description>Statamic CMS is a Laravel and Git powered content management system (CMS). Prior to versions 3.4.15 an 4.36.0, HTML files crafted to look like images may be uploaded regardless of mime validation. This is only applicable on front-end forms using the "Forms" feature containing an assets field, or within the control panel which requires authentication. This issue has been patched on 3.4.15 and 4.36.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48699 | fastbots Eval Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48699</link><description>fastbots is a library for fast bot and scraper development using selenium and the Page Object Model (POM) design. Prior to version 0.1.5, an attacker could modify the locators.ini locator file with python code that without proper validation it's executed and it could lead to rce. The vulnerability is in the function `def __locator__(self, locator_name: str)` in `page.py`. In order to mitigate this issue, upgrade to fastbots version 0.1.5 or above.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48700 | Clear Text Credentials Exposed via Onboarding Task</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48700</link><description>The Nautobot Device Onboarding plugin uses the netmiko and NAPALM libraries to simplify the onboarding process of a new device into Nautobot down to, in many cases, an IP Address and a Location. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to version 3.0.0, credentials provided to onboarding task are visible via Job Results from an execution of an Onboarding Task. Version 3.0.0 fixes this issue; no known workarounds are available. Mitigation recommendations include deleting all Job Results for any onboarding task to remove clear text credentials from database entries that were run while on v2.0.X, upgrading to v3.0.0, and rotating any exposed credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48305 | Nextcloud Server user_ldap app logs user passwords in the log file on level debug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48305</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, when the log level was set to debug, the user_ldap app logged user passwords in plaintext into the log file. If the log file was then leaked or shared in any way the users' passwords would be leaked. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, change config setting `loglevel` to `1` or higher (should always be higher than 1 in production environments).</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48306 | Nextcloud Server DNS pin middleware can be tricked into DNS rebinding allowing SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48306</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and starting in version 22.0.0 and prior to versions 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Enterprise Server, the DNS pin middleware was vulnerable to DNS rebinding allowing an attacker to perform SSRF as a final result. Nextcloud Server 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain patches for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48307 | Nextcloud Mail app vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48307</link><description>Nextcloud Mail is the mail app for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Starting in version 1.13.0 and prior to version 2.2.8 and 3.3.0, an attacker can use an unprotected endpoint in the Mail app to perform a SSRF attack. Nextcloud Mail app versions 2.2.8 and 3.3.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable the mail app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48303 | Nextcloud Server admins can change authentication details of user configured external storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48303</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, admins can change authentication details of user configured external storage. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48304 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to attacker enabling/disabling birthday calendar for any user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48304</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and starting in version 22.0.0 and prior to versions 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Enterprise Server, an attacker could enable and disable the birthday calendar for any user on the same server. Nextcloud Server 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain patches for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48302 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to Self XSS when pasting HTML into Text app with Ctrl+Shift+V</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48302</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, when a user is tricked into copy pasting HTML code without markup (Ctrl+Shift+V) the markup will actually render. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 contain a fix for this issue. As a workaround, disable app text.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6248 | Data leakage and arbitrary remote code execution in Syrus cloud devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6248</link><description>The Syrus4 IoT gateway utilizes an unsecured MQTT server to download and execute arbitrary commands, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute code on any Syrus4 device connected to the cloud service. The MQTT server also leaks the location, video and diagnostic data from each connected device. An attacker who knows the IP address of the server is able to connect and perform the following operations:

  *  Get location data of the vehicle the device is connected to
  *  Send CAN bus messages via the ECU module ( https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/ecu-1 https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/ecu-1 )

  *  Immobilize the vehicle via the safe-immobilizer module ( https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#safe-immobilization https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#safe-immobilization )

  *  Get live video through the connected video camera

  *  Send audio messages to the driver ( https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#apx-tts https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#apx-tts )</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48301 | Nextcloud Server HTML injection in search UI when selecting a circle with HTML in the display name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48301</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, an attacker could insert links into circles name that would be opened when clicking the circle name in a search filter. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 contain a fix for this issue. As a workaround, disable app circles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49103 | An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/graphapi 0.2.x before 0.2.1 and 0.3.x before 0.3.1. The graphapi app relies on a third-party Ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49103</link><description>An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/graphapi 0.2.x before 0.2.1 and 0.3.x before 0.3.1. The graphapi app relies on a third-party GetPhpInfo.php library that provides a URL. When this URL is accessed, it reveals the configuration details of the PHP environment (phpinfo). This information includes all the environment variables of the webserver. In containerized deployments, these environment variables may include sensitive data such as the ownCloud admin password, mail server credentials, and license key. Simply disabling the graphapi app does not eliminate the vulnerability. Additionally, phpinfo exposes various other potentially sensitive configuration details that could be exploited by an attacker to gather information about the system. Therefore, even if ownCloud is not running in a containerized environment, this vulnerability should still be a cause for concern. Note that Docker containers from before February 2023 are not vulnerable to the credential disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49104 | An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/oauth2 before 0.6.1, when Allow Subdomains is enabled. An attacker is able to pass in a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49104</link><description>An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/oauth2 before 0.6.1, when Allow Subdomains is enabled. An attacker is able to pass in a crafted redirect-url that bypasses validation, and consequently allows an attacker to redirect callbacks to a Top Level Domain controlled by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49105 | An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/core before 10.13.1. An attacker can access, modify, or delete any file without authentication ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49105</link><description>An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/core before 10.13.1. An attacker can access, modify, or delete any file without authentication if the username of a victim is known, and the victim has no signing-key configured. This occurs because pre-signed URLs can be accepted even when no signing-key is configured for the owner of the files. The earliest affected version is 10.6.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48239 | Nextcloud Server users can make external storage mount points inaccessible for other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48239</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Server and starting in version 20.0.0 and prior to versions 20.0.14.16, 21.0.9.13, 22.2.10.15, 23.0.12.12, 24.0.12.8, 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Enterprise Server, a malicious user could update any personal or global external storage, making them inaccessible for everyone else as well. Nextcloud Server 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 20.0.14.16, 21.0.9.13, 22.2.10.15, 23.0.12.12, 24.0.12.8, 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable app files_external. This workaround also makes the external storage inaccessible but retains the configurations until a patched version has been deployed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48230 | Cap&amp;#x27;n Proto WebSocket message can cause crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48230</link><description>Cap'n Proto is a data interchange format and capability-based RPC system. In versions 1.0 and 1.0.1, when using the KJ HTTP library with WebSocket compression enabled, a buffer underrun can be caused by a remote peer. The underrun always writes a constant value that is not attacker-controlled, likely resulting in a crash, enabling a remote denial-of-service attack. Most Cap'n Proto and KJ users are unlikely to have this functionality enabled and so unlikely to be affected. Maintainers suspect only the Cloudflare Workers Runtime is affected.

If KJ HTTP is used with WebSocket compression enabled, a malicious peer may be able to cause a buffer underrun on a heap-allocated buffer. KJ HTTP is an optional library bundled with Cap'n Proto, but is not directly used by Cap'n Proto. WebSocket compression is disabled by default. It must be enabled via a setting passed to the KJ HTTP library via `HttpClientSettings` or `HttpServerSettings`. The bytes written out-of-bounds are always a specific constant 4-byte string `{ 0x00, 0x00, 0xFF, 0xFF }`. Because this string is not controlled by the attacker, maintainers believe it is unlikely that remote code execution is possible. However, it cannot be ruled out. This functionality first appeared in Cap'n Proto 1.0. Previous versions are not affected.

This issue is fixed in Cap'n Proto 1.0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48299 | TorchServe ZipSlip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48299</link><description>TorchServe is a tool for serving and scaling PyTorch models in production. Starting in version 0.1.0 and prior to version 0.9.0, using the model/workflow management API, there is a chance of uploading potentially harmful archives that contain files that are extracted to any location on the filesystem that is within the process permissions. Leveraging this issue could aid third-party actors in hiding harmful code in open-source/public models, which can be downloaded from the internet, and take advantage of machines running Torchserve. The ZipSlip issue in TorchServe has been fixed by validating the paths of files contained within a zip archive before extracting them. TorchServe release 0.9.0 includes fixes to address the ZipSlip vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48228 | OAuth2: PKCE can be fully circumvented</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48228</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. When initialising a oauth2 flow with a `code_challenge` and `code_method` (thus requesting PKCE), the single sign-on provider (authentik) must check if there is a matching and existing `code_verifier` during the token step. Prior to versions 2023.10.4 and 2023.8.5, authentik checks if the contents of `code_verifier` is matching only when it is provided. When it is left out completely, authentik simply accepts the token request with out it; even when the flow was started with a `code_challenge`. authentik 2023.8.5 and 2023.10.4 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6238 | Kernel: nvme: memory corruption via unprivileged user passthrough</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6238</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was found in the NVM Express (NVMe) driver in the Linux kernel. An unprivileged user could specify a small meta buffer and let the device perform larger Direct Memory Access (DMA) into the same buffer, overwriting unrelated kernel memory, causing random kernel crashes and memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48226 | OpenReplay HTML Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48226</link><description>OpenReplay is a self-hosted session replay suite. In version 1.14.0, due to lack of validation Name field - Account Settings (for registration looks like validation is correct), a bad actor can send emails with HTML injected code to the victims. Bad actors can use this to phishing actions for example. Email is really send from OpenReplay, but bad actors can add there HTML code injected (content spoofing). Please notice that during Registration steps for FullName looks like is validated correct - can not type there, but using this kind of bypass/workaround - bad actors can achieve own goal. As of time of publication, no known fixes or workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47643 | SuiteCRM has Unauthenticated Graphql Introspection Enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47643</link><description>SuiteCRM is a Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to version 8.4.2, Graphql Introspection is enabled without authentication, exposing the scheme defining all object types, arguments, and functions. An attacker can obtain the GraphQL schema and understand the entire attack surface of the API, including sensitive fields such as UserHash. This issue is patched in version 8.4.2. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20208 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack ag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20208</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20272 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20272</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload malicious files to the web root of the application. This vulnerability is due to insufficient file input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to the web interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to replace files and gain access to sensitive server-side information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20274 | A vulnerability in the installer script of Cisco AppDynamics PHP Agent could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20274</link><description>A vulnerability in the installer script of Cisco AppDynamics PHP Agent could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient permissions that are set by the PHP Agent Installer on the PHP Agent install directory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying objects in the PHP Agent install directory, which would run with the same privileges as PHP. A successful exploit could allow a lower-privileged attacker to elevate their privileges to root on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20265 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of a small subset of Cisco IP Phones could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20265</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of a small subset of Cisco IP Phones could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to view a page containing malicious HTML or script content. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid credentials to access the web-based management interface of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38405 | Siemens Solid Edge, JT2Go, and Teamcenter Visualization Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38405</link><description>The Datalogics APDFL library used in affected products is vulnerable to memory corruption condition while parsing specially crafted PDF files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22516 | This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in versions 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, and 9.3.0 of Bamb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22516</link><description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in versions 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, and 9.3.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.7.&#13;
  JDK 1.8u121+ should be used in case Java 8 used to run Bamboo Data Center and Server. See Bamboo 9.2 Upgrade notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-9-2-upgrade-notes-1207179212.html)&#13;
&#13;
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.3: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.3.4&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22521 | This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 3.4.6 of Crowd Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22521</link><description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 3.4.6 of Crowd Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.0, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Crowd Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Crowd Data Center and Server 3.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 5.1.6&#13;
 Crowd Data Center and Server 5.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 5.2.1&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/crowd/crowd-release-notes-199094.html]). You can download the latest version of Crowd Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/crowd/download-archive]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by m1sn0w and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5055 | L2CAP: Possible Stack based buffer overflow in le_ecred_reconf_req()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5055</link><description>Possible variant of CVE-2021-3434 in function le_ecred_reconf_req.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27504 | Texas Instruments FREERTOS Integer Overflow or Wraparound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27504</link><description>Texas Instruments devices running FREERTOS, malloc returns a valid 
pointer to a small buffer on extremely large values, which can trigger 
an integer overflow vulnerability in 'malloc' for FreeRTOS, resulting in
 code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27502 | Texas Instruments TI-RTOS Integer Overflow or Wraparound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27502</link><description>Texas Instruments TI-RTOS, when configured to use HeapMem heap(default),
 malloc returns a valid pointer to a small buffer on extremely large 
values, which can trigger an integer overflow vulnerability in 
'HeapMem_allocUnprotected' and result in code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49060 | An attacker could have accessed internal pages or data by ex-filtrating a security key from ReaderMode via the `referrerpolicy` attribute. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49060</link><description>An attacker could have accessed internal pages or data by ex-filtrating a security key from ReaderMode via the `referrerpolicy` attribute. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49061 | An attacker could have performed HTML template injection via Reader Mode and exfiltrated user information. This vulnerability affects Firefo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49061</link><description>An attacker could have performed HTML template injection via Reader Mode and exfiltrated user information. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6204 | On some systems—depending on the graphics settings and drivers—it was possible to force an out-of-bounds read and leak memory data into the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6204</link><description>On some systems—depending on the graphics settings and drivers—it was possible to force an out-of-bounds read and leak memory data into the images created on the canvas element. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6205 | It was possible to cause the use of a MessagePort after it had already been freed, which could potentially have led to an exploitable crash....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6205</link><description>It was possible to cause the use of a MessagePort after it had already been freed, which could potentially have led to an exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6206 | The black fade animation when exiting fullscreen is roughly the length of the anti-clickjacking delay on permission prompts. It was possible...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6206</link><description>The black fade animation when exiting fullscreen is roughly the length of the anti-clickjacking delay on permission prompts. It was possible to use this fact to surprise users by luring them to click where the permission grant button would be about to appear. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6207 | Ownership mismanagement led to a use-after-free in ReadableByteStreams This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6207</link><description>Ownership mismanagement led to a use-after-free in ReadableByteStreams This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6208 | When using X11, text selected by the page using the Selection API was erroneously copied into the primary selection, a temporary storage not...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6208</link><description>When using X11, text selected by the page using the Selection API was erroneously copied into the primary selection, a temporary storage not unlike the clipboard.
*This bug only affects Firefox on X11. Other systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6209 | Relative URLs starting with three slashes were incorrectly parsed, and a path-traversal "/../" part in the path could be used to override th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6209</link><description>Relative URLs starting with three slashes were incorrectly parsed, and a path-traversal "/../" part in the path could be used to override the specified host. This could contribute to security problems in web sites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6210 | When an https: web page created a pop-up from a "javascript:" URL, that pop-up was incorrectly allowed to load blockable content such as ifr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6210</link><description>When an https: web page created a pop-up from a "javascript:" URL, that pop-up was incorrectly allowed to load blockable content such as iframes from insecure http: URLs This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6211 | If an attacker needed a user to load an insecure http: page and knew that user had enabled HTTPS-only mode, the attacker could have tricked ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6211</link><description>If an attacker needed a user to load an insecure http: page and knew that user had enabled HTTPS-only mode, the attacker could have tricked the user into clicking to grant an HTTPS-only exception if they could get the user to participate in a clicking game. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6212 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119, Firefox ESR 115.4, and Thunderbird 115.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6212</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119, Firefox ESR 115.4, and Thunderbird 115.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.5.0, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6213 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6213</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48124 | Cross Site Scripting in SUP Online Shopping v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Name, Email and Address paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48124</link><description>Cross Site Scripting in SUP Online Shopping v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Name, Email and Address parameters in the Register New Account component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6235 | Arbitrary code execution in Duet Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6235</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability has been found in the Duet Display product, affecting version 2.5.9.1. An attacker could place an arbitrary libusk.dll file in the C:\Users\user\AppData\Local\Microsoft\WindowsApps\ directory, which could lead to the execution and persistence of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28802 | Disable Zscaler using machine tunnel restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28802</link><description>An Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value in Zscaler Client Connector on Windows allows an authenticated user to disable ZIA/ZPA by interrupting the service restart from Zscaler Diagnostics. This issue affects Client Connector: before 4.2.0.149.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5598 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5598</link><description>Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilitiesÂ affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x allow an attacker to execute arbitrary script code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5599 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5599</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5776 | The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5776</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the pmdm_wp_ajax_delete_meta, pmdm_wp_delete_user_meta, and pmdm_wp_delete_user_meta functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user, term, and post meta via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4149 | WAGO: OS Command Injection Vulnerability in Managed Switch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4149</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to inject arbitrary system commands and gain full system control. Those commands are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is located in the user request handling of the web-based management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5553 | During internal Axis Security Development Model (ASDM) threat-modelling, a flaw was found in the protection for device tampering (commonly k...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5553</link><description>During internal Axis Security Development Model (ASDM) threat-modelling, a flaw was found in the protection for device tampering (commonly known as Secure Boot) in AXIS OS making it vulnerable to a sophisticated attack to bypass this protection. To Axis' knowledge, there are no known exploits of the vulnerability at this time. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21417 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program,

has found that the VAPIX API manageoverlayimage.cgi was vulnerable to path traversa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21417</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program,

has found that the VAPIX API manageoverlayimage.cgi was vulnerable to path traversal attacks that allows for file/folder deletion. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator- privileged service account. The impact of exploiting this vulnerability is lower with operator service accounts and limited to non-system files compared to administrator-privileges.
 Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21418 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API irissetup.cgi was vulnerable to path traversal attacks ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21418</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API irissetup.cgi was vulnerable to path traversal attacks that allows for file deletion. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator-privileged service account. The impact of exploiting this vulnerability is lower with operator service accounts and limited to non-system files compared to administrator-privileges. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21416 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API dynamicoverlay.cgi was vulnerable to a Denial-of-Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21416</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API dynamicoverlay.cgi was vulnerable to a Denial-of-Service attack allowing for an attacker to block access to the overlay configuration page in the web interface of the Axis device. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator-privileged service account however the impact is equal. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4424 | bt: hci: DoS and possible RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4424</link><description>An malicious BLE device can cause buffer overflow by sending malformed advertising packet BLE device using Zephyr OS, leading to DoS or potential RCE on the victim BLE device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46935 | eyoucms v1.6.4 is vulnerable Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which can lead to stealing sensitive information of logged-in users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46935</link><description>eyoucms v1.6.4 is vulnerable Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which can lead to stealing sensitive information of logged-in users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45886 | The BGP daemon (bgpd) in IP Infusion ZebOS through 7.10.6 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending crafted BGP update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45886</link><description>The BGP daemon (bgpd) in IP Infusion ZebOS through 7.10.6 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending crafted BGP update messages containing a malformed attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5274 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5274</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the function by sending specially crafted packets. However, the attacker would need to send the packets from within the same personal computer where the function is running.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 03:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5275 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5275</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the function by sending specially crafted packets. However, the attacker would need to send the packets from within the same personal computer where the function is running.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 03:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42770 | Red Lion Controls Sixnet RTU Authentication Bypass Using An Alternative Path Or Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42770</link><description>Red Lion SixTRAK and VersaTRAK Series RTUs with authenticated users enabled (UDR-A) any Sixnet UDR message will meet an authentication challenge over UDP/IP. When the same message is received over TCP/IP the RTU will simply accept the message with no authentication challenge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40151 | Red Lion Controls Sixnet RTU Exposed Dangerous Method Or Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40151</link><description>When user authentication is not enabled the shell can execute commands with the highest privileges. Red Lion SixTRAK and VersaTRAK Series RTUs with authenticated users enabled (UDR-A) any Sixnet UDR message will meet an authentication challenge over UDP/IP. When the same message comes over TCP/IP the RTU will simply accept the message with no authentication challenge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>