<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:10:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-50121 | Autel EVO NANO drone flight control firmware version 1.6.5 is vulnerable to denial of service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50121</link><description>Autel EVO NANO drone flight control firmware version 1.6.5 is vulnerable to denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46953 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS v.5.9.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the d parameter in the Documents modul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46953</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS v.5.9.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the d parameter in the Documents module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39853 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Dzzoffice version 2.01, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doobj and doevent par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39853</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Dzzoffice version 2.01, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doobj and doevent parameters in the Network Disk backend module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50609 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AVA teaching video application service platform version 3.1, allows remote attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50609</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AVA teaching video application service platform version 3.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to ajax.aspx.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 03:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50612 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in fit2cloud Cloud Explorer Lite version 1.4.1, allow local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50612</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in fit2cloud Cloud Explorer Lite version 1.4.1, allow local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the cloud accounts parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 02:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21642 | D-Tale server-side request forgery through Web uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21642</link><description>D-Tale is a visualizer for Pandas data structures. Users hosting versions D-Tale prior to 3.9.0 publicly can be vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF), allowing attackers to access files on the server. Users should upgrade to version 3.9.0, where the `Load From the Web` input is turned off by default. The only workaround for versions earlier than 3.9.0 is to only host D-Tale to trusted users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 21:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21641 | Flarum&amp;#x27;s Logout Route allows open redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21641</link><description>Flarum is open source discussion platform software. Prior to version 1.8.5, the Flarum `/logout` route includes a redirect parameter that allows any third party to redirect users from a (trusted) domain of the Flarum installation to redirect to any link. For logged-in users, the logout must be confirmed. Guests are immediately redirected. This could be used by spammers to redirect to a web address using a trusted domain of a running Flarum installation. The vulnerability has been fixed and published as flarum/core v1.8.5. As a workaround, some extensions modifying the logout route can remedy this issue if their implementation is safe.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0247 | CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System Admin Panel sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0247</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249778 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46835 | x86/AMD: mismatch in IOMMU quarantine page table levels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46835</link><description>The current setup of the quarantine page tables assumes that the
quarantine domain (dom_io) has been initialized with an address width
of DEFAULT_DOMAIN_ADDRESS_WIDTH (48) and hence 4 page table levels.

However dom_io being a PV domain gets the AMD-Vi IOMMU page tables
levels based on the maximum (hot pluggable) RAM address, and hence on
systems with no RAM above the 512GB mark only 3 page-table levels are
configured in the IOMMU.

On systems without RAM above the 512GB boundary
amd_iommu_quarantine_init() will setup page tables for the scratch
page with 4 levels, while the IOMMU will be configured to use 3 levels
only, resulting in the last page table directory (PDE) effectively
becoming a page table entry (PTE), and hence a device in quarantine
mode gaining write access to the page destined to be a PDE.

Due to this page table level mismatch, the sink page the device gets
read/write access to is no longer cleared between device assignment,
possibly leading to data leaks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46836 | x86: BTC/SRSO fixes not fully effective</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46836</link><description>The fixes for XSA-422 (Branch Type Confusion) and XSA-434 (Speculative
Return Stack Overflow) are not IRQ-safe.  It was believed that the
mitigations always operated in contexts with IRQs disabled.

However, the original XSA-254 fix for Meltdown (XPTI) deliberately left
interrupts enabled on two entry paths; one unconditionally, and one
conditionally on whether XPTI was active.

As BTC/SRSO and Meltdown affect different CPU vendors, the mitigations
are not active together by default.  Therefore, there is a race
condition whereby a malicious PV guest can bypass BTC/SRSO protections
and launch a BTC/SRSO attack against Xen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46837 | arm32: The cache may not be properly cleaned/invalidated (take two)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46837</link><description>Arm provides multiple helpers to clean &amp; invalidate the cache
for a given region.  This is, for instance, used when allocating
guest memory to ensure any writes (such as the ones during scrubbing)
have reached memory before handing over the page to a guest.

Unfortunately, the arithmetics in the helpers can overflow and would
then result to skip the cache cleaning/invalidation.  Therefore there
is no guarantee when all the writes will reach the memory.

This undefined behavior was meant to be addressed by XSA-437, but the
approach was not sufficient.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34323 | xenstored: A transaction conflict can crash C Xenstored</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34323</link><description>When a transaction is committed, C Xenstored will first check
the quota is correct before attempting to commit any nodes.  It would
be possible that accounting is temporarily negative if a node has
been removed outside of the transaction.

Unfortunately, some versions of C Xenstored are assuming that the
quota cannot be negative and are using assert() to confirm it.  This
will lead to C Xenstored crash when tools are built without -DNDEBUG
(this is the default).</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34324 | Possible deadlock in Linux kernel event handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34324</link><description>Closing of an event channel in the Linux kernel can result in a deadlock.
This happens when the close is being performed in parallel to an unrelated
Xen console action and the handling of a Xen console interrupt in an
unprivileged guest.

The closing of an event channel is e.g. triggered by removal of a
paravirtual device on the other side. As this action will cause console
messages to be issued on the other side quite often, the chance of
triggering the deadlock is not neglectable.

Note that 32-bit Arm-guests are not affected, as the 32-bit Linux kernel
on Arm doesn't use queued-RW-locks, which are required to trigger the
issue (on Arm32 a waiting writer doesn't block further readers to get
the lock).</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34325 | Multiple vulnerabilities in libfsimage disk handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34325</link><description>[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

libfsimage contains parsing code for several filesystems, most of them based on
grub-legacy code.  libfsimage is used by pygrub to inspect guest disks.

Pygrub runs as the same user as the toolstack (root in a priviledged domain).

At least one issue has been reported to the Xen Security Team that allows an
attacker to trigger a stack buffer overflow in libfsimage.  After further
analisys the Xen Security Team is no longer confident in the suitability of
libfsimage when run against guest controlled input with super user priviledges.

In order to not affect current deployments that rely on pygrub patches are
provided in the resolution section of the advisory that allow running pygrub in
deprivileged mode.

CVE-2023-4949 refers to the original issue in the upstream grub
project ("An attacker with local access to a system (either through a
disk or external drive) can present a modified XFS partition to
grub-legacy in such a way to exploit a memory corruption in grub’s XFS
file system implementation.")  CVE-2023-34325 refers specifically to
the vulnerabilities in Xen's copy of libfsimage, which is decended
from a very old version of grub.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34326 | x86/AMD: missing IOMMU TLB flushing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34326</link><description>The caching invalidation guidelines from the AMD-Vi specification (48882—Rev
3.07-PUB—Oct 2022) is incorrect on some hardware, as devices will malfunction
(see stale DMA mappings) if some fields of the DTE are updated but the IOMMU
TLB is not flushed.

Such stale DMA mappings can point to memory ranges not owned by the guest, thus
allowing access to unindented memory regions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34327 | x86/AMD: Debug Mask handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34327</link><description>[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

AMD CPUs since ~2014 have extensions to normal x86 debugging functionality.
Xen supports guests using these extensions.

Unfortunately there are errors in Xen's handling of the guest state, leading
to denials of service.

 1) CVE-2023-34327 - An HVM vCPU can end up operating in the context of
    a previous vCPUs debug mask state.

 2) CVE-2023-34328 - A PV vCPU can place a breakpoint over the live GDT.
    This allows the PV vCPU to exploit XSA-156 / CVE-2015-8104 and lock
    up the CPU entirely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34328 | x86/AMD: Debug Mask handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34328</link><description>[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

AMD CPUs since ~2014 have extensions to normal x86 debugging functionality.
Xen supports guests using these extensions.

Unfortunately there are errors in Xen's handling of the guest state, leading
to denials of service.

 1) CVE-2023-34327 - An HVM vCPU can end up operating in the context of
    a previous vCPUs debug mask state.

 2) CVE-2023-34328 - A PV vCPU can place a breakpoint over the live GDT.
    This allows the PV vCPU to exploit XSA-156 / CVE-2015-8104 and lock
    up the CPU entirely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34321 | arm32: The cache may not be properly cleaned/invalidated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34321</link><description>Arm provides multiple helpers to clean &amp; invalidate the cache
for a given region.  This is, for instance, used when allocating
guest memory to ensure any writes (such as the ones during scrubbing)
have reached memory before handing over the page to a guest.

Unfortunately, the arithmetics in the helpers can overflow and would
then result to skip the cache cleaning/invalidation.  Therefore there
is no guarantee when all the writes will reach the memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34322 | top-level shadow reference dropped too early for 64-bit PV guests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34322</link><description>For migration as well as to work around kernels unaware of L1TF (see
XSA-273), PV guests may be run in shadow paging mode.  Since Xen itself
needs to be mapped when PV guests run, Xen and shadowed PV guests run
directly the respective shadow page tables.  For 64-bit PV guests this
means running on the shadow of the guest root page table.

In the course of dealing with shortage of memory in the shadow pool
associated with a domain, shadows of page tables may be torn down.  This
tearing down may include the shadow root page table that the CPU in
question is presently running on.  While a precaution exists to
supposedly prevent the tearing down of the underlying live page table,
the time window covered by that precaution isn't large enough.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39294 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39294</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39296 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39296</link><description>A prototype pollution vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to override existing attributes with ones that have incompatible type, which may lead to a crash via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41287 | Video Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41287</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Video Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Video Station 5.7.2 ( 2023/11/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41288 | Video Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41288</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Video Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Video Station 5.7.2 ( 2023/11/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41289 | QcalAgent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41289</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QcalAgent. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QcalAgent 1.1.8 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45039 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45039</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45040 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45040</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45041 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45041</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45042 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45042</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45043 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45043</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45044 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45044</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47219 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47219</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.2.1 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47559 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47559</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.2.1 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47560 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47560</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.2.1 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36677 | Obsidian Mind Map v1.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload injected into an uploaded document.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36677</link><description>Obsidian Mind Map v1.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload injected into an uploaded document.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0246 | IceWarp Utility Download cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0246</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in IceWarp 12.0.2.1/12.0.3.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /install/ of the component Utility Download Handler. The manipulation of the argument lang with the input 1%27"()%26%25&lt;zzz&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(document.domain)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249759. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 14:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52124 | WordPress WP Tabs Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ShapedPlugin LLC WP Tabs – Responsive Tabs Plugin for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Tabs – Responsive Tabs Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52125 | WordPress iFrame Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webvitaly iframe allows Stored XSS.This issue affects iframe: from n/a through 4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52126 | WordPress Send Users Email Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52126</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Suman Bhattarai Send Users Email.This issue affects Send Users Email: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52143 | WordPress WP Stripe Checkout Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2.37 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52143</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Naa986 WP Stripe Checkout.This issue affects WP Stripe Checkout: from n/a through 1.2.2.37.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52146 | WordPress 404 Solution Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.33.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52146</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Aaron J 404 Solution.This issue affects 404 Solution: from n/a through 2.33.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52148 | WordPress Affiliates Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.30 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52148</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in wp.Insider, wpaffiliatemgr Affiliates Manager.This issue affects Affiliates Manager: from n/a through 2.9.30.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52151 | WordPress Uncanny Automator Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52151</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Uncanny Automator, Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator – Automate everything with the #1 no-code automation and integration plugin.This issue affects Uncanny Automator – Automate everything with the #1 no-code automation and integration plugin: from n/a through 5.1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46839 | WordPress JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46839</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in JS Help Desk JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin.This issue affects JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 10:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51678 | WordPress Doofinder for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.33 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51678</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Doofinder Doofinder WP &amp; WooCommerce Search.This issue affects Doofinder WP &amp; WooCommerce Search: from n/a through 2.0.33.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 10:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51535 | WordPress Spam protection, AntiSpam, FireWall by CleanTalk Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.20 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51535</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in СleanTalk - Anti-Spam Protection Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk.This issue affects Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk: from n/a through 6.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 10:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51668 | WordPress Inline Image Upload for BBPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51668</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Zone Inline Image Upload for BBPress.This issue affects Inline Image Upload for BBPress: from n/a through 1.1.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51673 | WordPress Stylish Price List Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.17 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51673</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Designful Stylish Price List – Price Table Builder &amp; QR Code Restaurant Menu.This issue affects Stylish Price List – Price Table Builder &amp; QR Code Restaurant Menu: from n/a through 7.0.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51538 | WordPress Awesome Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51538</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Awesome Support Team Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin.This issue affects Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 6.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51539 | WordPress Apollo13 Framework Extensions Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51539</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Apollo13Themes Apollo13 Framework Extensions.This issue affects Apollo13 Framework Extensions: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50991 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda i29 versions 1.0 V1.0.0.5 and 1.0 V1.0.0.2, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50991</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda i29 versions 1.0 V1.0.0.5 and 1.0 V1.0.0.2, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the pingIp parameter in the pingSet function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52119 | WordPress Icegram Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52119</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Icegram Icegram Engage – WordPress Lead Generation, Popup Builder, CTA, Optins and Email List Building.This issue affects Icegram Engage – WordPress Lead Generation, Popup Builder, CTA, Optins and Email List Building: from n/a through 3.1.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52120 | WordPress NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52120</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Basix NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more.This issue affects NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more: from n/a through 8.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52121 | WordPress NitroPack Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52121</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NitroPack Inc. NitroPack – Cache &amp; Speed Optimization for Core Web Vitals, Defer CSS &amp; JavaScript, Lazy load Images.This issue affects NitroPack – Cache &amp; Speed Optimization for Core Web Vitals, Defer CSS &amp; JavaScript, Lazy load Images: from n/a through 1.10.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52122 | WordPress Simple Job Board Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52122</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Job Board.This issue affects Simple Job Board: from n/a through 2.10.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50027 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Buy Addons baproductzoommagnifier module for PrestaShop versions 1.0.16 and before, allows remote attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50027</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Buy Addons baproductzoommagnifier module for PrestaShop versions 1.0.16 and before, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and gain sensitive information via BaproductzoommagnifierZoomModuleFrontController::run() method.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52123 | WordPress Strong Testimonials Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52123</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPChill Strong Testimonials.This issue affects Strong Testimonials: from n/a through 3.1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52127 | WordPress WPC Product Bundles for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52127</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPClever WPC Product Bundles for WooCommerce.This issue affects WPC Product Bundles for WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52128 | WordPress White Label Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52128</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WhiteWP White Label – WordPress Custom Admin, Custom Login Page, and Custom Dashboard.This issue affects White Label – WordPress Custom Admin, Custom Login Page, and Custom Dashboard: from n/a through 2.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52129 | WordPress teachPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52129</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Winkler teachPress.This issue affects teachPress: from n/a through 9.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52130 | WordPress Affiliates Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.31 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52130</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wp.Insider, wpaffiliatemgr Affiliates Manager.This issue affects Affiliates Manager: from n/a through 2.9.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52136 | WordPress Custom Twitter Feeds (Tweets Widget) Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52136</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Smash Balloon Custom Twitter Feeds – A Tweets Widget or X Feed Widget.This issue affects Custom Twitter Feeds – A Tweets Widget or X Feed Widget: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-13880 | IrfanView B3D PlugIns before version 4.56 has a B3d.dll!+1cbf heap-based out-of-bounds write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-13880</link><description>IrfanView B3D PlugIns before version 4.56 has a B3d.dll!+1cbf heap-based out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52145 | WordPress Republish Old Posts Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.21 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52145</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marios Alexandrou Republish Old Posts.This issue affects Republish Old Posts: from n/a through 1.21.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52149 | WordPress Floating Button Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52149</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Floating Button.This issue affects Floating Button: from n/a through 6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-13878 | IrfanView B3D PlugIns before version 4.56 has a B3d.dll!+27ef heap-based out-of-bounds write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-13878</link><description>IrfanView B3D PlugIns before version 4.56 has a B3d.dll!+27ef heap-based out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-13879 | IrfanView B3D PlugIns before version 4.56 has a B3d.dll!+214f heap-based out-of-bounds write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-13879</link><description>IrfanView B3D PlugIns before version 4.56 has a B3d.dll!+214f heap-based out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52150 | WordPress Dynamic Content for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt; 2.12.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52150</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ovation S.R.L. Dynamic Content for Elementor.This issue affects Dynamic Content for Elementor: from n/a before 2.12.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51502 | WordPress WooCommerce Stripe Payment Gateway Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.1 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51502</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WooCommerce WooCommerce Stripe Payment Gateway.This issue affects WooCommerce Stripe Payment Gateway: from n/a through 7.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52184 | WordPress WP Job Portal Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52184</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Job Portal WP Job Portal – A Complete Job Board.This issue affects WP Job Portal – A Complete Job Board: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 08:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52178 | WordPress WP Affiliate Disclosure Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52178</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MojofyWP WP Affiliate Disclosure allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Affiliate Disclosure: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 07:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51277 | nbviewer-app (aka Jupyter Notebook Viewer) before 0.1.6 has the get-task-allow entitlement for release builds.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51277</link><description>nbviewer-app (aka Jupyter Notebook Viewer) before 0.1.6 has the get-task-allow entitlement for release builds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 04:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22086 | handle_request in http.c in cherry through 4b877df has an sscanf stack-based buffer overflow via a long URI, leading to remote code executio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22086</link><description>handle_request in http.c in cherry through 4b877df has an sscanf stack-based buffer overflow via a long URI, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 03:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22087 | route in main.c in Pico HTTP Server in C through f3b69a6 has an sprintf stack-based buffer overflow via a long URI, leading to remote code e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22087</link><description>route in main.c in Pico HTTP Server in C through f3b69a6 has an sprintf stack-based buffer overflow via a long URI, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 03:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22088 | Lotos WebServer through 0.1.1 (commit 3eb36cc) has a use-after-free in buffer_avail() at buffer.h via a long URI, because realloc is mishand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22088</link><description>Lotos WebServer through 0.1.1 (commit 3eb36cc) has a use-after-free in buffer_avail() at buffer.h via a long URI, because realloc is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 03:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52323 | PyCryptodome and pycryptodomex before 3.19.1 allow side-channel leakage for OAEP decryption, exploitable for a Manger attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52323</link><description>PyCryptodome and pycryptodomex before 3.19.1 allow side-channel leakage for OAEP decryption, exploitable for a Manger attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22075 | Firefly III (aka firefly-iii) before 6.1.1 allows webhooks HTML Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22075</link><description>Firefly III (aka firefly-iii) before 6.1.1 allows webhooks HTML Injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 02:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6493 | The Depicter Slider – Responsive Image Slider, Video Slider &amp; Post Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6493</link><description>The Depicter Slider – Responsive Image Slider, Video Slider &amp; Post Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. CVE-2023-51491 appears to be a duplicate of this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41782 | DLL Hijacking Vulnerability in ZTE ZXCLOUD iRAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41782</link><description>There is a DLL hijacking vulnerability in ZTE ZXCLOUD iRAI, an attacker could place a fake DLL file in a specific directory and successfully exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7207 | Debian's cpio contains a path traversal vulnerability. This issue was introduced by reverting CVE-2015-1197 patches which had caused a regre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7207</link><description>Debian's cpio contains a path traversal vulnerability. This issue was introduced by reverting CVE-2015-1197 patches which had caused a regression in --no-absolute-filenames. Upstream has since provided a proper fix to --no-absolute-filenames.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 01:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0241 | encoded_id-rails Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0241</link><description>encoded_id-rails versions before 1.0.0.beta2 are affected by an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. A remote and unauthenticated attacker might cause a denial of service condition by sending an HTTP request with an extremely long "id" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22048 | govuk_tech_docs XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22048</link><description>govuk_tech_docs versions from 2.0.2 to before 3.3.1 are vulnerable to a cross-site scripting vulnerability. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in the user's browser if a malicious search result is displayed on the search page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22047 | Audited Log Integrity Errors Due to Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22047</link><description>A race condition exists in Audited 4.0.0 to 5.3.3 that can result in an authenticated user to cause audit log entries to be attributed to another user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22051 | CommonMarker Integer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22051</link><description>CommonMarker versions prior to 0.23.4 are at risk of an integer overflow vulnerability. This vulnerability can result in possibly unauthenticated remote attackers to cause heap memory corruption, potentially leading to an information leak or remote code execution, via parsing tables with marker rows that contain more than UINT16_MAX columns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22050 | Iodine Static File Server Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22050</link><description>Path traversal in the static file service in Iodine less than 0.7.33 allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read files outside the public folder via malicious URLs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22049 | httparty Multipart/Form-Data Request Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22049</link><description>httparty before 0.21.0 is vulnerable to an assumed-immutable web parameter vulnerability. A remote and unauthenticated attacker can provide a crafted filename parameter during multipart/form-data uploads which could result in attacker controlled filenames being written.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21636 | view_component Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21636</link><description>view_component is a framework for building reusable, testable, and encapsulated view components in Ruby on Rails. Versions prior to 3.9.0 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability that has the potential to impact anyone rendering a component directly from a controller with the view_component gem. Note that only components that define a `#call` method (i.e. instead of using a sidecar template) are affected. The return value of the `#call` method is not sanitized and can include user-defined content. In addition, the return value of the `#output_postamble` methodis not sanitized, which can also lead to cross-site scripting issues. Versions 3.9.0 has been released and fully mitigates both the `#call` and the `#output_postamble` vulnerabilities. As a workaround, sanitize the return value of `#call`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51154 | Jizhicms v2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file download vulnerability via the component /admin/c/PluginsController.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51154</link><description>Jizhicms v2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file download vulnerability via the component /admin/c/PluginsController.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51812 | Tenda AX3 v16.03.12.11 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the list parameter at /goform/SetNetControl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51812</link><description>Tenda AX3 v16.03.12.11 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the list parameter at /goform/SetNetControlList.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6270 | Kernel: aoe: improper reference count leads to use-after-free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6270</link><description>A flaw was found in the ATA over Ethernet (AoE) driver in the Linux kernel. The aoecmd_cfg_pkts() function improperly updates the refcnt on `struct net_device`, and a use-after-free can be triggered by racing between the free on the struct and the access through the `skbtxq` global queue. This could lead to a denial of service condition or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6551 | Stored XSS in class.upload.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6551</link><description>As a simple library, class.upload.php does not perform an in-depth check on uploaded files, allowing a stored XSS vulnerability when the default configuration is used. 


Developers must be aware of that fact and use extension whitelisting accompanied by forcing the server to always provide content-type based on the file extension. 


The README has been updated to include these guidelines.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21625 | One-click remote code execution via malicious deep link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21625</link><description>SideQuest is a place to get virtual reality applications for Oculus Quest. The SideQuest desktop application uses deep links with a custom protocol (`sidequest://`) to trigger actions in the application from its web contents. Because, prior to version 0.10.35, the deep link URLs were not sanitized properly in all cases, a one-click remote code execution can be achieved in cases when a device is connected, the user is presented with a malicious link and clicks it from within the application. As of version 0.10.35, the custom protocol links within the electron application are now being parsed and sanitized properly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3726 | OCSInventory-ocsreports 2.12.0 - Stored cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3726</link><description>OCSInventory allow stored email template with special characters that lead to a Stored cross-site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50862 | Travel Website v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50862</link><description>Travel Website v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'hotelIDHidden' parameter of the booking.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50863 | Travel Website v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50863</link><description>Travel Website v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'hotelIDHidden' parameter of the generateReceipt.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50864 | Travel Website v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50864</link><description>Travel Website v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'hotelId' parameter of the hotelDetails.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50865 | Travel Website v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50865</link><description>Travel Website v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'city' parameter of the hotelSearch.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50866 | Travel Website v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50866</link><description>Travel Website v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the loginAction.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50867 | Travel Website v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50867</link><description>Travel Website v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the signupAction.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50760 | Online Notice Board System v1.0 - Insecure File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50760</link><description>Online Notice Board System v1.0 is vulnerable to an Insecure File Upload vulnerability on the 'f' parameter of user/update_profile_pic.php page, allowing an authenticated attacker to obtain Remote Code Execution on the server hosting the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50743 | Online Notice Board System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50743</link><description>Online Notice Board System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'dd' parameter of the registration.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50752 | Online Notice Board System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50752</link><description>Online Notice Board System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'e' parameter of the login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50753 | Online Notice Board System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50753</link><description>Online Notice Board System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'dd' parameter of the user/update_profile.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49658 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49658</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'bank_details' parameter of the party_submit.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49665 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49665</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'quantity[]' parameter of the submit_delivery_list.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49666 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49666</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'custmer_details' parameter of the submit_material_list.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49625 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49625</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'id' parameter of the partylist_edit_submit.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49633 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49633</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'buyer_address' parameter of the buyer_detail_submit.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49639 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49639</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'customer_details' parameter of the buyer_invoice_submit.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49622 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49622</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'itemnameid' parameter of the material_bill.php?action=itemRelation resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49624 | Billing Software v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49624</link><description>Billing Software v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'cancelid' parameter of the material_bill.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-40367 | A vulnerability has been identified in syngo fastView (All versions). The affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40367</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in syngo fastView (All versions). The affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing DICOM files. This could result in an out-of-bounds write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-15097)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42028 | A vulnerability has been identified in syngo fastView (All versions). The affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42028</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in syngo fastView (All versions). The affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing BMP files. This could result in an out-of-bounds write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-14860)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-45465 | A vulnerability has been identified in syngo fastView (All versions). The affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45465</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in syngo fastView (All versions). The affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing BMP files. This could result in a write-what-where condition and an attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-15696)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6992 | Memory corruption issues is Cloudflare zlib implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6992</link><description>Cloudflare version of zlib library was found to be vulnerable to memory corruption issues affecting the deflation algorithm implementation (deflate.c). The issues resulted from improper input validation and heap-based buffer overflow.
A local attacker could exploit the problem during compression using a crafted malicious file potentially leading to denial of service of the software.
Patches: The issue has been patched in commit  8352d10 https://github.com/cloudflare/zlib/commit/8352d108c05db1bdc5ac3bdf834dad641694c13c . The upstream repository is not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6944 | Rhdh: catalog-import function leaks credentials to frontend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6944</link><description>A flaw was found in the Red Hat Developer Hub (RHDH). The catalog-import function leaks GitLab access tokens on the frontend when the base64 encoded GitLab token includes a newline at the end of the string. The sanitized error can display on the frontend, including the raw access token. Upon gaining access to this token and depending on permissions, an attacker could push malicious code to repositories, delete resources in Git, revoke or generate new keys, and sign code illegitimately.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3864 | A vulnerability exists in the Relion update package signature validation. A tampered update package could cause the IED to restart. After re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3864</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Relion update package signature validation. A tampered update package could cause the IED to restart. After restart the device is back to normal operation.
An attacker could exploit the vulnerability by first gaining access to
the system with security privileges and attempt to update the IED
with a malicious update package. Successful exploitation of this
vulnerability will cause the IED to restart, causing a temporary Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7044 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7044</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom ID in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access and higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2081 | A vulnerability exists in the HCI Modbus TCP function included in the product versions listed above. If the HCI Modbus TCP is enabled and co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2081</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the HCI Modbus TCP function included in the product versions listed above. If the HCI Modbus TCP is enabled and configured, an attacker could exploit the vulnerability by sending a specially crafted message to the RTU500 in a high rate, causing the targeted RTU500 CMU to reboot. The vulnerability is caused by a lack of flood control which eventually if exploited causes an internal stack overflow in the HCI Modbus TCP function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41784 | Permissions and Access Control Vulnerability in ZTE Red Magic 8 Pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41784</link><description>Permissions and Access Control Vulnerability in ZTE Red Magic 8 Pro</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 08:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50630 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in xiweicheng TMS v.2.28.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50630</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in xiweicheng TMS v.2.28.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the click here function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50082 | Aoyun Technology pbootcms V3.1.2 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, allows remote attackers to gain sensitive information via sessio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50082</link><description>Aoyun Technology pbootcms V3.1.2 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, allows remote attackers to gain sensitive information via session leakage allows a user to avoid logging into the backend management platform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52322 | ecrire/public/assembler.php in SPIP before 4.1.3 and 4.2.x before 4.2.7 allows XSS because input from _request() is not restricted to safe c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52322</link><description>ecrire/public/assembler.php in SPIP before 4.1.3 and 4.2.x before 4.2.7 allows XSS because input from _request() is not restricted to safe characters such as alphanumerics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 06:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29962 | S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29962</link><description>S-CMS v5.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6498 | The Complianz – GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6498</link><description>The Complianz – GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to and including 6.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 03:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6733 | The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6733</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8 via the wpmem_field shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to extract sensitive data including user emails, password hashes, usernames, and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 03:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6738 | The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pagel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6738</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pagelayer_header_code', 'pagelayer_body_open_code', and 'pagelayer_footer_code' meta fields in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This appears to be a reintroduction of a vulnerability patched in version 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 03:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0222 | Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0222</link><description>Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 02:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0223 | Heap buffer overflow in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0223</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 02:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0224 | Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0224</link><description>Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 02:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0225 | Use after free in WebGPU in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0225</link><description>Use after free in WebGPU in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 02:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20802 | Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung DeX prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 allows owner to access other users&amp;#39; notification in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20802</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung DeX prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 allows owner to access other users&amp;#39; notification in a multi-user environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20803 | Improper authentication vulnerability in Bluetooth pairing process prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to establish pair...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20803</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in Bluetooth pairing process prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to establish pairing process without user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20804 | Path traversal vulnerability in FileUriConverter of MyFiles prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 in Android 11 and Android 12, and version 14.5.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20804</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in FileUriConverter of MyFiles prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 in Android 11 and Android 12, and version 14.5.00.21 in Android 13 allows attackers to write arbitrary file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20805 | Path traversal vulnerability in ZipCompressor of MyFiles prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 in Android 11 and Android 12, and version 14.5.00.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20805</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in ZipCompressor of MyFiles prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 in Android 11 and Android 12, and version 14.5.00.21 in Android 13 allows attackers to write arbitrary file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20806 | Improper access control in Notification service prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to access notification data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20806</link><description>Improper access control in Notification service prior to SMR Jan-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to access notification data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20807 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.90.16 allows attacker to get sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20807</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.90.16 allows attacker to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20808 | Improper access control vulnerability in Nearby device scanning prior version 11.1.14.7 allows local attacker to access data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20808</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Nearby device scanning prior version 11.1.14.7 allows local attacker to access data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20809 | Improper access control vulnerability in Nearby device scanning prior version 11.1.14.7 allows local attacker to access data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20809</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Nearby device scanning prior version 11.1.14.7 allows local attacker to access data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 01:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>