<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:37:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11011 | BehaviorTree json_export.cpp fromJson null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11011</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BehaviorTree up to 4.7.0. Affected by this issue is the function JsonExporter::fromJson of the file /src/json_export.cpp. Performing manipulation of the argument Source results in null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named 4b23dcaf0ce951a31299ebdd61df69f9ce99a76d. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11012 | BehaviorTree Diagnostic Message script_parser.cpp ParseScript stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11012</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in BehaviorTree up to 4.7.0. This affects the function ParseScript of the file /src/script_parser.cpp of the component Diagnostic Message Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument error_msgs_buffer can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called cb6c7514efa628adb8180b58b4c9ccdebbe096e3. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11010 | vstakhov libucl ucl_util.c ucl_include_common heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11010</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in vstakhov libucl up to 0.9.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ucl_include_common of the file /src/ucl_util.c. Such manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10544 | Unrestricted uploading of dangerous file types to AvePoint products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10544</link><description>Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in DocAve 6.13.2, Perimeter 1.12.3, Compliance Guardian 4.7.1, and earlier versions, allowing administrator users to upload files without proper validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious files that compromise the system. In addition, it is vulnerable to Path Traversal, which allows files to be written to arbitrary directories within the web root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10868 | Business Logic Errors in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10868</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.4 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1 where certain string conversion methods exhibit performance degradation with large inputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11042 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11042</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.2 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1, that allows an attacker to cause uncontrolled CPU consumption, potentially leading to a Denial of Service (DoS) condition while using specific GraphQL queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5069 | Incorrect Ownership Assignment in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5069</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.10 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to gain unauthorized access to confidential issues by creating a project with an identical name to the victim's project.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10858 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10858</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1 that allows unauthenticated users to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) condition while uploading specifically crafted large JSON files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10867 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10867</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 18.1 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to create a denial-of-service condition by exploiting an unprotected GraphQL API through repeated requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10871 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10871</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.6 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1. Project Maintainers can exploit a vulnerability where they can assign custom roles to users with permissions exceeding their own, effectively granting themselves elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7691 | Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7691</link><description>A privilege escalation issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 18.2.7, 18.3 prior to 18.3.3, and 18.4 prior to 18.4.1 that could have allowed a developer with specific group management permissions to escalate their privileges and obtain unauthorized access to additional system capabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9642 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9642</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 14.10 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1 that could allow an attacker to inject malicious content that may lead to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9958 | Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9958</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 14.10 before 18.2.7, 18.3 before 18.3.3, and 18.4 before 18.4.1, that could have allowed Guest users to access sensitive information stored in virtual registry configurations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11021 | Libsoup: out-of-bounds read in cookie date handling of libsoup http library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11021</link><description>A flaw was found in the cookie date handling logic of the libsoup HTTP library, widely used by GNOME and other applications for web communication. When processing cookies with specially crafted expiration dates, the library may perform an out-of-bounds memory read. This flaw could result in unintended disclosure of memory contents, potentially exposing sensitive information from the process using libsoup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27006 | WordPress Authorsy Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27006</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themeplugs Authorsy allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Authorsy: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48107 | WordPress Uncode theme &amp;lt; 2.9.4.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48107</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in undsgn Uncode allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Uncode: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48326 | WordPress Acclectic Media Organizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48326</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Acclectic Media Acclectic Media Organizer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Acclectic Media Organizer: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4957 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.5.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4957</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid  allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.9.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58914 | WordPress Di Themes Demo Site Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Plugin Activation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58914</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Di Themes Di Themes Demo Site Importer allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Di Themes Demo Site Importer: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58917 | WordPress Quantities and Units for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58917</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nick Verwymeren Quantities and Units for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Quantities and Units for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58919 | WordPress Wide Banner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58919</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in guihom Wide Banner allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Wide Banner: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59002 | WordPress BM Content Builder Plugin &amp;lt; 3.16.3.3 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59002</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in SeaTheme BM Content Builder allows Path Traversal. This issue affects BM Content Builder: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59010 | WordPress Permalink Manager Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59010</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Maciej Bis Permalink Manager Lite allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Permalink Manager Lite: from n/a through 2.5.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59011 | WordPress Traveler Theme &amp;lt; 3.2.3 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59011</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in shinetheme Traveler allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Traveler: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59012 | WordPress Traveler theme &amp;lt; 3.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59012</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in shinetheme Traveler allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Traveler: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60040 | WordPress wp-mpdf Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60040</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fkrauthan wp-mpdf allows Stored XSS. This issue affects wp-mpdf: from n/a through 3.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60092 | WordPress Download Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.24 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60092</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Shahjada Download Manager allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Download Manager: from n/a through 3.3.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60093 | WordPress Download Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.24 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60093</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shahjada Download Manager allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Download Manager: from n/a through 3.3.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60094 | WordPress Stackable Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.18.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60094</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Benjamin Intal Stackable allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Stackable: from n/a through 3.18.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60095 | WordPress Stackable Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.18.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60095</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Benjamin Intal Stackable allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Stackable: from n/a through 3.18.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60096 | WordPress TheGem (Elementor) Theme &amp;lt;= 5.10.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60096</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem (Elementor) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TheGem (Elementor): from n/a through 5.10.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60097 | WordPress TheGem Theme &amp;lt;= 5.10.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60097</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TheGem: from n/a through 5.10.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60098 | WordPress Theme My Login Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.12 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60098</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jeff Farthing Theme My Login allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Theme My Login: from n/a through 7.1.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60099 | WordPress Embed Any Document Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60099</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in awsm.in Embed Any Document allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Embed Any Document: from n/a through 2.7.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60100 | WordPress XStore Theme &amp;lt;= 9.5.3 - Content Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60100</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in 8theme XStore allows Code Injection. This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60101 | WordPress Woostify Theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60101</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Woostify Woostify allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Woostify: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60102 | WordPress WPFront User Role Editor Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60102</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Syam Mohan WPFront User Role Editor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPFront User Role Editor: from n/a through 4.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60103 | WordPress ListingPro Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60103</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60104 | WordPress Gallery Custom Links Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60104</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jordy Meow Gallery Custom Links allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gallery Custom Links: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60105 | WordPress Ditty Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.58 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60105</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in metaphorcreations Ditty allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ditty: from n/a through 3.1.58.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60106 | WordPress EmailKit Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60106</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Roxnor EmailKit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects EmailKit: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60107 | WordPress LambertGroup - AllInOne - Banner with Playlist Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60107</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup LambertGroup - AllInOne - Banner with Playlist allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects LambertGroup - AllInOne - Banner with Playlist: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60108 | WordPress LambertGroup - AllInOne - Banner with Thumbnails Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8  - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60108</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup LambertGroup - AllInOne - Banner with Thumbnails allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects LambertGroup - AllInOne - Banner with Thumbnails: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60109 | WordPress LambertGroup - AllInOne - Content Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60109</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup LambertGroup - AllInOne - Content Slider allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects LambertGroup - AllInOne - Content Slider: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60110 | WordPress AllInOne - Banner Rotator Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60110</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup AllInOne - Banner Rotator allows SQL Injection. This issue affects AllInOne - Banner Rotator: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60111 | WordPress Javo Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0.266 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60111</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in javothemes Javo Core allows Authentication Bypass. This issue affects Javo Core: from n/a through 3.0.0.266.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60112 | WordPress aThemes Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60112</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Syed Balkhi aThemes Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects aThemes Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60113 | WordPress Groovy Menu Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60113</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in grooni Groovy Menu allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Groovy Menu: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60114 | WordPress YayCurrency Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60114</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in YayCommerce YayCurrency allows Code Injection. This issue affects YayCurrency: from n/a through 3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60115 | WordPress Instapage Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.12 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60115</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in instapagedev Instapage Plugin allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Instapage Plugin: from n/a through 3.5.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60116 | WordPress Grand Conference Theme Custom Post Type Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60116</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeGoods Grand Conference Theme Custom Post Type allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Grand Conference Theme Custom Post Type: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60117 | WordPress Vehica Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.100 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60117</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in TangibleWP Vehica Core allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Vehica Core: from n/a through 1.0.100.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60118 | WordPress PGS Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60118</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Potenzaglobalsolutions PGS Core allows SQL Injection. This issue affects PGS Core: from n/a through 5.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60119 | WordPress CoSchedule Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.10 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60119</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in CoSchedule CoSchedule allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects CoSchedule: from n/a through 3.3.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60120 | WordPress WP Directory Kit Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60120</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpdirectorykit WP Directory Kit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Directory Kit: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60121 | WordPress WooEvents Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60121</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ex-Themes WooEvents allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WooEvents: from n/a through 4.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60122 | WordPress HivePress Claim Listings Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60122</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HivePress HivePress Claim Listings allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects HivePress Claim Listings: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60123 | WordPress HivePress Claim Listings Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60123</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HivePress HivePress Claim Listings allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects HivePress Claim Listings: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60124 | WordPress Simple Colorbox Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ryan Hellyer Simple Colorbox allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Colorbox: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60125 | WordPress FoodBook Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60125</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in themelooks FoodBook allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects FoodBook: from n/a through 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60126 | WordPress Testimonial Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60126</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in PluginOps Testimonial Slider allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Testimonial Slider: from n/a through 3.5.8.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60127 | WordPress CopySafe Web Protection Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60127</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ArtistScope CopySafe Web Protection allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CopySafe Web Protection: from n/a through 4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60128 | WordPress Delisho Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60128</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Delicious Delisho allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Delisho: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60129 | WordPress Yext Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60129</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Yext Yext allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Yext: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60130 | WordPress WEDOS Global Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60130</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wedos.com WEDOS Global allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WEDOS Global: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60133 | WordPress PE Easy Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DJ-Extensions.com PE Easy Slider allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PE Easy Slider: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60136 | WordPress User Notes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60136</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in cartpauj User Notes allows Stored XSS. This issue affects User Notes: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60137 | WordPress Post Featured Video Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60137</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Galaxy Weblinks Post Featured Video allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Post Featured Video: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60138 | WordPress SKT Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60138</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sonalsinha21 SKT Blocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SKT Blocks: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60139 | WordPress Sendle Shipping Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.02 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60139</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Joovii Sendle Shipping allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Sendle Shipping: from n/a through 6.02.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60140 | WordPress The Tribal Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60140</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in thetechtribe The Tribal allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects The Tribal: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60141 | WordPress The Tribal Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60141</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in thetechtribe The Tribal allows Stored XSS. This issue affects The Tribal: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60142 | WordPress Simple Meta Tags Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60142</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DaganLev Simple Meta Tags allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Simple Meta Tags: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60143 | WordPress Netgsm Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.58 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60143</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in netgsm Netgsm allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Netgsm: from n/a through 2.9.58.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60144 | WordPress Lenix scss compiler Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60144</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in yonifre Lenix scss compiler allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Lenix scss compiler: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60145 | WordPress Lenix scss compiler Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60145</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in yonifre Lenix scss compiler allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Lenix scss compiler: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60146 | WordPress Map Categories to Pages Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60146</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Amit Verma Map Categories to Pages allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Map Categories to Pages: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60147 | WordPress HT Feed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60147</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HT Plugins HT Feed allows Stored XSS. This issue affects HT Feed: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60148 | WordPress Subscribe to Download Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60148</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpshuffle Subscribe to Download allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Subscribe to Download: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60149 | WordPress Notely Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60149</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Ott Notely allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Notely: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60150 | WordPress Subscribe to Download Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60150</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in wpshuffle Subscribe to Download allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Subscribe to Download: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60152 | WordPress Subscribe To Unlock Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60152</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpshuffle Subscribe To Unlock allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Subscribe To Unlock: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60153 | WordPress Subscribe To Unlock Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60153</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in wpshuffle Subscribe To Unlock allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Subscribe To Unlock: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60154 | WordPress MWW Disclaimer Buttons Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.41 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60154</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jennifer Moss MWW Disclaimer Buttons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MWW Disclaimer Buttons: from n/a through 3.41.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60155 | WordPress WP Virtual Assistant Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60155</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in loopus WP Virtual Assistant allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Virtual Assistant: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60156 | WordPress AR For WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.98 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60156</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in webandprint AR For WordPress allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects AR For WordPress: from n/a through 7.98.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60157 | WordPress WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp;amp; Support Ticket System Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60157</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in emarket-design WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp; Support Ticket System allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp; Support Ticket System: from n/a through 6.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60158 | WordPress Nota Fiscal Eletrônica WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60158</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webmaniabr Nota Fiscal Eletrônica WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Nota Fiscal Eletrônica WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60159 | WordPress Nota Fiscal Eletrônica WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.0.6 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60159</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in webmaniabr Nota Fiscal Eletrônica WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Nota Fiscal Eletrônica WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60160 | WordPress Smart Related Products Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60160</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sharkthemes Smart Related Products allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Smart Related Products: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60161 | WordPress ZoloBlocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60161</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in bdthemes ZoloBlocks allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects ZoloBlocks: from n/a through 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60162 | WordPress Job Board Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.61 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60162</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Job Board Manager allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Job Board Manager: from n/a through 2.1.61.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60163 | WordPress bbp topic count Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60163</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Robin W bbp topic count allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects bbp topic count: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60164 | WordPress NewsmanApp Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60164</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NewsMAN NewsmanApp allows Stored XSS. This issue affects NewsmanApp: from n/a through 2.7.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60165 | WordPress Frames Theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60165</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HaruTheme Frames allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Frames: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60166 | WordPress WP Subscription Forms PRO Plugin &amp;lt;=  2.0.5 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60166</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpshuffle WP Subscription Forms PRO allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Subscription Forms PRO: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60167 | WordPress Page Manager for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60167</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in honzat Page Manager for Elementor allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Page Manager for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60169 | WordPress W3SCloud Contact Form 7 to Zoho CRM Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60169</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in W3S Cloud Technology W3SCloud Contact Form 7 to Zoho CRM allows Stored XSS. This issue affects W3SCloud Contact Form 7 to Zoho CRM: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60170 | WordPress HTACCESS IP Blocker Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60170</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Taraprasad Swain HTACCESS IP Blocker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects HTACCESS IP Blocker: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60171 | WordPress Conditional Cart Messages for WooCommerce – YourPlugins.com Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60171</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in yourplugins Conditional Cart Messages for WooCommerce &amp;#8211; YourPlugins.com allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Conditional Cart Messages for WooCommerce &amp;#8211; YourPlugins.com: from n/a through 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60172 | WordPress Flytedesk Digital Plugin &amp;lt;= 20181101 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60172</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flytedesk Flytedesk Digital allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Flytedesk Digital: from n/a through 20181101.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60173 | WordPress GST for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60173</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ashwani kumar GST for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects GST for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60177 | WordPress Recaptcha – wp Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60177</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rozx Recaptcha &amp;#8211; wp allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Recaptcha &amp;#8211; wp: from n/a through 0.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60179 | WordPress Click &amp;amp; Tweet Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60179</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Space Studio Click &amp;amp; Tweet allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Click &amp;amp; Tweet: from n/a through 0.8.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60181 | WordPress Silencesoft RSS Reader Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60181</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in silence Silencesoft RSS Reader allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Silencesoft RSS Reader: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60184 | WordPress SEO Search Permalink Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60184</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Terry L. SEO Search Permalink allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SEO Search Permalink: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60185 | WordPress kontur Admin Style Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60185</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kontur.us kontur Admin Style allows Stored XSS. This issue affects kontur Admin Style: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60186 | WordPress Google+ Comments Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60186</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alex Moss Google+ Comments allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google+ Comments: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60219 | WordPress WooCommerce Designer Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.24 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60219</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in HaruTheme WooCommerce Designer Pro allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects WooCommerce Designer Pro: from n/a through 1.9.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1862 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload in Multiple WSO2 Products via BPEL Uploader SOAP Service Leading to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1862</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to improper validation of user-supplied filenames in the BPEL uploader SOAP service endpoint. A malicious actor with administrative privileges can upload arbitrary files to a user-controlled location on the server.


By leveraging this vulnerability, an attacker can upload a specially crafted payload and achieve remote code execution (RCE), potentially compromising the server and its data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1396 | Username Enumeration in Multiple WSO2 Products with Multi-Attribute Login Enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1396</link><description>A username enumeration vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products when Multi-Attribute Login is enabled. In this configuration, the system returns a distinct "User does not exist" error message to the login form, regardless of the validate_username setting. This behavior allows malicious actors to determine which usernames exist in the system based on observable discrepancies in the application's responses.


Exploitation of this vulnerability could aid in brute-force attacks, targeted phishing campaigns, or other social engineering techniques by confirming the validity of user identifiers within the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54831 | Apache Airflow: Connection sensitive details exposed to users with READ permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54831</link><description>Apache Airflow 3 introduced a change to the handling of sensitive information in Connections. The intent was to restrict access to sensitive connection fields to Connection Editing Users, effectively applying a "write-only" model for sensitive values.


In Airflow 3.0.3, this model was unintentionally violated: sensitive connection information could be viewed by users with READ permissions through both the API and the UI. This behavior also bypassed the `AIRFLOW__CORE__HIDE_SENSITIVE_VAR_CONN_FIELDS` configuration option.


This issue does not affect Airflow 2.x, where exposing sensitive information to connection editors was the intended and documented behavior.






Users of Airflow 3.0.3 are advised to upgrade Airflow to &gt;=3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35027 | Unitree Multiple Robotic Products Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35027</link><description>Multiple robotic products by Unitree sharing a common firmware, including the Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices, contain a command injection vulnerability. By setting a malicious string when configuring the on-board WiFi via a BLE module of an affected robot, then triggering a restart of the WiFi service, an attacker can ultimately trigger commands to be run as root via the wpa_supplicant_restart.sh shell script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10136 | TweetThis Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10136</link><description>The TweetThis Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tweetthis' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10137 | Snow Monkey &amp;lt;= 29.1.5 - Unauthenticated Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10137</link><description>The Snow Monkey theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 29.1.5 via the request() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10180 | Markdown Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10180</link><description>The Markdown Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'markdown' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10307 | Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10307</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the delete backup functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10490 | Zephyr Project Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.202 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10490</link><description>The Zephyr Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.202 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10747 | WP-DownloadManager &amp;lt;= 1.68.11 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10747</link><description>The WP-DownloadManager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the download-add.php file in all versions up to, and including, 1.68.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 05:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9490 | Popup Maker &amp;lt;= 1.20.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9490</link><description>The Popup Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.20.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 05:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10036 | Featured Image from URL (FIFU) &amp;lt;= 5.2.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10036</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the get_all_urls() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10037 | Featured Image from URL (FIFU) &amp;lt;= 5.2.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10037</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the get_posts_with_internal_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9984 | Featured Image from URL (FIFU) &amp;lt;= 5.2.7 - Missing Authorization to Password Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9984</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the fifu_api_debug_posts() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read private/password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9985 | Featured Image from URL (FIFU) &amp;lt;= 5.2.7 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9985</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.7 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10173 | ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon – All in One WooCommerce Solution &amp;lt;= 4.8.3 - Insufficient Authorization to Authenticated (Editor+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10173</link><description>The ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon – All in One WooCommerce Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to an incorrect capability check on the post_save() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10377 | System Dashboard &amp;lt;= 2.8.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10377</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.20. This is due to missing nonce validation on the sd_toggle_logs() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to toggle critical logging settings including Page Access Logs, Error Logs, and Email Delivery Logs via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10745 | Banhammer – Monitor Site Traffic, Block Bad Users and Bots &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - Unauthenticated Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10745</link><description>The Banhammer – Monitor Site Traffic, Block Bad Users and Bots plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blocking Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8. This is due to a site-wide “secret key” being deterministically generated from a constant character set using md5() and base64_encode() and then stored in the `banhammer_secret_key` option. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin’s logging and blocking by appending a GET parameter named `banhammer-process_{SECRET}` where `{SECRET}` is the predictable value, thereby causing Banhammer to abort its protections for that request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11000 | Open Babel PQSformat.cpp ReadMolecule null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11000</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. This affects the function PQSFormat::ReadMolecule of the file /src/formats/PQSformat.cpp. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9044 | Mapster WP Maps &amp;lt;= 1.20.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9044</link><description>The Mapster WP Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple fields in versions up to, and including, 1.20.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level permissions and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10998 | Open Babel chemkinformat.cpp ReadReactionQualifierLines null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10998</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. The affected element is the function ChemKinFormat::ReadReactionQualifierLines of the file /src/formats/chemkinformat.cpp. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10999 | Open Babel cacaoformat.cpp SetHilderbrandt null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10999</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. The impacted element is the function CacaoFormat::SetHilderbrandt of the file /src/formats/cacaoformat.cpp. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10996 | Open Babel smilesformat.cpp ParseSmiles heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10996</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. This issue affects the function OBSmilesParser::ParseSmiles of the file /src/formats/smilesformat.cpp. Performing manipulation results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10997 | Open Babel chemkinformat.cpp CheckSpecies heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10997</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. Impacted is the function ChemKinFormat::CheckSpecies of the file /src/formats/chemkinformat.cpp. Executing manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10178 | CM Business Directory &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10178</link><description>The CM Business Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cmbd_featured_image' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10752 | OAuth Single Sign On – SSO (OAuth Client) &amp;lt;= 6.26.12 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10752</link><description>The OAuth Single Sign On – SSO (OAuth Client) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.26.12. This is due to using a predictable state parameter (base64 encoded app name) without any randomness in the OAuth flow. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to forge OAuth authorization requests and potentially hijack the OAuth flow via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10994 | Open Babel gamessformat.cpp ReadMolecule use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10994</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. This affects the function GAMESSOutputFormat::ReadMolecule of the file gamessformat.cpp. This manipulation causes use after free. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10995 | Open Babel zipstreamimpl.h underflow memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10995</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. This vulnerability affects the function zlib_stream::basic_unzip_streambuf::underflow in the library /src/zipstreamimpl.h. Such manipulation leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8200 | Mega Elements – Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Timer Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8200</link><description>The Mega Elements – Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown Timer widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8906 | Widgets for Tiktok Feed &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8906</link><description>The Widgets for Tiktok Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'trustindex-feed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10992 | roncoo roncoo-pay lookupList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10992</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in roncoo roncoo-pay up to 9428382af21cd5568319eae7429b7e1d0332ff40. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/info/lookupList. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10993 | MuYuCMS Template Management admin.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10993</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in MuYuCMS up to 2.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin.php of the component Template Management. The manipulation results in code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60017 | Unitree Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices through 2025-09-20 allow root OS command injection via the hostapd_restart.sh wifi_ssid or wifi_pass par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60017</link><description>Unitree Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices through 2025-09-20 allow root OS command injection via the hostapd_restart.sh wifi_ssid or wifi_pass parameter (within restart_wifi_ap and restart_wifi_sta).</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60250 | Unitree Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices through 2025-09-20 decrypt BLE packet data by using the df98b715d5c6ed2b25817b6f2554124a key and the 284...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60250</link><description>Unitree Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices through 2025-09-20 decrypt BLE packet data by using the df98b715d5c6ed2b25817b6f2554124a key and the 2841ae97419c2973296a0d4bdfe19a4f IV.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60251 | Unitree Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices through 2025-09-20 accept any handshake secret with the unitree substring.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60251</link><description>Unitree Go2, G1, H1, and B2 devices through 2025-09-20 accept any handshake secret with the unitree substring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10988 | YunaiV ruoyi-vue-pro transfer improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10988</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in YunaiV ruoyi-vue-pro up to 2025.09. This affects an unknown part of the file /crm/business/transfer. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10989 | yangzongzhuan RuoYi selectAll improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10989</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yangzongzhuan RuoYi up to 4.8.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/role/authUser/selectAll. Performing manipulation of the argument userIds results in improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10981 | JeecgBoot exportXls improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10981</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /sys/tenant/exportXls. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10987 | YunaiV yudao-cloud HTTP Request transfer improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10987</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in YunaiV yudao-cloud up to 2025.09. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /crm/contact/transfer of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument contactId causes improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10980 | JeecgBoot exportXls improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10980</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. This affects an unknown function of the file /sys/position/exportXls. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10979 | JeecgBoot exportXls improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10979</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /sys/role/exportXls. This manipulation causes improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56769 | An issue was discovered in chinabugotech hutool before 5.8.4 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary expressions that lead to arbitrary meth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56769</link><description>An issue was discovered in chinabugotech hutool before 5.8.4 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary expressions that lead to arbitrary method invocation and potentially remote code execution (RCE) via the QLExpressEngine class.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10977 | JeecgBoot deleteBatch improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10977</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /sys/tenant/deleteBatch. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10978 | JeecgBoot Filter exportXls improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10978</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /sys/user/exportXls of the component Filter Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10976 | JeecgBoot getDepartUserList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10976</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/getDepartUserList. Executing manipulation of the argument departId can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10974 | giantspatula SewKinect Endpoint calculate pickle.loads deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10974</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in giantspatula SewKinect up to 7fd963ceb3385af3706af02b8a128a13399dffb1. This affects the function pickle.loads of the file /calculate of the component Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument body_parts/point_cloud leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10975 | GuanxingLu vlarl ZeroMQ reasoning_server.py run_reasoning_server deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10975</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GuanxingLu vlarl up to 31abc0baf53ef8f5db666a1c882e1ea64def2997. This vulnerability affects the function experiments.robot.bridge.reasoning_server::run_reasoning_server of the file experiments/robot/bridge/reasoning_server.py of the component ZeroMQ. Performing manipulation of the argument Message results in deserialization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26482 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell iDRAC9, all versions, contains an Information Disclosure vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26482</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell iDRAC9, all versions, contains an Information Disclosure vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10973 | JackieDYH Resume-management-system show.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10973</link><description>A flaw has been found in JackieDYH Resume-management-system up to fb6b857d852dd796e748ce30c606fe5e61c18273. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/show.php. This manipulation of the argument userid causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59402 | Flock Safety Bravo Edge AI Compute Device BRAVO_00.00_local_20241017 accepts the default Thundercomm TurboX 6490 Firehose loader in EDL/QDL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59402</link><description>Flock Safety Bravo Edge AI Compute Device BRAVO_00.00_local_20241017 accepts the default Thundercomm TurboX 6490 Firehose loader in EDL/QDL mode. This enables attackers with physical access to flash arbitrary firmware, dump partitions, and bypass bootloader and OS security controls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59404 | Flock Safety Bravo Edge AI Compute Device BRAVO_00.00_local_20241017 ships with its bootloader unlocked. This permits bypass of Android Veri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59404</link><description>Flock Safety Bravo Edge AI Compute Device BRAVO_00.00_local_20241017 ships with its bootloader unlocked. This permits bypass of Android Verified Boot (AVB) and allows direct modification of partitions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59408 | Flock Safety Bravo Edge AI Compute Device BRAVO_00.00_local_20241017 ships with Secure Boot disabled. This allows an attacker to flash modif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59408</link><description>Flock Safety Bravo Edge AI Compute Device BRAVO_00.00_local_20241017 ships with Secure Boot disabled. This allows an attacker to flash modified firmware with no cryptographic protections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11005 | TOTOLINK X6000R Unauthenticated Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11005</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in TOTOLINK X6000R allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects X6000R: through V9.4.0cu.1458_B20250708.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10965 | LazyAGI LazyLLM server.py lazyllm_call deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10965</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LazyAGI LazyLLM up to 0.6.1. Affected by this issue is the function lazyllm_call of the file lazyllm/components/deploy/relay/server.py. Such manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10967 | MuFen-mker PHP-Usermm chkuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10967</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in MuFen-mker PHP-Usermm up to 37f2d24e51b04346dfc565b93fc2fc6b37bdaea9. This affects an unknown part of the file /chkuser.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43816 | A memory leak in the headless API for StructuredContents in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.119, and older unsupported versions, and Life...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43816</link><description>A memory leak in the headless API for StructuredContents in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.119, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.5, 2023.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions allows an attacker to cause server unavailability (denial of service) via repeatedly calling the API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57632 | libsmb2 6.2+ is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. When processing SMB2 chained PDUs (NextCommand), libsmb2 repeatedly calls smb2_add_iovector()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57632</link><description>libsmb2 6.2+ is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. When processing SMB2 chained PDUs (NextCommand), libsmb2 repeatedly calls smb2_add_iovector() to append to a fixed-size iovec array without checking the upper bound of v-&gt;niov (SMB2_MAX_VECTORS=256). An attacker can craft responses with many chained PDUs to overflow v-&gt;niov and perform heap out-of-bounds writes, causing memory corruption, crashes, and potentially arbitrary code execution. The SMB2_OPLOCK_BREAK path bypasses message ID validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43993 | Dell Wireless 5932e and Qualcomm Snapdragon X62 Firmware and GNSS/GPS Driver, versions prior to 3.2.0.22 contain an Unquoted Search Path or ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43993</link><description>Dell Wireless 5932e and Qualcomm Snapdragon X62 Firmware and GNSS/GPS Driver, versions prior to 3.2.0.22 contain an Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10964 | Wavlink NU516U1 firewall.cgi sub_401B30 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10964</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Wavlink NU516U1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_401B30 of the file /cgi-bin/firewall.cgi. This manipulation of the argument remoteManagementEnabled causes command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59814 | Unauthenticated SQL-injection in password field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59814</link><description>This vulnerability allows malicious actors to gain unauthorized access to the Zenitel ICX500 and ICX510 Gateway Billing Admin endpoint, enabling them to read the entire contents of the Billing Admin database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59815 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in the Billing Administration portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59815</link><description>This vulnerability allows malicious actors to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system of the Zenitel ICX500 and ICX510 Gateway, granting shell access. Exploitation can compromise the device’s availability, confidentiality, and integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59816 | Authenticated Union based SQL-injection in the search input field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59816</link><description>This vulnerability allows attackers to directly query the underlying database, potentially retrieving all data stored in the Billing Admin database, including user credentials. User passwords are stored in plaintext, significantly increasing the severity of this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59817 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in zForm_auto_config</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59817</link><description>This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system. Because the web portal runs with root privileges, successful exploitation grants full control over the device, potentially compromising its availability, confidentiality, and integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10963 | Wavlink NU516U1 firewall.cgi sub_4016F0 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10963</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Wavlink NU516U1 M16U1_V240425. Affected is the function sub_4016F0 of the file /cgi-bin/firewall.cgi. The manipulation of the argument del_flag results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29156 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in petstore v.1.0.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the /api/v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29156</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in petstore v.1.0.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the /api/v3/pet</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10962 | Wavlink NU516U1 SetName wireless.cgi sub_403198 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10962</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Wavlink NU516U1 M16U1_V240425. This impacts the function sub_403198 of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi of the component SetName Page. The manipulation of the argument mac_5g leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29157 | An issue in petstore v.1.0.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via accessing a non-existent endpoint/cart, the server retur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29157</link><description>An issue in petstore v.1.0.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via accessing a non-existent endpoint/cart, the server returns a 404-error page exposing sensitive information including the Servlet name (default) and server version</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10960 | Wavlink NU516U1 DeleteMac wireless.cgi sub_402D1C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Wavlink NU516U1 M16U1_V240425. The impacted element is the function sub_402D1C of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi of the component DeleteMac Page. Performing manipulation of the argument delete_list results in command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10961 | Wavlink NU516U1 Delete_Mac_list wireless.cgi sub_4030C0 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10961</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Wavlink NU516U1 M16U1_V240425. This affects the function sub_4030C0 of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi of the component Delete_Mac_list Page. Executing manipulation of the argument delete_list can lead to command injection. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48707 | An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) before 5.0.1. TPM authentication information could, in some HA use cases, be s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48707</link><description>An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) before 5.0.1. TPM authentication information could, in some HA use cases, be shared among administrators, which can cause secret sharing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29155 | An issue in petstore v.1.0.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DELETE endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29155</link><description>An issue in petstore v.1.0.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DELETE endpoint</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10958 | Wavlink NU516U1 AddMac wireless.cgi sub_403010 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10958</link><description>A flaw has been found in Wavlink NU516U1 M16U1_V240425. Impacted is the function sub_403010 of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi of the component AddMac Page. This manipulation of the argument macAddr causes command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10959 | Wavlink NU516U1 firewall.cgi sub_401778 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10959</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Wavlink NU516U1 M16U1_V240425. The affected element is the function sub_401778 of the file /cgi-bin/firewall.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument dmz_flag leads to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57623 | A NULL pointer dereference in TOTOLINK N600R firmware v4.3.0cu.7866_B2022506 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57623</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in TOTOLINK N600R firmware v4.3.0cu.7866_B2022506 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60249 | vulnerability-lookup 2.16.0 allows XSS in bundle.py, comment.py, and user.py, by a user on a vulnerability-lookup instance who can add bundl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60249</link><description>vulnerability-lookup 2.16.0 allows XSS in bundle.py, comment.py, and user.py, by a user on a vulnerability-lookup instance who can add bundles, comments, or sightings. A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the handling of user-supplied input in the Bundles, Comments, and Sightings components. Untrusted data was not properly sanitized before being rendered in templates and tables, which could allow attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript into the application. The issue was due to unsafe use of innerHTML and insufficient validation of dynamic URLs and model fields. This vulnerability has been fixed by escaping untrusted data, replacing innerHTML assignments with safer DOM methods, encoding URLs with encodeURIComponent, and improving input validation in the affected models.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34227 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 2026R1 Configuration Wizard Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34227</link><description>Nagios XI &lt; 2026R1 is vulnerable to an authenticated command injection vulnerability within the MongoDB Database, MySQL Query, MySQL Server, Postgres Server, and Postgres Query wizards. It is possible to inject shell characters into arguments provided to the service and execute arbitrary system commands on the underlying host as the `nagios` user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10879 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in Dingtian DT-R002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10879</link><description>All versions of Dingtian DT-R002 are vulnerable to an Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability that could allow an attacker to retrieve the current user's username without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10880 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in Dingtian DT-R002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10880</link><description>All versions of Dingtian DT-R002 are vulnerable to an Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability that could allow an attacker to extract the proprietary "Dingtian Binary" protocol password by sending an unauthenticated GET request</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20333 | A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20333</link><description>A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in HTTP(S) requests. An attacker with valid VPN user credentials could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as root, possibly resulting in the complete compromise of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20362 | A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20362</link><description>A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access restricted URL endpoints without authentication that should otherwise be inaccessible without authentication. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in HTTP(S) requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access a restricted URL without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20363 | A vulnerability in the web services of Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software, Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20363</link><description>A vulnerability in the web services of Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software, Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense (FTD) Software, Cisco IOS Software, Cisco IOS XE Software, and Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker (Cisco ASA and FTD Software) or authenticated, remote attacker (Cisco IOS, IOS XE, and IOS XR Software) with low user privileges to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to a targeted web service on an affected device after obtaining additional information about the system, overcoming exploit mitigations, or both. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as root, which may lead to the complete compromise of the affected device.
&#13; For more information about this vulnerability, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57446 | An issue in O-RAN Near Realtime RIC ric-plt-submgr in the J-Release environment, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57446</link><description>An issue in O-RAN Near Realtime RIC ric-plt-submgr in the J-Release environment, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via a crafted request to the Subscription Manager API component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10953 | UTT 1200GW/1250GW formApMail buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10953</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 1200GW and 1250GW up to 3.0.0-170831/3.2.2-200710. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/formApMail. The manipulation of the argument senderEmail leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55560 | An issue in pytorch v2.7.0 can lead to a Denial of Service (DoS) when a PyTorch model consists of torch.Tensor.to_sparse() and torch.Tensor....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55560</link><description>An issue in pytorch v2.7.0 can lead to a Denial of Service (DoS) when a PyTorch model consists of torch.Tensor.to_sparse() and torch.Tensor.to_dense() and is compiled by Inductor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60018 | Glib-networking: out of bound reads on glib-networking through tls/openssl/gtlscertificate-openssl.c via &amp;quot;g_tls_certificate_openssl_get_property()&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60018</link><description>glib-networking's OpenSSL backend fails to properly check the return value of a call to BIO_write(), resulting in an out of bounds read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60019 | Glib-networking: uninitialized memory dereferences on glib-networking through glib-networking/tls/openssl/gtlsbio.c via g_tls_bio_new_from_iostream() and g_tls_bio_new_from_datagram_based()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60019</link><description>glib-networking's OpenSSL backend fails to properly check the return value of memory allocation routines. An out of memory condition could potentially result in writing to an invalid memory location.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10952 | geyang ml-logger File server.py stream_handler information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10952</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in geyang ml-logger up to acf255bade5be6ad88d90735c8367b28cbe3a743. Affected by this issue is the function stream_handler of the file ml_logger/server.py of the component File Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument key results in information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55559 | An issue was discovered TensorFlow v2.18.0. A Denial of Service (DoS) occurs when padding is set to 'valid' in tf.keras.layers.Conv2D.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55559</link><description>An issue was discovered TensorFlow v2.18.0. A Denial of Service (DoS) occurs when padding is set to 'valid' in tf.keras.layers.Conv2D.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26333 | Dell Crypto-J generates an error message that includes sensitive information about its environment and associated data. A remote attacker co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26333</link><description>Dell Crypto-J generates an error message that includes sensitive information about its environment and associated data. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43943 | Dell Cloud Disaster Recovery, version(s) prior to 19.20, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('O...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43943</link><description>Dell Cloud Disaster Recovery, version(s) prior to 19.20, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55558 | A buffer overflow occurs in pytorch v2.7.0 when a PyTorch model consists of torch.nn.Conv2d, torch.nn.functional.hardshrink, and torch.Tenso...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55558</link><description>A buffer overflow occurs in pytorch v2.7.0 when a PyTorch model consists of torch.nn.Conv2d, torch.nn.functional.hardshrink, and torch.Tensor.view-torch.mv() and is compiled by Inductor, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48014 | Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions prior to 5.0.2.3 contain an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48014</link><description>Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions prior to 5.0.2.3 contain an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10911 | Libxslt: use-after-free with key data stored cross-rvt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10911</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in libxslt while parsing xsl nodes that may lead to the dereference of expired pointers and application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33116 | IBM Watson Studio on Cloud Pak for Data cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33116</link><description>IBM Watson Studio 4.0 through 5.2.0 on Cloud Pak for Data is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55552 | pytorch v2.8.0 was discovered to display unexpected behavior when the components torch.rot90 and torch.randn_like are used together.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55552</link><description>pytorch v2.8.0 was discovered to display unexpected behavior when the components torch.rot90 and torch.randn_like are used together.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55553 | A syntax error in the component proxy_tensor.py of pytorch v2.7.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55553</link><description>A syntax error in the component proxy_tensor.py of pytorch v2.7.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55554 | pytorch v2.8.0 was discovered to contain an integer overflow in the component torch.nan_to_num-.long().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55554</link><description>pytorch v2.8.0 was discovered to contain an integer overflow in the component torch.nan_to_num-.long().</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55556 | TensorFlow v2.18.0 was discovered to output random results when compiling Embedding, leading to unexpected behavior in the application.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55556</link><description>TensorFlow v2.18.0 was discovered to output random results when compiling Embedding, leading to unexpected behavior in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55557 | A Name Error occurs in pytorch v2.7.0 when a PyTorch model consists of torch.cummin and is compiled by Inductor, leading to a Denial of Serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55557</link><description>A Name Error occurs in pytorch v2.7.0 when a PyTorch model consists of torch.cummin and is compiled by Inductor, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59841 | FlagForgeCTF&amp;#x27;s Improper Session Handling Allows Access After Logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59841</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. In versions from 2.2.0 to before 2.3.1, the FlagForge web application improperly handles session invalidation. Authenticated users can continue to access protected endpoints, such as /api/profile, even after logging out. CSRF tokens are also still valid post-logout, which can allow unauthorized actions. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10951 | geyang ml-logger server.py log_handler path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10951</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in geyang ml-logger up to acf255bade5be6ad88d90735c8367b28cbe3a743. Affected by this vulnerability is the function log_handler of the file ml_logger/server.py. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36601 | Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions 9.5.0.0 through 9.11.0.0, contains an exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36601</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions 9.5.0.0 through 9.11.0.0, contains an exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40837 | Ericsson Indoor Connect 8855 - Missing Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40837</link><description>Ericsson
Indoor Connect 8855 contains a missing authorization vulnerability which if
exploited can allow access to the system as a user with higher privileges than
intended.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40838 | Ericsson Indoor Connect 8855 - Insufficiently Protected Credentials Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40838</link><description>Ericsson
Indoor Connect 8855 contains a vulnerability where server-side security can be
bypassed in the client which if exploited can lead to unauthorized disclosure
of user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55551 | An issue in the component torch.linalg.lu of pytorch v2.8.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when performing a slice oper...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55551</link><description>An issue in the component torch.linalg.lu of pytorch v2.8.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when performing a slice operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59838 | Monkeytype Vulnerable to Self-XSS on loading saved custom text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59838</link><description>Monkeytype is a minimalistic and customizable typing test. In versions 25.36.0 and prior, improper handling of user input when loading a saved custom text results in XSS. This issue has been patched via commit f025b12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36851 | Rob--W / cors-anywhere Misconfigured CORS Proxy Allows SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36851</link><description>Rob -- W / cors-anywhere instances configured as an open proxy allow unauthenticated external users to induce the server to make HTTP requests to arbitrary targets (SSRF). Because the proxy forwards requests and headers, an attacker can reach internal-only endpoints and link-local metadata services, retrieve instance role credentials or other sensitive metadata, and interact with internal APIs and services that are not intended to be internet-facing. The vulnerability is exploitable by sending crafted requests to the proxy with the target resource encoded in the URL; many cors-anywhere deployments forward arbitrary methods and headers (including PUT), which can permit exploitation of IMDSv2 workflows as well as access to internal management APIs. Successful exploitation can result in theft of cloud credentials, unauthorized access to internal services, remote code execution or privilege escalation (depending on reachable backends), data exfiltration, and full compromise of cloud resources. Mitigation includes: restricting the proxy to trusted origins or authentication, whitelisting allowed target hosts, preventing access to link-local and internal IP ranges, removing support for unsafe HTTP methods/headers, enabling cloud provider mitigations, and deploying network-level protections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40836 | Ericsson Indoor Connect 8855 - Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40836</link><description>Ericsson
Indoor Connect 8855 contains an improper input validation vulnerability which if exploited can lead to loss of integrity and confidentiality, as well
as unauthorized disclosure and modification of



of user
and configuration data. It may also be possible to execute commands with escalated privileges, impact
service availability, as well as modify system files and configuration
data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59832 | Horrila Stored XSS Vulnerability via Ticket Comment section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59832</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). Prior to version 1.4.0, there is a stored XSS vulnerability in the ticket comment editor. A low-privilege authenticated user could run arbitrary JavaScript in an admin’s browser, exfiltrate the admin’s cookies/CSRF token, and hijack their session. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27262 | Ericsson Indoor Connect 8855 -  Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27262</link><description>Ericsson
Indoor Connect 8855 contains a command injection vulnerability which if
exploited can lead to loss of integrity and confidentiality, as well as
unauthorized disclosure and modification of user and configuration data. It
may also be possible to execute commands with escalated privileges, impact
service availability, as well as modify system files and configuration
data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36857 | Rapid7 Appspider Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36857</link><description>Rapid7 Appspider Pro versions below 7.5.021, suffer from a broken access control vulnerability in the application's configuration file loading mechanism, whereby an attacker can place files in directories belonging to other users or projects. Affected versions allow standard users to add custom configuration files. These files, which are loaded in alphabetical order, can override or change the settings of the original configuration files, creating a security vulnerability. This issue stems from improper directory access management.

This vulnerability was remediated in version 7.5.021 of the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59830 | Rack QueryParser has an unsafe default allowing params_limit bypass via semicolon-separated parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59830</link><description>Rack is a modular Ruby web server interface. Prior to version 2.2.18, Rack::QueryParser enforces its params_limit only for parameters separated by &amp;, while still splitting on both &amp; and ;. As a result, attackers could use ; separators to bypass the parameter count limit and submit more parameters than intended. Applications or middleware that directly invoke Rack::QueryParser with its default configuration (no explicit delimiter) could be exposed to increased CPU and memory consumption. This can be abused as a limited denial-of-service vector. This issue has been patched in version 2.2.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10541 | Local Privilege Escalation via Insecure Update Mechanism in iMonitor EAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10541</link><description>iMonitor EAM 9.6394 installs a system service (eamusbsrv64.exe) that runs with NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM privileges. This service includes an insecure update mechanism that automatically loads files placed in the C:\sysupdate\ directory during startup. Because any local user can create and write to this directory, an attacker can place malicious DLLs or executables in it. Upon service restart, the files are moved to the application’s installation path and executed with SYSTEM privileges, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10542 | Insecure Default Admin Credentials Enable Full Administrative Access in iMonitor EAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10542</link><description>iMonitor EAM 9.6394 ships with default administrative credentials that are also displayed within the management client’s connection dialog. If the administrator does not change these defaults, a remote attacker can authenticate to the EAM server and gain full control over monitored agents and data. This enables reading highly sensitive telemetry (including keylogger output) and issuing arbitrary actions to all connected clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10949 | Changsha Developer Technology iView Editor Markdown cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10949</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Changsha Developer Technology iView Editor up to 1.1.1. This impacts an unknown function of the component Markdown Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10950 | geyang ml-logger Ping server.py log_handler deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10950</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in geyang ml-logger up to acf255bade5be6ad88d90735c8367b28cbe3a743. Affected is the function log_handler of the file ml_logger/server.py of the component Ping Handler. This manipulation of the argument data causes deserialization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46148 | In PyTorch through 2.6.0, when eager is used, nn.PairwiseDistance(p=2) produces incorrect results.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46148</link><description>In PyTorch through 2.6.0, when eager is used, nn.PairwiseDistance(p=2) produces incorrect results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46149 | In PyTorch before 2.7.0, when inductor is used, nn.Fold has an assertion error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46149</link><description>In PyTorch before 2.7.0, when inductor is used, nn.Fold has an assertion error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46150 | In PyTorch before 2.7.0, when torch.compile is used, FractionalMaxPool2d has inconsistent results.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46150</link><description>In PyTorch before 2.7.0, when torch.compile is used, FractionalMaxPool2d has inconsistent results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46152 | In PyTorch before 2.7.0, bitwise_right_shift produces incorrect output for certain out-of-bounds values of the "other" argument.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46152</link><description>In PyTorch before 2.7.0, bitwise_right_shift produces incorrect output for certain out-of-bounds values of the "other" argument.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46153 | PyTorch before 3.7.0 has a bernoulli_p decompose function in decompositions.py even though it lacks full consistency with the eager CPU impl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46153</link><description>PyTorch before 3.7.0 has a bernoulli_p decompose function in decompositions.py even though it lacks full consistency with the eager CPU implementation, negatively affecting nn.Dropout1d, nn.Dropout2d, and nn.Dropout3d for fallback_random=True.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59823 | Gardner providers vulnerable to code injection when Terraformer is used for infrastructure provisioning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59823</link><description>Project Gardener implements the automated management and operation of Kubernetes clusters as a service. Code injection may be possible in Gardener Extensions for AWS providers prior to version 1.64.0, Azure providers prior to version 1.55.0, OpenStack providers prior to version 1.49.0, and GCP providers prior to version 1.46.0. This vulnerability could allow a user with administrative privileges for a Gardener project to obtain control over the seed cluster where the shoot cluster is managed. This affects all Gardener installations where Terraformer is used/can be enabled for infrastructure provisioning with any of the affected components. This issue has been patched in Gardener Extensions for AWS providers version 1.64.0, Azure providers version 1.55.0, OpenStack providers version 1.49.0, and GCP providers version 1.46.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10540 | Unencrypted and Unauthenticated Communication Allows Data Exposure and Manipulation in iMonitor EAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10540</link><description>iMonitor EAM 9.6394 transmits communication between the EAM client agent and the EAM server, as well as between the EAM monitor management software and the server, in plaintext without authentication or encryption. An attacker with network access can intercept sensitive information (such as credentials, keylogger data, and personally identifiable information) and tamper with traffic. This allows both unauthorized disclosure and modification of data, including issuing arbitrary commands to client agents.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26278 | A prototype pollution in the lib.set function of dref v0.1.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted pay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26278</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.set function of dref v0.1.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57317 | apidoc-core is the core parser library to generate apidoc result following the apidoc-spec. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the prePr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57317</link><description>apidoc-core is the core parser library to generate apidoc result following the apidoc-spec. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the preProcess function of apidoc-core versions thru 0.15.0 allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10948 | MikroTik RouterOS libjson.so print parse_json_element buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10948</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MikroTik RouterOS 7. This affects the function parse_json_element of the file /rest/ip/address/print of the component libjson.so. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59426 | lobe-chat has an Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59426</link><description>Lobe Chat is an open-source artificial intelligence chat framework. Prior to version 1.130.1, the project's OIDC redirect handling logic constructs the host and protocol of the final redirect URL based on the X-Forwarded-Host or Host headers and the X-Forwarded-Proto value. In deployments where a reverse proxy forwards client-supplied X-Forwarded-* headers to the origin as-is, or where the origin trusts them without validation, an attacker can inject an arbitrary host and trigger an open redirect that sends users to a malicious domain. This issue has been patched in version 1.130.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59839 | Star Citizen EmbedVideo Extension Stored XSS through wikitext caused by usage of non-reserved data attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59839</link><description>The EmbedVideo Extension is a MediaWiki extension which adds a parser function called #ev and various parser tags for embedding video clips from various video sharing services. In versions 4.0.0 and prior, the EmbedVideo extension allows adding arbitrary attributes to an HTML element, allowing for stored XSS through wikitext. This issue has been patched via commit 4e075d3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27261 | Ericsson Indoor Connect 8855 - Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27261</link><description>Ericsson
Indoor Connect 8855 contains a SQL injection vulnerability
which if exploited can lead to unauthorized disclosure and
modification of  user and configuration data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59831 | `git-comiters` Command Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59831</link><description>git-commiters is a Node.js function module providing committers stats for their git repository. Prior to version 0.1.2, there is a command injection vulnerability in git-commiters. This vulnerability manifests with the library's primary exported API: gitCommiters(options, callback) which allows specifying options such as cwd for current working directory and revisionRange as a revision pointer, such as HEAD. However, the library does not sanitize for user input or practice secure process execution API to separate commands from their arguments and as such, uncontrolled user input is concatenated into command execution. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59834 | Command Injection in adb-mcp MCP Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59834</link><description>ADB MCP Server is a MCP (Model Context Protocol) server for interacting with Android devices through ADB. In versions 0.1.0 and prior, the MCP Server is written in a way that is vulnerable to command injection vulnerability attacks as part of some of its MCP Server tool definition and implementation. This issue has been patched via commit 041729c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10467 | Stored XSS in Proliz Software&amp;#x27;s OBS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10467</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PROLIZ Computer Software Hardware Service Trade Ltd. Co. OBS (Student Affairs Information System) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects OBS (Student Affairs Information System): before v25.0401.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59422 | Dify Has Broken Access Control on Log Message Endpoint Allows Reading of Chats of Others</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59422</link><description>Dify is an open-source LLM app development platform. In version 1.8.1, a broken access control vulnerability on the /console/api/apps/chat-messages?conversation_id=&amp;amp;limit=10 endpoint allows users in the same workspace to read chat messages of other users. A regular user is able to read the query data and the filename of the admins and probably other users chats, if they know the conversation_id. This impacts the confidentiality of chats. This issue has been patched in version 1.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5494 | Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5494</link><description>ZohoCorp ManageEngine Endpoint Central was impacted by an improper privilege management issue in the agent setup.

This issue affects Endpoint Central: through 11.4.2500.25, through 11.4.2508.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10946 | nuz007 smsboom dy.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10946</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in nuz007 smsboom up to 01b2f35bbbc23f3e0f60f38ca0e3d1b286f8d674. The affected element is an unknown function of the file dy.php. Performing manipulation of the argument hm results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10947 | Sistemas Pleno Gestão de Locação CPF validarCpf authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10947</link><description>A flaw has been found in Sistemas Pleno Gestão de Locação up to 2025.7.x. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /api/areacliente/pessoa/validarCpf of the component CPF Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument pes_cpf can lead to authorization bypass. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version 2025.8.0 is sufficient to resolve this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10449 | Path Traversal in Saysis Computer Systems&amp;#x27; Saysis Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10449</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Saysis Computer Systems Trade Ltd. Co. Saysis Web Portal allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Saysis Web Portal: from 3.1.9 &amp; 3.2.0 before 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10944 | yi-ge get-header-ip ip.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10944</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yi-ge get-header-ip up to 589b23d0eb0043c310a6a13ce4bbe2505d0d0b15. This issue affects the function ip of the file ip.php. This manipulation of the argument callback causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10945 | nuz007 smsboom d.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10945</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in nuz007 smsboom up to 01b2f35bbbc23f3e0f60f38ca0e3d1b286f8d674. Impacted is an unknown function of the file d.php. Such manipulation of the argument hm leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10943 | MikeCen WeChat-Face-Recognition wx.php valid cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10943</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in MikeCen WeChat-Face-Recognition up to 6e3f72bf8547d80b59e330f1137e4aa505f492c1. This vulnerability affects the function valid of the file wx.php. The manipulation of the argument echostr results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10957 | Unrestricted FTP Access Vulnerability in Syrotech Router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10957</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Syrotech SY-GPON-2010-WADONT router due to improper access control in its FTP service. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an FTP connection using default credentials, potentially gaining unauthorized access to configuration files, user credentials, or other sensitive information stored on the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40698 | SQL injection vulnerability in Prevengos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40698</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Prevengos v2.44 by Nedatec Consulting. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases by sending a POST request using the parameters “mpsCentroin”, “mpsEmpresa”, “mpsProyecto”, and “mpsContrata” in “/servicios/autorizaciones.asmx/mfsRecuperarListado”.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10941 | Topaz SERVCore Teller Installer SERVCoreTeller_2.0.40D.msi permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10941</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Topaz SERVCore Teller 2.14.0-RC2/2.14.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file SERVCoreTeller_2.0.40D.msi of the component Installer. Executing manipulation can lead to permission issues. The attack needs to be launched locally. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10942 | H3C Magic B3 aspForm AddMacList buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10942</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in H3C Magic B3 up to 100R002. This affects the function AddMacList of the file /goform/aspForm. The manipulation of the argument param leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10940 | Total.js CMS Layout admin layouts_save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10940</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Total.js CMS 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function layouts_save of the file /admin/ of the component Layout Page. Performing manipulation of the argument HTML results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10438 | Path Traversal in Yordam BT&amp;#x27;s Yordam Katalog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10438</link><description>Path Traversal: 'dir/../../filename' vulnerability in Yordam Information Technology Consulting Education and Electrical Systems Industry Trade Inc. Yordam Katalog allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Yordam Katalog: before 21.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21056 | Improper input validation in Retail Mode prior to version 5.59.4 allows self attackers to execute privileged commands on their own devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21056</link><description>Improper input validation in Retail Mode prior to version 5.59.4 allows self attackers to execute privileged commands on their own devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 06:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54520 | Improper Protection Against Voltage and Clock Glitches in FPGA devices, could allow an attacker with physical access to undervolt the platfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54520</link><description>Improper Protection Against Voltage and Clock Glitches in FPGA devices, could allow an attacker with physical access to undervolt the platform resulting in a loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10894 | Nx: nx/devkit: malicious versions of nx and plugins published to npm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10894</link><description>Malicious code was inserted into the Nx (build system) package and several related plugins. The tampered package was published to the npm software registry, via a supply-chain attack. Affected versions contain code that scans the file system, collects credentials, and posts them to GitHub as a repo under user's accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57318 | A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the toCsv function of csvjson versions thru 5.1.0 allows attackers to inject properties on Object.pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57318</link><description>A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the toCsv function of csvjson versions thru 5.1.0 allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57319 | fast-redact is a package that provides do very fast object redaction. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the nestedRestore function of f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57319</link><description>fast-redact is a package that provides do very fast object redaction. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the nestedRestore function of fast-redact version 3.5.0 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57320 | json-schema-editor-visual is a package that provides jsonschema editor. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the setData and deleteData fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57320</link><description>json-schema-editor-visual is a package that provides jsonschema editor. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the setData and deleteData function of json-schema-editor-visual versions thru 1.1.1 allows attackers to inject or delete properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57324 | parse is a package designed to parse JavaScript SDK. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the SingleInstanceStateController.initializeStat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57324</link><description>parse is a package designed to parse JavaScript SDK. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the SingleInstanceStateController.initializeState function of parse version 5.3.0 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59833 | FlagForgeCTF Hint Exposure via API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59833</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. In versions from 2.1.0 to before 2.3.0, the API endpoint GET /api/problems/:id returns challenge hints in plaintext within the question object, regardless of whether the user has unlocked them via point deduction. Users can view all hints for free, undermining the business logic of the platform and reducing the integrity of the challenge system. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59827 | FlagForgeCTF is Missing Authorization in main-v2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59827</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. In version 2.1.0, the /api/admin/assign-badge endpoint lacks proper access control, allowing any authenticated user to assign high-privilege badges (e.g., Staff) to themselves. This could lead to privilege escalation and impersonation of administrative roles. This issue has been patched in version 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57321 | A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the util-deps.addFileDepend function of magix-combine-ex versions thru 1.2.10 allows attackers to inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57321</link><description>A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the util-deps.addFileDepend function of magix-combine-ex versions thru 1.2.10 allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57323 | mpregular is a package that provides a small program development framework based on RegularJS. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the mp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57323</link><description>mpregular is a package that provides a small program development framework based on RegularJS. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the mp.addEventHandler function of mpregular version 0.2.0 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59824 | Omni Wireguard SideroLink potential escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59824</link><description>Omni manages Kubernetes on bare metal, virtual machines, or in a cloud. Prior to version 0.48.0, Omni Wireguard SideroLink has the potential to escape. Omni and each Talos machine establish a peer-to-peer (P2P) SideroLink connection using WireGuard to mutually authenticate and authorize access. The WireGuard interface on Omni is configured to ensure that the source IP address of an incoming packet matches the IPv6 address assigned to the Talos peer. However, it performs no validation on the packet's destination address. The Talos end of the SideroLink connection cannot be considered a trusted environment. Workloads running on Kubernetes, especially those configured with host networking, could gain direct access to this link. Therefore, a malicious workload could theoretically send arbitrary packets over the SideroLink interface. This issue has been patched in version 0.48.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57326 | A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the byGroupAndType function of sassdoc-extras v2.5.1 and before allows attackers to inject properties...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57326</link><description>A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the byGroupAndType function of sassdoc-extras v2.5.1 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57327 | spmrc is a package that provides the rc manager for spm. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the set and config function of spmrc version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57327</link><description>spmrc is a package that provides the rc manager for spm. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the set and config function of spmrc version 1.2.0 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59828 | Claude Code Vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution via Plugin Autoloading with Specific Yarn Versions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59828</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to Claude Code version 1.0.39, when using Claude Code with Yarn versions 2.0+, Yarn plugins are auto-executed when running yarn --version. This could lead to a bypass of the directory trust dialog in Claude Code, as plugins would be executed prior to the user accepting the risks of working in an untrusted directory. Users running Yarn Classic were unaffected by this issue. This issue has been fixed in version 1.0.39. Users on standard Claude Code auto-update will have received this fix automatically. Users performing manual updates are advised to update to the latest version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57325 | rollbar is a package designed to effortlessly track and debug errors in JavaScript applications. This package includes advanced error tracki...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57325</link><description>rollbar is a package designed to effortlessly track and debug errors in JavaScript applications. This package includes advanced error tracking features and an intuitive interface to help you identify and fix issues more quickly. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the utility.set function of rollbar v2.26.4 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57328 | toggle-array is a package designed to enables a property on the object at the specified index, while disabling the property on all other obj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57328</link><description>toggle-array is a package designed to enables a property on the object at the specified index, while disabling the property on all other objects. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the enable and disable function of toggle-array v1.0.1 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57329 | web3-core-method is a package designed to creates the methods on the web3 modules. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the attachToObject...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57329</link><description>web3-core-method is a package designed to creates the methods on the web3 modules. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the attachToObject function of web3-core-method version 1.10.4 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55322 | OmniParser Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55322</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57330 | The web3-core-subscriptions is a package designed to manages web3 subscriptions. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the attachToObject f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57330</link><description>The web3-core-subscriptions is a package designed to manages web3 subscriptions. A Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the attachToObject function of web3-core-subscriptions version 1.10.4 and before allows attackers to inject properties on Object.prototype via supplying a crafted payload, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59251 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59251</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57349 | The messageformat package, an implementation of the Unicode MessageFormat 2 specification for JavaScript, is vulnerable to prototype polluti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57349</link><description>The messageformat package, an implementation of the Unicode MessageFormat 2 specification for JavaScript, is vulnerable to prototype pollution due to improper handling of message key paths in versions prior to 2.3.0. The flaw arises when processing nested message keys containing special characters (e.g., __proto__ ), which can lead to unintended modification of the JavaScript Object prototype. This vulnerability may allow a remote attacker to inject properties into the global object prototype via specially crafted message input, potentially causing denial of service or other undefined behaviors in applications using the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55178 | Llama Stack prior to version v0.2.20 accepted unverified parameters in the resolve_ast_by_type function which could potentially allow for re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55178</link><description>Llama Stack prior to version v0.2.20 accepted unverified parameters in the resolve_ast_by_type function which could potentially allow for remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57347 | A vulnerability exists in the 'dagre-d3-es' Node.js package version 7.0.9, specifically within the 'bk' module's addConflict function, which...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57347</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the 'dagre-d3-es' Node.js package version 7.0.9, specifically within the 'bk' module's addConflict function, which fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input during property assignment operations. This flaw allows attackers to exploit prototype pollution vulnerabilities by injecting malicious input values (e.g., "__proto__"), enabling unauthorized modification of the JavaScript Object prototype chain. Successful exploitation could lead to denial of service conditions, unexpected application behavior, or potential execution of arbitrary code in contexts where polluted properties are later accessed or executed. The issue affects versions prior to 7.0.11 and remains unpatched at the time of disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57348 | The node-cube package (prior to version 5.0.0) contains a vulnerability in its handling of prototype chain initialization, which could allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57348</link><description>The node-cube package (prior to version 5.0.0) contains a vulnerability in its handling of prototype chain initialization, which could allow an attacker to inject properties into the prototype of built-in objects. This issue, categorized under CWE-1321, arises from improper validation of user-supplied input in the package's resource initialization process. Successful exploitation may lead to denial of service or arbitrary code execution in affected environments. The vulnerability affects versions up to and including 5.0.0-beta.19, and no official fix has been released to date.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57351 | A prototype pollution vulnerability exists in the ts-fns package versions prior to 13.0.7, where insufficient validation of user-provided ke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57351</link><description>A prototype pollution vulnerability exists in the ts-fns package versions prior to 13.0.7, where insufficient validation of user-provided keys in the assign function allows attackers to manipulate the Object.prototype chain. By leveraging this flaw, adversaries may inject arbitrary properties into the global object's prototype, potentially leading to application crashes, unexpected code execution behaviors, or bypasses of security-critical validation logic dependent on prototype integrity. The vulnerability stems from improper handling of deep property assignment operations within the library's public API functions. This issue remains unaddressed in the latest available version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59525 | Horilla has Improper Input Sanitization Leading to XSS and Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59525</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). Prior to version 1.4.0, improper sanitization across the application allows XSS via uploaded SVG (and via allowed ), which can be chained to execute JavaScript whenever users view impacted content (e.g., announcements). This can result in admin account takeover. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52907 | TOTOLINK X6000R Security Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52907</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in TOTOLINK X6000R allows Command Injection, File Manipulation.This issue affects X6000R: through V9.4.0cu.1360_B20241207.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57350 | The csvtojson package, a tool for converting CSV data to JSON with customizable parsing capabilities, contains a prototype pollution vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57350</link><description>The csvtojson package, a tool for converting CSV data to JSON with customizable parsing capabilities, contains a prototype pollution vulnerability in versions prior to 2.0.10. This issue arises due to insufficient sanitization of nested header names during the parsing process in the parser_jsonarray component. When processing CSV input containing specially crafted header fields that reference prototype chains (e.g., using __proto__ syntax), the application may unintentionally modify properties of the base Object prototype. This vulnerability can lead to denial of service conditions or unexpected behavior in applications relying on unmodified prototype chains, particularly when untrusted CSV data is processed. The flaw does not require user interaction beyond providing a maliciously constructed CSV file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57352 | A vulnerability exists in the 'min-document' package prior to version 2.19.0, stemming from improper handling of namespace operations in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57352</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the 'min-document' package prior to version 2.19.0, stemming from improper handling of namespace operations in the removeAttributeNS method. By processing malicious input involving the __proto__ property, an attacker can manipulate the prototype chain of JavaScript objects, leading to denial of service or arbitrary code execution. This issue arises from insufficient validation of attribute namespace removal operations, allowing unintended modification of critical object prototypes. The vulnerability remains unaddressed in the latest available version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57353 | The Runtime components of messageformat package for Node.js prior to version 3.0.1 contain a prototype pollution vulnerability. Due to insuf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57353</link><description>The Runtime components of messageformat package for Node.js prior to version 3.0.1 contain a prototype pollution vulnerability. Due to insufficient validation of nested message keys during the processing of message data, an attacker can manipulate the prototype chain of JavaScript objects by providing specially crafted input. This can result in the injection of arbitrary properties into the Object.prototype, potentially leading to denial of service conditions or unexpected application behavior. The vulnerability allows attackers to alter the prototype of base objects, impacting all subsequent object instances throughout the application's lifecycle. This issue remains unaddressed in the latest available version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57354 | A vulnerability exists in the 'counterpart' library for Node.js and the browser due to insufficient sanitization of user-controlled input in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57354</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the 'counterpart' library for Node.js and the browser due to insufficient sanitization of user-controlled input in translation key processing. The affected versions prior to 0.18.6 allow attackers to manipulate the library's translation functionality by supplying maliciously crafted keys containing prototype chain elements (e.g., __proto__ ), leading to prototype pollution. This weakness enables adversaries to inject arbitrary properties into the JavaScript Object prototype through the first parameter of the translate method when combined with specific separator configurations, potentially resulting in denial-of-service conditions or remote code execution in vulnerable applications. The issue arises from the library's failure to properly validate or neutralize special characters in translation key inputs before processing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59305 | Improper authorization in the background migration endpoints of Langfuse 3.1 before d67b317 allows any authenticated user to invoke migratio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59305</link><description>Improper authorization in the background migration endpoints of Langfuse 3.1 before d67b317 allows any authenticated user to invoke migration control functions. This can lead to data corruption or denial of service through unauthorized access to TRPC endpoints such as backgroundMigrations.all, backgroundMigrations.status, and backgroundMigrations.retry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59524 | Horilla Stored XSS Vulnerability via File Upload in Reimbursement Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59524</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). Prior to version 1.4.0, the file upload flow performs validation only in the browser and does not enforce server-side checks. An attacker can bypass the client-side validation (for example, with an intercepting proxy or by submitting a crafted request) to store an executable HTML document on the server. When an administrator or other privileged user views the uploaded file, the embedded script runs in their context and sends session cookies (or other credentials) to an attacker-controlled endpoint. The attacker then reuses those credentials to impersonate the admin. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56241 | Aztech DSL5005EN firmware 1.00.AZ_2013-05-10 and possibly other versions allows unauthenticated attackers to change the administrator passwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56241</link><description>Aztech DSL5005EN firmware 1.00.AZ_2013-05-10 and possibly other versions allows unauthenticated attackers to change the administrator password via a crafted POST request to sysAccess.asp. This allows full administrative control of the router without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20314 | A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with level-15 privileges or an unauthenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20314</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with level-15 privileges or an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to an affected device to execute persistent code at boot time and break the chain of trust.
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of software packages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing a crafted file into a specific location on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute persistent code on the underlying operating system.
Because this vulnerability allows an attacker to bypass a major security feature of a device, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52906 | TOTOLINK X6000R Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52906</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in TOTOLINK X6000R allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects X6000R: through V9.4.0cu.1360_B20241207.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59343 | tar-fs has a symlink validation bypass if destination directory is predictable with a specific tarball</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59343</link><description>tar-fs provides filesystem bindings for tar-stream. Versions prior to 3.1.1, 2.1.3, and 1.16.5 are vulnerable to symlink validation bypass if the destination directory is predictable with a specific tarball. This issue has been patched in version 3.1.1, 2.1.4, and 1.16.6. A workaround involves using the ignore option on non files/directories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48867 | Horilla Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Project and Task Modules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48867</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Horilla HRM 1.3.0 allows authenticated admin or privileged users to inject malicious JavaScript payloads into multiple fields in the Project and Task modules. These payloads persist in the database and are executed when viewed by an admin or other privileged users through the web interface. Although the issue is not exploitable by unauthenticated users, it still poses a high risk of session hijacking and unauthorized action within high-privilege accounts. At time of publication there is no known patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20149 | A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20149</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a buffer overflow. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the CLI prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20160 | A vulnerability in the implementation of the TACACS+ protocol in Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20160</link><description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the TACACS+ protocol in Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive data or bypass authentication. 
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the system does not properly check whether the required TACACS+ shared secret is configured. A machine-in-the-middle attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and reading unencrypted TACACS+ messages or impersonating the TACACS+ server and falsely accepting arbitrary authentication requests. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive information in a TACACS+ message or bypass authentication and gain access to the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20240 | A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20240</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting attack (XSS) on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute a reflected XSS attack and steal user cookies from the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20293 | A vulnerability in the Day One setup process of Cisco IOS XE Software for Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers for Cloud (9800-CL) coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20293</link><description>A vulnerability in the Day One setup process of Cisco IOS XE Software for Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers for Cloud (9800-CL) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the public-key infrastructure (PKI) server that is running on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete cleanup upon completion of the Day One setup process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to request a certificate from the virtual wireless controller and then use the acquired certificate to join an attacker-controlled device to the virtual wireless controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20311 | A vulnerability in the handling of certain Ethernet frames in Cisco IOS XE Software for Catalyst 9000 Series Switches could allow an unauthe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20311</link><description>A vulnerability in the handling of certain Ethernet frames in Cisco IOS XE Software for Catalyst 9000 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an egress port to become blocked and drop all outbound traffic.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of crafted Ethernet frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted Ethernet frames through an affected switch. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the egress port to which the crafted frame is forwarded to start dropping all frames, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20312 | A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20312</link><description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing a specific SNMP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specific SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMPv2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMPv3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20313 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS XE Software of could allow an authenticated, local attacker with level-15 privileges or an unauthentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20313</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS XE Software of could allow an authenticated, local attacker with level-15 privileges or an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to the device to execute persistent code at boot time and break the chain of trust.
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due path traversal and improper image integrity validation.  A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute persistent code on the underlying operating system.
&#13; Because this allows the attacker to bypass a major security feature of the device, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.
&#13;   
&#13;  
&#13;  
&#13; ERP</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20315 | A vulnerability in the Network-Based Application Recognition (NBAR) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20315</link><description>A vulnerability in the Network-Based Application Recognition (NBAR) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of malformed Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed CAPWAP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20316 | A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9500X and 9600X Series Switches cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20316</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9500X and 9600X Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the flooding of traffic from an unlearned MAC address on a switch virtual interface (SVI) that has an egress ACL applied. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by causing the VLAN to flush its MAC address table. This condition can also occur if the MAC address table is full. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an egress ACL on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20327 | A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to cause a denial of s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20327</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted URL in an HTTP request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20338 | A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative privileges to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20338</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the device CLI with valid administrative (level 15) credentials and using crafted commands at the CLI prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20352 | A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20352</link><description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow the following:
&#13; &#13; An authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges could cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device that is running Cisco IOS Software or Cisco IOS XE Software. To cause the DoS, the attacker must have the SNMPv2c or earlier read-only community string or valid SNMPv3 user credentials.&#13; An authenticated, remote attacker with high privileges could execute code as the root user on an affected device that is running Cisco IOS XE Software. To execute code as the root user, the attacker must have the SNMPv1 or v2c read-only community string or valid SNMPv3 user credentials and administrative or privilege 15 credentials on the affected device. &#13; &#13; An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP packet to an affected device over IPv4 or IPv6 networks. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a stack overflow condition in the SNMP subsystem of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow a low-privileged attacker to cause the affected system to reload, resulting in a DoS condition, or allow a high-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user and obtain full control of the affected system.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability affects all versions of SNMP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48869 | Horilla Unauthorized Access to Candidate Resume Files Due to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48869</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). Unauthenticated users can access uploaded resume files in Horilla 1.3.0 by directly guessing or predicting file URLs. These files are stored in a publicly accessible directory, allowing attackers to retrieve sensitive candidate information without authentication. At time of publication there is no known patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20334 | A vulnerability in the HTTP API subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow a remote attacker to inject commands that will execute with r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20334</link><description>A vulnerability in the HTTP API subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow a remote attacker to inject commands that will execute with root privileges into the underlying operating system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected system and performing an API call with crafted input. Alternatively, an unauthenticated attacker could persuade a legitimate user with administrative privileges who is currently logged in to the system to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20339 | Cisco SD-WAN vEdge Software Access Control List Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20339</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing of IPv4 packets of Cisco SD-WAN vEdge Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.

This vulnerability is due to the improper enforcement of the implicit deny all at the end of a configured ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send unauthorized traffic to an interface on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ACL on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20364 | Cisco Wireless Access Point Software Device Analytics Action Frame Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20364</link><description>A vulnerability in the Device Analytics action frame processing of Cisco Wireless Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to inject wireless 802.11 action frames with arbitrary information.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient verification checks of incoming 802.11 action frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending 802.11 Device Analytics action frames with arbitrary parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject Device Analytics action frames with arbitrary information, which could modify the Device Analytics data of valid wireless clients that are connected to the same wireless controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20365 | Cisco Access Point Software Intermittent IPv6 Gateway Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20365</link><description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 Router Advertisement (RA) packet processing of Cisco Access Point Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to modify the IPv6 gateway on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to a logic error in the processing of IPv6 RA packets that are received from wireless clients. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by associating to a wireless network and sending a series of crafted IPv6 RA packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to temporarily change the IPv6 gateway of an affected device. This could also lead to intermittent packet loss for any wireless clients that are associated with the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10909 | Mangati NovoSGA SVG File admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10909</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Mangati NovoSGA up to 2.2.9. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin of the component SVG File Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument logoNavbar/logoLogin results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56815 | Datart 1.0.0-rc.3 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in the POST /viz/image interface, since the server directly uses MultipartFile.transf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56815</link><description>Datart 1.0.0-rc.3 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in the POST /viz/image interface, since the server directly uses MultipartFile.transferTo() to save the uploaded file to a path controllable by the user, and lacks strict verification of the file name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56816 | Datart 1.0.0-rc.3 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The configuration file handling of the application allows attackers to upload arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56816</link><description>Datart 1.0.0-rc.3 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The configuration file handling of the application allows attackers to upload arbitrary YAML files to the config/jdbc-driver-ext.yml path. The application parses this file using SnakeYAML's unsafe load() or loadAs() method without input sanitization. This allows deserialization of attacker-controlled YAML content, leading to arbitrary class instantiation. Under certain conditions, this can be exploited to achieve remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10500 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10500</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10501 | Use after free in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10501</link><description>Use after free in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10502 | Heap buffer overflow in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10502</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via malicious network traffic. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10585 | Type confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10585</link><description>Type confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.185 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10890 | Side-channel information leakage in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.207 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10890</link><description>Side-channel information leakage in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.207 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10891 | Integer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.207 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10891</link><description>Integer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.207 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10892 | Integer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.207 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10892</link><description>Integer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.207 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56819 | An issue in Datart v.1.0.0-rc.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the INIT connection parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56819</link><description>An issue in Datart v.1.0.0-rc.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the INIT connection parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10360 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in Puppet Enterprise 2025.4 and 2025.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10360</link><description>In Puppet Enterprise versions 2025.4.0 and 2025.5, the encryption key used for encrypting content in the Infra Assistant database was not excluded from the files gathered by Puppet backup. The key is only present on the system if the user has a Puppet Enterprise Advanced license and has enabled the Infra Assistant feature. The key is used for encrypting one particular bit of data in the Infra Assistant database: the API key for their AI provider account. This has been fixed in Puppet Enterprise version 2025.6, and release notes for 2025.6 have remediation steps for users of affected versions who can't update to the latest version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21476 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21476</link><description>Memory corruption when passing parameters to the Trusted Virtual Machine during the handshake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21481 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21481</link><description>Memory corruption while performing private key encryption in trusted application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21482 | Cryptographic Issues in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21482</link><description>Cryptographic issue while performing RSA PKCS padding decoding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21483 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21483</link><description>Memory corruption when the UE receives an RTP packet from the network, during the reassembly of NALUs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21484 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21484</link><description>Information disclosure when UE receives the RTP packet from the network, while decoding and reassembling the fragments from RTP packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21487 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21487</link><description>Information disclosure while decoding RTP packet received by UE from the network, when payload length mentioned is greater than the available buffer length.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21488 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21488</link><description>Information disclosure while decoding this RTP packet headers received by UE from the network when the padding bit is set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27030 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27030</link><description>information disclosure while invoking calibration data from user space to update firmware size.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27032 | Improper Access Control Applied to Mirrored or Aliased Memory Regions in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27032</link><description>memory corruption while loading a PIL authenticated VM, when authenticated VM image is loaded without maintaining cache coherency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27033 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27033</link><description>Information disclosure while running video usecase having rogue firmware.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27034 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27034</link><description>Memory corruption while selecting the PLMN from SOR failed list.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27036 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27036</link><description>Information disclosure when Video engine escape input data is less than expected minimum size.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27037 | Use After Free in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27037</link><description>Memory corruption while processing config_dev IOCTL when camera kernel driver drops its reference to CPU buffers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27077 | Use After Free in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27077</link><description>Memory corruption while processing message in guest VM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47314 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47314</link><description>Memory corruption while processing data sent by FE driver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47315 | Use After Free in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47315</link><description>Memory corruption while handling repeated memory unmap requests from guest VM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47316 | Double Free in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47316</link><description>Memory corruption due to double free when multiple threads race to set the timestamp store.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47317 | Buffer Over-read in BT Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47317</link><description>Memory corruption due to global buffer overflow when a test command uses an invalid payload type.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47318 | Buffer Over-read in BT Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47318</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the EPTM test control message to get the test pattern.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47326 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HAL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47326</link><description>Transient DOS while handling command data during power control processing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47327 | Use After Free in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47327</link><description>Memory corruption while encoding the image data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47328 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HAL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47328</link><description>Transient DOS while processing power control requests with invalid antenna or stream values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47329 | Release of Invalid Pointer or Reference in Android Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47329</link><description>Memory corruption while handling invalid inputs in application info setup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8869 | Fallback tar extraction in pip doesn&amp;#x27;t check symbolic links point to extraction directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8869</link><description>When extracting a tar archive pip may not check symbolic links point into the extraction directory if the tarfile module doesn't implement PEP 706.
Note that upgrading pip to a "fixed" version for this vulnerability doesn't fix all known vulnerabilities that are remediated by using a Python version that implements PEP 706.

Note that this is a vulnerability in pip's fallback implementation of tar extraction for Python versions that don't implement PEP 706
and therefore are not secure to all vulnerabilities in the Python 'tarfile' module. If you're using a Python version that implements PEP 706
then pip doesn't use the "vulnerable" fallback code.

Mitigations include upgrading to a version of pip that includes the fix, upgrading to a Python version that implements PEP 706 (Python &gt;=3.9.17, &gt;=3.10.12, &gt;=3.11.4, or &gt;=3.12),
applying the linked patch, or inspecting source distributions (sdists) before installation as is already a best-practice.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48868 | Horilla vulnerable to authenticated RCE via eval() in project_bulk_archive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48868</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). An authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in Horilla 1.3.0 due to the unsafe use of Python’s eval() function on a user-controlled query parameter in the project_bulk_archive view. This allows privileged users (e.g., administrators) to execute arbitrary system commands on the server. While having Django’s DEBUG=True makes exploitation visibly easier by returning command output in the HTTP response, this is not required. The vulnerability can still be exploited in DEBUG=False mode by using blind payloads such as a reverse shell, leading to full remote code execution. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23248 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23248</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to nvdisasm. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23255 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23255</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23271 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23271</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to nvdisasm. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23272 | NVIDIA nvJPEG library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds read by means of a specially crafted JPEG file. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23272</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds read by means of a specially crafted JPEG file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23273 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvJPEG where a local authenticated user may cause a divide by zero error b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23273</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvJPEG where a local authenticated user may cause a divide by zero error by submitting a specially crafted JPEG file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23274 | NVIDIA nvJPEG contains a vulnerability in jpeg encoding where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by providing a maliciously crafted inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23274</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG contains a vulnerability in jpeg encoding where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by providing a maliciously crafted input image with dimensions that cause integer overflows in array index calculations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23275 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvJPEG where a local authenticated user may cause a GPU out-of-bounds writ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23275</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvJPEG where a local authenticated user may cause a GPU out-of-bounds write by providing certain image dimensions.  A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23308 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a heap-based buffer overflow by getti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23308</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a heap-based buffer overflow by getting the user to run nvdisasm on a malicious ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution at the privilege level of the user running nvdisasm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23338 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm where a user may cause an out-of-bounds write by running nvdisasm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23338</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm where a user may cause an out-of-bounds write by running nvdisasm on a malicious ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23339 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump where an attacker may cause a stack-based buffer overflow by get...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23339</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump where an attacker may cause a stack-based buffer overflow by getting the user to run cuobjdump on a malicious ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution at the privilege level of the user running 
cuobjdump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23340 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23340</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to nvdisasm. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23346 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump, where an unprivileged user can cause a NULL pointer dereference.  A successful ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23346</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump, where an unprivileged user can cause a NULL pointer dereference.  A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a limited denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23348 | NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the pretrain_gpt script, where malicious data created by an attacker may ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23348</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the pretrain_gpt script, where malicious data created by an attacker may cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23349 | NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the tasks/orqa/unsupervised/nq.py component, where an attacker may cause a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23349</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the tasks/orqa/unsupervised/nq.py component, where an attacker may cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23353 | NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the msdp preprocessing script where malicious data created by an attacker m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23353</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the msdp preprocessing script where malicious data created by an attacker may cause an injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, Information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23354 | NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the ensemble_classifer script where malicious data created by an attacker m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23354</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the ensemble_classifer script where malicious data created by an attacker may cause an injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, Information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10906 | Magnetism Studios Endurance NSXPC com.MagnetismStudios.endurance.helper loadModuleNamed:WithReply missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10906</link><description>A flaw has been found in Magnetism Studios Endurance up to 3.3.0 on macOS. This affects the function loadModuleNamed:WithReply of the file /Applications/Endurance.app/Contents/Library/LaunchServices/com.MagnetismStudios.endurance.helper of the component NSXPC Interface. Executing manipulation can lead to missing authentication. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60020 | nncp before 8.12.0 allows path traversal (for reading or writing) during freqing and file saving via a crafted path in packet data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60020</link><description>nncp before 8.12.0 allows path traversal (for reading or writing) during freqing and file saving via a crafted path in packet data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9353 | Themify Builder &amp;lt;= 7.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9353</link><description>The Themify Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 7.6.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9054 | MultiLoca - WooCommerce Multi Locations Inventory Management &amp;lt;= 4.2.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update via &amp;#x27;wcmlim_settings_ajax_handler&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9054</link><description>The MultiLoca - WooCommerce Multi Locations Inventory Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'wcmlim_settings_ajax_handler' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58241 | Bluetooth: hci_core: Disable works on hci_unregister_dev</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58241</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: hci_core: Disable works on hci_unregister_dev

This make use of disable_work_* on hci_unregister_dev since the hci_dev is
about to be freed new submissions are not disarable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39889 | Bluetooth: l2cap: Check encryption key size on incoming connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39889</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: l2cap: Check encryption key size on incoming connection

This is required for passing GAP/SEC/SEM/BI-04-C PTS test case:
  Security Mode 4 Level 4, Responder - Invalid Encryption Key Size
  - 128 bit

This tests the security key with size from 1 to 15 bytes while the
Security Mode 4 Level 4 requests 16 bytes key size.

Currently PTS fails with the following logs:
- expected:Connection Response:
    Code: [3 (0x03)] Code
    Identifier: (lt)WildCard: Exists(gt)
    Length: [8 (0x0008)]
    Destination CID: (lt)WildCard: Exists(gt)
    Source CID: [64 (0x0040)]
    Result: [3 (0x0003)] Connection refused - Security block
    Status: (lt)WildCard: Exists(gt),
but received:Connection Response:
    Code: [3 (0x03)] Code
    Identifier: [1 (0x01)]
    Length: [8 (0x0008)]
    Destination CID: [64 (0x0040)]
    Source CID: [64 (0x0040)]
    Result: [0 (0x0000)] Connection Successful
    Status: [0 (0x0000)] No further information available

And HCI logs:
&lt; HCI Command: Read Encrypti.. (0x05|0x0008) plen 2
        Handle: 14 Address: 00:1B:DC:F2:24:10 (Vencer Co., Ltd.)
&gt; HCI Event: Command Complete (0x0e) plen 7
      Read Encryption Key Size (0x05|0x0008) ncmd 1
        Status: Success (0x00)
        Handle: 14 Address: 00:1B:DC:F2:24:10 (Vencer Co., Ltd.)
        Key size: 7
&gt; ACL Data RX: Handle 14 flags 0x02 dlen 12
      L2CAP: Connection Request (0x02) ident 1 len 4
        PSM: 4097 (0x1001)
        Source CID: 64
&lt; ACL Data TX: Handle 14 flags 0x00 dlen 16
      L2CAP: Connection Response (0x03) ident 1 len 8
        Destination CID: 64
        Source CID: 64
        Result: Connection successful (0x0000)
        Status: No further information available (0x0000)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39890 | wifi: ath12k: fix memory leak in ath12k_service_ready_ext_event</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39890</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath12k: fix memory leak in ath12k_service_ready_ext_event

Currently, in ath12k_service_ready_ext_event(), svc_rdy_ext.mac_phy_caps
is not freed in the failure case, causing a memory leak. The following
trace is observed in kmemleak:

unreferenced object 0xffff8b3eb5789c00 (size 1024):
 comm "softirq", pid 0, jiffies 4294942577
 hex dump (first 32 bytes):
   00 00 00 00 01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 7b 00 00 10  ............{...
   01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 01 00 00 00 1f 38 00 00  .............8..
 backtrace (crc 44e1c357):
   __kmalloc_noprof+0x30b/0x410
   ath12k_wmi_mac_phy_caps_parse+0x84/0x100 [ath12k]
   ath12k_wmi_tlv_iter+0x5e/0x140 [ath12k]
   ath12k_wmi_svc_rdy_ext_parse+0x308/0x4c0 [ath12k]
   ath12k_wmi_tlv_iter+0x5e/0x140 [ath12k]
   ath12k_service_ready_ext_event.isra.0+0x44/0xd0 [ath12k]
   ath12k_wmi_op_rx+0x2eb/0xd70 [ath12k]
   ath12k_htc_rx_completion_handler+0x1f4/0x330 [ath12k]
   ath12k_ce_recv_process_cb+0x218/0x300 [ath12k]
   ath12k_pci_ce_workqueue+0x1b/0x30 [ath12k]
   process_one_work+0x219/0x680
   bh_worker+0x198/0x1f0
   tasklet_action+0x13/0x30
   handle_softirqs+0xca/0x460
   __irq_exit_rcu+0xbe/0x110
   irq_exit_rcu+0x9/0x30

Free svc_rdy_ext.mac_phy_caps in the error case to fix this memory leak.

Tested-on: QCN9274 hw2.0 PCI WLAN.WBE.1.4.1-00199-QCAHKSWPL_SILICONZ-1</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58457 | Apache ZooKeeper: Insufficient Permission Check in AdminServer Snapshot/Restore Commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58457</link><description>Improper permission check in ZooKeeper AdminServer lets authorized clients to run snapshot and restore command with insufficient permissions.

This issue affects Apache ZooKeeper: from 3.9.0 before 3.9.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.9.4, which fixes the issue.

The issue can be mitigated by disabling both commands (via admin.snapshot.enabled and admin.restore.enabled), disabling the whole AdminServer interface (via admin.enableServer), or ensuring that the root ACL does not provide open permissions. (Note that ZooKeeper ACLs are not recursive, so this does not impact operations on child nodes besides notifications from recursive watches.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41715 | Missing Authentication for Database Access in Web Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41715</link><description>The database for the web application is exposed without authentication, allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain unauthorized access and potentially compromise it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41716 | Unauthenticated User Enumeration via Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41716</link><description>The web application allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to learn information about existing user accounts with their corresponding role due to missing authentication for critical function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9031 | Timing-Based Username Enumeration in DivvyDrive Information Technologies&amp;#x27; DivvyDrive Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9031</link><description>Observable Timing Discrepancy vulnerability in DivvyDrive Information Technologies Inc. DivvyDrive Web allows Cross-Domain Search Timing.This issue affects DivvyDrive Web: from 4.8.2.2 before 4.8.2.15.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 08:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48392 | Apache IoTDB: DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48392</link><description>A vulnerability in Apache IoTDB.

This issue affects Apache IoTDB: from 1.3.3 through 1.3.4, from 2.0.1-beta through 2.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.5, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 08:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48459 | Apache IoTDB: Deserialization of untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48459</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache IoTDB.

This issue affects Apache IoTDB: from 1.0.0 before 2.0.5.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.5, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 08:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58317 | File Parsing Memory Corruption in CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58317</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58319 | File Parsing Memory Corruption in CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58319</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43819 | A Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.3.121 through 7.3.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43819</link><description>A Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.3.121 through 7.3.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.3, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 is allow an remote non-authenticated attacker to reuse old user session by SLO API</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43779 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43779</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.18 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript code via _com_liferay_commerce_product_definitions_web_internal_portlet_CPDefinitionsPortlet_productTypeName parameter. This malicious payload is then reflected and executed within the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 01:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>