<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-34053 | Spring Framework server Web Observations DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34053</link><description>In Spring Framework versions 6.0.0 - 6.0.13, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when all of the following are true:

  *  the application uses Spring MVC or Spring WebFlux
  *  io.micrometer:micrometer-core is on the classpath
  *  an ObservationRegistry is configured in the application to record observations


Typically, Spring Boot applications need the org.springframework.boot:spring-boot-actuator dependency to meet all conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34054 | Reactor Netty HTTP Server Metrics DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34054</link><description>In Reactor Netty HTTP Server, versions 1.1.x prior to 1.1.13 and versions 1.0.x prior to 1.0.39, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable if Reactor Netty HTTP Server built-in integration with Micrometer is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4667 | Stored Cross Site Scripting in webserver administration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4667</link><description>The web interface of the PAC Device allows the device administrator user profile to store malicious scripts in some fields. The stored malicious script is then executed when the GUI is opened by any users of the webserver administration interface. 



The root cause of the vulnerability is inadequate input validation and output encoding in the web administration interface component of the firmware.

This could lead to  unauthorized access and data leakage</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48022 | Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the job submission API. NOTE: the vendor's position is t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48022</link><description>Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the job submission API. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this report is irrelevant because Ray, as stated in its documentation, is not intended for use outside of a strictly controlled network environment</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48023 | Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows /log_proxy SSRF. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this report is irrelevant because Ray, as stated in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48023</link><description>Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows /log_proxy SSRF. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this report is irrelevant because Ray, as stated in its documentation, is not intended for use outside of a strictly controlled network environment</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4224 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4224</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/dropbox.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4225 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4225</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/exercise.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4226 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4226</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/work.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4220 | Chamilo LMS Unauthenticated Big Upload File Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4220</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in big file upload functionality in `/main/inc/lib/javascript/bigupload/inc/bigUpload.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows unauthenticated attackers to perform stored cross-site scripting attacks and obtain remote code execution via uploading of web shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4221 | Chamilo LMS Learning Path PPT2LP Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4221</link><description>Command injection in `main/lp/openoffice_presentation.class.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows users permitted to upload Learning Paths to obtain remote code execution via improper neutralisation of special characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4222 | Chamilo LMS Learning Path PPT2LP Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4222</link><description>Command injection in `main/lp/openoffice_text_document.class.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows users permitted to upload Learning Paths to obtain remote code execution via improper neutralisation of special characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4223 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4223</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/document.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3368 | Chamilo LMS Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3368</link><description>Command injection in `/main/webservices/additional_webservices.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.20 allows unauthenticated attackers to obtain remote code execution via improper neutralisation of special characters. This is a bypass of CVE-2023-34960.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3533 | Chamilo LMS Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3533</link><description>Path traversal in file upload functionality in `/main/webservices/additional_webservices.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.20 allows unauthenticated attackers to perform stored cross-site scripting attacks and obtain remote code execution via arbitrary file write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3545 | Chamilo LMS Htaccess File Upload Security Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3545</link><description>Improper sanitisation in `main/inc/lib/fileUpload.lib.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.20 on Windows and Apache installations allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass file upload security protections and obtain remote code execution via uploading of `.htaccess` file. This vulnerability may be exploited by privileged attackers or chained with unauthenticated arbitrary file write vulnerabilities, such as CVE-2023-3533, to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24023 | Bluetooth BR/EDR devices with Secure Simple Pairing and Secure Connections pairing in Bluetooth Core Specification 4.2 through 5.4 allow cer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24023</link><description>Bluetooth BR/EDR devices with Secure Simple Pairing and Secure Connections pairing in Bluetooth Core Specification 4.2 through 5.4 allow certain man-in-the-middle attacks that force a short key length, and might lead to discovery of the encryption key and live injection, aka BLUFFS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49075 | Pimcore Admin UI has Two Factor Authentication disabled for non admin security firewalls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49075</link><description>The Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. `AdminBundle\Security\PimcoreUserTwoFactorCondition` introduced in v11 disable the two factor authentication for all non-admin security firewalls. An authenticated user can access the system without having to provide the two factor credentials. This issue has been patched in version 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6225 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_meta sh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6225</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_meta shortcode combined with post meta data in all versions up to, and including, 5.13.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied meta values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6226 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6226</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.13.3 via the su_meta shortcode due to missing validation on the user controlled keys 'key' and 'post_id'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to retrieve arbitrary post meta values which may contain sensitive information when combined with another plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48713 | Knative Serving vulnerable to attacker-controlled pod causing denial of service of autoscaler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48713</link><description>Knative Serving builds on Kubernetes to support deploying and serving of applications and functions as serverless containers. An attacker who controls a pod to a degree where they can control the responses from the /metrics endpoint can cause Denial-of-Service of the autoscaler from an unbound memory allocation bug. This is a DoS vulnerability, where a non-privileged Knative user can cause a DoS for the cluster. This issue has been patched in version 0.39.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32064 | OroCommerce Customer Portal Incorrect Customer and Customer Group Frontend Menus pages visibility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32064</link><description>OroCommerce package with customer portal and non authenticated visitor website base features. Back-office users can access information about Customer and Customer User menus, bypassing ACL security restrictions due to insufficient security checks. This issue has been patched in version 5.0.11 and 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32065 | OroCommerce get-totals-for-checkout API endpoint returns unwanted data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32065</link><description>OroCommerce is an open-source Business to Business Commerce application built with flexibility in mind. Detailed Order totals information may be received by Order ID. This issue is patched in version 5.0.11 and 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32063 | OroCRMCallBundle has incorrect call view page visibility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32063</link><description>OroCalendarBundle enables a Calendar feature and related functionality in Oro applications. Back-office users can access information from any call event, bypassing ACL security restrictions due to insufficient security checks. This issue has been patched in version 5.0.4 and 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6219 | The BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'bookingpress_proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6219</link><description>The BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'bookingpress_process_upload' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.76. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5797 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5797</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, NWA50AX firmware version 6.29(ABYW.2), WAC500 firmware version 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware version 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware version 6.65(ACGG.1), could allow an authenticated local attacker to access the administrator’s logs on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5960 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the hotspot feature of the Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37 and V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5960</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the hotspot feature of the Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37 and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37 could allow an authenticated local attacker to access the system files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37926 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37926</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command to dump system logs on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47503 | An issue in jflyfox jfinalCMS v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.jsp component in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47503</link><description>An issue in jflyfox jfinalCMS v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.jsp component in the template management module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4397 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4397</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware version 5.37, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware version 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command with crafted strings on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4398 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the source code of the QuickSec IPSec toolkit used in the VPN feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4398</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the source code of the QuickSec IPSec toolkit used in the VPN feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions on an affected device by sending a crafted IKE packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5650 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the ZySH of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5650</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the ZySH of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to modify the URL of the registration page in the web GUI of an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30585 | A vulnerability has been identified in the Node.js (.msi version) installation process, specifically affecting Windows users who install Nod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30585</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Node.js (.msi version) installation process, specifically affecting Windows users who install Node.js using the .msi installer. This vulnerability emerges during the repair operation, where the "msiexec.exe" process, running under the NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM context, attempts to read the %USERPROFILE% environment variable from the current user's registry.

The issue arises when the path referenced by the %USERPROFILE% environment variable does not exist. In such cases, the "msiexec.exe" process attempts to create the specified path in an unsafe manner, potentially leading to the creation of arbitrary folders in arbitrary locations.

The severity of this vulnerability is heightened by the fact that the %USERPROFILE% environment variable in the Windows registry can be modified by standard (or "non-privileged") users. Consequently, unprivileged actors, including malicious entities or trojans, can manipulate the environment variable key to deceive the privileged "msiexec.exe" process. This manipulation can result in the creation of folders in unintended and potentially malicious locations.

It is important to note that this vulnerability is specific to Windows users who install Node.js using the .msi installer. Users who opt for other installation methods are not affected by this particular issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35136 | An improper input validation vulnerability in the “Quagga” package of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35136</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability in the “Quagga” package of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to access configuration files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35139 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG FLEX series f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35139</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.37, could allow an unauthenticated LAN-based attacker to store malicious scripts in a vulnerable device. A successful XSS attack could then result in the stored malicious scripts being executed to steal cookies when the user visits the specific CGI used for dumping ZTP logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37925 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37925</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, NWA50AX firmware version 6.29(ABYW.2), WAC500 firmware version 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware version 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware version 6.65(ACGG.1), could allow an authenticated local attacker to access system files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47437 | A vulnerability has been identified in Pachno 1.0.6 allowing an authenticated attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. The v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47437</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Pachno 1.0.6 allowing an authenticated attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. The vulnerability exists due to inadequate input validation in the Project Description and comments, which enables an attacker to inject malicious java script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29770 | In Sentrifugo 3.5, the AssetsController::uploadsaveAction function allows an authenticated attacker to upload any file without extension fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29770</link><description>In Sentrifugo 3.5, the AssetsController::uploadsaveAction function allows an authenticated attacker to upload any file without extension filtering.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46480 | An issue in OwnCast v.0.1.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the authHost parameter o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46480</link><description>An issue in OwnCast v.0.1.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the authHost parameter of the indieauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46355 | In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) &lt; 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal information without restricti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46355</link><description>In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) &lt; 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal information without restriction. Due to too permissive access control which does not force administrator to use password on feeds, a guest can access exports from the module which can lead to leaks of personal information from ps_customer / ps_order table such as name / surname / email / phone number / postal address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46349 | In the module "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel) Export/Update" (updateproducts) &lt; 3.8.5 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46349</link><description>In the module "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel) Export/Update" (updateproducts) &lt; 3.8.5 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `productsUpdateModel::getExportIds()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48188 | SQL injection vulnerability in PrestaShop opartdevis v.4.5.18 thru v.4.6.12 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48188</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PrestaShop opartdevis v.4.5.18 thru v.4.6.12 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the getModuleTranslation function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42366 | A heap-buffer-overflow was discovered in BusyBox v.1.36.1 in the next_token function at awk.c:1159.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42366</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow was discovered in BusyBox v.1.36.1 in the next_token function at awk.c:1159.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42365 | A use-after-free vulnerability was discovered in BusyBox v.1.36.1 via a crafted awk pattern in the awk.c copyvar function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42365</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was discovered in BusyBox v.1.36.1 via a crafted awk pattern in the awk.c copyvar function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42364 | A use-after-free vulnerability in BusyBox v.1.36.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted awk pattern in the awk.c eval...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42364</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability in BusyBox v.1.36.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted awk pattern in the awk.c evaluate function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49145 | Apache NiFi: Improper Neutralization of Input in Advanced User Interface for Jolt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49145</link><description>Apache NiFi 0.7.0 through 1.23.2 include the JoltTransformJSON Processor, which provides an advanced configuration user interface that is vulnerable to DOM-based cross-site scripting. If an authenticated user, who is authorized to configure a JoltTransformJSON Processor, visits a crafted URL, then arbitrary
JavaScript code can be executed within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.24.0 or 2.0.0-M1 is the recommended mitigation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42363 | A use-after-free vulnerability was discovered in xasprintf function in xfuncs_printf.c:344 in BusyBox v.1.36.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42363</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was discovered in xasprintf function in xfuncs_printf.c:344 in BusyBox v.1.36.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 21:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5885 | Franklin Electric Fueling Systems Colibri Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5885</link><description>The discontinued FFS Colibri product allows a remote user to access files on the system including files containing login credentials for other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 21:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32062 | OroCalendarBundle has incorrect system calendar events visibility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32062</link><description>OroPlatform is a package that assists system and user calendar management. Back-office users can access information from any system calendar event, bypassing ACL security restrictions due to insufficient security checks. This vulnerability has been patched in version 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 21:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48034 | An issue discovered in Acer Wireless Keyboard SK-9662 allows attacker in physical proximity to both decrypt wireless keystrokes and inject a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48034</link><description>An issue discovered in Acer Wireless Keyboard SK-9662 allows attacker in physical proximity to both decrypt wireless keystrokes and inject arbitrary keystrokes via use of weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 20:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49030 | SQL Injection vulnerability in32ns KLive v.2019-1-19 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49030</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in32ns KLive v.2019-1-19 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the web/user.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 20:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49044 | Stack Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ssid parameter in the func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49044</link><description>Stack Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ssid parameter in the function form_fast_setting_wifi_set.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 20:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41951 | OroPlatform vulnerable to path traversal during temporary file manipulations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41951</link><description>OroPlatform is a PHP Business Application Platform (BAP) designed to make development of custom business applications easier and faster. Path Traversal is possible in `Oro\Bundle\GaufretteBundle\FileManager::getTemporaryFileName`. With this method, an attacker can pass the path to a non-existent file, which will allow writing the content to a new file that will be available during script execution. This vulnerability has been fixed in version 5.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 20:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49316 | In Math/BinaryField.php in phpseclib before 3.0.34, excessively large degrees can lead to a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49316</link><description>In Math/BinaryField.php in phpseclib before 3.0.34, excessively large degrees can lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42000 | Arcserve UDP Agent Unauthenticated Path Traversal File Upload </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42000</link><description>Arcserve UDP prior to 9.2 contains a path traversal vulnerability in com.ca.arcflash.ui.server.servlet.FileHandlingServlet.doUpload(). An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit it to upload arbitrary files to any location on the file system where the UDP agent is installed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41998 | Arcserve UDP Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41998</link><description>Arcserve UDP prior to 9.2 contained a vulnerability in the com.ca.arcflash.rps.webservice.RPSService4CPMImpl interface. A routine exists that allows an attacker to upload and execute arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41999 | Arcserve UDP Management Authentication Bypass </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41999</link><description>An authentication bypass exists in Arcserve UDP prior to version 9.2. An unauthenticated, remote attacker can obtain a valid authentication identifier that allows them to authenticate to the management console and perform tasks that require authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49040 | An issue in Tneda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the adslPwd parameter in the form_fast_setting_int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49040</link><description>An issue in Tneda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the adslPwd parameter in the form_fast_setting_internet_set function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49042 | Heap Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the schedStartTime parameter or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49042</link><description>Heap Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the schedStartTime parameter or the schedEndTime parameter in the function setSchedWifi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49047 | Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow via the devName parameter in the function formSetDeviceName.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49047</link><description>Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow via the devName parameter in the function formSetDeviceName.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6329 | Control iD iDSecure passwordCustom Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6329</link><description>[PROBLEMTYPE] in [COMPONENT] in [VENDOR] [PRODUCT] [VERSION] on [PLATFORMS] allows [ATTACKER] to [IMPACT] via [VECTOR]</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2707 | Appointment booking addon for Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 1.9.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2707</link><description>The gAppointments WordPress plugin through 1.9.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4252 | EventPrime &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Booking Pricing Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4252</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin through 3.2.9 specifies the price of a booking in the client request, allowing an attacker to purchase bookings without payment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4297 | Mmm Simple File List &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Directory Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4297</link><description>The Mmm Simple File List WordPress plugin through 2.3 does not validate the generated path to list files from, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscribers, to list the content of arbitrary directories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4514 | Mmm Simple File List &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4514</link><description>The Mmm Simple File List WordPress plugin through 2.3 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4642 | kk Star Ratings &amp;lt; 5.4.6 - Rating Tampering via Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4642</link><description>The kk Star Ratings WordPress plugin before 5.4.6 does not implement atomic operations, allowing one user vote multiple times on a poll due to a Race Condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4922 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4922</link><description>The WPB Show Core WordPress plugin through 2.2 is vulnerable to a local file inclusion via the `path` parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5209 | Bookly &amp;lt; 22.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5209</link><description>The WordPress Online Booking and Scheduling Plugin WordPress plugin before 22.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5239 | Security &amp;amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk &amp;lt; 2.121 - IP Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5239</link><description>The Security &amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk WordPress plugin before 2.121 retrieves client IP addresses from potentially untrusted headers, allowing an attacker to manipulate its value. This may be used to bypass bruteforce protection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5325 | Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout &amp;lt; 2.0.6 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5325</link><description>The Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout WordPress plugin before 2.0.6 does not escape the custom shipping phone field no the checkout form leading to XSS</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5525 | Limit Login Attempts Reloaded &amp;lt; 2.25.26 - Admin+ Missing Authorization to Toggle Plugin Auto-Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5525</link><description>The Limit Login Attempts Reloaded WordPress plugin before 2.25.26 is missing authorization on the `toggle_auto_update` AJAX action, allowing any user with a valid nonce to toggle the auto-update status of the plugin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5559 | 10Web Booster &amp;lt; 2.24.18 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Option Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5559</link><description>The 10Web Booster WordPress plugin before 2.24.18 does not validate the option name given to some AJAX actions, allowing unauthenticated users to delete arbitrary options from the database, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5560 | WP-UserOnline &amp;lt; 2.88.3 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5560</link><description>The WP-UserOnline WordPress plugin before 2.88.3 does not sanitise and escape the X-Forwarded-For header before outputting its content on the page, which allows unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5604 | Asgaros Forum &amp;lt; 2.7.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5604</link><description>The Asgaros Forum WordPress plugin before 2.7.1 allows forum administrators, who may not be WordPress (super-)administrators, to set insecure configuration that allows unauthenticated users to upload dangerous files (e.g. .php, .phtml), potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5611 | Seraphinite Accelerator &amp;lt; 2.20.32 - Unauthorised Settings Reset/Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5611</link><description>The Seraphinite Accelerator WordPress plugin before 2.20.32 does not have authorisation and CSRF checks when resetting and importing its settings, allowing unauthenticated users to reset them</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5620 | Webpushr &amp;lt; 4.35.0 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5620</link><description>The Web Push Notifications WordPress plugin before 4.35.0 does not prevent visitors on the site from changing some of the plugin options, some of which may be used to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5641 | Martins Free &amp;amp; Easy SEO Link buildings &amp;lt; 1.2.30 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5641</link><description>The Martins Free &amp; Easy SEO BackLink Link Building Network WordPress plugin before 1.2.30 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5653 | WassUp Real Time Analytics &amp;lt;= 1.9.4.5 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5653</link><description>The WassUp Real Time Analytics WordPress plugin through 1.9.4.5 does not escape IP address provided via some headers before outputting them back in an admin page, allowing unauthenticated users to perform Stored XSS attacks against logged in admins</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5737 | WordPress Backup &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Subscriber+ Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5737</link><description>The WordPress Backup &amp; Migration WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not authorize some AJAX requests, allowing users with a role as low as Subscriber to update some plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5738 | WordPress Backup &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt; 1.4.5 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5738</link><description>The WordPress Backup &amp; Migration WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Subscriber to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5845 | Simple Social Buttons &amp;lt; 5.1.1 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Post Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5845</link><description>The Simple Social Media Share Buttons WordPress plugin before 5.1.1 leaks password-protected post content to unauthenticated visitors in some meta tags</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5906 | Job Manager &amp;amp; Career &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Directory listing to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5906</link><description>The Job Manager &amp; Career WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 contains a vulnerability in the Directory Listings system, which allows an unauthorized user to view and download private files of other users. This vulnerability poses a serious security threat because it allows an attacker to gain access to confidential data and files of other users without their permission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5942 | Medialist &amp;lt; 1.4.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5942</link><description>The Medialist WordPress plugin before 1.4.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5958 | POST SMTP Mailer &amp;lt; 2.7.1 - Unauthenticated Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5958</link><description>The POST SMTP Mailer WordPress plugin before 2.7.1 does not escape email message content before displaying it in the backend, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to perform XSS attacks against highly privileged users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5974 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Unauthenticated Server Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5974</link><description>The WPB Show Core WordPress plugin through 2.2 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) via the `path` parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49028 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in smpn1smg absis v.2017-10-19 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49028</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in smpn1smg absis v.2017-10-19 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the user parameter in the lock/lock.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49043 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wpapsk_crypto parameter i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49043</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wpapsk_crypto parameter in the function fromSetWirelessRepeat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49029 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in smpn1smg absis v.2017-10-19 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the nama...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49029</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in smpn1smg absis v.2017-10-19 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the nama parameter in the lock/lock.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31275 | An uninitialized pointer use vulnerability exists in the functionality of WPS Office 11.2.0.11537 that handles Data elements in an Excel fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31275</link><description>An uninitialized pointer use vulnerability exists in the functionality of WPS Office 11.2.0.11537 that handles Data elements in an Excel file. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32616 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 12.1.2.15356 handles 3D annotations. A specially crafted Javascript code insid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32616</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 12.1.2.15356 handles 3D annotations. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35985 | An arbitrary file creation vulnerability exists in the Javascript exportDataObject API of Foxit Reader 12.1.3.15356 due to a failure to prop...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35985</link><description>An arbitrary file creation vulnerability exists in the Javascript exportDataObject API of Foxit Reader 12.1.3.15356 due to a failure to properly validate a dangerous extension. A specially crafted malicious file can create files at arbitrary locations, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially-crafted malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38573 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 12.1.2.15356 handles a signature field. A specially crafted Javascript code in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38573</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 12.1.2.15356 handles a signature field. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39542 | A code execution vulnerability exists in the Javascript saveAs API of Foxit Reader 12.1.3.15356. A specially crafted malformed file can crea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39542</link><description>A code execution vulnerability exists in the Javascript saveAs API of Foxit Reader 12.1.3.15356. A specially crafted malformed file can create arbitrary files, which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40194 | An arbitrary file creation vulnerability exists in the Javascript exportDataObject API of Foxit Reader 12.1.3.15356 due to mistreatment of w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40194</link><description>An arbitrary file creation vulnerability exists in the Javascript exportDataObject API of Foxit Reader 12.1.3.15356 due to mistreatment of whitespace characters. A specially crafted malicious file can create files at arbitrary locations, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41257 | A type confusion vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 12.1.2.15356 handles field value properties.  A specially crafted Javascript c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41257</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 12.1.2.15356 handles field value properties.  A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49046 | Stack Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the devName parameter in the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49046</link><description>Stack Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v.1.0.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the devName parameter in the function formAddMacfilterRule.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4931 | Uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Plesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4931</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Plesk Installer affects version 3.27.0.0. A local attacker could execute arbitrary code by injecting DLL files into the same folder where the application is installed, resulting in DLL hijacking in edputil.dll, samlib.dll, urlmon.dll, sspicli.dll, propsys.dll and profapi.dll files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6287 | Backup password in GET parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6287</link><description>Sensitive data exposure in Webconf in Tribe29 Checkmk Appliance before 1.6.8 allows local attacker to retrieve passwords via reading log files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4590 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Frhed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4590</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in Frhed hex editor, affecting version 1.6.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a long filename argument through the Structured Exception Handler (SEH) registers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5871 | Libnbd: a malicious nbd server may crash libnbd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5871</link><description>A flaw was found in libnbd, due to a malicious Network Block Device (NBD), a protocol for accessing Block Devices such as hard disks over a Network. This issue may allow a malicious NBD server to cause a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43701 | Apache Superset: Stored XSS on API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43701</link><description>Improper payload validation and an improper REST API response type, made it possible for an authenticated malicious actor to store malicious code into Chart's metadata, this code could get executed if a user specifically accesses a specific deprecated API endpoint. This issue affects Apache Superset versions prior to 2.1.2. 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.2, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5607 | An improper limitation of a path name to a restricted directory (path traversal) vulnerability in the TACC ePO extension, for on-premises eP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5607</link><description>An improper limitation of a path name to a restricted directory (path traversal) vulnerability in the TACC ePO extension, for on-premises ePO servers, prior to version 8.4.0 could lead to an authorised administrator attacker executing arbitrary code through uploading a specially crafted GTI reputation file. The attacker would need the appropriate privileges to access the relevant section of the User Interface. The import logic has been updated to restrict file types and content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40610 | Apache Superset: Privilege escalation with default examples database</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40610</link><description>Improper authorization check and possible privilege escalation on Apache Superset up to but excluding 2.1.2. Using the default examples database connection that allows access to both the examples schema and Apache Superset's metadata database, an attacker using a specially crafted CTE SQL statement could change data on the metadata database. This weakness could result on tampering with the authentication/authorization data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42501 | Apache Superset: Unnecessary read permissions within the Gamma role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42501</link><description>Unnecessary read permissions within the Gamma role would allow authenticated users to read configured CSS templates and annotations.
This issue affects Apache Superset: before 2.1.2.
Users should upgrade to version or above 2.1.2 and run `superset init` to reconstruct the Gamma role or remove `can_read` permission from the mentioned resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49068 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Information Leakage Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49068</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler.This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue. At the time of disclosure of this advisory, this version has not yet been released. In the mean time, we recommend you make sure the logs are only available to trusted operators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6254 | Password is send back to client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6254</link><description>A Vulnerability in OTRS AgentInterface and ExternalInterface allows the reading of plain text passwords which are send back to the client in the server response-
This issue affects OTRS: from 8.0.X through 8.0.37.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35075 | HTML injection via channel autocomplete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35075</link><description>Mattermost fails to use  innerText / textContent when setting the channel name in the webapp during autocomplete, allowing an attacker to inject HTML to a victim's page by create a channel name that is valid HTML. No XSS is possible though.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40703 | Denial of Service via specially crafted block fields in Mattermost Boards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40703</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly limit the characters allowed in different fields of a block in Mattermost Boards allowing a attacker to consume excessive resources, possibly leading to Denial of Service, by patching the field of a block using a specially crafted string.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43754 | Permalink previews displayed for posts in archived channels even if users are disallowed to view archived channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43754</link><description>Mattermost fails to check whether the  “Allow users to view archived channels”  setting is enabled during permalink previews display, allowing members to view permalink previews of archived channels even if the “Allow users to view archived channels” setting is disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45223 | Users full name disclosure through Mattermost Boards with Show Full Name Option disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45223</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly validate the "Show Full Name" option in a few endpoints in Mattermost Boards, allowing a member to get the full name of another user even if the Show Full Name option was disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47168 | Open redirect in /oauth/&amp;lt;service&amp;gt;/mobile_login?redirect_to=</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47168</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly check a redirect URL parameter allowing for an open redirect was possible when the user clicked "Back to Mattermost" after providing a invalid custom url scheme in /oauth/{service}/mobile_login?redirect_to=</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48268 | Denial of Service via Board Import Zip Bomb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48268</link><description>Mattermost fails to limit the amount of data extracted from compressed archives during board import in Mattermost Boards allowing an attacker to consume excessive resources, possibly leading to Denial of Service, by importing a board using a specially crafted zip (zip bomb).</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48369 | Log Flooding due to specially crafted requests in different endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48369</link><description>Mattermost fails to limit the log size of server logs allowing an attacker sending specially crafted requests to different endpoints to potentially overflow the log.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6202 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in /plugins/focalboard/ api/v2/users of Mattermost Boards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6202</link><description>Mattermost fails to perform proper authorization in the /plugins/focalboard/api/v2/users endpoint allowing an attacker who is a guest user and knows the ID of another user to get their information (e.g. name, surname, nickname) via Mattermost Boards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47865 | Username and Icon override can be used by members when Hardened Mode is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47865</link><description>Mattermost fails to check if hardened mode is enabled when overriding the username and/or the icon when posting a post. If settings allowed integrations to override the username and profile picture when posting, a member could also override the username and icon when making a post even if the Hardened Mode setting was enabled</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25632 | The Android Mobile Whale browser app before 3.0.1.2 allows the attacker to bypass its browser unlock function via 'Open in Whale' feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25632</link><description>The Android Mobile Whale browser app before 3.0.1.2 allows the attacker to bypass its browser unlock function via 'Open in Whale' feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 07:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6312 | SourceCodester Loan Management System Users Page deleteUser.php delete_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6312</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function delete_user of the file deleteUser.php of the component Users Page. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246138 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6313 | SourceCodester URL Shortener Long URL cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6313</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester URL Shortener 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Long URL Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246139.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6310 | SourceCodester Loan Management System deleteBorrower.php delete_borrower sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6310</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function delete_borrower of the file deleteBorrower.php. The manipulation of the argument borrower_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246136.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6311 | SourceCodester Loan Management System Loan Type Page delete_ltype.php delete_ltype sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6311</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function delete_ltype of the file delete_ltype.php of the component Loan Type Page. The manipulation of the argument ltype_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246137 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6308 | Xiamen Four-Faith Video Surveillance Management System Apache Struts unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6308</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Xiamen Four-Faith Video Surveillance Management System 2016/2017. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Apache Struts. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246134 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:04:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6309 | moses-smt mosesdecoder trans_result.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6309</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in moses-smt mosesdecoder up to 4.0. This affects an unknown part of the file contrib/iSenWeb/trans_result.php. The manipulation of the argument input1 leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246135.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:04:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6306 | SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System member_data.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6306</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ample/app/ajax/member_data.php. The manipulation of the argument columns leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246132.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:04:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6307 | jeecgboot JimuReport image path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6307</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 1.6.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /download/image. The manipulation of the argument imageUrl leads to relative path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246133 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:04:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6304 | Tecno 4G Portable WiFi TR118 Ping Tool goform_get_cmd_process os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6304</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tecno 4G Portable WiFi TR118 TR118-M30E-RR-D-EnFrArSwHaPo-OP-V008-20220830. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/goform_get_cmd_process of the component Ping Tool. The manipulation of the argument url leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246130 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:10:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6305 | SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System suppliar_data.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6305</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ample/app/ajax/suppliar_data.php. The manipulation of the argument columns leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246131.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:10:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6302 | CSZCMS File Manager Page templates permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6302</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CSZCMS 1.3.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file \views\templates of the component File Manager Page. The manipulation leads to permission issues. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246128. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6303 | CSZCMS Site Settings Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6303</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CSZCMS 1.3.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/settings/ of the component Site Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument Additional Meta Tag with the input &lt;svg&gt;&lt;animate onbegin=alert(1) attributeName=x dur=1s&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246129 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49321 | Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because scanning a crafted file takes a long time, and causes the scanner to hang. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49321</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because scanning a crafted file takes a long time, and causes the scanner to hang. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant 1.0.35-1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49322 | Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because there is an unpack handler crash that can lead to a scanning engine crash. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49322</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because there is an unpack handler crash that can lead to a scanning engine crash. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant 1.0.35-1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6300 | SourceCodester Best Courier Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6300</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument page with the input &lt;/TiTlE&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(1)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6301 | SourceCodester Best Courier Management System GET Parameter parcel_list.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6301</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file parcel_list.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id with the input &lt;/TiTlE&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(1)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246127.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6298 | Apryse iText PdfDocument.java main array index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6298</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Apryse iText 8.0.2. This vulnerability affects the function main of the file PdfDocument.java. The manipulation leads to improper validation of array index. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246124. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6299 | Apryse iText Reference Table PdfDocument.java memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6299</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Apryse iText 8.0.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file PdfDocument.java of the component Reference Table Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246125 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6297 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System Search Report Page patient-search-report.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6297</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file patient-search-report.php of the component Search Report Page. The manipulation of the argument Search By Patient Name with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246123.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 22:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6296 | osCommerce Instant Message compare cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6296</link><description>A vulnerability was found in osCommerce 4. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /catalog/compare of the component Instant Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument compare with the input 40dz4iq"&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt;zohkx leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-246122 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 21:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49312 | Precision Bridge PrecisionBridge.exe (aka the thick client) before 7.3.21 allows an integrity violation in which the same license key is use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49312</link><description>Precision Bridge PrecisionBridge.exe (aka the thick client) before 7.3.21 allows an integrity violation in which the same license key is used on multiple systems, via vectors involving a Process Hacker memory dump, error message inspection, and modification of a MAC address.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 21:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>