<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-25008 | Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller 6610 - Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25008</link><description>Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller 6610 contains a vulnerability in the Control System where Improper Input Validation can lead to arbitrary code execution, for example to obtain a Linux Shell with the same privileges as the attacker. The attacker would require elevated privileges for example a valid OAM user having the system administrator role to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7501 | Download Plugins and Themes from Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7501</link><description>The Download Plugins and Themes in ZIP from Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the download_theme() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary themes from the website via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. In versions prior to 1.8.6 it was possible to download the entire sites files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6460 | Grow by Tradedoubler &amp;lt;= 2.0.21 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6460</link><description>The Grow by Tradedoubler  WordPress plugin through 2.0.21 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via the component parameter. This makes it possible for attackers to include and execute PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7301 | WordPress File Upload &amp;lt;= 4.24.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7301</link><description>The WordPress File Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7422 | Theme My Login &amp;lt;= 7.1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7422</link><description>The Theme My Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the tml_admin_save_ms_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the theme's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note that this only affects multi-site instances.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 03:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3399 | Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Compliance for GDPR / CCPA &amp;lt;= 2.4.17.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3399</link><description>The Cookie Notice &amp; Compliance for GDPR / CCPA plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cookie_notice_options[refuse_code_head]' parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.4.17.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected /wp-admin/admin.php?page=cookie-notice page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7049 | Custom Field For WP Job Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2 -  Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7049</link><description>The Custom Field For WP Job Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 via the the 'cm_fieldshow' shortcode due to missing validation on the 'job_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to expose potentially sensitive post metadata.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7630 | Relevanssi &amp;lt;= 4.22.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7630</link><description>The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.22.2 via the relevanssi_do_query() due to insufficient limitations on the posts that are returned when searching. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive information from password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7852 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System view_inquiry.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7852</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/inquiries/view_inquiry.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7853 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7853</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=categories/view_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7851 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System Add User Users.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7851</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save of the component Add User Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43374 | Vim heap-use-after-free in src/arglist.c:207</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43374</link><description>The UNIX editor Vim prior to version 9.1.0678 has a use-after-free error in argument list handling. When adding a new file to the argument list, this triggers `Buf*` autocommands. If in such an autocommand the buffer that was just opened is closed (including the window where it is shown), this causes the window structure to be freed which contains a reference to the argument list that we are actually modifying. Once the autocommands are completed, the references to the window and argument list are no longer valid and as such cause an use-after-free. Impact is low since the user must either intentionally add some unusual autocommands that wipe a buffer during creation (either manually or by sourcing a malicious plugin), but it will crash Vim. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.0678.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43378 | calamares-nixos-extensions LUKS keyfile exposure regression on legacy BIOS systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43378</link><description>calamares-nixos-extensions provides Calamares branding and modules for NixOS, a distribution of GNU/Linux. Users who installed NixOS through the graphical installer who used manual disk partitioning to create a setup where the system was booted via legacy BIOS rather than UEFI; some disk partitions are encrypted; but the partitions containing either `/` or `/boot` are unencrypted; have their LUKS disk encryption key file in plain text either in `/crypto_keyfile.bin`, or in a CPIO archive attached to their NixOS initrd. `nixos-install` is not affected, nor are UEFI installations, nor was the default automatic partitioning configuration on legacy BIOS systems. The problem has been fixed in calamares-nixos-extensions 0.3.17, which was included in NixOS. The current installer images for the NixOS 24.05 and unstable (24.11) channels are unaffected. The fix reached 24.05 at 2024-08-13 20:06:59 UTC, and unstable at 2024-08-15 09:00:20 UTC. Installer images downloaded before those times may be vulnerable. The best solution for affected users is probably to back up their data and do a complete reinstallation. However, the mitigation procedure in GHSA-3rvf-24q2-24ww should work solely for the case where `/` is encrypted but `/boot` is not. If `/` is unencrypted, then the `/crypto_keyfile.bin` file will need to be deleted in addition to the remediation steps in the previous advisory. This issue is a partial regression of CVE-2023-36476 / GHSA-3rvf-24q2-24ww, which was more severe as it applied to the default configuration on BIOS systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43370 | gettext.js vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43370</link><description>gettext.js is a GNU gettext port for node and the browser. There is a cross-site scripting (XSS) injection if `.po` dictionary definition files are corrupted. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.0.3. As a workaround, control the origin of the definition catalog to prevent the use of this flaw in the definition of plural forms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7845 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System fetch_it.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7845</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/fetch_it.php. The manipulation of the argument request leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7849 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_create_album buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7849</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This affects the function cgi_create_album of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43369 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting in Ibexa RichText Field Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43369</link><description>Ibexa RichText Field Type is a Field Type for supporting rich formatted text stored in a structured XML format. In versions on the 4.6 branch prior to 4.6.10, the validator for the RichText fieldtype blocklists `javascript:` and `vbscript:` in links to prevent XSS. This can leave other options open, and the check can be circumvented using upper case. Content editing permissions for RichText content is required to exploit this vulnerability, which typically means Editor role or higher. The fix implements an allowlist instead, which allows only approved link protocols. The new check is case insensitive. Version 4.6.10 contains a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7844 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System add_acc.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7844</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/add_acc.php. The manipulation of the argument name/user/position leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7843 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System exportcs.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7843</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tracking/admin/exportcs.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31333 | In _MMU_AllocLevel of mmu_common.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31333</link><description>In _MMU_AllocLevel of mmu_common.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34727 | In sdpu_compare_uuid_with_attr of sdp_utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34727</link><description>In sdpu_compare_uuid_with_attr of sdp_utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34731 | In multiple functions of TranscodingResourcePolicy.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34731</link><description>In multiple functions of TranscodingResourcePolicy.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34734 | In onForegroundServiceButtonClicked of FooterActionsViewModel.kt, there is a possible way to disable the active VPN app from the lockscreen ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34734</link><description>In onForegroundServiceButtonClicked of FooterActionsViewModel.kt, there is a possible way to disable the active VPN app from the lockscreen due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34736 | In setupVideoEncoder of StagefrightRecorder.cpp, there is a possible asynchronous playback when B-frame support is enabled. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34736</link><description>In setupVideoEncoder of StagefrightRecorder.cpp, there is a possible asynchronous playback when B-frame support is enabled. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34737 | In ensureSetPipAspectRatioQuotaTracker of ActivityClientController.java, there is a possible way to generate unmovable and undeletable pip w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34737</link><description>In ensureSetPipAspectRatioQuotaTracker of ActivityClientController.java, there is a possible way to generate unmovable and undeletable pip windows due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34738 | In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way for unprivileged apps to read their own restrictRead app-op states due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34738</link><description>In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way for unprivileged apps to read their own restrictRead app-op states due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34739 | In shouldRestrictOverlayActivities of UsbProfileGroupSettingsManager.java, there is a possible escape from SUW due to a logic error in the c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34739</link><description>In shouldRestrictOverlayActivities of UsbProfileGroupSettingsManager.java, there is a possible escape from SUW due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34740 | In attributeBytesBase64 and attributeBytesHex of BinaryXmlSerializer.java, there is a possible arbitrary XML injection due to an integer ove...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34740</link><description>In attributeBytesBase64 and attributeBytesHex of BinaryXmlSerializer.java, there is a possible arbitrary XML injection due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34741 | In setForceHideNonSystemOverlayWindowIfNeeded of WindowState.java, there is a possible way for message content to be visible on the screensa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34741</link><description>In setForceHideNonSystemOverlayWindowIfNeeded of WindowState.java, there is a possible way for message content to be visible on the screensaver while lock screen visibility settings are restricted by the user due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34742 | In shouldWrite of OwnersData.java, there is a possible edge case that prevents MDM policies from being persisted due to a logic error in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34742</link><description>In shouldWrite of OwnersData.java, there is a possible edge case that prevents MDM policies from being persisted due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34743 | In setTransactionState of SurfaceFlinger.cpp, there is a possible way to perform tapjacking due to a logic error in the code. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34743</link><description>In setTransactionState of SurfaceFlinger.cpp, there is a possible way to perform tapjacking due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7841 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System check_user_name.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7841</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pms/ajax/check_user_name.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7842 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System export_it.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7842</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /tracking/admin/export_it.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7839 | itsourcecode Billing System addbill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7839</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file addbill.php. The manipulation of the argument owners_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43367 | Boa has an uncaught exception when transitioning the state of `AsyncGenerator` objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43367</link><description>Boa is an embeddable and experimental Javascript engine written in Rust. Starting in version 0.16 and prior to version 0.19.0, a wrong assumption made when handling ECMAScript's `AsyncGenerator` operations can cause an uncaught exception on certain scripts. Boa's implementation of `AsyncGenerator` makes the assumption that the state of an `AsyncGenerator` object cannot change while resolving a promise created by methods of `AsyncGenerator` such as `%AsyncGeneratorPrototype%.next`, `%AsyncGeneratorPrototype%.return`, or `%AsyncGeneratorPrototype%.throw`. However, a carefully constructed code could trigger a state transition from a getter method for the promise's `then` property, which causes the engine to fail an assertion of this assumption, causing an uncaught exception. This could be used to create a Denial Of Service attack in applications that run arbitrary ECMAScript code provided by an external user. Version 0.19.0 is patched to correctly handle this case. Users unable to upgrade to the patched version would want to use `std::panic::catch_unwind` to ensure any exceptions caused by the engine don't impact the availability of the main application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42488 | Cilium agent&amp;#x27;s race condition may lead to policy bypass for Host Firewall policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42488</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. Prior to versions 1.14.14 and 1.15.8, a race condition in the Cilium agent can cause the agent to ignore labels that should be applied to a node. This could in turn cause CiliumClusterwideNetworkPolicies intended for nodes with the ignored label to not apply, leading to policy bypass. This issue has been patched in Cilium v1.14.14 and v1.15.8 As the underlying issue depends on a race condition, users unable to upgrade can restart the Cilium agent on affected nodes until the affected policies are confirmed to be working as expected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42487 | Cilium&amp;#x27;s Gateway API route matching order contradicts specification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42487</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. In the 1.15 branch prior to 1.15.8 and the 1.16 branch prior to 1.16.1, Gateway API HTTPRoutes and GRPCRoutes do not follow the match precedence specified in the Gateway API specification. In particular, request headers are matched before request methods, when the specification describes that the request methods must be respected before headers are matched. This could result in unexpected behaviour with security This issue is fixed in Cilium v1.15.8 and v1.16.1. There is no workaround for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7868 | Uninitialized variable in Xpdf 4.05 due to invalid JPEG header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7868</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), invalid header info in a DCT (JPEG) stream can lead to an uninitialized variable in the DCT decoder. The proof-of-concept PDF file causes a segfault attempting to read from an invalid address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43366 | zkvyper ignored loop range bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43366</link><description>zkvyper is a Vyper compiler. Starting in version 1.3.12 and prior to version 1.5.3, since LLL IR has no Turing-incompletness restrictions, it is compiled to a loop with a much more late exit condition. It leads to a loss of funds or other unwanted behavior if the loop body contains it. However, more real-life use cases like iterating over an array are not affected. No contracts were affected by this issue, which was fixed in version 1.5.3. Upgrading and redeploying affected contracts is the only way to avoid the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6456 | SQL Injection vulnerability in AVEVA Historian Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6456</link><description>AVEVA Historian Server has a vulnerability, if exploited, could allow a malicious SQL command to execute under the privileges of an interactive Historian REST Interface user who had been socially engineered by a miscreant into opening a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7838 | itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System addcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7838</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument cname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7867 | Integer overflow and divide-by-zero in Xpdf 4.05 due to bogus page box coordinates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7867</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), very large coordinates in a page box can cause an integer overflow and divide-by-zero.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7866 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in PDF pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7866</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in a pattern resource leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 19:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42476 | oauth CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42476</link><description>In the OAuth library for nim prior to version 0.11, the Authorization Code grant and Implicit grant both rely on the `state` parameter to prevent cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks where a resource owner might have their session associated with protected resources belonging to an attacker. When this project is compiled with certain compiler flags set, it is possible that the `state` parameter will not be checked at all, creating a CSRF vulnerability. Version 0.11 checks the `state` parameter using a regular `if` statement or `doAssert` instead of relying on a plain `assert`. `doAssert` will achieve the desired behavior even if `-d:danger` or `--assertions:off` is set.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42475 | OAuth library for nim allows insecure generation of state values by generateState - entropy too low and uses regular PRNG instead of CSPRNG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42475</link><description>In the OAuth library for nim prior to version 0.11, the `state` values generated by the `generateState` function do not have sufficient entropy. These can be successfully guessed by an attacker allowing them to perform a CSRF vs a user, associating the user's session with the attacker's protected resources. While `state` isn't exactly a cryptographic value, it should be generated in a cryptographically secure way. `generateState` should be using a CSPRNG. Version 0.11 modifies the `generateState` function to generate `state` values of at least 128 bits of entropy while using a CSPRNG.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27729 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the location paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27729</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the location parameter of the calendar event feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27730 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27730</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the cid parameter of the calendar event feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27731 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lack of file type...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27731</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lack of file type filtering in the file attachment parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42472 | Flatpak may allow access to files outside sandbox for certain apps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42472</link><description>Flatpak is a Linux application sandboxing and distribution framework. Prior to versions 1.14.0 and 1.15.10, a malicious or compromised Flatpak app using persistent directories could access and write files outside of what it would otherwise have access to, which is an attack on integrity and confidentiality.

When `persistent=subdir` is used in the application permissions (represented as `--persist=subdir` in the command-line interface), that means that an application which otherwise doesn't have access to the real user home directory will see an empty home directory with a writeable subdirectory `subdir`. Behind the scenes, this directory is actually a bind mount and the data is stored in the per-application directory as `~/.var/app/$APPID/subdir`. This allows existing apps that are not aware of the per-application directory to still work as intended without general home directory access.

However, the application does have write access to the application directory `~/.var/app/$APPID` where this directory is stored. If the source directory for the `persistent`/`--persist` option is replaced by a symlink, then the next time the application is started, the bind mount will follow the symlink and mount whatever it points to into the sandbox.

Partial protection against this vulnerability can be provided by patching Flatpak using the patches in commits ceec2ffc and 98f79773. However, this leaves a race condition that could be exploited by two instances of a malicious app running in parallel. Closing the race condition requires updating or patching the version of bubblewrap that is used by Flatpak to add the new `--bind-fd` option using the patch and then patching Flatpak to use it. If Flatpak has been configured at build-time with `-Dsystem_bubblewrap=bwrap` (1.15.x) or `--with-system-bubblewrap=bwrap` (1.14.x or older), or a similar option, then the version of bubblewrap that needs to be patched is a system copy that is distributed separately, typically `/usr/bin/bwrap`. This configuration is the one that is typically used in Linux distributions. If Flatpak has been configured at build-time with `-Dsystem_bubblewrap=` (1.15.x) or with `--without-system-bubblewrap` (1.14.x or older), then it is the bundled version of bubblewrap that is included with Flatpak that must be patched. This is typically installed as `/usr/libexec/flatpak-bwrap`. This configuration is the default when building from source code.

For the 1.14.x stable branch, these changes are included in Flatpak 1.14.10. The bundled version of bubblewrap included in this release has been updated to 0.6.3. For the 1.15.x development branch, these changes are included in Flatpak 1.15.10. The bundled version of bubblewrap in this release is a Meson "wrap" subproject, which has been updated to 0.10.0. The 1.12.x and 1.10.x branches will not be updated for this vulnerability. Long-term support OS distributions should backport the individual changes into their versions of Flatpak and bubblewrap, or update to newer versions if their stability policy allows it. As a workaround, avoid using applications using the `persistent` (`--persist`) permission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43357 | JavaScript specification issue may lead to type confusion and pointer dereference in implementations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43357</link><description>ECMA-262 is the language specification for the scripting language ECMAScript. A problem in the ECMAScript (JavaScript) specification of async generators, introduced by a May 2021 spec refactor, may lead to mis-implementation in a way that could present as a security vulnerability, such as type confusion and pointer dereference.

The internal async generator machinery calls regular promise resolver functions on IteratorResult (`{ done, value }`) objects that it creates, assuming that the IteratorResult objects will not be then-ables. Unfortunately, these IteratorResult objects inherit from `Object.prototype`, so these IteratorResult objects can be made then-able, triggering arbitrary behaviour, including re-entering the async generator machinery in a way that violates some internal invariants.

The ECMAScript specification is a living standard and the issue has been addressed at the time of this advisory's public disclosure. JavaScript engine implementors should refer to the latest specification and update their implementations to comply with the `AsyncGenerator` section.

## References

- https://github.com/tc39/ecma262/commit/1e24a286d0a327d08e1154926b3ee79820232727
- https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=1901411
- https://github.com/boa-dev/boa/security/advisories/GHSA-f67q-wr6w-23jq
- https://bugs.webkit.org/show_bug.cgi?id=275407
- https://issues.chromium.org/issues/346692561
- https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7652</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25633 | In eLabFTW, if administrators can create users, users can too</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25633</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs.  In an eLabFTW system, one might disallow user creation except for by system administrators, administrators and trusted services. If administrators are allowed to create new users (which is the default), the vulnerability allows any user to create new users in teams where they are members. The new users are automatically validated and administrators are not notified. This can allow a user with permanent or temporary access to a user account or API key to maintain persistence in an eLabFTW system. Additionally, it allows the user to create separate account under a different name, and produce misleading revision histories. No additional privileges are granted to the new user. Users should upgrade to version 5.0.0 to receive a patch. As a workaround, disabling both options that allow *administrators* to create users will provide a mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27728 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the text parameter of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27728</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the text parameter of the babel debug feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42757 | Command injection vulnerability in Asus RT-N15U 3.0.0.4.376_3754 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the netstat function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42757</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in Asus RT-N15U 3.0.0.4.376_3754 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the netstat function page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23168 | Vulnerability in Xiexe XSOverlay before build 647 allows non-local websites to send the malicious commands to the WebSocket API, resulting i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23168</link><description>Vulnerability in Xiexe XSOverlay before build 647 allows non-local websites to send the malicious commands to the WebSocket API, resulting in the arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32231 | Stash up to v0.25.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sort parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32231</link><description>Stash up to v0.25.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sort parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22217 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Terminalfour before 8.3.19 allows authenticated users to use specific features to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22217</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Terminalfour before 8.3.19 allows authenticated users to use specific features to access internal services including sensitive information on the server that Terminalfour runs on.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22219 | XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22219</link><description>XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users to submit malicious XML via unspecified features which could lead to various actions such as accessing the underlying server, remote code execution (RCE), or performing Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22218 | XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22218</link><description>XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users to submit malicious XML via unspecified features which could lead to various actions such as accessing the underlying server, remote code execution (RCE), or performing Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31905 | IBM QRadar Network Packet Capture information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31905</link><description>IBM QRadar Network Packet Capture 7.5 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  289858.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40705 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40705</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server could allow an authenticated user to consume file space resources due to unrestricted file uploads.  IBM X-Force ID:  298279.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31798 | Identical Hardcoded Root Password for All Devices in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to retr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31798</link><description>Identical Hardcoded Root Password for All Devices in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to retrieve the root password for all similar devices</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31799 | Information Disclosure in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to read the WiFi passphrase via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31799</link><description>Information Disclosure in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to read the WiFi passphrase via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31800 | Authentication Bypass in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to gain a privileged command shell ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31800</link><description>Authentication Bypass in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to gain a privileged command shell via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40704 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40704</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a privileged user to obtain sensitive information from authentication request headers.   IBM X-Force ID:  298277.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42843 | Projectworlds Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the subject parameter in feed.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42843</link><description>Projectworlds Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the subject parameter in feed.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42940 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42940</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42941 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanmode parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42941</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanmode parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42942 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42942</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42943 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42943</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42944 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42944</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42945 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromAddressNat function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42945</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromAddressNat function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42946 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42946</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42947 | An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42947</link><description>An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42948 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42948</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42949 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42949</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42950 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42950</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42951 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the mit_pptpusrpw parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42951</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the mit_pptpusrpw parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42952 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42952</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42953 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPW parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42953</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPW parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42954 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42954</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42955 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42955</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42966 | Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK N350RT V9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42966</link><description>Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK N350RT V9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains the username and the password, via a crafted request to /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42967 | Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42967</link><description>Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains the username and the password, via a crafted request to /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42968 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42968</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42969 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42969</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42973 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSetlpBind function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42973</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSetlpBind function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42974 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42974</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42976 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42976</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42977 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42977</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42978 | An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42978</link><description>An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42979 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ProtForm function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42979</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ProtForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42980 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42980</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42981 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42981</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42982 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42982</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42983 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the pptpPPW parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42983</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the pptpPPW parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42984 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42984</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42985 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42985</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42986 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42986</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42987 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the modino parameter in the fromPptpUserAdd function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42987</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the modino parameter in the fromPptpUserAdd function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42681 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in xxl-job v.2.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sub-Task ID component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42681</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in xxl-job v.2.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sub-Task ID component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43373 | webcrack has an Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability on Windows when Parsing and Saving a Malicious Bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43373</link><description>webcrack is a tool for reverse engineering javascript. An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists in the webcrack module when processing specifically crafted malicious code on Windows systems. This vulnerability is triggered when using the unpack bundles feature in conjunction with the saving feature. If a module name includes a path traversal sequence with Windows path separators, an attacker can exploit this to overwrite files on the host system. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write arbitrary `.js` files to the host system, which can be leveraged to hijack legitimate Node.js modules to gain arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6347 | Unauthorized access to ECU functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6347</link><description>*  Unprotected privileged mode access through UDS session in the Blind Spot Detection Sensor ECU firmware in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) by unauthorized access to the ECU's programming session.
  *  No preconditions implemented for ECU management functionality through UDS session in the Blind Spot Detection Sensor ECU in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to disrupt normal ECU operations by triggering a control command without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7262 | Arbitrary Code Execution in WPS Office</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7262</link><description>Improper path validation in promecefpluginhost.exe in Kingsoft WPS Office version ranging from 12.2.0.13110 to 12.2.0.13489 on Windows allows an attacker to load an arbitrary Windows library.
Using the MHTML format allows an attacker to automatically deliver a malicious library on opening the document and a single user click on a crafted hyperlink leads to the execution of the library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7263 | Arbitrary Code Execution in WPS Office</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7263</link><description>Improper path validation in promecefpluginhost.exe in Kingsoft WPS Office version ranging from 12.2.0.13110 to 12.2.0.13489 on Windows allows an attacker to load an arbitrary Windows library.
The patch released in version 12.2.0.16909 to mitigate CVE-2024-7262 was not restrictive enough. Another hyperlink parameter was not properly sanitized which leads to the execution of an arbitrary Windows library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7833 | D-Link DI-8100 upgrade_filter.asp upgrade_filter_asp command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7833</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function upgrade_filter_asp of the file upgrade_filter.asp. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42679 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42679</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the/ajax/Login.ashx component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42680 | An issue in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain the server absolute path by enterin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42680</link><description>An issue in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain the server absolute path by entering a single quotation mark.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42676 | File Upload vulnerability in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42676</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /nssys/common/Upload. Aspx? Action=DNPageAjaxPostBack component</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42677 | An issue in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42677</link><description>An issue in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /nssys/common/filehandle. Aspx component</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7832 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_get_fullscreen_photos buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7832</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_get_fullscreen_photos of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument user leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42678 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42678</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the /WebSet/DlgGridSet.html component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7830 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_move_photo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7830</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_move_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument photo_name leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7831 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_get_cooliris buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7831</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_get_cooliris of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument path leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7828 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_set_cover buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7829 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_del_photo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43275 | WordPress Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43275</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Xyzscripts Insert PHP Code Snippet.This issue affects Insert PHP Code Snippet: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 08:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7411 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7411</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the /vendor/mobiledetect/mobiledetectlib/export/exportToJSON.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7063 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.6.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7063</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.6 via the 'render_raw' function. This can allow authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level permissions and above, to extract sensitive data including private, future, and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7064 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7064</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7815 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Update Employee Page admin-update-employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7815</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-update-employee.php of the component Update Employee Page. The manipulation of the argument emp_fname /emp_lname /emp_nat_idno/emp_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 04:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7814 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Add Employee Page admin-add-employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7814</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin-add-employee.php of the component Add Employee Page. The manipulation of the argument emp_fname /emp_lname /emp_nat_idno/emp_addr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6534 | Directus 10.13.0 - Insecure object reference via PATH presets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6534</link><description>Directus v10.13.0 allows an authenticated external attacker to modify presets created by the same user to assign them to another user. This is possible because the application only validates the user parameter in the 'POST /presets' request but not in the PATCH request. When chained with CVE-2024-6533, it could result in account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6533 | Directus 10.13.0 - DOM-Based cross-site scripting (XSS) via layout_options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6533</link><description>Directus v10.13.0 allows an authenticated external attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript on the client. This is possible because the application injects an attacker-controlled parameter that will be stored in the server and used by the client into an unsanitized DOM element. When chained with CVE-2024-6534, it could result in account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7812 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System POST Parameter ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7812</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /rental_0/rental/ajax.php?action=save_tenant of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument lastname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7813 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Profile Image insufficiently protected credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7813</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /uploadImage/Profile/ of the component Profile Image Handler. The manipulation leads to insufficiently protected credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25024 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25024</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  281430.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7420 | Insert PHP Code Snippet &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Code Snippet Activate/Deactivate/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7420</link><description>The Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the /admin/snippets.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to activate/deactivate and delete code snippets via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7624 | Zephyr Project Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.101 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7624</link><description>The Zephyr Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.101. This is due to the plugin not properly checking a users capabilities before allowing them to enable access to the plugin's settings through the update_user_access() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to grant themselves full access to the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7628 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.15.2 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7628</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 4.15.2. This is due to the use of loose comparison in the 'verify_id_token' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to an @flutter.io email address or phone number. This also requires firebase to be configured on the website and the user to have set up firebase for their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7811 | SourceCodester Daily Expenses Monitoring App delete-expense.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7811</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Daily Expenses Monitoring App 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/delete-expense.php. The manipulation of the argument expense leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7810 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System view_itprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/view_itprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7809 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System nbproject exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tracking/nbproject/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7808 | code-projects Job Portal logindbc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file logindbc.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7625 | Nomad Vulnerable to Allocation Directory Escape On Non-Existing File Paths Through Archive Unpacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7625</link><description>In HashiCorp Nomad and Nomad Enterprise from 0.6.1 up to 1.16.13, 1.7.10, and 1.8.2, the archive unpacking process is vulnerable to writes outside the allocation directory during migration of allocation directories when multiple archive headers target the same file. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-7625, is fixed in Nomad 1.6.14, 1.7.11, and 1.8.3. Access or compromise of the Nomad client agent at the source allocation first is a prerequisite for leveraging this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7799 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System users.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7799</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/users.php. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7800 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7800</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/ajax.php?action=delete_product. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7797 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7798 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7798</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/admin/ajax.php?action=login2. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43368 | Trix has a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on copy &amp;amp; paste</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43368</link><description>The Trix editor, versions prior to 2.1.4, is vulnerable to XSS when pasting malicious code. This vulnerability is a bypass of the fix put in place for GHSA-qjqp-xr96-cj99. In pull request 1149, sanitation was added for Trix attachments with a `text/html` content type. However, Trix only checks the content type on the paste event's `dataTransfer` object. As long as the `dataTransfer` has a content type of `text/html`, Trix parses its contents and creates an `Attachment` with them, even if the attachment itself doesn't have a `text/html` content type. Trix then uses the attachment content to set the attachment element's `innerHTML`. An attacker could trick a user to copy and paste malicious code that would execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's session, potentially leading to unauthorized actions being performed or sensitive information being disclosed. This vulnerability was fixed in version 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7793 | SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker add-task.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7793</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7794 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System mybill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file mybill.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42353 | WebOb&amp;#x27;s location header normalization during redirect leads to open redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42353</link><description>WebOb provides objects for HTTP requests and responses. When WebOb normalizes the HTTP Location header to include the request hostname, it does so by parsing the URL that the user is to be redirected to with Python's urlparse, and joining it to the base URL. `urlparse` however treats a `//` at the start of a string as a URI without a scheme, and then treats the next part as the hostname. `urljoin` will then use that hostname from the second part as the hostname replacing the original one from the request. This vulnerability is patched in WebOb version 1.8.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27120 | Local File Inclusion in ComfortKey before version 24.1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27120</link><description>A Local File Inclusion vulnerability has been found in ComfortKey, a product of Celsius Benelux. Using this vulnerability, an unauthenticated attacker may retrieve sensitive information about the underlying system. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 24.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40620 | Rockwell Automation Pavilion8® Unencrypted Data Vulnerability via HTTP protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40620</link><description>CVE-2024-40620 IMPACT

A vulnerability exists in the affected product due to lack of encryption of sensitive information. The vulnerability results in data being sent between the Console and the Dashboard without encryption, which can be seen in the logs of proxy servers, potentially impacting the data's confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40619 | Rockwell Automation GuardLogix/ControlLogix 5580 Controller denial-of-service Vulnerability via Malformed Packet Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40619</link><description>CVE-2024-40619 IMPACT

A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability occurs when a malformed CIP packet is sent over the network to the device and results in a major nonrecoverable fault causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42360 | Command Injection in sequenceserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42360</link><description>SequenceServer lets you rapidly set up a BLAST+ server with an intuitive user interface for personal or group use. Several HTTP endpoints did not properly sanitize user input and/or query parameters. This could be exploited to inject and run unwanted shell commands. This vulnerability has been fixed in 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7513 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View Site Edition Code Execution Vulnerability via File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7513</link><description>CVE-2024-7513 IMPACT

A code execution vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability occurs due to improper default file permissions allowing any user to edit or replace files, which are executed by account with elevated permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6078 | Rockwell Automation Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in DataMosaix™</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6078</link><description>CVE-2024-6078 IMPACT

An improper authentication vulnerability exists in the affected product, which could allow a malicious user to generate cookies for any user ID without the use of a username or password. If exploited, a malicious user could take over the account of a legitimate user. The malicious user would be able to view and modify data stored in the cloud.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7507 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix/GuardLogix 5580 and CompactLogix/Compact GuardLogix® 5380 Controller Denial-of-Service Vulnerability via Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7507</link><description>CVE-2024-7507 IMPACT

A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products.  This vulnerability occurs when a malformed PCCC message is received, causing a fault in the controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7515 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix/GuardLogix 5580 and CompactLogix/Compact GuardLogix® 5380 Controller Denial-of-Service Vulnerability via Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7515</link><description>CVE-2024-7515 IMPACT

A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. A malformed PTP management packet can cause a major nonrecoverable fault in the controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7792 | SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker delete-task.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7792</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/delete-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31882 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31882</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.1 and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service, under specific configurations, as the server may crash when using a specially crafted SQL statement by an authenticated user.  IBM X-Force ID:  287614.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37529 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37529</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.1 and 11.5 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service with a specially crafted query due to improper memory allocation.  IBM X-Force ID:  294295.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35136 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35136</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) federated server 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted query under certain conditions.  IBM X-Force ID:  291307.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35152 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35152</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.5 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service with a specially crafted query due to improper memory allocation. IBM X-Force ID:  292639.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50314 | IBM WebSphere Application Server Libery information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50314</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 24.0.0.8 could allow an attacker with access to the network to conduct spoofing attacks.  An attacker could exploit this vulnerability using a certificate issued by a trusted authority to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  274713.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50315 | IBM WebSphere Application Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50315</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 could allow an attacker with access to the network to conduct spoofing attacks.  An attacker could exploit this vulnerability using a certificate issued by a trusted authority to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  274714.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42436 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42436</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42437 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42437</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42438 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42438</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42439 | Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS and Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS - Untrusted Search Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42439</link><description>Untrusted search path in the installer for Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS and Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS before 6.1.0 may allow a privileged user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42440 | Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS, Zoom Rooms Client for macOS -  Improper Privilege Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42440</link><description>Improper privilege management in the installer for Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS and Zoom Rooms Client for macOS before 6.1.5 may allow a privileged user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42441 | Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS, Zoom Rooms Client for macOS -  Improper Privilege Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42441</link><description>Improper privilege management in the installer for Zoom Workplace Desktop App for macOS, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS and Zoom Rooms Client for macOS before 6.1.5 may allow a privileged user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5915 | GlobalProtect App: Local Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5915</link><description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5916 | PAN-OS: Cleartext Exposure of External System Secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5916</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a local system administrator to unintentionally disclose secrets, passwords, and tokens of external systems. A read-only administrator who has access to the config log, can read secrets, passwords, and tokens to external systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39818 | Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs - Protection Mechanism Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39818</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs may allow an authenticated user to conduct information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39822 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39822</link><description>Sensitive information exposure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow an authenticated user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39823 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39823</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39824 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39824</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39825 | Zoom Workplace Apps and Rooms Clients - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39825</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps and Rooms Clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42434 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42434</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42435 | Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers -  Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42435</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in some Zoom Workplace Apps, SDKs, Rooms Clients, and Rooms Controllers may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5914 | Cortex XSOAR: Command Injection in CommonScripts Pack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5914</link><description>A command injection issue in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR CommonScripts Pack allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of an integration container.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27267 | IBM SDK, Java Technology Edition denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27267</link><description>The Object Request Broker (ORB) in IBM SDK, Java Technology Edition 7.1.0.0 through 7.1.5.18 and 8.0.0.0 through 8.0.8.26 is vulnerable to remote denial of service, caused by a race condition in the management of ORB listener threads.  IBM X-Force ID:  284573.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28799 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28799</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 displays sensitive data improperly during back-end commands which may result in the unexpected disclosure of this information.  IBM X-Force ID:  287173.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25157 | Authentication bypass in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25157</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.6.0 allows Admin Users with access to the Agent Console to circumvent some permission checks when attempting to visit other pages. This could lead to unauthorized information disclosure or modification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34127 | Adobe Indesign TIF File Parsing Out Of Bound Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34127</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39383 | PoC sample of unknown vulnerability detected by EXPMON system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39383</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39386 | ZDI-CAN-24057: Adobe Bridge AVI FIle Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39386</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.8, 14.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39387 | ZDI-CAN-24047: Adobe Bridge AVI FIle Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39387</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.8, 14.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39388 | ZDI-CAN-24055: Adobe Substance 3D Stager SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39388</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.2 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39389 | Adobe Indesign PDF File Parsing Stack Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39389</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39390 | Adobe Indesign 2024 DOC File Parsing Memory Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39390</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39391 | Adobe Indesign XLS File Parsing Out Of Bound Write Remote Code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39391</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39393 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PCT File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39393</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39394 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PDF File Parsing Out Of Bound Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39394</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39395 | Adobe Indesign 2024 DOC File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39395</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39420 | Talos Security Advisory for Adobe (TALOS-2024-2011)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39420</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. This issue occurs when the state of a resource changes between its check-time and use-time, allowing an attacker to manipulate the resource. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39422 | ZDI-CAN-24090: New Vulnerability Report - Use-after-free remote code execution vulnerability in Adobe Acrobat Reader DC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39422</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39423 | ZDI-CAN-24182: New Vulnerability Report - Adobe Acrobat Reader DC AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39423</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39424 | ZDI-CAN-24309: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39424</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39425 | Security vulnerability in AdobeARMHelper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39425</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability that could lead to privilege escalation. Exploitation of this issue require local low-privilege access to the affected system and attack complexity is high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39426 | ZDI-CAN-24312: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39426</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41830 | Talos Security Advisory for Adobe (TALOS-2024-2009)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41830</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41831 | ZDI-CAN-24569: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41831</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41832 | TALOS-2024-2002 | Adobe Acrobat Reader Font gvar TupleVariation Data Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41832</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41833 | ZDI-CAN-24310: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41833</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41834 | ZDI-CAN-24311: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41834</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41835 | TALOS-2024-2003 | Adobe Acrobat Reader Font Packed Point Numbers Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41835</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30636, 24.002.20965, 24.002.20964, 24.001.30123 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41840 | ZDI-CAN-24607: Adobe Bridge JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41840</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.8, 14.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41850 | Adobe Indesign 2024 TIF File Parsing Heap Memory Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41850</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41851 | Adobe InDesign (Beta) has an integer overflow vulnerability when parsing SVG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41851</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41852 | Adobe Indesign 2024 AVI File Parsing Stack Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41852</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41853 | Indesign 2024 EPS File Parsing Heap Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41853</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41854 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PDF File parsing memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41854</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41866 | Adobe Indesign 2024 DOC File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41866</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.4, ID18.5.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20789 | ZDI-CAN-24030: Adobe Dimension SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20789</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20790 | Adobe Dimension Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability I, when parsing FBX file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20790</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34117 | Adobe Photoshop 2024 MPO File Parsing Use-After-Free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34117</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 24.7.3, 25.9.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34118 | Adobe illustrator 2024 TIF File parsing Division by zero denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34118</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to render the application unresponsive or terminate its execution. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34124 | ZDI-CAN-24031: Adobe Dimension SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34124</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34125 | ZDI-CAN-24027: Adobe Dimension GLB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34125</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34126 | ZDI-CAN-24028: Adobe Dimension USD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34126</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34133 | Adobe Illustrator CC 2023 v27.9 Vulnerability I</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34133</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34134 | Adobe Illustrator 2023 CC 27.7 Memory Corruption Out-Of-Bounds-Read Vulnerability II.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34134</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34135 | Adobe Illustrator CC 2023 v27.9 Vulnerability II</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34135</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34136 | Adobe Illustrator PSD File Parsing Null Pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34136</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34137 | Adobe Illustrator 2024 CGM File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34137</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS) condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34138 | Adobe Illustrator CGM File Parsing Division By zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34138</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41856 | Adobe Illustrator 2024 GIF File Parsing Memory Corruption vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41856</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.5, 27.9.4 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41865 | Adobe Dimension Untrusted Search Path lead to load malicious DLL swift.dll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41865</link><description>Dimension versions 3.4.11 and earlier are affected by an Untrusted Search Path vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting a malicious file into the search path, which the application might execute instead of the legitimate file. This could occur if the application uses a search path to locate executables or libraries. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42259 | drm/i915/gem: Fix Virtual Memory mapping boundaries calculation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42259</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/i915/gem: Fix Virtual Memory mapping boundaries calculation

Calculating the size of the mapped area as the lesser value
between the requested size and the actual size does not consider
the partial mapping offset. This can cause page fault access.

Fix the calculation of the starting and ending addresses, the
total size is now deduced from the difference between the end and
start addresses.

Additionally, the calculations have been rewritten in a clearer
and more understandable form.

[Joonas: Add Requires: tag]
Requires: 60a2066c5005 ("drm/i915/gem: Adjust vma offset for framebuffer mmap offset")
(cherry picked from commit 97b6784753da06d9d40232328efc5c5367e53417)</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37028 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37028</link><description>BIG-IP Next Central Manager may allow an attacker to lock out an account that has never been logged in.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39778 | BIG-IP HSB vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39778</link><description>When a stateless virtual server is configured on BIG-IP system with a High-Speed Bridge (HSB), undisclosed requests can cause TMM to terminate.

  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39792 | NGINX Plus MQTT vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39792</link><description>When the NGINX Plus is configured to use the MQTT pre-read module, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39809 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39809</link><description>The Central Manager user session refresh token does not expire when a user logs out.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41164 | BIG-IP MPTCP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41164</link><description>When TCP profile with Multipath TCP enabled (MPTCP) is configured on a Virtual Server, undisclosed traffic along with conditions beyond the attackers control can cause TMM to terminate.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41719 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41719</link><description>When generating QKView of BIG-IP Next instance from the BIG-IP Next Central Manager (CM),  F5 iHealth credentials will be logged in the BIG-IP Central Manager logs.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41723 | BIG-IP iControl REST vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41723</link><description>Undisclosed requests to BIG-IP iControl REST can lead to information leak of user account names.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41727 | BIG-IP TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41727</link><description>In BIG-IP tenants running on r2000 and r4000 series hardware, or BIG-IP Virtual Edition (VEs) using Intel E810 SR-IOV NIC, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7347 | NGINX MP4 module vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7347</link><description>NGINX Open Source and NGINX Plus have a vulnerability in the ngx_http_mp4_module, which might allow an attacker to over-read NGINX worker memory resulting in its termination, using a specially crafted mp4 file. The issue only affects NGINX if it is built with the ngx_http_mp4_module and the mp4 directive is used in the configuration file. Additionally, the attack is possible only if an attacker can trigger the processing of a specially crafted mp4 file with the ngx_http_mp4_module.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34424 | Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34424</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35123 | Uncaught exception in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.14-0, bhs-0.27 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35123</link><description>Uncaught exception in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.14-0, bhs-0.27 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38655 | Improper buffer restrictions in firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow a privileged user to potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38655</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40067 | Unchecked return value in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40067</link><description>Unchecked return value in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via physical access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42667 | Improper isolation in the Intel(R) Core(TM) Ultra Processor stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42667</link><description>Improper isolation in the Intel(R) Core(TM) Ultra Processor stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43489 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10717 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43489</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10717 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43747 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Connectivity Performance Suite software installers before version 2.0 may allow an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43747</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Connectivity Performance Suite software installers before version 2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48361 | Improper initialization in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48361</link><description>Improper initialization in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49141 | Improper isolation in some Intel(R) Processors stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49141</link><description>Improper isolation in some Intel(R) Processors stream cache mechanism may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49144 | Out of bounds read in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.15-0, bhs-0.27 may allow a privileged user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49144</link><description>Out of bounds read in OpenBMC Firmware for some Intel(R) Server Platforms before versions egs-1.15-0, bhs-0.27 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21766 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Math Kernel Library software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21766</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Math Kernel Library software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21769 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219-LM install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21769</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219-LM install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21784 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21784</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21787 | Inadequate encryption strength for some BMRA software before version 22.08 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21787</link><description>Inadequate encryption strength for some BMRA software before version 22.08 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21801 | Insufficient control flow management in some Intel(R) TDX module software before version 1.5.05.46.698 may allow a privileged user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21801</link><description>Insufficient control flow management in some Intel(R) TDX module software before version 1.5.05.46.698 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21806 | Improper conditions check in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21806</link><description>Improper conditions check in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21807 | Improper initialization in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21807</link><description>Improper initialization in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21810 | Improper input validation in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21810</link><description>Improper input validation in the Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21844 | Integer overflow in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21844</link><description>Integer overflow in firmware for some Intel(R) CSME may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21857 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Compiler software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21857</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Compiler software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22184 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Quartus(R) Prime Pro Edition Design Software before version 24.1 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22184</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Quartus(R) Prime Pro Edition Design Software before version 24.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22374 | Insufficient control flow management for some Intel(R) Xeon Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22374</link><description>Insufficient control flow management for some Intel(R) Xeon Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22376 | Uncontrolled search path element in some installation software for Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Driver Pack before version 28.3 may allow an au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22376</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some installation software for Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Driver Pack before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22378 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Unite(R) Client Extended Display Plugin software installers before version 1.1.352.157 may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22378</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Unite(R) Client Extended Display Plugin software installers before version 1.1.352.157 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23489 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.6.0.1191 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23489</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.6.0.1191 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23491 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23491</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23495 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23495</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23497 | Out-of-bounds write in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23497</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23499 | Protection mechanism failure in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23499</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 28.3 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23907 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) High Level Synthesis Compiler software before version 23.4 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23907</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) High Level Synthesis Compiler software before version 23.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23908 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Flexlm License Daemons for Intel(R) FPGA software before version v11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23908</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Flexlm License Daemons for Intel(R) FPGA software before version v11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23909 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) FPGA SDK for OpenCL(TM) software technology may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23909</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) FPGA SDK for OpenCL(TM) software technology may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23974 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) ISH software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23974</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) ISH software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23981 | Wrap-around error in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23981</link><description>Wrap-around error in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24580 | Improper conditions check in some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Max Series 1100 and 1550 products may allow a privileged user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24580</link><description>Improper conditions check in some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Max Series 1100 and 1550 products may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24853 | Incorrect behavior order in transition between executive monitor and SMI transfer monitor (STM) in some Intel(R) Processor may allow a privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24853</link><description>Incorrect behavior order in transition between executive monitor and SMI transfer monitor (STM) in some Intel(R) Processor may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24973 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24973</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24977 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) License Manager for FLEXlm product software before version 11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24977</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) License Manager for FLEXlm product software before version 11.19.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24980 | Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd, 4th, and 5th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24980</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd, 4th, and 5th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24983 | Protection mechanism failure in firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 4.4 may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24983</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters E810 Series before version 4.4 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24986 | Improper access control in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24986</link><description>Improper access control in Linux kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Controllers and Adapters before version 28.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25561 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) HID Event Filter software installers before version 2.2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25561</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) HID Event Filter software installers before version 2.2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25562 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25562</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Distribution for GDB software before version 2024.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25576 | improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) FPGA products before version 24.1 may allow a privileged user to enable escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25576</link><description>improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) FPGA products before version 24.1 may allow a privileged user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25939 | Mirrored regions with different values in 3rd Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Scalable Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25939</link><description>Mirrored regions with different values in 3rd Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Scalable Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26022 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) UEFI Integrator Tools on Aptio V for Intel(R) NUC may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26022</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) UEFI Integrator Tools on Aptio V for Intel(R) NUC may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26025 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Advisor software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26025</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Advisor software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26027 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Simics Package Manager software before version 1.8.3 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26027</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Simics Package Manager software before version 1.8.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27461 | Incorrect default permissions in software installer for Intel(R) MAS (GUI) may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27461</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in software installer for Intel(R) MAS (GUI) may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28046 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) GPA software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28046</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) GPA software before version 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28050 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics software before version 31.0.101.4824 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28050</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics software before version 31.0.101.4824 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28172 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Trace Analyzer and Collector software before version 2022.1 may allow an authenticated user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28172</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Trace Analyzer and Collector software before version 2022.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28876 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library software before version 2021.12 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28876</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library software before version 2021.12 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28887 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) IPP software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28887</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) IPP software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28947 | Improper input validation in kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST Family firmware before version 02.01.0017 may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28947</link><description>Improper input validation in kernel mode driver for some Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST Family firmware before version 02.01.0017 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28953 | Uncontrolled search path in some EMON software before version 11.44 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28953</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some EMON software before version 11.44 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29015 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) VTune(TM) Profiler software before versions 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29015</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) VTune(TM) Profiler software before versions 2024.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34163 | Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) NUC may allow a privileged user to potentially enableescalation of privilege via loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34163</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) NUC may allow a privileged user to potentially enableescalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39283 | Incomplete filtering of special elements in Intel(R) TDX module software before version TDX_1.5.01.00.592 may allow an authenticated user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39283</link><description>Incomplete filtering of special elements in Intel(R) TDX module software before version TDX_1.5.01.00.592 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7790 | DevikaAI Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7790</link><description>A stored cross site scripting vulnerabilities exists in DevikaAI from commit 6acce21fb08c3d1123ef05df6a33912bf0ee77c2 onwards via improperly decoded user input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39397 | Remote code execution vulnerability in product custom options via file upload and POST /checkout/cart/updateItemOptions/id/{id}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39397</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution by an attacker. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which can then be executed on the server. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction, but attack complexity is high and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39398 | OTP 2FA can be bruteforced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39398</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to perform brute force attacks and potentially gain unauthorized access to accounts. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction, but attack complexity is high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39399 | [Paris] Path Traversal lead to local file read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39399</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. A low-privileged attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to files and directories that are outside the restricted directory. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39400 | DOM XSS through integrations can impact other admins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39400</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow an admin attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's browser session. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, such as convincing a victim to click on a malicious link. Confidentiality and integrity impact is high as it affects other admin accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39401 | Blind RCE in Adobe Commerce support module through a malicious AC Cloud Console config for support/backup_items/code/params/output_file_extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39401</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that could lead in arbitrary code execution by an admin attacker. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39402 | Blind RCE in Adobe Commerce support module through a malicious AC Cloud Console config for `support/backup_items/db/params/output_file_extension`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39402</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that could lead in arbitrary code execution by an admin attacker. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39403 | Stored XSS through Webhook module public key configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39403</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. Confidentiality impact is high due to the attacker being able to exfiltrate sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39404 | A user without Shop Policy Parameters section privilege can alter the shop policy parameters section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39404</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39405 | A user without Send Sales Emails permission can send sales email of order to the customers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39405</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39406 | [Magento Commerce] Limited path traversal allows reading files in var/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39406</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to files and directories that are outside the restricted directory. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39407 | A user without  Credit Memos privilege can create/access credit memos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39407</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39408 | [Spain] CSRF to delete user roles at Adobe Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39408</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could allow an attacker to bypass security features and perform minor unauthorised actions on behalf of a user. The vulnerability could be exploited by tricking a victim into clicking a link or loading a page that submits a malicious request. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39409 | [Spain] CSRF to delete Gift Registry at Adobe Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39409</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could allow an attacker to bypass security features and perform minor unauthorised actions on behalf of a user. The vulnerability could be exploited by tricking a victim into clicking a link or loading a page that submits a malicious request. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39410 | [Magento B2B] CSRF allows attackers to force remove negotiation from a quote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39410</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could allow an attacker to bypass security features and perform minor unauthorised actions on behalf of a user. The vulnerability could be exploited by tricking a victim into clicking a link or loading a page that submits a malicious request. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39411 | A user without Reviews &amp;gt; By Products  permission can export the Reviews Product Report via GET /admin/reports/report_review/exportProductCsv/key/{key}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39411</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39412 | Being able to queue/create newsletter templates without appropriate permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39412</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39413 | An unauthorized user can export the Invoiced Sales Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39413</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39414 | Being able to import/export tax rates without proper privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39414</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39415 | An unauthorized user can export the Tax Sales Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39415</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39416 | Unauthorized user can export Orders Sale Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39416</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39417 | An unauthorized user can export the Shipping Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39417</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and disclose minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39418 | User without `Customers` permission can view/delete customer shopping cart, View Wishlist, Last Ordered Items, Comparison List, etc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39418</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures to view and edit low-sensitivity information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39419 | A user without ship permissions can ship the orders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39419</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p1, 2.4.6-p6, 2.4.5-p8, 2.4.4-p9 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and modify minor information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6532 | Sheet to Table Live Sync for Google Sheet &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via STWT_Sheet_Table Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6532</link><description>The Sheet to Table Live Sync for Google Sheet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's STWT_Sheet_Table shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38483 | Dell BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker with local ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38483</link><description>Dell BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41864 | Adobe Substance 3D Designer ICO Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41864</link><description>Substance3D - Designer versions 13.1.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4389 | Slider &amp;amp; Popup Builder by Depicter – Add Image Slider, Carousel Slider, Exit Intent Popup, Popup Modal, Coupon Popup, Post Slider Carousel &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4389</link><description>The Slider and Carousel slider by Depicter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the uploadFile function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41858 | Adobe InCopy has an integer overflow vulnerability when parsing SVG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41858</link><description>InCopy versions 18.5.2, 19.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41860 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Vulnerability I, when parsing PSD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41860</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41861 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability I, when parsing PSD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41861</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41862 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability II, when parsing PSD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41862</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41863 | Adobe Substance 3D Sampler Memory Corruption Out-of-Bounds-READ Vulnerability III, when parsing DNG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41863</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7732 | SECOM Dr.ID Attendance system - Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7732</link><description>Dr.ID Access Control System from SECOM does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 07:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7731 | SECOM Dr.ID Access control  system - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7731</link><description>Dr.ID Access Control System from SECOM does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7588 | Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.87 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Accordion Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7588</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion block in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.87 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7729 | CAYIN Technology CMS - Sensitive File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7729</link><description>The CAYIN Technology CMS lacks proper access control, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to download arbitrary CGI files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7728 | CAYIN Technology CMS - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7728</link><description>The specific CGI of the CAYIN Technology CMS does not properly validate user input, allowing a remote attacker with administrator privileges to inject OS commands into the specific parameter and execute them on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20082 | In Modem, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20082</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01182594; Issue ID: MSV-1529.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20083 | In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20083</link><description>In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08810810 / ALPS08805789; Issue ID: MSV-1502.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36136 | An off-by-one error in WLInfoRailService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36136</link><description>An off-by-one error in WLInfoRailService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting in a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37373 | Improper input validation in the Central Filestore in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin rights to ach...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37373</link><description>Improper input validation in the Central Filestore in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin rights to achieve RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37399 | A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37399</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting in a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38652 | Path traversal in the skin management component of Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38652</link><description>Path traversal in the skin management component of Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve denial of service via arbitrary file deletion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38653 | XXE in SmartDeviceServer in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38653</link><description>XXE in SmartDeviceServer in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7753 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System user_images direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user_images/. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7754 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System check_medicine_name.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7754</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax/check_medicine_name.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>