<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2019-25222 | Thumbnail carousel slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25222</link><description>The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2157 | Foreman: disclosure of executed commands and outputs in foreman / red hat satellite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2157</link><description>A flaw was found in Foreman/Red Hat Satellite. Improper file permissions allow low-privileged OS users to monitor and access temporary files under /var/tmp, exposing sensitive command outputs, such as /etc/shadow. This issue can lead to information disclosure and privilege escalation if exploited effectively.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2325 | WP Test Email &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2325</link><description>The WP Test Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30066 | tj-actions changed-files through 45.0.7 allows remote attackers to discover secrets by reading actions logs. (The tags v1 through v45.0.7 we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30066</link><description>tj-actions changed-files through 45.0.7 allows remote attackers to discover secrets by reading actions logs. (The tags v1 through v45.0.7 were not originally affected, but were modified by a threat actor to point at commit 0e58ed8, which contains the malicious updateFeatures code.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13497 | WordPress form builder plugin for contact forms, surveys and quizzes – Tripetto &amp;lt;= 8.0.9 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13497</link><description>The WordPress form builder plugin for contact forms, surveys and quizzes – Tripetto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via attachment uploads in all versions up to, and including, 8.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the uploaded file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1771 | Traveler &amp;lt;= 3.1.8 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion via hotel_alone_load_more_post</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1771</link><description>The Traveler theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.8 via the 'hotel_alone_load_more_post' function 'style' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1773 | Traveler &amp;lt;= 3.1.8  - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1773</link><description>The Traveler theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12336 | WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure via wf-export-all</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12336</link><description>The WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'export_all_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to expose sensitive affiliate data, including personally identifiable information (PII).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13847 | Portfolio and Projects &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13847</link><description>The Portfolio and Projects plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1667 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1667</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the wpsp_UpdateTeacher() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to update arbitrary user details including email which makes it possible to request a password reset and access arbitrary user accounts, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1668 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1668</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary user deletion due to a missing capability check on the wpsp_DeleteUser() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to delete arbitrary user accounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1669 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Authenticated (Teacher+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1669</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'addNotify' action in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1670 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Authenticated (Parent+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1670</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'cid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2163 | Zoorum Comments &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2163</link><description>The Zoorum Comments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on  the zoorum_set_options() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2164 | pixelstats &amp;lt;= 0.8.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2164</link><description>The pixelstats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'post_id' and 'sortby' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2267 | WP01 – Speed, Security, SEO consultant &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2267</link><description>The WP01 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Download in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 due to a missing capability check and insufficient restrictions on the make_archive() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download and read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1653 | Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1653</link><description>The Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7. This is due to the stm_listing_profile_edit AJAX action not having enough restriction on the user meta that can be updated. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1657 | Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Meta Update and PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1657</link><description>The Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and PHP Object Injection due to a missing capability check on the stm_listing_ajax AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update post meta data and inject PHP Objects that may be unserialized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2320 | 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt User submit improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2320</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt e84f6f5 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function submit of the file /api/blade-user/submit of the component User Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2295 | Potential iSCSI R2T PDU Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2295</link><description>EDK2 contains a vulnerability in BIOS where a user may cause an Integer Overflow or Wraparound by network means. A successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2309 | HDF5 Type Conversion Logic H5T__bit_copy heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2309</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HDF5 1.14.6 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function H5T__bit_copy of the component Type Conversion Logic. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor was contacted early about a batch of vulnerabilities. His response was "reject" without further explanation. We have not received an elaboration even after asking politely for further details. Currently we assume that the vendor wants to "dispute" the entries which is why they are flagged as such until further details become available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2310 | HDF5 Metadata Attribute Decoder H5MM_strndup heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2310</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HDF5 1.14.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function H5MM_strndup of the component Metadata Attribute Decoder. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor was contacted early about a batch of vulnerabilities. His response was "reject" without further explanation. We have not received an elaboration even after asking politely for further details. Currently we assume that the vendor wants to "dispute" the entries which is why they are flagged as such until further details become available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2308 | HDF5 Scale-Offset Filter H5Z__scaleoffset_decompress_one_byte heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2308</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in HDF5 1.14.6. This affects the function H5Z__scaleoffset_decompress_one_byte of the component Scale-Offset Filter. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor was contacted early about a batch of vulnerabilities. His response was "reject" without further explanation. We have not received an elaboration even after asking politely for further details. Currently we assume that the vendor wants to "dispute" the entries which is why they are flagged as such until further details become available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 20:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29782 | WeGIA Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored in endpoint `adicionar_tipo_docs_atendido.php` parameter `tipo`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29782</link><description>WeGIA is Web manager for charitable institutions A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the `adicionar_tipo_docs_atendido.php` endpoint in versions of the WeGIA application prior to 3.2.17. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the `tipo` parameter. The injected scripts are stored on the server and executed automatically whenever the affected page is accessed by users, posing a significant security risk. Version 3.2.17 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 19:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29771 | HtmlSanitizer vulnerable to XSS when used with contentEditable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29771</link><description>HtmlSanitizer is a client-side HTML Sanitizer. Versions prior to 2.0.3 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability when the sanitizer is used with a `contentEditable` element to set the elements `innerHTML` to a sanitized string produced by the package. If the code is particularly crafted to abuse the code beautifier, that runs AFTER sanitation. The issue is patched in version 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 19:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12019 | Arbitrary File Read via Document API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12019</link><description>The API used to interact with documents in the application contains a flaw that allows an authenticated attacker to read the contents of files on the underlying operating system. An account with ‘read’ and ‘download’ privileges on at least one existing document in the application is required to exploit the vulnerability. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an attacker to read the contents of any file available within the privileges of the system user running the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12020 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12020</link><description>There is a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) within JSP files used to control application appearance. An unauthenticated attacker could deceive a user into clicking a crafted link to trigger the vulnerability. Stealing the session cookie is not possible due to cookie security flags, however the XSS may be used to induce a victim to perform on-site requests without their knowledge.

This vulnerability only affects LogicalDOC Enterprise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12245 | Blind SQL Injection in Logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12245</link><description>Logout functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54449 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Arbitrary File Write In Document API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54449</link><description>The API used to interact with documents in the application contains two endpoints with a flaw that allows an authenticated attacker to write a file with controlled contents to an arbitrary location on the underlying file system. This can be used to facilitate RCE. An account with ‘read’ and ‘write’ privileges on at least one existing document in the application is required to exploit the vulnerability. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an attacker to run commands of their choosing on the underlying operating system of the web server running LogicalDOC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54447 | Blind SQLi in Saved Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54447</link><description>Saved search functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by authenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54448 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Automation Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54448</link><description>The Automation Scripting functionality can be exploited by attackers to run arbitrary system commands on the underlying operating system. An account with administrator privileges or that has been explicitly granted access to use Automation Scripting is needed to carry out the attack. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an attacker to run commands of their choosing on the underlying operating system of the web server running LogicalDOC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54446 | Blind SQLi in Document History</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54446</link><description>Document history functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by authenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54445 | Blind SQLi in Login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54445</link><description>Login functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29409 | File Upload vulnerability in nestjs nest v.10.3.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Content-Type header.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29409</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in nestjs nest v.10.3.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Content-Type header.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29780 | Post-Quantum Secure Feldman&amp;#x27;s Verifiable Secret Sharing has Timing Side-Channels in Matrix Operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29780</link><description>Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing provides a Python implementation of Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing (VSS) scheme. In versions 0.7.6b0 and prior, the `feldman_vss` library contains timing side-channel vulnerabilities in its matrix operations, specifically within the `_find_secure_pivot` function and potentially other parts of `_secure_matrix_solve`. These vulnerabilities are due to Python's execution model, which does not guarantee constant-time execution. An attacker with the ability to measure the execution time of these functions (e.g., through repeated calls with carefully crafted inputs) could potentially recover secret information used in the Verifiable Secret Sharing (VSS) scheme. The `_find_secure_pivot` function, used during Gaussian elimination in `_secure_matrix_solve`, attempts to find a non-zero pivot element. However, the conditional statement `if matrix[row][col] != 0 and row_random &lt; min_value:` has execution time that depends on the value of `matrix[row][col]`. This timing difference can be exploited by an attacker. The `constant_time_compare` function in this file also does not provide a constant-time guarantee. The Python implementation of matrix operations in the _find_secure_pivot and _secure_matrix_solve functions cannot guarantee constant-time execution, potentially leaking information about secret polynomial coefficients. An attacker with the ability to make precise timing measurements of these operations could potentially extract secret information through statistical analysis of execution times, though practical exploitation would require significant expertise and controlled execution environments. Successful exploitation of these timing side-channels could allow an attacker to recover secret keys or other sensitive information protected by the VSS scheme. This could lead to a complete compromise of the shared secret. As of time of publication, no patched versions of Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing exist, but other mitigations are available. As acknowledged in the library's documentation, these vulnerabilities cannot be adequately addressed in pure Python. In the short term, consider using this library only in environments where timing measurements by attackers are infeasible. In the medium term, implement your own wrappers around critical operations using constant-time libraries in languages like Rust, Go, or C. In the long term, wait for the planned Rust implementation mentioned in the library documentation that will properly address these issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26312 | SendQuick Entera devices before 11HF5 are vulnerable to CAPTCHA bypass via the captcha parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26312</link><description>SendQuick Entera devices before 11HF5 are vulnerable to CAPTCHA bypass via the captcha parameter</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29779 | Post-Quantum Secure Feldman&amp;#x27;s Verifiable Secret Sharing has Inadequate Fault Injection Countermeasures in `secure_redundant_execution`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29779</link><description>Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing provides a Python implementation of Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing (VSS) scheme. In versions 0.7.6b0 and prior, the `secure_redundant_execution` function in feldman_vss.py attempts to mitigate fault injection attacks by executing a function multiple times and comparing results. However, several critical weaknesses exist. Python's execution environment cannot guarantee true isolation between redundant executions, the constant-time comparison implementation in Python is subject to timing variations, the randomized execution order and timing provide insufficient protection against sophisticated fault attacks, and the error handling may leak timing information about partial execution results. These limitations make the protection ineffective against targeted fault injection attacks, especially from attackers with physical access to the hardware. A successful fault injection attack could allow an attacker to bypass the redundancy check mechanisms, extract secret polynomial coefficients during share generation or verification, force the acceptance of invalid shares during verification, and/or manipulate the commitment verification process to accept fraudulent commitments. This undermines the core security guarantees of the Verifiable Secret Sharing scheme. As of time of publication, no patched versions of Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing exist, but other mitigations are available. Long-term remediation requires reimplementing the security-critical functions in a lower-level language like Rust. Short-term mitigations include deploying the software in environments with physical security controls, increasing the redundancy count (from 5 to a higher number) by modifying the source code, adding external verification of cryptographic operations when possible, considering using hardware security modules (HSMs) for key operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29775 | xml-crypto Vulnerable to XML Signature Verification Bypass via DigestValue Comment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29775</link><description>xml-crypto is an XML digital signature and encryption library for Node.js. An attacker may be able to exploit a vulnerability in versions prior to 6.0.1, 3.2.1, and 2.1.6 to bypass authentication or authorization mechanisms in systems that rely on xml-crypto for verifying signed XML documents. The vulnerability allows an attacker to modify a valid signed XML message in a way that still passes signature verification checks. For example, it could be used to alter critical identity or access control attributes, enabling an attacker to escalate privileges or impersonate another user. Users of versions 6.0.0 and prior should upgrade to version 6.0.1 to receive a fix. Those who are still using v2.x or v3.x should upgrade to patched versions 2.1.6 or 3.2.1, respectively.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29384 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanMTU parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29384</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanMTU parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29385 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the cloneType parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29385</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the cloneType parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29386 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the mac parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29386</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the mac parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29387 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanSpeed parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29387</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanSpeed parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29774 | xml-crypto Vulnerable to XML Signature Verification Bypass via Multiple SignedInfo References</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29774</link><description>xml-crypto is an XML digital signature and encryption library for Node.js. An attacker may be able to exploit a vulnerability in versions prior to 6.0.1, 3.2.1, and 2.1.6 to bypass authentication or authorization mechanisms in systems that rely on xml-crypto for verifying signed XML documents. The vulnerability allows an attacker to modify a valid signed XML message in a way that still passes signature verification checks. For example, it could be used to alter critical identity or access control attributes, enabling an attacker with a valid account to escalate privileges or impersonate another user. Users of versions 6.0.0 and prior should upgrade to version 6.0.1 to receive a fix. Those who are still using v2.x or v3.x should upgrade to patched versions 2.1.6 or 3.2.1, respectively.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27606 | Element Android PIN autologout bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27606</link><description>Element Android is an Android Matrix Client provided by Element. Element Android up to version 1.6.32 can, under certain circumstances, fail to logout the user if they input the wrong PIN more than the configured amount of times. An attacker with physical access to a device can exploit this to guess the PIN. Version 1.6.34 solves the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55594 | An improper handling of syntactically invalid structure in Fortinet FortiWeb at least vesrions 7.4.0 through 7.4.6 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55594</link><description>An improper handling of syntactically invalid structure in Fortinet FortiWeb at least vesrions 7.4.0 through 7.4.6 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.10 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via HTTP/S crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1888 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting in Aperio Eslide Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1888</link><description>The Leica Web Viewer within the Aperio Eslide Manager Application is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting (XSS). An authenticated user can access the slides within a project and injecting malicious JavaScript into the "memo" field. The memo field has a hover over action that will display a Microsoft Tool Tip which a user can use to quickly view the memo associated with the slide and execute the JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-29059 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in FortiWeb version 7.0.1 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29059</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in FortiWeb version 7.0.1 and below, 6.4.2 and below, 6.3.20 and below, 6.2.7 and below may allow a privileged attacker to execute SQL commands over the log database via specifically crafted strings parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33300 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiNAC 7.2.1 and earlier, 9.4.3 and earl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33300</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiNAC 7.2.1 and earlier, 9.4.3 and earlier allows attacker a limited, unauthorized file access via specifically crafted request in inter-server  communication port.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45588 | An external control of file name or path vulnerability [CWE-73] in  FortiClientMac version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.10 and below install...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45588</link><description>An external control of file name or path vulnerability [CWE-73] in  FortiClientMac version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.10 and below installer may allow a local attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via writing a malicious configuration file in /tmp before starting the installation process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48785 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiNAC-F version 7.2.4 and below may allow a remote and unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48785</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiNAC-F version 7.2.4 and below may allow a remote and unauthenticated attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle attack on the HTTPS communication channel between the FortiOS device, an inventory, and FortiNAC-F.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40585 | An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerabilities [CWE-532] in FortiManager version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40585</link><description>An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerabilities [CWE-532] in FortiManager version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, version 6.4.12 and below, version 6.2.11 and below and FortiAnalyzer version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, version 6.4.12 and below, version 6.2.11 and below eventlog may allow any low privileged user with access to event log section to retrieve certificate private key and encrypted password logged as system log.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25871 | An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25871</link><description>An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25873 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Open Panel OpenAdmin v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Change Root...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25873</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Open Panel OpenAdmin v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Change Root Password function</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25872 | An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25872</link><description>An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40590 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiPortal version 7.4.0, version 7.2.4 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40590</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiPortal version 7.4.0, version 7.2.4 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, version 6.0.15 and below when connecting to a FortiManager device, a FortiAnalyzer device, or an SMTP server may allow an unauthenticated attacker in a Man-in-the-Middle position to intercept on and tamper with the encrypted communication channel established between the FortiPortal and those endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46662 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.4.1 through 7.4.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46662</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.4.1 through 7.4.3, FortiManager Cloud versions 7.4.1 through 7.4.3 allows attacker to escalation of privilege via specifically crafted packets</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47573 | An improper validation of integrity check value vulnerability [CWE-354] in FortiNDR version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.1 and below, versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47573</link><description>An improper validation of integrity check value vulnerability [CWE-354] in FortiNDR version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.1 and below, version 7.1.1 and below, version 7.0.6 and below may allow an authenticated attacker with at least Read/Write permission on system maintenance to install a corrupted firmware image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45638 | IBM QRadar EDR information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45638</link><description>IBM Security QRadar 3.12 EDR stores user credentials in plain text which can be read by a local privileged user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45643 | IBM QRadar EDR information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45643</link><description>IBM Security QRadar 3.12 EDR uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt sensitive credential information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52927 | netfilter: allow exp not to be removed in nf_ct_find_expectation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52927</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: allow exp not to be removed in nf_ct_find_expectation

Currently nf_conntrack_in() calling nf_ct_find_expectation() will
remove the exp from the hash table. However, in some scenario, we
expect the exp not to be removed when the created ct will not be
confirmed, like in OVS and TC conntrack in the following patches.

This patch allows exp not to be removed by setting IPS_CONFIRMED
in the status of the tmpl.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29029 | Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formSetSpeedWan function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29029</link><description>Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formSetSpeedWan function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29030 | Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29030</link><description>Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29031 | Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the fromAddressNat function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29031</link><description>Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the fromAddressNat function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29032 | Tenda AC9 v15.03.05.19(6318) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29032</link><description>Tenda AC9 v15.03.05.19(6318) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2268 | HP LaserJet MFP M232-M237 Printer Series - Potential Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2268</link><description>The HP LaserJet MFP M232-M237 Printer Series may be vulnerable to a denial of service attack when a specially crafted request message is sent via Internet Printing Protocol (IPP).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29776 | Azle calling `setTimer` causes infinite loop of timers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29776</link><description>Azle is a WebAssembly runtime for TypeScript and JavaScript on ICP. Calling `setTimer` in Azle versions `0.27.0`, `0.28.0`, and `0.29.0` causes an immediate infinite loop of timers to be executed on the canister, each timer attempting to clean up the global state of the previous timer. The infinite loop will occur with any valid invocation of `setTimer`. The problem has been fixed as of Azle version `0.30.0`. As a workaround, if a canister is caught in this infinite loop after calling `setTimer`, the canister can be upgraded and the timers will all be cleared, thus ending the loop.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2000 | Qiskit SDK code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2000</link><description>A maliciously crafted QPY file can potential execute arbitrary-code embedded in the payload without privilege escalation when deserialising QPY formats &lt; 13. A python process calling Qiskit 0.18.0 through 1.4.1's `qiskit.qpy.load()` function could potentially execute any arbitrary Python code embedded in the correct place in the binary file as part of specially constructed payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26626 | GLPI Inventory Plugin vulnerable to reflective Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26626</link><description>The GLPI Inventory Plugin handles various types of tasks for GLPI agents for the GLPI asset and IT management software package. Versions prior to 1.5.0 are vulnerable to reflective cross-site scripting, which may lead to executing javascript code. Version 1.5.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27593 | RCE due to Device Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27593</link><description>The product can be used to distribute malicious code using SDD Device Drivers due to missing download verification checks, leading to code execution on target systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27594 | Unencrypted transmission of password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27594</link><description>The device uses an unencrypted, proprietary protocol for communication. Through this protocol, configuration data is transmitted and device authentication is performed. An attacker can thereby intercept the authentication hash and use it to log into the device using a pass-the-hash attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27595 | Weak hashing alghrythm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27595</link><description>The device uses a weak hashing alghorithm to create the password hash. Hence, a matching password can be easily calculated by an attacker. This impacts the security and the integrity of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2304 | Camaleon CMS Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2304</link><description>A Privilege Escalation through a Mass Assignment exists in Camaleon CMS

When a user wishes to change his password, the 'updated_ajax' method of the UsersController is called. The vulnerability stems from the use of the dangerous permit! method, which allows all parameters to pass through without any filtering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 12:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12810 | JobCareer | Job Board Responsive WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Multiple Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12810</link><description>The JobCareer | Job Board Responsive WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability checks on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files, generate backups, restore backups, update theme options, and reset theme options to default settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13771 | Civi - Job Board &amp;amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authentication Bypass via Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13771</link><description>The Civi - Job Board &amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to a lack of user validation before changing a password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the password of arbitrary users, including administrators, if the attacker knows the username of the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13772 | Civi - Job Board &amp;amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authentication Bypass via Non-Randomized Password for SSO Accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13772</link><description>The Civi - Job Board &amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to a lack of randomization of a password created during Single Sign-On via Google or Facebook. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the password of arbitrary Candidate-level users if the attacker knows the username assigned to the victim during account creation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13773 | Civi - Job Board &amp;amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13773</link><description>The Civi - Job Board &amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 via hard-coded credentials. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including LinkedIn client and secret keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2232 | Realteo - Real Estate Plugin by Purethemes &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authentication Bypass via &amp;#x27;do_register_user&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2232</link><description>The Realteo - Real Estate Plugin by Purethemes plugin for WordPress, used by the Findeo Theme, is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8. This is due to insufficient role restrictions in the 'do_register_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an account with the Administrator role.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26006 | An improper neutralization of input during web page Generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS version 7.4.3 and below, version 7.2.7 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26006</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page Generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS version 7.4.3 and below, version 7.2.7 and below, version 7.0.13 and below and FortiProxy version 7.4.3 and below, version 7.2.9 and below, version 7.0.16 and below web SSL VPN UI may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to perform a Cross-Site Scripting attack via a malicious samba server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8176 | Libexpat: expat: improper restriction of xml entity expansion depth in libexpat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8176</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability exists in the libexpat library due to the way it handles recursive entity expansion in XML documents. When parsing an XML document with deeply nested entity references, libexpat can be forced to recurse indefinitely, exhausting the stack space and causing a crash. This issue could lead to denial of service (DoS) or, in some cases, exploitable memory corruption, depending on the environment and library usage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1507 | ShareThis Dashboard for Google Analytics &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Feature Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1507</link><description>The ShareThis Dashboard for Google Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_actions() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable all features.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13321 | AnalyticsWP &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13321</link><description>The AnalyticsWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'custom_sql' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient authorization checks on the handle_get_stats() function.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 07:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13407 | Omnipress &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13407</link><description>The Omnipress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 via the megamenu block due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 07:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1526 | DethemeKit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1526</link><description>The DethemeKit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the De Product Display Widget (countdown feature) in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 07:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13824 | CiyaShop - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 4.19.0 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13824</link><description>The CiyaShop - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.19.0 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'add_ciyashop_wishlist' and 'ciyashop_get_compare' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2221 | WPCOM Member &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Unauthenticated Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2221</link><description>The WPCOM Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘user_phone’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13376 | Industrial &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13376</link><description>The Industrial theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the _ajax_get_total_content_import_items() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13913 | InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.83 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13913</link><description>The InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.0.83. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the '/migrate/templates/main.php' file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0952 | Eco Nature - Environment &amp;amp; Ecology WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0952</link><description>The Eco Nature - Environment &amp; Ecology WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'cmsmasters_hide_admin_notice' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'hide' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1764 | LoginPress &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1764</link><description>The LoginPress | wp-login Custom Login Page Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'custom_plugin_set_option' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site. The 'WPBRIGADE_SDK__DEV_MODE' constant must be set to 'true' to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2103 | SoundRise Music &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2103</link><description>The SoundRise Music plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on theironMusic_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2289 | Zegen - Church WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Options Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2289</link><description>The Zegen - Church WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several AJAX endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to import, export, and update theme options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11283 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Authentication Bypass to Candidate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11283</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This is due to wp_ajax_google_api_login_callback function not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access arbitrary candidate accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11284 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Reset/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11284</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 6.9. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password through the account_settings_save_callback() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11285 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Email Update/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11285</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email via the account_settings_callback() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11286 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11286</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them through the cs_parse_request() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to to log in to any user's account, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0955 | VidoRev Extensions &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.9.9.9.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Youtube Video Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0955</link><description>The VidoRev Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'vidorev_import_single_video' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.9.9.9.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import arbitrary youtube videos.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1285 | Resido - Real Estate WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery and API Key Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1285</link><description>The Resido - Real Estate WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the delete_api_key and save_api_key AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to issue requests to internal services and update API key details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1528 | Search and filter pro &amp;lt;= 2.5.19 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Meta Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1528</link><description>The Search &amp; Filter Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_meta_values' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the values of arbitrary post meta.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2056 | WP Ghost &amp;lt;= 5.4.01 - Unauthenticated Limited File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2056</link><description>The WP Ghost (Hide My WP Ghost) – Security &amp; Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.01 via the showFile function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of specific file types on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2166 | CM FAQ  – Simplify support with an intuitive FAQ management tool &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2166</link><description>The CM FAQ  – Simplify support with an intuitive FAQ management tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26163 | CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the CPF parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26163</link><description>CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the CPF parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30022 | CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the DATANASC parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30022</link><description>CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the DATANASC parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55549 | xsltGetInheritedNsList in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free issue related to exclusion of result prefixes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55549</link><description>xsltGetInheritedNsList in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free issue related to exclusion of result prefixes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24855 | numbers.c in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free because, in nested XPath evaluations, an XPath context node can be modified but neve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24855</link><description>numbers.c in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free because, in nested XPath evaluations, an XPath context node can be modified but never restored. This is related to xsltNumberFormatGetValue, xsltEvalXPathPredicate, xsltEvalXPathStringNs, and xsltComputeSortResultInternal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55060 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component index.php of Rafed CMS Website v1.44 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55060</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component index.php of Rafed CMS Website v1.44 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27496 | Snowflake JDBC Driver client-side encryption key in DEBUG logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27496</link><description>Snowflake, a platform for using artificial intelligence in the context of cloud computing, has a vulnerability in the Snowflake JDBC driver ("Driver") in versions 3.0.13 through 3.23.0 of the driver. When the logging level was set to DEBUG, the Driver would log locally the client-side encryption master key of the target stage during the execution of GET/PUT commands. This key by itself does not grant access to any sensitive data without additional access authorizations,  and is not logged server-side by Snowflake. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.23.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2229 | Philips Intellispace Cardiovascular (ISCV) Use of Weak Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2229</link><description>A token is created using the username, current date/time, and a fixed 
AES-128 encryption key, which is the same across all installations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2230 | Philips Intellispace Cardiovascular (ISCV) Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2230</link><description>A flaw exists in the Windows login flow where an AuthContext token can 
be exploited for replay attacks and authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25363 | An authenticated stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in The Plugin People Enterprise Mail Handler for Jira Data Center (JEMH) be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25363</link><description>An authenticated stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in The Plugin People Enterprise Mail Handler for Jira Data Center (JEMH) before v4.1.69-dc allows attackers with Administrator privileges to execute arbitrary Javascript in context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the HTML field of a template.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25598 | Incorrect access control in the scheduled tasks console of Inova Logic CUSTOMER MONITOR (CM) v3.1.757.1 allows attackers to escalate privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25598</link><description>Incorrect access control in the scheduled tasks console of Inova Logic CUSTOMER MONITOR (CM) v3.1.757.1 allows attackers to escalate privileges via placing a crafted executable into a scheduled task.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30143 | A path traversal vulnerability in HCL AppScan Traffic Recorder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30143</link><description>HCL AppScan Traffic Recorder fails to adequately neutralize special characters within the filename, potentially allowing it to resolve to a location beyond the restricted directory. Potential exploits can completely disrupt or takeover the application or the computer where the application is running.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24053 | Microsoft Dataverse Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24053</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53406 | Espressif Esp idf v5.3.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions resulting in Authentication bypass. In the reconnection phase, the device reu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53406</link><description>Espressif Esp idf v5.3.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions resulting in Authentication bypass. In the reconnection phase, the device reuses the session key from a previous connection session, creating an opportunity for attackers to execute security bypass attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29768 | Vim vulnerable to potential data loss with zip.vim and special crafted zip files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29768</link><description>Vim, a text editor, is vulnerable to potential data loss with zip.vim and special crafted zip files in versions prior to 9.1.1198. The impact is medium because a user must be made to view such an archive with Vim and then press 'x' on such a strange filename. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.1198.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29773 | Froxlor allows Multiple Accounts to Share the Same Email Address Leading to Potential Privilege Escalation or Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29773</link><description>Froxlor is open-source server administration software. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.2.6 allows users (such as resellers or customers) to create accounts with the same email address as an existing account. This creates potential issues with account identification and security. This vulnerability can be exploited by authenticated users (e.g., reseller, customer) who can create accounts with the same email address that has already been used by another account, such as the admin. The attack vector is email-based, as the system does not prevent multiple accounts from registering the same email address, leading to possible conflicts and security issues. Version 2.2.6 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2081 | Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 are vulnerable to an attacker impersona...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2081</link><description>Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 are vulnerable to an attacker impersonating the web application service and mislead victim clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27107 | Integrated Scripting vulnerable to arbitrary code execution via Java reflection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27107</link><description>Integrated Scripting is a tool for creating scripts for handling complex operations in Integrated Dynamics. Minecraft users who use Integrated Scripting prior to versions 1.21.1-1.0.17, 1.21.4-1.0.9-254, 1.20.1-1.0.13, and 1.19.2-1.0.10 may be vulnerable to arbitrary code execution. By using Java reflection on a thrown exception object it's possible to escape the JavaScript sandbox for IntegratedScripting's Variable Cards, and leverage that to construct arbitrary Java classes and invoke arbitrary Java methods.
This vulnerability allows for execution of arbitrary Java methods, and by extension arbitrary native code e.g. from `java.lang.Runtime.exec`, on the Minecraft server by any player with the ability to create and use an IntegratedScripting Variable Card. Versions 1.21.1-1.0.17, 1.21.4-1.0.9-254, 1.20.1-1.0.13, and 1.19.2-1.0.10 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2079 | Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain a hard coded secret key. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2079</link><description>Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain a hard coded secret key. This could allow an attacker to generate valid JWT (JSON Web Token) sessions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2080 | Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain an exposed web management servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2080</link><description>Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain an exposed web management service that could allow an attacker to bypass authentication measures and gain controls over utilities within the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12858 | Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12858</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 Version 2.1.0.16 and prior lacks proper 
validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a 
fixed-length heap-based buffer. If a target visits a malicious page or 
opens a malicious file an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to 
execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1427 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1427</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Uninitialized Variable vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1428 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1428</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1429 | MODEL File Parsing Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1429</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Heap-Based Overflow vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1430 | SLDPRT File Parsing Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1430</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1431 | SLDPRT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1431</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1432 | 3DM File Parsing Use-After-Free Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1432</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1433 | MODEL File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1433</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1649 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1649</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Uninitialized Variable vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1650 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1650</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Uninitialized Variable vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1651 | MODEL File Parsing Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1651</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Heap-Based Overflow vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1652 | MODEL File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1652</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27138 | DataEase has an improper authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27138</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, there is a flaw in the authentication in the io.dataease.auth.filter.TokenFilter class, which may cause the risk of unauthorized access. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.6. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9042 | This CVE affects only Windows worker nodes. Your worker node is vulnerable to this issue if it is running one of the affected versions liste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9042</link><description>This CVE affects only Windows worker nodes. Your worker node is vulnerable to this issue if it is running one of the affected versions listed below.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1767 | This CVE only affects Kubernetes clusters that utilize the in-tree gitRepo volume to clone git repositories from other pods within the same ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1767</link><description>This CVE only affects Kubernetes clusters that utilize the in-tree gitRepo volume to clone git repositories from other pods within the same node. Since the in-tree gitRepo volume feature has been deprecated and will not receive security updates upstream, any cluster still using this feature remains vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24974 | DataEase Mysql JDBC Connection Parameters Not Being Verified Leads to Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24974</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, authenticated users can read and deserialize arbitrary files through the background JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.6. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27103 | Dataease Mysql JDBC Connection Parameters Not Being Verified Leads to Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability​</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27103</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, a bypass for the patch for CVE-2024-55953 allows authenticated users to read and deserialize arbitrary files through the background JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.6. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2284 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server Access of Uninitialized Pointer DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2284</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the "GetWebLoginCredentials" function in "Sante PACS Server.exe".</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2263 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2263</link><description>During login to the web server in "Sante PACS Server.exe", OpenSSL function EVP_DecryptUpdate is called to decrypt the username and password. A fixed 0x80-byte stack-based buffer is passed to the function as the output buffer. A stack-based buffer overflow exists if a long encrypted username or password is supplied by an unauthenticated remote attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2264 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server Path Traversal Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2264</link><description>A Path Traversal Information Disclosure vulnerability exists in "Sante PACS Server.exe". An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit it to download arbitrary files on the disk drive where the application is installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2265 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server HTTP.db SHA1 Hash Truncation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2265</link><description>The password of a web user in "Sante PACS Server.exe" is zero-padded to 0x2000 bytes, SHA1-hashed, base64-encoded, and stored in the USER table in the SQLite database HTTP.db. However, the number of hash bytes encoded and stored is truncated if the hash contains a zero byte</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28011 | A SQL Injection was found in loginsystem/change-password.php in PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System v3.3 allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28011</link><description>A SQL Injection was found in loginsystem/change-password.php in PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System v3.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the currentpassword POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28010 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in MODX prior to 3.1.0. The vulnerability allows authenticated users to uploa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28010</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in MODX prior to 3.1.0. The vulnerability allows authenticated users to upload SVG files containing malicious JavaScript code as profile images, which gets executed in victims' browsers when viewing the profile image.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28015 | A HTML Injection vulnerability was found in loginsystem/edit-profile.php of the PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28015</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was found in loginsystem/edit-profile.php of the PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System V3.3. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary HTML code via the fname, lname, and contact parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57062 | An issue in SoundCloud IOS application v.7.65.2 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the sess...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57062</link><description>An issue in SoundCloud IOS application v.7.65.2 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the session handling component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25625 | FS Inc S3150 8T2F Switch s3150-8t2f-switch-fsos-220d_118101 has a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the web management inte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25625</link><description>FS Inc S3150 8T2F Switch s3150-8t2f-switch-fsos-220d_118101 has a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the web management interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55198 | User Enumeration via Discrepancies in Error Messages in the Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 password recovery functionality which allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55198</link><description>User Enumeration via Discrepancies in Error Messages in the Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 password recovery functionality which allows a remote attacker to enumerate users through discrepancies in the responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22880 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zadarma Zadarma extension v.1.0.11 allows a remote attacker to execute a arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22880</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zadarma Zadarma extension v.1.0.11 allows a remote attacker to execute a arbitrary code via a crafted script to the webchat component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29357 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the startIp and endIp parameters at /goform/SetPptpServ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29357</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the startIp and endIp parameters at /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57348 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in PecanProject pecan v.1.7.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57348</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in PecanProject pecan v.1.7.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the crafted payload to the hostname, sitegroupid, lat, lon and sitename parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29358 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the firewallEn parameter at /goform/SetFirewallCfg. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29358</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the firewallEn parameter at /goform/SetFirewallCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29359 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter at /goform/saveParentControlInfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29359</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter at /goform/saveParentControlInfo. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29360 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the time and timeZone parameters at /goform/SetSysTimeC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29360</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the time and timeZone parameters at /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28803 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Italtel S.p.A. i-MCS NFV v.12.1.0-20211215 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28803</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Italtel S.p.A. i-MCS NFV v.12.1.0-20211215 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML into HTTP/POST parameter</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29361 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29361</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29362 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/setPptpUserList. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29362</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/setPptpUserList. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29363 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to buffer overflow via the schedStartTime and schedEndTime parameters at /gofo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29363</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to buffer overflow via the schedStartTime and schedEndTime parameters at /goform/saveParentControlInfo. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2278 | Improper access control in temporary access requests and checkout requests endpoints in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2278</link><description>Improper access control in temporary access requests and checkout requests endpoints in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an authenticated user to access information about these requests via a known request ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2280 | Improper access control in web extension restriction feature in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an authenticated user to byp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2280</link><description>Improper access control in web extension restriction feature in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the browser extension restriction feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10942 | All in One WP Migration &amp;lt;= 7.89 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10942</link><description>The All-in-One WP Migration and Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.89 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'replace_serialized_values' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must export and restore a backup in order to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1635 | Exposure of sensitive information in hub data source export feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and earlier on Windows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1635</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in hub data source export feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and earlier on Windows allows a user exporting a hub data source to include his authenticated session in the export due to faulty business logic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1636 | Exposure of sensitive information in My Personnal Credentials password history component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1636</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in My Personnal Credentials password history component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user to inadvertently leak the My Personnal Credentials in a shared vault via the clear history feature due to faulty business logic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2277 | Exposure of password in web-based SSH authentication component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows a user to unadvertently le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2277</link><description>Exposure of password in web-based SSH authentication component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows a user to unadvertently leak his SSH password due to missing password masking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21104 | Dell NetWorker, 19.11.0.3 and below versions, contain(s) an Open Redirect Vulnerability in NMC. An unauthenticated attacker with remoter acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21104</link><description>Dell NetWorker, 19.11.0.3 and below versions, contain(s) an Open Redirect Vulnerability in NMC. An unauthenticated attacker with remoter access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a targeted application user being redirected to arbitrary web URLs. The vulnerability could be leveraged by attackers to conduct phishing attacks that cause users to divulge sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29996 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29996</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to improper implementation of OTP verification mechanism in its API based login. A remote attacker with valid credentials could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API request URL/payload. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) for other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29997 | Improper Access Control Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29997</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to improper authorization checks on certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API request URL to gain unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29998 | No Rate Limiting Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29998</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to missing rate limiting on OTP requests in an API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoint which could lead to the OTP bombing/flooding on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29994 | Improper Authentication Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29994</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to improper authentication check at the API endpoint. An unauthenticated remote attacker with a valid login ID could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API input parameters through API request URL/payload leading to unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29995 | Account Takeover Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29995</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to a weak password-reset mechanism implemented at API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker with a valid login ID could exploit this vulnerability through vulnerable API endpoint which could lead to account takeover of targeted users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25175 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap V2401 (All versions &lt; V2401.0003), Simcenter Femap V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0002)....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25175</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap V2401 (All versions &lt; V2401.0003), Simcenter Femap V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0002). The affected application contains a memory corruption vulnerability while  parsing specially crafted .NEU files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-25443)</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 09:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1785 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.08 - Authenticated (Author+) Path Traversal to Limited File Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1785</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.08 via the 'wpdm_newfile' action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to overwrite select file types outside of the originally intended directory, which may cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 07:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1119 | Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1119</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.8.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 07:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2271 | IDOR in Issuetrak NewAuditID parameter via Inv_PopTrakXShow.asp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2271</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Issuetrak v17.2.2 and prior that allows a low-privileged user to access audit results of other users by exploiting an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Issuetrak audit component. The vulnerability enables unauthorized access to sensitive information, including user details, network and hardware information, installed programs, running processes, drives, and printers. Due to improper access controls, an attacker can retrieve audit data belonging to other users, potentially leading to unauthorized data exposure, privacy violations, and security risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13884 | Limit Bio &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13884</link><description>The Limit Bio WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13885 | WP E Customers &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13885</link><description>The WP e-Customers Beta WordPress plugin through 0.0.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13891 | Schedule &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13891</link><description>The Schedule WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7296 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7296</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.5 prior to 17.7.7, 17.8 prior to 17.8.5, and 17.9 prior to 17.9.2  which allowed a user with a custom permission to approve pending membership requests beyond the maximum number of allowed users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1257 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1257</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting with 12.3 before 17.7.7, 17.8 prior to 17.8.5, and 17.9 prior to 17.9.2. A vulnerability in certain GitLab instances could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service condition by manipulating specific API inputs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1401 | WP Click Info &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1401</link><description>The WP Click Info WordPress plugin through 2.7.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1436 | Limit Bio &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1436</link><description>The Limit Bio WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check when updating its settings, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1486 | WoWPth &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1486</link><description>The WoWPth WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1487 | WoWPth &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1487</link><description>The WoWPth WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12380 | Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12380</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 11.5 before 17.7.7, all versions starting from 17.8 before 17.8.5, all versions starting from 17.9 before 17.9.2. Certain user inputs in repository mirroring settings could potentially expose sensitive authentication information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13054 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13054</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.7.7, 17.8 prior to 17.8.5, and 17.9 prior to 17.9.2. where a denial of service vulnerability could allow an attacker to cause a system reboot under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8402 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (&amp;#x27;Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8402</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 17.2 before 17.7.7, all versions starting from 17.8 before 17.8.5, all versions starting from 17.9 before 17.9.2. An input validation issue in the Google Cloud IAM integration feature could have enabled a Maintainer to introduce malicious code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0652 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0652</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 17.7.7, all versions starting from 17.8 before 17.8.5, all versions starting from 17.9 before 17.9.2 could allow unauthorized users to access confidential information intended for internal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36843 | The implementation of EdDSA in EdDSA-Java (aka ed25519-java) through 0.3.0 exhibits signature malleability and does not satisfy the SUF-CMA ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36843</link><description>The implementation of EdDSA in EdDSA-Java (aka ed25519-java) through 0.3.0 exhibits signature malleability and does not satisfy the SUF-CMA (Strong Existential Unforgeability under Chosen Message Attacks) property. This allows attackers to create new valid signatures different from previous signatures for a known message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1503 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 9.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1503</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Roundup Recipe Name field in all versions up to, and including, 9.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1561 | AppPresser – Mobile App Framework &amp;lt;= 4.4.10 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1561</link><description>The AppPresser – Mobile App Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages when logging is enabled that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2104 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Publication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2104</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post publication due to insufficient validation on the pagelayer_save_content() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to bypass post moderation and publish posts to the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13887 | Business Directory Plugin - Easy Listing Directories for WordPress &amp;lt;= 6.4.14 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Listing Arbitrary Image Addition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13887</link><description>The Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.14 via the 'ajax_listing_submit_image_upload' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary images to listings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2250 | WordPress Report Brute Force Attacks and Login Protection ReportAttacks Plugins &amp;lt;= 2.32 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2250</link><description>The WordPress Report Brute Force Attacks and Login Protection ReportAttacks Plugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.32 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13703 | CRM and Lead Management by vcita &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Susbcriber+) Widget Toggle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13703</link><description>The CRM and Lead Management by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the vcita_ajax_toggle_ae() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enable and disable plugin widgets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1559 | CC-IMG-Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1559</link><description>The CC-IMG-Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'img' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2106 | Arielbrailovsky-Viralad &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2106</link><description>The ArielBrailovsky-ViralAd plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'text' and 'id' parameters of the limpia() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This only appears to be exploitable on very old versions of WordPress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2107 | Arielbrailovsky-Viralad &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2107</link><description>The ArielBrailovsky-ViralAd plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the printResultAndDie() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This only appears to be exploitable on very old versions of WordPress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>