<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:26:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-13544 | ashraf-kabir travel-agency customer_register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13544</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ashraf-kabir travel-agency up to 1f25aa03544bc5fb7a9e846f8a7879cecdb0cad3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /customer_register.php. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13526 | OneClick Chat to Order &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13526</link><description>The OneClick Chat to Order plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 via the 'wa_order_thank_you_override' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view sensitive customer information including names, email addresses, phone numbers, billing/shipping addresses, order contents, and payment methods by simply changing the order ID in the URL.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13136 | GSheetConnector For Ninja Forms &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) System Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13136</link><description>The GSheetConnector For Ninja Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'njform-google-sheet-config ' page in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve information about the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 08:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13318 | Booking Calendar Contact Form &amp;lt;= 1.2.60 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Booking Confirmation via &amp;#x27;dex_bccf_ipn&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13318</link><description>The Booking Calendar Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.60. This is due to missing authorization checks and payment verification in the `dex_bccf_check_IPN_verification` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily confirm bookings and bypass payment requirements via the 'dex_bccf_ipn' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 08:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12752 | Subscriptions &amp;amp; Memberships for PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Unauthenticated Fake Payment Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12752</link><description>The Subscriptions &amp; Memberships for PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to fake payment creation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying the authenticity of an IPN request. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create fake payment entries that have not actually occurred.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 07:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12877 | IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System &amp;lt;= 2.1.15 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12877</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification od data due to a missing capability check on the panding_blood_request_action() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.15. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 07:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13317 | Appointment Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.3.96 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Booking Confirmation via &amp;#x27;cpabc_ipncheck&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13317</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.96. This is due to the plugin exposing an unauthenticated booking processing endpoint (cpabc_appointments_check_IPN_verification) that trusts attacker-supplied payment notifications without verifying their origin, authenticity, or requiring proper authorization checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily confirm bookings and insert them into the live calendar via the 'cpabc_ipncheck' parameter, triggering administrative and customer notification emails and disrupting operations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 07:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13384 | CP Contact Form with PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.3.56 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Payment Confirmation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13384</link><description>The CP Contact Form with PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.56. This is due to the plugin exposing an unauthenticated IPN-like endpoint (via the 'cp_contactformpp_ipncheck' query parameter) that processes payment confirmations without any authentication, nonce verification, or PayPal IPN signature validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to mark form submissions as paid without making actual payments by sending forged payment notification requests with arbitrary POST data (payment_status, txn_id, payer_email).</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 07:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11186 | Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Compliance for GDPR / CCPA &amp;lt;= 2.5.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11186</link><description>The Cookie Notice &amp; Compliance for GDPR / CCPA plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cookies_accepted shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 05:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12889 | TLS 1.2 Client Can Downgrade Digest Used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12889</link><description>With TLS 1.2 connections a client can use any digest, specifically a weaker digest that is supported, rather than those in the CertificateRequest.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11932 | Timing Side-Channel in PSK Binder Verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11932</link><description>The server previously verified the TLS 1.3 PSK binder using a non-constant time method which could potentially leak information about the PSK binder</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11931 | Integer Underflow Leads to Out-of-Bounds Access in XChaCha20-Poly1305 Decrypt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11931</link><description>Integer Underflow Leads to Out-of-Bounds Access in XChaCha20-Poly1305 Decrypt. This issue is hit specifically with a call to the function wc_XChaCha20Poly1305_Decrypt() which is not used with TLS connections, only from direct calls from an application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12888 | Constant Time Issue with Xtensa-based ESP32 and X22519</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12888</link><description>Vulnerability in X25519 constant-time cryptographic implementations due to timing side channels introduced by compiler optimizations and CPU architecture limitations, specifically with the Xtensa-based ESP32 chips. If targeting Xtensa it is recommended to use the low memory implementations of X25519, which is now turned on as the default for Xtensa.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11936 | Potential DoS Vulnerability through Multiple KeyShareEntry with Same Group in TLS 1.3 ClientHello</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11936</link><description>Improper input validation in the TLS 1.3 KeyShareEntry parsing in wolfSSL v5.8.2 on multiple platforms allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service by sending a crafted ClientHello message containing duplicate KeyShareEntry values for the same supported group, leading to excessive CPU and memory consumption during ClientHello processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11933 | DoS Vulnerability in wolfSSL TLS 1.3 CKS Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11933</link><description>Improper Input Validation in the TLS 1.3 CKS extension parsing in wolfSSL 5.8.2 and earlier on multiple platforms allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to potentially cause a denial-of-service via a crafted ClientHello message with duplicate CKS extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11934 | Improper Validation of Signature Algorithm Used in TLS 1.3 CertificateVerify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11934</link><description>Improper input validation in the TLS 1.3 CertificateVerify signature algorithm negotiation in wolfSSL 5.8.2 and earlier on multiple platforms allows for downgrading the signature algorithm used. For example when a client sends ECDSA P521 as the supported signature algorithm the server previously could respond as ECDSA P256 being the accepted signature algorithm and the connection would continue with using ECDSA P256, if the client supports ECDSA P256.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65946 | Roo Code is Vulnerable to Potential Remote Code Execution via zsh Command Validation Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65946</link><description>Roo Code is an AI-powered autonomous coding agent that lives in users' editors. Prior to version 3.26.7, Due to an error in validation it was possible for Roo to automatically execute commands that did not match the allow list prefixes. This issue has been patched in version 3.26.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65947 | thread-amount is Vulnerable to Resource Exhaustion (Memory and Handle Leaks) on Windows and macOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65947</link><description>thread-amount is a tool that gets the amount of threads in the current process. Prior to version 0.2.2, there are resource leaks when querying thread counts on Windows and Apple platforms. In Windows platforms, the thread_amount function calls CreateToolhelp32Snapshot but fails to close the returned HANDLE using CloseHandle. Repeated calls to this function will cause the handle count of the process to grow indefinitely, eventually leading to system instability or process termination when the handle limit is reached. In Apple platforms, the thread_amount function calls task_threads (via Mach kernel APIs) which allocates memory for the thread list. The function fails to deallocate this memory using vm_deallocate. Repeated calls will result in a steady memory leak, eventually causing the process to be killed by the OOM (Out of Memory) killer. This issue has been patched in version 0.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11935 | Forward Secrecy Violation in WolfSSL TLS 1.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11935</link><description>With TLS 1.3 pre-shared key (PSK) a malicious or faulty server could ignore the request for PFS (perfect forward secrecy) and the client would continue on with the connection using PSK without PFS. This happened when a server responded to a ClientHello containing psk_dhe_ke without a key_share extension. The re-use of an authenticated PSK connection that on the clients side unexpectedly did not have PFS, reduces the security of the connection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65111 | SpiceDB&amp;#x27;s LookupResources with Multiple Entrypoints across Different Definitions Can Return Incomplete Results</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65111</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source database system for creating and managing security-critical application permissions. Prior to version 1.47.1, if a schema includes the following characteristics: permission defined in terms of a union (+) and that union references the same relation on both sides (but one side arrows to a different permission). Then SpiceDB may have missing LookupResources results when checking the permission. This only affects LookupResources; other APIs calculate permissionship correctly. The issue is fixed in version 1.47.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65109 | Minder does not sandbox http.send in Rego programs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65109</link><description>Minder is an open source software supply chain security platform. In Minder Helm version 0.20241106.3386+ref.2507dbf and Minder Go versions from 0.0.72 to 0.0.83, Minder users may fetch content in the context of the Minder server, which may include URLs which the user would not normally have access to. This issue has been patched in Minder Helm version 0.20250203.3849+ref.fdc94f0 and Minder Go version 0.0.84.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65107 | Langfuse SSO Account Takeover via CSRF or phishing attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65107</link><description>Langfuse is an open source large language model engineering platform. In versions from 2.95.0 to before 2.95.12 and from 3.17.0 to before 3.131.0, in SSO provider configurations without an explicit AUTH__CHECK setting, a potential account takeover may happen if an authenticated user is made to call a specifically crafted URL via a CSRF or phishing attack. This issue has been patched in versions 2.95.12 and 3.131.0. A workaround for this issue involves setting AUTH__CHECK.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65108 | md-to-pdf is vulnerable to arbitrary JavaScript code execution when parsing front matter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65108</link><description>md-to-pdf is a CLI tool for converting Markdown files to PDF using Node.js and headless Chrome. Prior to version 5.2.5, a Markdown front-matter block that contains JavaScript delimiter causes the JS engine in gray-matter library to execute arbitrary code in the Markdown to PDF converter process of md-to-pdf library, resulting in remote code execution. This issue has been patched in version 5.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65106 | LangChain Vulnerable to Template Injection via Attribute Access in Prompt Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65106</link><description>LangChain is a framework for building agents and LLM-powered applications. From versions 0.3.79 and prior and 1.0.0 to 1.0.6, a template injection vulnerability exists in LangChain's prompt template system that allows attackers to access Python object internals through template syntax. This vulnerability affects applications that accept untrusted template strings (not just template variables) in ChatPromptTemplate and related prompt template classes. This issue has been patched in versions 0.3.80 and 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65102 | PJSIP is vulnerable to buffer overflow in Opus PLC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65102</link><description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library. Prior to version 2.16, Opus PLC may zero-fill the input frame as long as the decoder ptime, while the input frame length, which is based on stream ptime, may be less than that. This issue affects PJSIP users who use the Opus audio codec in receiving direction. The vulnerability can lead to unexpected application termination due to a memory overwrite. This issue has been patched in version 2.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0504 | Black Duck SCA Project Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0504</link><description>Black Duck SCA versions prior to 2025.10.0 had user role permissions configured in an overly broad manner. Users with the scoped Project Manager user role with the Global User Read access permission enabled access to certain Project Administrator functionalities which should have be inaccessible. Exploitation does not grant full system control, but it may enable unauthorized changes to project configurations or access to system sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65092 | ESP32-P4 JPEG Decoder Header Parsing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65092</link><description>ESF-IDF is the Espressif Internet of Things (IOT) Development Framework. In versions 5.5.1, 5.4.3, and 5.3.4, when the ESP32-P4 uses its hardware JPEG decoder, the software parser lacks necessary validation checks. A specially crafted (malicious) JPEG image could exploit the parsing routine and trigger an out-of-bounds array access. This issue has been fixed in versions 5.5.2, 5.4.4, and 5.3.5. At time of publication versions 5.5.2, 5.4.4, and 5.3.5 have not been released but are fixed respectively in commits 4b8f585, c79cb4d, and 34e2726.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31216 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5. An attacker with physical acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31216</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5. An attacker with physical access to a device may be able to override managed Wi-Fi profiles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31248 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31248</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.5, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31266 | A spoofing issue was addressed with improved truncation when displaying the fully qualified domain name This issue is fixed in Safari 18.5, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31266</link><description>A spoofing issue was addressed with improved truncation when displaying the fully qualified domain name This issue is fixed in Safari 18.5, macOS Sequoia 15.5. A website may be able to spoof the domain name in the title of a pop-up window.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43374 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5, visionOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43374</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5, visionOS 2.5, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.5, watchOS 11.5. An attacker in physical proximity may be able to cause an out-of-bounds read in kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11087 | Zegen Core &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11087</link><description>The Zegen Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Upload in versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This is due to missing nonce validation and missing file type validation in the '/custom-font-code/custom-fonts-uploads.php' file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13524 | Improper resource release in the call termination process in AWS Wickr before version 6.62.13 on Windows, macOS and Linux may allow a call p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13524</link><description>Improper resource release in the call termination process in AWS Wickr before version 6.62.13 on Windows, macOS and Linux may allow a call participant to continue receiving audio input from another user after they close their call window. This issue occurs under certain conditions, which require the affected user to take a particular action within the application

To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade AWS Wickr, Wickr Gov and Wickr Enterprise desktop version to version 6.62.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36149 | IBM Concert Software clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36149</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48502 | Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to overwrite MSR registers, potentially resulting in crash or denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48502</link><description>Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to overwrite MSR registers, potentially resulting in crash or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62608 | MLX has heap-buffer-overflow in load()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62608</link><description>MLX is an array framework for machine learning on Apple silicon. Prior to version 0.29.4, there is a heap buffer overflow in mlx::core::load() when parsing malicious NumPy .npy files. Attacker-controlled file causes 13-byte out-of-bounds read, leading to crash or information disclosure. This issue has been patched in version 0.29.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62609 | MLX has Wild Pointer Dereference in load_gguf()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62609</link><description>MLX is an array framework for machine learning on Apple silicon. Prior to version 0.29.4, there is a segmentation fault in mlx::core::load_gguf() when loading malicious GGUF files. Untrusted pointer from external gguflib library is dereferenced without validation, causing application crash. This issue has been patched in version 0.29.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62626 | Improper handling of insufficient entropy in the AMD CPUs could allow a local attacker to influence the values returned by the RDSEED instru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62626</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient entropy in the AMD CPUs could allow a local attacker to influence the values returned by the RDSEED instruction, potentially resulting in the consumption of insufficiently random values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29934 | A bug within some AMD CPUs could allow a local admin-privileged attacker to run a SEV-SNP guest using stale TLB entries, potentially resulti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29934</link><description>A bug within some AMD CPUs could allow a local admin-privileged attacker to run a SEV-SNP guest using stale TLB entries, potentially resulting in loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64169 | Wazuh NULL pointer dereference in fim_alert line 666</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64169</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. From version 3.7.0 to before 4.12.0, fim_alert() implementation does not check whether oldsum-&gt;md5 is NULL or not before dereferencing it. A compromised agent can cause a crash of analysisd by sending a specially crafted message to the wazuh manager. This issue has been patched in version 4.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64767 | hpke-js reuses AEAD nonces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64767</link><description>hpke-js is a Hybrid Public Key Encryption (HPKE) module built on top of Web Cryptography API. Prior to version 1.7.5, the public SenderContext Seal() API has a race condition which allows for the same AEAD nonce to be re-used for multiple Seal() calls. This can lead to complete loss of Confidentiality and Integrity of the produced messages. This issue has been patched in version 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30201 | Wazuh NetNTLMv2 Hash Theft In Multiple Centralized Configuration Capabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30201</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. Prior to version 4.13.0, a vulnerability in Wazuh Agent allows authenticated attackers to force NTLM authentication through malicious UNC paths in various agent configuration settings, potentially leading NTLM relay attacks that would result privilege escalation and remote code execution. This issue has been patched in version 4.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54866 | Wazuh installation fails to protected authd.pass on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54866</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. From version 4.3.0 to before 4.13.0, a missing ACL on "C:\Program Files (x86)\ossec-agent\authd.pass" exposes the password to all "Authenticated Users" on the local machine. This issue has been patched in version 4.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13132 | Dia: Increased Spoof Risk; Missing full screen toast</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13132</link><description>This vulnerability allowed a site to enter fullscreen, after a user click, without a full-screen notification (toast) appearing. Without this notification, users could potentially be misled about what site they were on if a malicious site renders a fake UI (like a fake address bar.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64483 | Wazuh API – Agent Configuration Has Improper Access Control in Agent Enrollment Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64483</link><description>Wazuh is a security detection, visibility, and compliance open source project. From version 4.9.0 to before 4.13.0, the Wazuh API – Agent Configuration in certain configurations allows authenticated users with read-only API roles to retrieve agent enrollment credentials through the /utils/configuration endpoint. These credentials can be used to register new agents within the same Wazuh tenant without requiring elevated permissions through the UI. This issue has been patched in version 4.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13470 | RNP 0.18.0 Vulnerable PKESK session keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13470</link><description>In RNP version 0.18.0 a refactoring regression causes the symmetric 
session key used for Public-Key Encrypted Session Key (PKESK) packets to
 be left uninitialized except for zeroing, resulting in it always being 
an all-zero byte array.

Any data encrypted using public-key encryption 
in this release can be decrypted trivially by supplying an all-zero 
session key, fully compromising confidentiality.

The vulnerability affects only public key encryption (PKESK packets).  Passphrase-based encryption (SKESK packets) is not affected.

Root cause: Vulnerable session key buffer used in PKESK packet generation.



The defect was introduced in commit `7bd9a8dc356aae756b40755be76d36205b6b161a` where initialization 
logic inside `encrypted_build_skesk()` only randomized the key for the 
SKESK path and omitted it for the PKESK path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12747 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12747</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 via uploaded files marked as private being exposed in wp-content without adequate protection.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive information from files that have been marked as private.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12973 | S2B AI Assistant – ChatBot, ChatGPT, OpenAI, Content &amp;amp; Image Generator &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Authenticated (Editor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12973</link><description>The S2B AI Assistant – ChatBot, ChatGPT, OpenAI, Content &amp; Image Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the storeFile() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13357 | Vault Terraform Provider Applied Incorrect Defaults for LDAP Auth Method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13357</link><description>Vault’s Terraform Provider incorrectly set the default deny_null_bind parameter for the LDAP auth method to false by default, potentially resulting in an insecure configuration. If the underlying LDAP server allowed anonymous or unauthenticated binds, this could result in authentication bypass. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-13357, is fixed in Vault Terraform Provider v5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13432 | Terraform Enterprise state versions can be created by users with specific permissions without sufficient write access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13432</link><description>Terraform state versions can be created by a user with specific but insufficient permissions in a Terraform Enterprise workspace. This may allow for the alteration of infrastructure if a subsequent plan operation is approved by a user with approval permission or auto-applied. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-13432, is fixed in Terraform Enterprise version 1.1.1 and 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41115 | Incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41115</link><description>SCIM provisioning was introduced in Grafana Enterprise and Grafana Cloud in April to improve how organizations manage users and teams in Grafana by introducing automated user lifecycle management.

In Grafana versions 12.x where SCIM provisioning is enabled and configured, a vulnerability in user identity handling allows a malicious or compromised SCIM client to provision a user with a numeric externalId, which in turn could allow to override internal user IDs and lead to impersonation or privilege escalation.

This vulnerability applies only if all of the following conditions are met:
- `enableSCIM` feature flag set to true
- `user_sync_enabled` config option in the `[auth.scim]` block set to true</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11127 | Mstoreapp Mobile (App &amp;lt;= 2.08, Multivendor &amp;lt;= 9.0.1) - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11127</link><description>The Mstoreapp Mobile App WordPress plugin through 2.08 and Mstoreapp Mobile Multivendor through 9.0.1 do not properly verify users identify when using an AJAX action, allowing unauthenticated users to retrieve a valid session for arbitrary users by knowing their email address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10039 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via &amp;#x27;eh_crm_ticket_single_view_client&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10039</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 via the 'eh_crm_ticket_single_view_client' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of all support tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10054 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Role Removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10054</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_remove_agent' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to remove the role and capabilities of any user with an Administrator, WSDesk Supervisor, or WSDesk Agents role.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12935 | FluentCRM - Marketing Automation For WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.9.84 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;fluentcrm_content&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12935</link><description>The FluentCRM – Email Newsletter, Automation, Email Marketing, Email Campaigns, Optins, Leads, and CRM Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'fluentcrm_content' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.84 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66053 | WordPress Enfold theme &amp;lt;= 7.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kriesi Enfold enfold allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Enfold: from n/a through &lt;= 7.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66055 | WordPress Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.10 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66055</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Icegram Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters email-subscribers allows Object Injection.This issue affects Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters: from n/a through &lt;= 5.9.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66056 | WordPress Uncanny Automator plugin &amp;lt; 6.10.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66056</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator uncanny-automator allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Uncanny Automator: from n/a through &lt; 6.10.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66057 | WordPress Bold Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in boldthemes Bold Page Builder bold-page-builder allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 5.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66059 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66059</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting seriously-simple-podcasting allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66060 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66060</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting seriously-simple-podcasting allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66061 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66061</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting seriously-simple-podcasting allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66062 | WordPress WP YouTube Lyte plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.28 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66062</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Frank Goossens WP YouTube Lyte wp-youtube-lyte allows Phishing.This issue affects WP YouTube Lyte: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.28.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66063 | WordPress WP Google Review Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 17.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66063</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in jgwhite33 WP Google Review Slider wp-google-places-review-slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Google Review Slider: from n/a through &lt;= 17.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66064 | WordPress Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66064</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Syed Balkhi Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress rafflepress allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress: from n/a through &lt;= 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66065 | WordPress Gutenverse plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66065</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jegstudio Gutenverse gutenverse allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gutenverse: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66066 | WordPress Envo Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66066</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EnvoThemes Envo Extra envo-extra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Envo Extra: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66067 | WordPress Funnel Builder by FunnelKit plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66067</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelKit Funnel Builder by FunnelKit funnel-builder allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Funnel Builder by FunnelKit: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66069 | WordPress PPOM for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 33.0.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66069</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeisle PPOM for WooCommerce woocommerce-product-addon allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PPOM for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 33.0.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66071 | WordPress Custom Order Numbers for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66071</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tychesoftwares Custom Order Numbers for WooCommerce custom-order-numbers-for-woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Custom Order Numbers for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.11.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66072 | WordPress UsersWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.47 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66072</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stiofan UsersWP userswp allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects UsersWP: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.47.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66073 | WordPress WP Webhooks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66073</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Cozmoslabs WP Webhooks wp-webhooks allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Webhooks: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66075 | WordPress WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp;amp; ePrivacy Consent plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66075</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Legal Pages WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy Consent gdpr-cookie-consent allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy Consent: from n/a through &lt;= 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66077 | WordPress Legal Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66077</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpWax Legal Pages legal-pages allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Legal Pages: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66079 | WordPress Gutenverse Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jegstudio Gutenverse Form gutenverse-form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gutenverse Form: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66081 | WordPress Head Meta Data plugin &amp;lt;= 20250327 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66081</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeff Starr Head Meta Data head-meta-data allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Head Meta Data: from n/a through &lt;= 20250327.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66082 | WordPress WpEvently plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66082</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in magepeopleteam WpEvently mage-eventpress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WpEvently: from n/a through &lt;= 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66083 | WordPress WpEvently plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66083</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in magepeopleteam WpEvently mage-eventpress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WpEvently: from n/a through &lt;= 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66084 | WordPress FluentCommunity plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66084</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shahjahan Jewel FluentCommunity fluent-community allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects FluentCommunity: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66085 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66085</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tychesoftwares Arconix Shortcodes arconix-shortcodes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66086 | WordPress SMS Alert Order Notifications plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66086</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cozy Vision SMS Alert Order Notifications sms-alert allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SMS Alert Order Notifications: from n/a through &lt;= 3.8.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66087 | WordPress PropertyHive plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66087</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Property Hive PropertyHive propertyhive allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66089 | WordPress Product Feed for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66089</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee Product Feed for WooCommerce webtoffee-product-feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Product Feed for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66090 | WordPress SKT Skill Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66090</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sonalsinha21 SKT Skill Bar skt-skill-bar allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects SKT Skill Bar: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66091 | WordPress Stylish Cost Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Design Stylish Cost Calculator stylish-cost-calculator allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Stylish Cost Calculator: from n/a through &lt;= 8.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66092 | WordPress Accordion Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66092</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bqworks Accordion Slider accordion-slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accordion Slider: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66093 | WordPress Extensions for Leaflet Map plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66093</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hupe13 Extensions for Leaflet Map extensions-leaflet-map allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Extensions for Leaflet Map: from n/a through &lt;= 4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66095 | WordPress KiviCare plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.13 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66095</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Iqonic Design KiviCare kivicare-clinic-management-system allows SQL Injection.This issue affects KiviCare: from n/a through &lt;= 3.6.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66096 | WordPress Table Block by Tableberg plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66096</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Imtiaz Rayhan Table Block by Tableberg tableberg allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Table Block by Tableberg: from n/a through &lt;= 0.6.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66097 | WordPress I Order Terms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66097</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Igor Jerosimić I Order Terms i-order-terms allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects I Order Terms: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66098 | WordPress Travelers&amp;#x27; Map plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66098</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Camille V Travelers' Map travelers-map allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Travelers' Map: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66099 | WordPress Chat Help plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66099</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeAtelier Chat Help chat-help allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Chat Help: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66101 | WordPress CBX Bookmark &amp;amp; Favorite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66101</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sabuj Kundu CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite cbxwpbookmark allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66106 | WordPress Featured Post Creative plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66106</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Essential Plugin Featured Post Creative featured-post-creative allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Post Creative: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66107 | WordPress Subscriptions &amp;amp; Memberships for PayPal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66107</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Scott Paterson Subscriptions &amp; Memberships for PayPal subscriptions-memberships-for-paypal allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Subscriptions &amp; Memberships for PayPal: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66108 | WordPress TNC Toolbox: Web Performance plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66108</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Merlot Digital (by TNC) TNC Toolbox: Web Performance tnc-toolbox allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects TNC Toolbox: Web Performance: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66109 | WordPress Cart Weight for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66109</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in octolize Cart Weight for WooCommerce woo-cart-weight allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cart Weight for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66110 | WordPress Tiktok Feed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.22 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66110</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Tiktok Feed b-tiktok-feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Tiktok Feed: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66111 | WordPress Nelio Popups plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66111</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nelio Software Nelio Popups nelio-popups allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Nelio Popups: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66112 | WordPress Accessibility Toolkit by WebYes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66112</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee Accessibility Toolkit by WebYes accessibility-plus allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Accessibility Toolkit by WebYes: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66113 | WordPress Better Chat Support for Messenger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66113</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeAtelier Better Chat Support for Messenger better-chat-support allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Better Chat Support for Messenger: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66114 | WordPress Show Variations as Single Products Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66114</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theme funda Show Variations as Single Products Woocommerce woo-show-single-variations-shop-category allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Show Variations as Single Products Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66115 | WordPress Easy Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66115</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in MatrixAddons Easy Invoice easy-invoice allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Easy Invoice: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40209 | btrfs: fix memory leak of qgroup_list in btrfs_add_qgroup_relation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40209</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix memory leak of qgroup_list in btrfs_add_qgroup_relation

When btrfs_add_qgroup_relation() is called with invalid qgroup levels
(src &gt;= dst), the function returns -EINVAL directly without freeing the
preallocated qgroup_list structure passed by the caller. This causes a
memory leak because the caller unconditionally sets the pointer to NULL
after the call, preventing any cleanup.

The issue occurs because the level validation check happens before the
mutex is acquired and before any error handling path that would free
the prealloc pointer. On this early return, the cleanup code at the
'out' label (which includes kfree(prealloc)) is never reached.

In btrfs_ioctl_qgroup_assign(), the code pattern is:

    prealloc = kzalloc(sizeof(*prealloc), GFP_KERNEL);
    ret = btrfs_add_qgroup_relation(trans, sa-&gt;src, sa-&gt;dst, prealloc);
    prealloc = NULL;  // Always set to NULL regardless of return value
    ...
    kfree(prealloc);  // This becomes kfree(NULL), does nothing

When the level check fails, 'prealloc' is never freed by either the
callee or the caller, resulting in a 64-byte memory leak per failed
operation. This can be triggered repeatedly by an unprivileged user
with access to a writable btrfs mount, potentially exhausting kernel
memory.

Fix this by freeing prealloc before the early return, ensuring prealloc
is always freed on all error paths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40210 | Revert &amp;quot;NFSD: Remove the cap on number of operations per NFSv4 COMPOUND&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40210</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "NFSD: Remove the cap on number of operations per NFSv4 COMPOUND"

I've found that pynfs COMP6 now leaves the connection or lease in a
strange state, which causes CLOSE9 to hang indefinitely. I've dug
into it a little, but I haven't been able to root-cause it yet.
However, I bisected to commit 48aab1606fa8 ("NFSD: Remove the cap on
number of operations per NFSv4 COMPOUND").

Tianshuo Han also reports a potential vulnerability when decoding
an NFSv4 COMPOUND. An attacker can place an arbitrarily large op
count in the COMPOUND header, which results in:

[   51.410584] nfsd: vmalloc error: size 1209533382144, exceeds total
pages, mode:0xdc0(GFP_KERNEL|__GFP_ZERO),
nodemask=(null),cpuset=/,mems_allowed=0

when NFSD attempts to allocate the COMPOUND op array.

Let's restore the operation-per-COMPOUND limit, but increased to 200
for now.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40211 | ACPI: video: Fix use-after-free in acpi_video_switch_brightness()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40211</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ACPI: video: Fix use-after-free in acpi_video_switch_brightness()

The switch_brightness_work delayed work accesses device-&gt;brightness
and device-&gt;backlight, freed by acpi_video_dev_unregister_backlight()
during device removal.

If the work executes after acpi_video_bus_unregister_backlight()
frees these resources, it causes a use-after-free when
acpi_video_switch_brightness() dereferences device-&gt;brightness or
device-&gt;backlight.

Fix this by calling cancel_delayed_work_sync() for each device's
switch_brightness_work in acpi_video_bus_remove_notify_handler()
after removing the notify handler that queues the work. This ensures
the work completes before the memory is freed.

[ rjw: Changelog edit ]</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12066 | WP Delete Post Copies &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12066</link><description>The WP Delete Post Copies plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12160 | Simple User Registration &amp;lt;= 6.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12160</link><description>The Simple User Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpr_admin_msg' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12750 | Groundhogg &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12750</link><description>The Groundhogg — CRM, Newsletters, and Marketing Automation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'term' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12964 | Magical Products Display &amp;lt;= 1.1.29 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via MPD Pricing Table Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12964</link><description>The Magical Products Display plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mpdpr_title_tag' and 'mpdpr_subtitle_tag' parameters in the MPD Pricing Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied HTML tag names. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13138 | WP Directory Kit &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via select_2_ajax() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13138</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'columns_search' parameter of the select_2_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11803 | WPSite Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11803</link><description>The WPSite Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'format' shortcode attribute in the wpsite_y shortcode and the 'before' attribute in the wpsite_postauthor shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping in error messages. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11808 | Shortcode for Google Street View &amp;lt;= 0.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11808</link><description>The Shortcode for Google Street View plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'streetview' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.7. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'id' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11826 | WP Company Info &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11826</link><description>The WP Company Info plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' attribute of the 'social-networks' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11973 | 简数采集器 &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11973</link><description>The 简数采集器 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 via the __kds_flag functionality that imports featured images. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Adminstrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12039 | BigBuy Dropshipping Connector for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Unauthenticated IP Spoofing to phpinfo() Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12039</link><description>The BigBuy Dropshipping Connector for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5 due to insufficient IP address validation and use of user-supplied HTTP headers as a primary method for IP retrieval. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to retrieve the output of phpinfo().</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13141 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Tag Attribute Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13141</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Gutenberg blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient input validation on user-supplied HTML tag names. This is due to the lack of a tag name whitelist allowing dangerous tags like 'script', 'iframe', and 'object' to be injected even though tag_escape() is used for sanitization. While some blocks use esc_html() for content, this can be bypassed using JavaScript encoding techniques (unquoted strings, backticks, String.fromCharCode()). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13149 | Schedule Post Changes With PublishPress Future: Unpublish, Delete, Change Status, Trash, Change Categories &amp;lt;= 4.9.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Missing Authorization to Post/Page Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13149</link><description>The Schedule Post Changes With PublishPress Future: Unpublish, Delete, Change Status, Trash, Change Categories plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing authorization check on the "saveFutureActionData" function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level access and above, to change the status of arbitrary posts and pages via the REST API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13156 | Vitepos – Point of Sale (POS) for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13156</link><description>The Vitepos – Point of Sale (POS) for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the insert_media_attachment() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This is due to the save_update_category_img() function accepting user-supplied file types without validation when processing category images. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which makes remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10938 | UiPress lite &amp;lt;= 3.5.08 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10938</link><description>The UiPress lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.08. This is due to missing capability checks in the 'uip_process_block_query' AJAX function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive user data including password hashes, emails, and other user information that could be used for account takeover attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11003 | UiPress lite &amp;lt;= 3.5.08 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11003</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'uip_save_ui_template' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.08. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to save templates that contain custom JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11456 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11456</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the eh_crm_new_ticket_post() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11763 | Display Pages Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11763</link><description>The Display Pages Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'column_count' parameter in the [display-pages] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11764 | Shortcodes Bootstrap &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11764</link><description>The Shortcodes Bootstrap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'type' parameter in the [notification] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11765 | Stock Tools &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11765</link><description>The Stock Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'image_height' and 'image_width' shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11767 | Tips Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11767</link><description>The Tips Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tip' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11768 | Islamic Phrases &amp;lt;= 2.12.2015 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11768</link><description>The Islamic Phrases plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'phrases' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.2015. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11770 | BrightTALK WordPress Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11770</link><description>The BrightTALK WordPress Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'format' shortcode attribute in the brighttalk-time shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11771 | Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp;amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Presale Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11771</link><description>The Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated and unauthorized modification of data due to missing authentication and capability checks on the 'createSaleRecord' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate presales counters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11773 | Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp;amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Contract Address Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11773</link><description>The Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'saveDeployedContract' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the WordPress option `tokenico_deployed_contracts`, poisoning the smart contract addresses displayed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11799 | Affiliate AI Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11799</link><description>The Affiliate AI Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'asin' shortcode attribute in the affiai_img shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11800 | Surbma | MiniCRM Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11800</link><description>The Surbma | MiniCRM Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' shortcode attribute of the 'minicrm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11801 | AudioTube &amp;lt;= 0.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11801</link><description>The AudioTube plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'caption' shortcode attribute of the 'audiotube' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11802 | Bulma Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11802</link><description>The Bulma Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'type' shortcode attribute in the bulma-notification shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11815 | UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.08 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11815</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the uip_save_site_option() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.08. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary plugin settings. Other AJAX actions are also affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11885 | EchBay Admin Security &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11885</link><description>The EchBay Admin Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_ebnonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11985 | Realty Portal &amp;lt;= 0.4.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11985</link><description>The Realty Portal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'rp_save_property_settings' function in versions 0.1 to 0.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12086 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.5.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Refund Request Cancellation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12086</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.5 via the 'wps_rma_cancel_return_request' AJAX endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete other users refund requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12135 | WPBookit &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12135</link><description>The WPBookit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'css_code' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to a missing capability check on the save_custome_code() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12138 | URL Image Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12138</link><description>The URL Image Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This is due to the plugin relying on a user-controlled Content-Type HTTP header to validate file uploads in the 'uimptr_import_image_from_url()' function which writes the file to the server before performing proper validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible via the uploaded PHP file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12170 | Checkbox &amp;lt;= 2.8.10 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Log Clearing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12170</link><description>The Checkbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_checkbox_clean_log' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12660 | Padlet Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12660</link><description>The Padlet Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'key' parameter in the 'wallwisher' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12661 | Pollcaster Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12661</link><description>The Pollcaster Shortcode Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'height' parameter in the 'pollcaster' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12746 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12746</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12881 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.5.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Order Message Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12881</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.5 via the wps_rma_fetch_order_msgs() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read other user's order messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12894 | Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.14.17 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12894</link><description>The Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.17 via the import/export functionality and a lack of .htaccess protection. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from exports stored in /exportwp and import data stored in /importwp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13134 | AuthorSure &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13134</link><description>The AuthorSure plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'authorsure' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13135 | HotelRunner Booking Widget &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13135</link><description>The HotelRunner Booking Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hotelrunner' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13142 | Custom Post Type &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom Post Type Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13142</link><description>The Custom Post Type plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the custom post type deletion functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete custom post types via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13159 | Flo Forms – Easy Drag &amp;amp; Drop Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.43 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13159</link><description>The Flo Forms – Easy Drag &amp; Drop Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.43. This is due to the plugin allowing SVG file uploads via an unauthenticated AJAX endpoint (`flo_form_submit`) without proper file content validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload malicious SVG files containing JavaScript that executes when an administrator views the uploaded file in the WordPress admin interface, leading to potential full site compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13322 | WP AUDIO GALLERY &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via &amp;#x27;audio_upload&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13322</link><description>The WP AUDIO GALLERY plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the `wpag_uploadaudio_callback()` AJAX handler not properly validating user-supplied file paths in the `audio_upload` parameter before passing them to `unlink()`. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when critical files like wp-config.php are deleted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58097 | The installation directory of LogStare Collector is configured with incorrect access permissions. A non-administrative user may manipulate f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58097</link><description>The installation directory of LogStare Collector is configured with incorrect access permissions. A non-administrative user may manipulate files within the installation directory and execute arbitrary code with the administrative privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61949 | LogStare Collector contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in UserManagement. If crafted user information is stored, an arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61949</link><description>LogStare Collector contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in UserManagement. If crafted user information is stored, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who logs in to the product's management page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62189 | LogStare Collector contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability in UserRegistration. If exploited, a non-administrative user may create...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62189</link><description>LogStare Collector contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability in UserRegistration. If exploited, a non-administrative user may create a new user account by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62687 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in LogStare Collector. If a user views a crafted page while logged, unintended operations ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62687</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in LogStare Collector. If a user views a crafted page while logged, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64299 | LogStare Collector improperly handles the password hash data. An administrative user may obtain the other users' password hashes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64299</link><description>LogStare Collector improperly handles the password hash data. An administrative user may obtain the other users' password hashes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64695 | Uncontrolled search path element issue exists in the installer of LogStare Collector (for Windows). If exploited, arbitrary code may be exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64695</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element issue exists in the installer of LogStare Collector (for Windows). If exploited, arbitrary code may be executed with the privilege of the user invoking the installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13499 | Access of Uninitialized Pointer in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13499</link><description>Kafka dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.10 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11368 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Callback Execution to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11368</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.9.4. This is due to missing capability checks in the REST endpoint /wp-json/lp/v1/load_content_via_ajax which allows arbitrary callback execution of admin-only template methods. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve admin curriculum HTML, quiz questions with correct answers, course materials, and other sensitive educational content via the REST API endpoint granted they can supply valid numeric IDs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12022 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Trash Restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12022</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_settings_restore_trash' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to restore all deleted tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12023 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Ticket Restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12023</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the eh_crm_restore_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to restore tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12085 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Trash Empty</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12085</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_settings_empty_trash' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to empty the ticket trash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12169 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenitcated (Subscriber+) to Scheduled Trigger Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12169</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_eh_crm_settings_empty_scheduled_actions' AJAX Action in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear the scheduled triggers option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9825 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9825</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.7 to 18.2.8, 18.3 before 18.3.4, and 18.4 before 18.4.2 that could have allowed authenticated users without project membership to view sensitive manual CI/CD variables by querying the GraphQL API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64310 | EPSON WebConfig and Epson Web Control for SEIKO EPSON Projector Products do not restrict excessive authentication attempts. An administrativ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64310</link><description>EPSON WebConfig and Epson Web Control for SEIKO EPSON Projector Products do not restrict excessive authentication attempts. An administrative user's password may be identified through a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 03:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62164 | VLLM deserialization vulnerability leading to DoS and potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62164</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From versions 0.10.2 to before 0.11.1, a memory corruption vulnerability could lead to a crash (denial-of-service) and potentially remote code execution (RCE), exists in the Completions API endpoint. When processing user-supplied prompt embeddings, the endpoint loads serialized tensors using torch.load() without sufficient validation. Due to a change introduced in PyTorch 2.8.0, sparse tensor integrity checks are disabled by default. As a result, maliciously crafted tensors can bypass internal bounds checks and trigger an out-of-bounds memory write during the call to to_dense(). This memory corruption can crash vLLM and potentially lead to code execution on the server hosting vLLM. This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62372 | vLLM vulnerable to DoS with incorrect shape of multimodal embedding inputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62372</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From version 0.5.5 to before 0.11.1, users can crash the vLLM engine serving multimodal models by passing multimodal embedding inputs with correct ndim but incorrect shape (e.g. hidden dimension is wrong), regardless of whether the model is intended to support such inputs (as defined in the Supported Models page). This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62426 | vLLM vulnerable to DoS via large Chat Completion or Tokenization requests with specially crafted `chat_template_kwargs`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62426</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From version 0.5.5 to before 0.11.1, the /v1/chat/completions and /tokenize endpoints allow a chat_template_kwargs request parameter that is used in the code before it is properly validated against the chat template. With the right chat_template_kwargs parameters, it is possible to block processing of the API server for long periods of time, delaying all other requests. This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64751 | OpenFGA Improper Policy Enforcement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64751</link><description>OpenFGA is a high-performance and flexible authorization/permission engine built for developers and inspired by Google Zanzibar. OpenFGA v1.4.0 to v1.11.0 ( openfga-0.1.34 &lt;= Helm chart &lt;= openfga-0.2.48, v.1.4.0 &lt;= docker &lt;= v.1.11.0) are vulnerable to improper policy enforcement when certain Check and ListObject calls are executed. This issue has been patched in version 1.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64755 | @anthropic-ai/claude-code has Sed Command Validation Bypass that Allows Arbitrary File Writes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64755</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.0.31, due to an error in sed command parsing, it was possible to bypass the Claude Code read-only validation and write to arbitrary files on the host system. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64762 | authkit-nextjs may let session cookies be cached in CDNs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64762</link><description>The AuthKit library for Next.js provides convenient helpers for authentication and session management using WorkOS &amp; AuthKit with Next.js. In authkit-nextjs version 2.11.0 and below, authenticated responses do not defensively apply anti-caching headers. In environments where CDN caching is enabled, this can result in session tokens being included in cached responses and subsequently served to multiple users. Next.js applications deployed on Vercel are unaffected unless they manually enable CDN caching by setting cache headers on authenticated paths. Patched in authkit-nextjs 2.11.1, which applies anti-caching headers to all responses behind authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13485 | itsourcecode Online File Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13485</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Online File Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 01:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>