<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2022-1751 | Skitter Slideshow &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1751</link><description>The Skitter Slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.2 via the /image.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4532 | LOGIN AND REGISTRATION ATTEMPTS LIMIT&amp;lt;= 2.1 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4532</link><description>The LOGIN AND REGISTRATION ATTEMPTS LIMIT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 2.1. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address from logging in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1604 | Short URL &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via configuration_page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1604</link><description>The Short URL plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.6.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the configuration_page function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add and import redirects, including comments containing cross-site scripting as detailed in CVE-2023-1602, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4024 | Radio Player &amp;lt;= 2.0.73 - Missing Authorization to Player Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4024</link><description>The Radio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_player function in versions up to, and including, 2.0.73. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete player instances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4025 | Radio Player &amp;lt;= 2.0.73 - Missing Authorization to Player Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4025</link><description>The Radio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update_player function in versions up to, and including, 2.0.73. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update player instances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4027 | Radio Player &amp;lt;= 2.0.73 - Missing Authorization to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4027</link><description>The Radio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update_settings function in versions up to, and including, 2.0.73. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4507 | Admission AppManager &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4507</link><description>The Admission AppManager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'q' parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4604 | Slideshow, Image Slider by 2J &amp;lt;= 1.3.54 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;post&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4604</link><description>The Slideshow, Image Slider by 2J plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘post’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.3.54 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4730 | LadiApp: Landing Page, PopupX, Marketing Automation, Affiliate Marketing… &amp;lt;= 4.3 - Missing Authorization via init_endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4730</link><description>The LadiApp plugn for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the init_endpoint() function hooked via 'init' in versions up to, and including, 4.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify a variety of settings. An attacker can directly modify the 'ladipage_key' which enables them to create new posts on the website and inject malicious web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 07:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6459 | News Element Elementor Blog Magazine &amp;lt; 1.0.6 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6459</link><description>The News Element Elementor Blog Magazine WordPress plugin before 1.0.6 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via the template parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attacker to include and execute PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 06:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6500 | InPost for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 and InPost PL &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read and Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6500</link><description>The InPost for WooCommerce plugin and InPost PL plugin for WordPress are vulnerable to unauthorized access and deletion of data due to a missing capability check on the 'parse_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 (for InPost for WooCommerce) as well as 1.4.4 (for InPost PL). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read and delete arbitrary files on Windows servers. On Linux servers, only files within the WordPress install will be deleted, but all files can be read.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 02:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7886 | Scooter Software Beyond Compare 7zxa.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7886</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability has been found in Scooter Software Beyond Compare up to 3.3.5.15075 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library 7zxa.dll. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Attacking locally is a requirement. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. NOTE: The vendor explains that a system must be breached before exploiting this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 21:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43395 | CraftOS-PC 2&amp;#x27;s improperly sanitizied paths cause filesystem escape (Windows)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43395</link><description>CraftOS-PC 2 is a rewrite of the desktop port of CraftOS from the popular Minecraft mod ComputerCraft using C++ and a modified version of PUC Lua, as well as SDL for drawing. Prior to version 2.8.3, users of CraftOS-PC 2 on Windows can escape the computer folder and access files anywhere without permission or notice by obfuscating `..`s to bypass the internal check preventing parent directory traversal. Version 2.8.3 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43011 | An arbitrary file deletion vulnerability exists in the admin/del.php file at line 62 in ZZCMS 2023 and earlier. Due to insufficient validati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43011</link><description>An arbitrary file deletion vulnerability exists in the admin/del.php file at line 62 in ZZCMS 2023 and earlier. Due to insufficient validation and sanitization of user input for file paths, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by using directory traversal techniques to delete arbitrary files on the server. This can lead to the deletion of critical files, potentially disrupting the normal operation of the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43009 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in user/login.php at line 24. The application directly inserts the value of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43009</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in user/login.php at line 24. The application directly inserts the value of the HTTP_REFERER header into the HTML response without proper sanitization. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by tricking a user into visiting a specially crafted URL, which includes a malicious Referer header. This can lead to the execution of arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the victim's browser, potentially resulting in session hijacking, defacement, or other malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43005 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component dl_liuyan_save.php of ZZCMS v2023 allows attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43005</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component dl_liuyan_save.php of ZZCMS v2023 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43006 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ZZCMS2023 in the ask/show.php file at line 21. An attacker can exploit this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43006</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ZZCMS2023 in the ask/show.php file at line 21. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted POST request to /user/ask_edit.php?action=add, which includes malicious JavaScript code in the 'content' parameter. When a user visits the ask/show_{newsid}.html page, the injected script is executed in the context of the user's browser, leading to potential theft of cookies, session tokens, or other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47728 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47728</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.22.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the request.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  272201.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43042 | Pluck CMS 4.7.18 does not restrict failed login attempts, allowing attackers to execute a brute force attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43042</link><description>Pluck CMS 4.7.18 does not restrict failed login attempts, allowing attackers to execute a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43472 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43472</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33162 | IBM Directory Server buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33162</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 does not perform any authentication for functionality that requires a provable user identity or consumes a significant amount of resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  228570.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42849 | An issue in Silverpeas v.6.4.2 and lower allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the password change function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42849</link><description>An issue in Silverpeas v.6.4.2 and lower allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the password change function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42850 | An issue in the password change function of Silverpeas v6.4.2 and lower allows for the bypassing of password complexity requirements.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42850</link><description>An issue in the password change function of Silverpeas v6.4.2 and lower allows for the bypassing of password complexity requirements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42637 | H3C R3010 v100R002L02 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42637</link><description>H3C R3010 v100R002L02 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42639 | H3C GR1100-P v100R009 was discovered to use a hardcoded password in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42639</link><description>H3C GR1100-P v100R009 was discovered to use a hardcoded password in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42638 | H3C Magic B1ST v100R012 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as roo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42638</link><description>H3C Magic B1ST v100R012 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25837 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in October CMS Bloghub Plugin v1.3.8 and lower allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25837</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in October CMS Bloghub Plugin v1.3.8 and lower allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload into the Comments section.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42758 | A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in version v2024-01-05 of the indexmenu plugin when is used and enabled in Dokuwiki (Open ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42758</link><description>A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in version v2024-01-05 of the indexmenu plugin when is used and enabled in Dokuwiki (Open Source Wiki Engine). A malicious attacker can input XSS payloads for example when creating or editing existing page, to trigger the XSS on Dokuwiki, which is then stored in .txt file (due to nature of how Dokuwiki is designed), which presents stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7646 | A security issue was discovered in ingress-nginx where an actor with permission to create Ingress objects (in the `networking.k8s.io` or `ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7646</link><description>A security issue was discovered in ingress-nginx where an actor with permission to create Ingress objects (in the `networking.k8s.io` or `extensions` API group) can bypass annotation validation to inject arbitrary commands and obtain the credentials of the ingress-nginx controller. In the default configuration, that credential has access to all secrets in the cluster.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42994 | VTiger CRM &lt;= 8.1.0 does not properly sanitize user input before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL Injection in the "CompanyDeta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42994</link><description>VTiger CRM &lt;= 8.1.0 does not properly sanitize user input before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL Injection in the "CompanyDetails" operation of the "MailManager" module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42995 | VTiger CRM &lt;= 8.1.0 does not correctly check user privileges. A low-privileged user can interact directly with the "Migration" administrativ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42995</link><description>VTiger CRM &lt;= 8.1.0 does not correctly check user privileges. A low-privileged user can interact directly with the "Migration" administrative module to disable arbitrary modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42634 | A Command Injection vulnerability exists in formWriteFacMac of the httpd binary in Tenda AC9 v15.03.06.42. As a result, attacker can execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42634</link><description>A Command Injection vulnerability exists in formWriteFacMac of the httpd binary in Tenda AC9 v15.03.06.42. As a result, attacker can execute OS commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6098 | PTC Kepware ThingWorx Kepware Server Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6098</link><description>When performing an online tag generation to devices which communicate 
using the ControlLogix protocol, a machine-in-the-middle, or a device 
that is not configured correctly, could deliver a response leading to 
unrestricted or unregulated resource allocation. This could cause a 
denial-of-service condition and crash the Kepware application. By 
default, these functions are turned off, yet they remain accessible for 
users who recognize and require their advantages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43807 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 multiple stored XSS was possible on Clouds page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43807</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 multiple stored XSS was possible on Clouds page</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43808 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 self XSS was possible in the HashiCorp Vault plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43808</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 self XSS was possible in the HashiCorp Vault plugin</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43809 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 reflected XSS was possible on the agentPushPreset page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43809</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 reflected XSS was possible on the agentPushPreset page</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43810 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 reflected XSS was possible in the AWS Core plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43810</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 reflected XSS was possible in the AWS Core plugin</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42486 | Cilium vulnerable to information leakage via incorrect ReferenceGrant update logic in Gateway API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42486</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. In versions on the 1.15.x branch prior to 1.15.8 and the 1.16.x branch prior to 1.16.1, ReferenceGrant changes are not correctly propagated in Cilium's GatewayAPI controller, which could lead to Gateway resources being able to access secrets for longer than intended, or to Routes having the ability to forward traffic to backends in other namespaces for longer than intended. This issue has been patched in Cilium v1.15.8 and v1.16.1. As a workaround, any modification of a related Gateway/HTTPRoute/GRPCRoute/TCPRoute CRD (for example, adding any label to any of these resources) will trigger a reconciliation of ReferenceGrants on an affected cluster.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43381 | reNgine vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via DNS Record Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43381</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. Versions 2.1.2 and prior are susceptible to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. This vulnerability occurs when scanning a domain, and if the target domain's DNS record contains an XSS payload, it leads to the execution of malicious scripts in the reNgine's dashboard view when any user views the scan results. The XSS payload is directly fetched from the DNS record of the remote target domain. Consequently, an attacker can execute the attack without requiring any additional input from the target or the reNgine user. A patch is available and expected to be part of version 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2175 | An insecure permissions vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Display Control Center (LDCC) and Lenovo Accessories and Display Manager (LADM)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2175</link><description>An insecure permissions vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Display Control Center (LDCC) and Lenovo Accessories and Display Manager (LADM)

 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4763 | An insecure driver vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Display Control Center (LDCC) and Lenovo Accessories and Display Manager (LADM)

 th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4763</link><description>An insecure driver vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Display Control Center (LDCC) and Lenovo Accessories and Display Manager (LADM)

 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges to kernel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4781 | A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4781</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to crash printer communications until the system is rebooted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4782 | A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4782</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to disrupt the printer's functionality until a manual system reboot occurs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5209 | A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5209</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to deny printing capabilities until the system is rebooted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5210 | A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5210</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to prevent printer services from being reachable until the system is rebooted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6004 | A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6004</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker on a shared network to deny printer connections until the system is rebooted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7144 | JetElements &amp;lt;= 2.6.20 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7144</link><description>The JetElements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' and 'slide_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7145 | JetElements &amp;lt;= 2.6.20 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7145</link><description>The JetElements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.20 via the 'progress_type' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42462 | Bypass multifactor authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42462</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions product upKeeper Manager allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42463 | Leak of organizations messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42463</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions product upKeeper Manager allows Utilizing REST's Trust in the System Resource to Obtain Sensitive Data.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42464 | Leak of user information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42464</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions product upKeeper Manager allows Utilizing REST's Trust in the System Resource to Obtain Sensitive Data.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42465 | Lack of resources and rate limiting - two factor authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42465</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions product upKeeper Manager allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42466 | Lack of resources and rate limiting - login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42466</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions product upKeeper Manager allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7136 | JetSearch &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7136</link><description>The JetSearch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7146 | JetTabs &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7146</link><description>The JetTabs for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3 via the 'switcher_preset' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7147 | JetBlocks &amp;lt;= 1.3.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7147</link><description>The JetBlocks for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple placeholder parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25008 | Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller 6610 - Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25008</link><description>Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller 6610 contains a vulnerability in the Control System where Improper Input Validation can lead to arbitrary code execution, for example to obtain a Linux Shell with the same privileges as the attacker. The attacker would require elevated privileges for example a valid OAM user having the system administrator role to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7501 | Download Plugins and Themes from Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7501</link><description>The Download Plugins and Themes in ZIP from Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the download_theme() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary themes from the website via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. In versions prior to 1.8.6 it was possible to download the entire sites files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6460 | Grow by Tradedoubler &amp;lt;= 2.0.21 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6460</link><description>The Grow by Tradedoubler  WordPress plugin through 2.0.21 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via the component parameter. This makes it possible for attackers to include and execute PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7301 | WordPress File Upload &amp;lt;= 4.24.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7301</link><description>The WordPress File Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7422 | Theme My Login &amp;lt;= 7.1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7422</link><description>The Theme My Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the tml_admin_save_ms_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the theme's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note that this only affects multi-site instances.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 03:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3399 | Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Compliance for GDPR / CCPA &amp;lt;= 2.4.17.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3399</link><description>The Cookie Notice &amp; Compliance for GDPR / CCPA plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cookie_notice_options[refuse_code_head]' parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.4.17.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected /wp-admin/admin.php?page=cookie-notice page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7049 | Custom Field For WP Job Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2 -  Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7049</link><description>The Custom Field For WP Job Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 via the the 'cm_fieldshow' shortcode due to missing validation on the 'job_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to expose potentially sensitive post metadata.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7630 | Relevanssi &amp;lt;= 4.22.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7630</link><description>The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.22.2 via the relevanssi_do_query() due to insufficient limitations on the posts that are returned when searching. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive information from password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7852 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System view_inquiry.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7852</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/inquiries/view_inquiry.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7853 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7853</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=categories/view_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7851 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System Add User Users.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7851</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save of the component Add User Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43374 | Vim heap-use-after-free in src/arglist.c:207</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43374</link><description>The UNIX editor Vim prior to version 9.1.0678 has a use-after-free error in argument list handling. When adding a new file to the argument list, this triggers `Buf*` autocommands. If in such an autocommand the buffer that was just opened is closed (including the window where it is shown), this causes the window structure to be freed which contains a reference to the argument list that we are actually modifying. Once the autocommands are completed, the references to the window and argument list are no longer valid and as such cause an use-after-free. Impact is low since the user must either intentionally add some unusual autocommands that wipe a buffer during creation (either manually or by sourcing a malicious plugin), but it will crash Vim. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.0678.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43378 | calamares-nixos-extensions LUKS keyfile exposure regression on legacy BIOS systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43378</link><description>calamares-nixos-extensions provides Calamares branding and modules for NixOS, a distribution of GNU/Linux. Users who installed NixOS through the graphical installer who used manual disk partitioning to create a setup where the system was booted via legacy BIOS rather than UEFI; some disk partitions are encrypted; but the partitions containing either `/` or `/boot` are unencrypted; have their LUKS disk encryption key file in plain text either in `/crypto_keyfile.bin`, or in a CPIO archive attached to their NixOS initrd. `nixos-install` is not affected, nor are UEFI installations, nor was the default automatic partitioning configuration on legacy BIOS systems. The problem has been fixed in calamares-nixos-extensions 0.3.17, which was included in NixOS. The current installer images for the NixOS 24.05 and unstable (24.11) channels are unaffected. The fix reached 24.05 at 2024-08-13 20:06:59 UTC, and unstable at 2024-08-15 09:00:20 UTC. Installer images downloaded before those times may be vulnerable. The best solution for affected users is probably to back up their data and do a complete reinstallation. However, the mitigation procedure in GHSA-3rvf-24q2-24ww should work solely for the case where `/` is encrypted but `/boot` is not. If `/` is unencrypted, then the `/crypto_keyfile.bin` file will need to be deleted in addition to the remediation steps in the previous advisory. This issue is a partial regression of CVE-2023-36476 / GHSA-3rvf-24q2-24ww, which was more severe as it applied to the default configuration on BIOS systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43370 | gettext.js vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43370</link><description>gettext.js is a GNU gettext port for node and the browser. There is a cross-site scripting (XSS) injection if `.po` dictionary definition files are corrupted. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.0.3. As a workaround, control the origin of the definition catalog to prevent the use of this flaw in the definition of plural forms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7845 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System fetch_it.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7845</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/fetch_it.php. The manipulation of the argument request leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7849 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_create_album buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7849</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This affects the function cgi_create_album of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43369 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting in Ibexa RichText Field Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43369</link><description>Ibexa RichText Field Type is a Field Type for supporting rich formatted text stored in a structured XML format. In versions on the 4.6 branch prior to 4.6.10, the validator for the RichText fieldtype blocklists `javascript:` and `vbscript:` in links to prevent XSS. This can leave other options open, and the check can be circumvented using upper case. Content editing permissions for RichText content is required to exploit this vulnerability, which typically means Editor role or higher. The fix implements an allowlist instead, which allows only approved link protocols. The new check is case insensitive. Version 4.6.10 contains a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7844 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System add_acc.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7844</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/add_acc.php. The manipulation of the argument name/user/position leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7843 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System exportcs.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7843</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tracking/admin/exportcs.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31333 | In _MMU_AllocLevel of mmu_common.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31333</link><description>In _MMU_AllocLevel of mmu_common.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34727 | In sdpu_compare_uuid_with_attr of sdp_utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34727</link><description>In sdpu_compare_uuid_with_attr of sdp_utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34731 | In multiple functions of TranscodingResourcePolicy.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34731</link><description>In multiple functions of TranscodingResourcePolicy.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34734 | In onForegroundServiceButtonClicked of FooterActionsViewModel.kt, there is a possible way to disable the active VPN app from the lockscreen ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34734</link><description>In onForegroundServiceButtonClicked of FooterActionsViewModel.kt, there is a possible way to disable the active VPN app from the lockscreen due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34736 | In setupVideoEncoder of StagefrightRecorder.cpp, there is a possible asynchronous playback when B-frame support is enabled. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34736</link><description>In setupVideoEncoder of StagefrightRecorder.cpp, there is a possible asynchronous playback when B-frame support is enabled. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34737 | In ensureSetPipAspectRatioQuotaTracker of ActivityClientController.java, there is a possible way to generate unmovable and undeletable pip w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34737</link><description>In ensureSetPipAspectRatioQuotaTracker of ActivityClientController.java, there is a possible way to generate unmovable and undeletable pip windows due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34738 | In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way for unprivileged apps to read their own restrictRead app-op states due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34738</link><description>In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way for unprivileged apps to read their own restrictRead app-op states due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34739 | In shouldRestrictOverlayActivities of UsbProfileGroupSettingsManager.java, there is a possible escape from SUW due to a logic error in the c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34739</link><description>In shouldRestrictOverlayActivities of UsbProfileGroupSettingsManager.java, there is a possible escape from SUW due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34740 | In attributeBytesBase64 and attributeBytesHex of BinaryXmlSerializer.java, there is a possible arbitrary XML injection due to an integer ove...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34740</link><description>In attributeBytesBase64 and attributeBytesHex of BinaryXmlSerializer.java, there is a possible arbitrary XML injection due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34741 | In setForceHideNonSystemOverlayWindowIfNeeded of WindowState.java, there is a possible way for message content to be visible on the screensa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34741</link><description>In setForceHideNonSystemOverlayWindowIfNeeded of WindowState.java, there is a possible way for message content to be visible on the screensaver while lock screen visibility settings are restricted by the user due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34742 | In shouldWrite of OwnersData.java, there is a possible edge case that prevents MDM policies from being persisted due to a logic error in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34742</link><description>In shouldWrite of OwnersData.java, there is a possible edge case that prevents MDM policies from being persisted due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34743 | In setTransactionState of SurfaceFlinger.cpp, there is a possible way to perform tapjacking due to a logic error in the code. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34743</link><description>In setTransactionState of SurfaceFlinger.cpp, there is a possible way to perform tapjacking due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7841 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System check_user_name.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7841</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pms/ajax/check_user_name.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7842 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System export_it.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7842</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /tracking/admin/export_it.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7839 | itsourcecode Billing System addbill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7839</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file addbill.php. The manipulation of the argument owners_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43367 | Boa has an uncaught exception when transitioning the state of `AsyncGenerator` objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43367</link><description>Boa is an embeddable and experimental Javascript engine written in Rust. Starting in version 0.16 and prior to version 0.19.0, a wrong assumption made when handling ECMAScript's `AsyncGenerator` operations can cause an uncaught exception on certain scripts. Boa's implementation of `AsyncGenerator` makes the assumption that the state of an `AsyncGenerator` object cannot change while resolving a promise created by methods of `AsyncGenerator` such as `%AsyncGeneratorPrototype%.next`, `%AsyncGeneratorPrototype%.return`, or `%AsyncGeneratorPrototype%.throw`. However, a carefully constructed code could trigger a state transition from a getter method for the promise's `then` property, which causes the engine to fail an assertion of this assumption, causing an uncaught exception. This could be used to create a Denial Of Service attack in applications that run arbitrary ECMAScript code provided by an external user. Version 0.19.0 is patched to correctly handle this case. Users unable to upgrade to the patched version would want to use `std::panic::catch_unwind` to ensure any exceptions caused by the engine don't impact the availability of the main application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42488 | Cilium agent&amp;#x27;s race condition may lead to policy bypass for Host Firewall policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42488</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. Prior to versions 1.14.14 and 1.15.8, a race condition in the Cilium agent can cause the agent to ignore labels that should be applied to a node. This could in turn cause CiliumClusterwideNetworkPolicies intended for nodes with the ignored label to not apply, leading to policy bypass. This issue has been patched in Cilium v1.14.14 and v1.15.8 As the underlying issue depends on a race condition, users unable to upgrade can restart the Cilium agent on affected nodes until the affected policies are confirmed to be working as expected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42487 | Cilium&amp;#x27;s Gateway API route matching order contradicts specification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42487</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. In the 1.15 branch prior to 1.15.8 and the 1.16 branch prior to 1.16.1, Gateway API HTTPRoutes and GRPCRoutes do not follow the match precedence specified in the Gateway API specification. In particular, request headers are matched before request methods, when the specification describes that the request methods must be respected before headers are matched. This could result in unexpected behaviour with security This issue is fixed in Cilium v1.15.8 and v1.16.1. There is no workaround for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7868 | Uninitialized variable in Xpdf 4.05 due to invalid JPEG header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7868</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), invalid header info in a DCT (JPEG) stream can lead to an uninitialized variable in the DCT decoder. The proof-of-concept PDF file causes a segfault attempting to read from an invalid address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43366 | zkvyper ignored loop range bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43366</link><description>zkvyper is a Vyper compiler. Starting in version 1.3.12 and prior to version 1.5.3, since LLL IR has no Turing-incompletness restrictions, it is compiled to a loop with a much more late exit condition. It leads to a loss of funds or other unwanted behavior if the loop body contains it. However, more real-life use cases like iterating over an array are not affected. No contracts were affected by this issue, which was fixed in version 1.5.3. Upgrading and redeploying affected contracts is the only way to avoid the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6456 | SQL Injection vulnerability in AVEVA Historian Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6456</link><description>AVEVA Historian Server has a vulnerability, if exploited, could allow a malicious SQL command to execute under the privileges of an interactive Historian REST Interface user who had been socially engineered by a miscreant into opening a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7838 | itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System addcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7838</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument cname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7867 | Integer overflow and divide-by-zero in Xpdf 4.05 due to bogus page box coordinates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7867</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), very large coordinates in a page box can cause an integer overflow and divide-by-zero.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7866 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in PDF pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7866</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in a pattern resource leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 19:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42476 | oauth CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42476</link><description>In the OAuth library for nim prior to version 0.11, the Authorization Code grant and Implicit grant both rely on the `state` parameter to prevent cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks where a resource owner might have their session associated with protected resources belonging to an attacker. When this project is compiled with certain compiler flags set, it is possible that the `state` parameter will not be checked at all, creating a CSRF vulnerability. Version 0.11 checks the `state` parameter using a regular `if` statement or `doAssert` instead of relying on a plain `assert`. `doAssert` will achieve the desired behavior even if `-d:danger` or `--assertions:off` is set.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42475 | OAuth library for nim allows insecure generation of state values by generateState - entropy too low and uses regular PRNG instead of CSPRNG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42475</link><description>In the OAuth library for nim prior to version 0.11, the `state` values generated by the `generateState` function do not have sufficient entropy. These can be successfully guessed by an attacker allowing them to perform a CSRF vs a user, associating the user's session with the attacker's protected resources. While `state` isn't exactly a cryptographic value, it should be generated in a cryptographically secure way. `generateState` should be using a CSPRNG. Version 0.11 modifies the `generateState` function to generate `state` values of at least 128 bits of entropy while using a CSPRNG.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27729 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the location paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27729</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the location parameter of the calendar event feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27730 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27730</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the cid parameter of the calendar event feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27731 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lack of file type...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27731</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lack of file type filtering in the file attachment parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42472 | Flatpak may allow access to files outside sandbox for certain apps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42472</link><description>Flatpak is a Linux application sandboxing and distribution framework. Prior to versions 1.14.0 and 1.15.10, a malicious or compromised Flatpak app using persistent directories could access and write files outside of what it would otherwise have access to, which is an attack on integrity and confidentiality.

When `persistent=subdir` is used in the application permissions (represented as `--persist=subdir` in the command-line interface), that means that an application which otherwise doesn't have access to the real user home directory will see an empty home directory with a writeable subdirectory `subdir`. Behind the scenes, this directory is actually a bind mount and the data is stored in the per-application directory as `~/.var/app/$APPID/subdir`. This allows existing apps that are not aware of the per-application directory to still work as intended without general home directory access.

However, the application does have write access to the application directory `~/.var/app/$APPID` where this directory is stored. If the source directory for the `persistent`/`--persist` option is replaced by a symlink, then the next time the application is started, the bind mount will follow the symlink and mount whatever it points to into the sandbox.

Partial protection against this vulnerability can be provided by patching Flatpak using the patches in commits ceec2ffc and 98f79773. However, this leaves a race condition that could be exploited by two instances of a malicious app running in parallel. Closing the race condition requires updating or patching the version of bubblewrap that is used by Flatpak to add the new `--bind-fd` option using the patch and then patching Flatpak to use it. If Flatpak has been configured at build-time with `-Dsystem_bubblewrap=bwrap` (1.15.x) or `--with-system-bubblewrap=bwrap` (1.14.x or older), or a similar option, then the version of bubblewrap that needs to be patched is a system copy that is distributed separately, typically `/usr/bin/bwrap`. This configuration is the one that is typically used in Linux distributions. If Flatpak has been configured at build-time with `-Dsystem_bubblewrap=` (1.15.x) or with `--without-system-bubblewrap` (1.14.x or older), then it is the bundled version of bubblewrap that is included with Flatpak that must be patched. This is typically installed as `/usr/libexec/flatpak-bwrap`. This configuration is the default when building from source code.

For the 1.14.x stable branch, these changes are included in Flatpak 1.14.10. The bundled version of bubblewrap included in this release has been updated to 0.6.3. For the 1.15.x development branch, these changes are included in Flatpak 1.15.10. The bundled version of bubblewrap in this release is a Meson "wrap" subproject, which has been updated to 0.10.0. The 1.12.x and 1.10.x branches will not be updated for this vulnerability. Long-term support OS distributions should backport the individual changes into their versions of Flatpak and bubblewrap, or update to newer versions if their stability policy allows it. As a workaround, avoid using applications using the `persistent` (`--persist`) permission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43357 | JavaScript specification issue may lead to type confusion and pointer dereference in implementations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43357</link><description>ECMA-262 is the language specification for the scripting language ECMAScript. A problem in the ECMAScript (JavaScript) specification of async generators, introduced by a May 2021 spec refactor, may lead to mis-implementation in a way that could present as a security vulnerability, such as type confusion and pointer dereference.

The internal async generator machinery calls regular promise resolver functions on IteratorResult (`{ done, value }`) objects that it creates, assuming that the IteratorResult objects will not be then-ables. Unfortunately, these IteratorResult objects inherit from `Object.prototype`, so these IteratorResult objects can be made then-able, triggering arbitrary behaviour, including re-entering the async generator machinery in a way that violates some internal invariants.

The ECMAScript specification is a living standard and the issue has been addressed at the time of this advisory's public disclosure. JavaScript engine implementors should refer to the latest specification and update their implementations to comply with the `AsyncGenerator` section.

## References

- https://github.com/tc39/ecma262/commit/1e24a286d0a327d08e1154926b3ee79820232727
- https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=1901411
- https://github.com/boa-dev/boa/security/advisories/GHSA-f67q-wr6w-23jq
- https://bugs.webkit.org/show_bug.cgi?id=275407
- https://issues.chromium.org/issues/346692561
- https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7652</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25633 | In eLabFTW, if administrators can create users, users can too</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25633</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs.  In an eLabFTW system, one might disallow user creation except for by system administrators, administrators and trusted services. If administrators are allowed to create new users (which is the default), the vulnerability allows any user to create new users in teams where they are members. The new users are automatically validated and administrators are not notified. This can allow a user with permanent or temporary access to a user account or API key to maintain persistence in an eLabFTW system. Additionally, it allows the user to create separate account under a different name, and produce misleading revision histories. No additional privileges are granted to the new user. Users should upgrade to version 5.0.0 to receive a patch. As a workaround, disabling both options that allow *administrators* to create users will provide a mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27728 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the text parameter of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27728</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Friendica v.2023.12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the text parameter of the babel debug feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42757 | Command injection vulnerability in Asus RT-N15U 3.0.0.4.376_3754 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the netstat function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42757</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in Asus RT-N15U 3.0.0.4.376_3754 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the netstat function page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23168 | Vulnerability in Xiexe XSOverlay before build 647 allows non-local websites to send the malicious commands to the WebSocket API, resulting i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23168</link><description>Vulnerability in Xiexe XSOverlay before build 647 allows non-local websites to send the malicious commands to the WebSocket API, resulting in the arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32231 | Stash up to v0.25.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sort parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32231</link><description>Stash up to v0.25.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sort parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22217 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Terminalfour before 8.3.19 allows authenticated users to use specific features to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22217</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Terminalfour before 8.3.19 allows authenticated users to use specific features to access internal services including sensitive information on the server that Terminalfour runs on.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22219 | XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22219</link><description>XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users to submit malicious XML via unspecified features which could lead to various actions such as accessing the underlying server, remote code execution (RCE), or performing Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22218 | XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22218</link><description>XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Terminalfour 8.0.0001 through 8.3.18 and XML JDBC versions up to 1.0.4 allows authenticated users to submit malicious XML via unspecified features which could lead to various actions such as accessing the underlying server, remote code execution (RCE), or performing Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31905 | IBM QRadar Network Packet Capture information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31905</link><description>IBM QRadar Network Packet Capture 7.5 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  289858.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40705 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40705</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server could allow an authenticated user to consume file space resources due to unrestricted file uploads.  IBM X-Force ID:  298279.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31798 | Identical Hardcoded Root Password for All Devices in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to retr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31798</link><description>Identical Hardcoded Root Password for All Devices in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to retrieve the root password for all similar devices</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31799 | Information Disclosure in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to read the WiFi passphrase via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31799</link><description>Information Disclosure in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to read the WiFi passphrase via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31800 | Authentication Bypass in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to gain a privileged command shell ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31800</link><description>Authentication Bypass in GNCC's GC2 Indoor Security Camera 1080P allows an attacker with physical access to gain a privileged command shell via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40704 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40704</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a privileged user to obtain sensitive information from authentication request headers.   IBM X-Force ID:  298277.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42843 | Projectworlds Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the subject parameter in feed.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42843</link><description>Projectworlds Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the subject parameter in feed.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42940 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42940</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42941 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanmode parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42941</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanmode parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42942 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42942</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42943 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42943</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42944 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42944</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42945 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromAddressNat function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42945</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromAddressNat function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42946 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42946</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42947 | An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42947</link><description>An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42948 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42948</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42949 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42949</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42950 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42950</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42951 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the mit_pptpusrpw parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42951</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the mit_pptpusrpw parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42952 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42952</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42953 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPW parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42953</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPW parameter in the fromWizardHandle function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42954 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42954</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42955 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42955</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 (408) was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42966 | Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK N350RT V9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42966</link><description>Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK N350RT V9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains the username and the password, via a crafted request to /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42967 | Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42967</link><description>Incorrect access control in TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 allows attackers to obtain the apmib configuration file, which contains the username and the password, via a crafted request to /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42968 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42968</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Go parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42969 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42969</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeUrlFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42973 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSetlpBind function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42973</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSetlpBind function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42974 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42974</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromwebExcptypemanFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42976 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42976</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromSafeClientFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42977 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42977</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the qos parameter in the fromqossetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42978 | An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42978</link><description>An issue in the handler function in /goform/telnet of Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42979 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ProtForm function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42979</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ProtForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42980 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42980</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the frmL7ImForm function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42981 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42981</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the delno parameter in the fromPptpUserSetting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42982 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42982</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromVirtualSer function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42983 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the pptpPPW parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42983</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the pptpPPW parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42984 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42984</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromP2pListFilter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42985 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42985</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the fromNatlimit function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42986 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42986</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the PPPOEPassword parameter in the fromAdvSetWan function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42987 | Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the modino parameter in the fromPptpUserAdd function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42987</link><description>Tenda FH1206 v02.03.01.35 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the modino parameter in the fromPptpUserAdd function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42681 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in xxl-job v.2.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sub-Task ID component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42681</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in xxl-job v.2.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Sub-Task ID component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43373 | webcrack has an Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability on Windows when Parsing and Saving a Malicious Bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43373</link><description>webcrack is a tool for reverse engineering javascript. An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists in the webcrack module when processing specifically crafted malicious code on Windows systems. This vulnerability is triggered when using the unpack bundles feature in conjunction with the saving feature. If a module name includes a path traversal sequence with Windows path separators, an attacker can exploit this to overwrite files on the host system. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write arbitrary `.js` files to the host system, which can be leveraged to hijack legitimate Node.js modules to gain arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6347 | Unauthorized access to ECU functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6347</link><description>*  Unprotected privileged mode access through UDS session in the Blind Spot Detection Sensor ECU firmware in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) by unauthorized access to the ECU's programming session.
  *  No preconditions implemented for ECU management functionality through UDS session in the Blind Spot Detection Sensor ECU in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to disrupt normal ECU operations by triggering a control command without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7262 | Arbitrary Code Execution in WPS Office</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7262</link><description>Improper path validation in promecefpluginhost.exe in Kingsoft WPS Office version ranging from 12.2.0.13110 to 12.2.0.13489 on Windows allows an attacker to load an arbitrary Windows library.
Using the MHTML format allows an attacker to automatically deliver a malicious library on opening the document and a single user click on a crafted hyperlink leads to the execution of the library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7263 | Arbitrary Code Execution in WPS Office</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7263</link><description>Improper path validation in promecefpluginhost.exe in Kingsoft WPS Office version ranging from 12.2.0.13110 to 12.2.0.13489 on Windows allows an attacker to load an arbitrary Windows library.
The patch released in version 12.2.0.16909 to mitigate CVE-2024-7262 was not restrictive enough. Another hyperlink parameter was not properly sanitized which leads to the execution of an arbitrary Windows library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7833 | D-Link DI-8100 upgrade_filter.asp upgrade_filter_asp command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7833</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function upgrade_filter_asp of the file upgrade_filter.asp. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42679 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42679</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the/ajax/Login.ashx component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42680 | An issue in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain the server absolute path by enterin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42680</link><description>An issue in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain the server absolute path by entering a single quotation mark.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42676 | File Upload vulnerability in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42676</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /nssys/common/Upload. Aspx? Action=DNPageAjaxPostBack component</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42677 | An issue in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42677</link><description>An issue in Huizhi enterprise resource management system v.1.0 and before allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /nssys/common/filehandle. Aspx component</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7832 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_get_fullscreen_photos buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7832</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_get_fullscreen_photos of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument user leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42678 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42678</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Super easy enterprise management system v.1.0.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the /WebSet/DlgGridSet.html component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7830 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_move_photo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7830</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_move_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument photo_name leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7831 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_get_cooliris buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7831</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_get_cooliris of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument path leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7828 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_set_cover buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7829 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi cgi_del_photo buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43275 | WordPress Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43275</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Xyzscripts Insert PHP Code Snippet.This issue affects Insert PHP Code Snippet: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 08:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7411 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7411</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the /vendor/mobiledetect/mobiledetectlib/export/exportToJSON.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7063 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.6.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7063</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.6 via the 'render_raw' function. This can allow authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level permissions and above, to extract sensitive data including private, future, and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7064 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7064</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7815 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Update Employee Page admin-update-employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7815</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-update-employee.php of the component Update Employee Page. The manipulation of the argument emp_fname /emp_lname /emp_nat_idno/emp_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 04:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7814 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Add Employee Page admin-add-employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7814</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin-add-employee.php of the component Add Employee Page. The manipulation of the argument emp_fname /emp_lname /emp_nat_idno/emp_addr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6534 | Directus 10.13.0 - Insecure object reference via PATH presets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6534</link><description>Directus v10.13.0 allows an authenticated external attacker to modify presets created by the same user to assign them to another user. This is possible because the application only validates the user parameter in the 'POST /presets' request but not in the PATCH request. When chained with CVE-2024-6533, it could result in account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6533 | Directus 10.13.0 - DOM-Based cross-site scripting (XSS) via layout_options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6533</link><description>Directus v10.13.0 allows an authenticated external attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript on the client. This is possible because the application injects an attacker-controlled parameter that will be stored in the server and used by the client into an unsanitized DOM element. When chained with CVE-2024-6534, it could result in account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7812 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System POST Parameter ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7812</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /rental_0/rental/ajax.php?action=save_tenant of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument lastname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7813 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Profile Image insufficiently protected credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7813</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /uploadImage/Profile/ of the component Profile Image Handler. The manipulation leads to insufficiently protected credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25024 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25024</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  281430.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7420 | Insert PHP Code Snippet &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Code Snippet Activate/Deactivate/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7420</link><description>The Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the /admin/snippets.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to activate/deactivate and delete code snippets via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7624 | Zephyr Project Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.101 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7624</link><description>The Zephyr Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.101. This is due to the plugin not properly checking a users capabilities before allowing them to enable access to the plugin's settings through the update_user_access() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to grant themselves full access to the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7628 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.15.2 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7628</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 4.15.2. This is due to the use of loose comparison in the 'verify_id_token' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to an @flutter.io email address or phone number. This also requires firebase to be configured on the website and the user to have set up firebase for their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7811 | SourceCodester Daily Expenses Monitoring App delete-expense.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7811</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Daily Expenses Monitoring App 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/delete-expense.php. The manipulation of the argument expense leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7810 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System view_itprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tracking/admin/view_itprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7809 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System nbproject exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tracking/nbproject/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7808 | code-projects Job Portal logindbc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file logindbc.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>