<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:28:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-3543 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request setsyncpppoecfg FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3543</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/setsyncpppoecfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3544 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getCapabilityWeb FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3544</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon of the file /api/wizard/getCapabilityWeb of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3542 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request getsyncpppoecfg FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3542</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014. This affects the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/getsyncpppoecfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3541 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request getSpecs FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3541</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014. Affected by this issue is the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/getSpecs of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3540 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request getCapability FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3540</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014. Affected by this vulnerability is the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/getCapability of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3445 | A Path Traversal "Zip Slip" vulnerability has been identified in mholt/archiver in Go. This vulnerability allows using a crafted ZIP file co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3445</link><description>A Path Traversal "Zip Slip" vulnerability has been identified in mholt/archiver in Go. This vulnerability allows using a crafted ZIP file containing path traversal symlinks to create or overwrite files with the user's privileges or application utilizing the library.

When using the archiver.Unarchive functionality with ZIP files, like this: archiver.Unarchive(zipFile, outputDir),  A crafted ZIP file can be extracted in such a way that it writes files to the affected system with the same privileges as the application executing this vulnerable functionality. Consequently, sensitive files may be overwritten, potentially leading to privilege escalation, code execution, and other severe outcomes in some cases.

It's worth noting that a similar vulnerability was found in TAR files (CVE-2024-0406). Although a fix was implemented, it hasn't been officially released, and the affected project has since been deprecated. The successor to mholt/archiver is a new project called mholt/archives, and its initial release (v0.1.0) removes the Unarchive() functionality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 22:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3539 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getBasicInfo FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3539</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. Affected is the function FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon of the file /api/wizard/getBasicInfo of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 22:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3538 | D-Link DI-8100 jhttpd auth.asp auth_asp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3538</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function auth_asp of the file /auth.asp of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument callback leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 18:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56406 | Perl 5.34, 5.36, 5.38 and 5.40 are vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow when transliterating non-ASCII bytes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56406</link><description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Perl. 

When there are non-ASCII bytes in the left-hand-side of the `tr` operator, `S_do_trans_invmap` can overflow the destination pointer `d`.

   $ perl -e '$_ = "\x{FF}" x 1000000; tr/\xFF/\x{100}/;' 
   Segmentation fault (core dumped)

It is believed that this vulnerability can enable Denial of Service and possibly Code Execution attacks on platforms that lack sufficient defenses.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3423 | IBM Aspera Faspex 5 cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3423</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.11 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3537 | Tutorials-Website Employee Management System update-user.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3537</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tutorials-Website Employee Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update-user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3536 | Tutorials-Website Employee Management System delete-user.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3536</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tutorials-Website Employee Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete-user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 11:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3535 | shuanx BurpAPIFinder BurpApiFinder.db denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3535</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in shuanx BurpAPIFinder up to 2.0.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file BurpApiFinder.db. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 11:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3534 | PowerCreator CMS OpenPublicCourse.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3534</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PowerCreator CMS 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /OpenPublicCourse.aspx. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3533 | YouDianCMS index.html.Attackers cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3533</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in YouDianCMS 9.5.21. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /App/Tpl/Admin/Default/Channel/index.html.Attackers. The manipulation of the argument Parent leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3532 | YouDianCMS index.html.Attackers cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3532</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in YouDianCMS 9.5.21. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /App/Tpl/Member/Default/Order/index.html.Attackers. The manipulation of the argument OrderNumber leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3531 | YouDianCMS index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3531</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in YouDianCMS 9.5.21. This affects an unknown part of the file /App/Tpl/Admin/Default/Log/index.html. The manipulation of the argument UserName/LogType leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 05:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2814 | Crypt::CBC versions between 1.21 and 3.04 for Perl may use insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2814</link><description>Crypt::CBC versions between 1.21 and 3.04 for Perl may use the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

This issue affects operating systems where "/dev/urandom'" is unavailable.  In that case, Crypt::CBC will fallback to use the insecure rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 02:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1455 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1012 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1455</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Woo Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1012 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 08:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1456 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1012 - Authenticated DOM-Based (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1456</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `widgetGrid`, `widgetCountDown`, and `widgetInstagramFeed` methods in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1012 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 08:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13337 | Webcraftic Clearfy – WordPress optimization plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update via &amp;#x27;setup-wbcr_clearfy&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13337</link><description>The Clearfy Cache – WordPress optimization plugin, Minify HTML, CSS &amp; JS, Defer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'setup-wbcr_clearfy' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugins settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13338 | Webcraftic Clearfy – WordPress optimization plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Clear Cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13338</link><description>The Clearfy Cache – WordPress optimization plugin, Minify HTML, CSS &amp; JS, Defer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wclearfy_cache_delete functionality . This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear the cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3276 | SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3276</link><description>The SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Carousel block in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3282 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Membership Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3282</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3 via the user_registration_membership_register_member() due to missing validation on the 'membership_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update any user's membership to any other active or non-active membership type.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3292 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3292</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3 via the user_registration_update_profile_details() due to missing validation on the 'user_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update other user's passwords, if they have access to the user ID and email.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3418 | WPC Admin Columns 2.0.6 - 2.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via User Meta Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3418</link><description>The WPC Admin Columns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions 2.0.6 to 2.1.0. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting user meta values that can be updated through the ajax_edit_save() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update their role to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2871 | WordPress Mega Menu – QuadMenu &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited User Meta Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2871</link><description>The WordPress Mega Menu – QuadMenu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ajax_dismiss_notice() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update any user meta to a value of one, including wp_capabilities which could result in a privilege deescalation of an administrator, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 03:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2841 | Cart66 Cloud &amp;lt;= 2.3.7 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2841</link><description>The Cart66 Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.7 through the publicly accessible phpinfo.php script. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2881 | Developer Toolbar &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2881</link><description>The Developer Toolbar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 through the publicly accessible phpinfo.php script. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29803 | Visual Studio Tools for Applications and SQL Server Management Studio Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29803</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29834 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29834</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32726 | Visual Studio Code Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32726</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>