<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:20:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-5980 | code-projects Restaurant Order System order.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5980</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Restaurant Order System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /order.php. The manipulation of the argument tabidNoti leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35940 | Hard-coded ArchiverSpaApi JWT Signing Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35940</link><description>The ArchiverSpaApi ASP.NET  application uses a hard-coded JWT signing key. An unauthenticated remote attacker can generate and use a verifiable JWT token to access protected ArchiverSpaApi URL endpoints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5978 | Tenda FH1202 VirtualSer fromVirtualSer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5978</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromVirtualSer of the file /goform/VirtualSer. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5979 | code-projects School Fees Payment System branch.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5979</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects School Fees Payment System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /branch.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5976 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System add-pass.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5976</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-pass.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5977 | code-projects School Fees Payment System datatable.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5977</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects School Fees Payment System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /datatable.php. The manipulation of the argument sSortDir_0 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41505 | Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Pessoas" (persons) section via the field "Prof...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41505</link><description>Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Pessoas" (persons) section via the field "Profisso" (professor).</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41503 | Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the field "Ttulo" (title) inside the filter Save op...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41503</link><description>Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the field "Ttulo" (title) inside the filter Save option in the "Busca" (search) function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41504 | Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). In the "Oportunidades" (opportunities) section of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41504</link><description>Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). In the "Oportunidades" (opportunities) section of the application when creating or editing an "Atividade" (activity), the form field "Descrico" allows injection of JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49133 | Libtpms contains a possible out-of-bound access and abort due to HMAC signing issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49133</link><description>Libtpms is a library that targets the integration of TPM functionality into hypervisors, primarily into Qemu. Libtpms, which is derived from the TPM 2.0 reference implementation code published by the Trusted Computing Group, is prone to a potential out of bounds (OOB) read vulnerability. The vulnerability occurs in the ‘CryptHmacSign’ function with an inconsistent pairing of the signKey and signScheme parameters, where the signKey is ALG_KEYEDHASH key and inScheme is an ECC or RSA scheme. The reported vulnerability is in the ‘CryptHmacSign’ function, which is defined in the "Part 4: Supporting Routines – Code" document, section "7.151 - /tpm/src/crypt/CryptUtil.c ". This vulnerability can be triggered from user-mode applications by sending malicious commands to a TPM 2.0/vTPM (swtpm) whose firmware is based on an affected TCG reference implementation. The effect on libtpms is that it will cause an abort due to the detection of the out-of-bounds access, thus for example making a vTPM (swtpm) unavailable to a VM. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.7.12, 0.8.10, 0.9.7, and 0.10.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41502 | Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the form field "Observaces" (observances) in the "...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41502</link><description>Jetimob Plataforma Imobiliaria 20240627-0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the form field "Observaces" (observances) in the "Pessoas" (persons) section when creating or editing either a legal or a natural person.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5974 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System check-status.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5974</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /check-status.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5975 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System download-pass.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5975</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /rpms/download-pass.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36852 | Build Cache Poisoning via Untrusted Pull Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36852</link><description>A critical security vulnerability exists in remote cache extensions for common build systems utilizing bucket-based remote cache (such as those using Amazon S3, Google Cloud Storage, or similar object storage) that allows any contributor with pull request privileges to inject compromised artifacts from an untrusted environment into trusted production environments without detection. 




The vulnerability exploits a fundamental design flaw in the "first-to-cache wins" principle, where artifacts built in untrusted environments (feature branches, pull requests) can poison the cache used by trusted environments (protected branches, production deployments). 




This attack bypasses all traditional security measures including encryption, access controls, and checksum validation because the poisoning occurs during the artifact construction phase, before any security measures are applied.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3052 | An arbitrary write vulnerability in Microsoft signed UEFI firmware from DT Research Inc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3052</link><description>An arbitrary write vulnerability in Microsoft signed UEFI firmware allows for code execution of untrusted software. This allows an attacker to control its value, leading to arbitrary memory writes, including modification of critical firmware settings stored in NVRAM. Exploiting this vulnerability could enable security bypasses, persistence mechanisms, or full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43550 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43550</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43573 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43573</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43574 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43574</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43575 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43575</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43576 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43576</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43577 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43577</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43578 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43578</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43579 | Acrobat Reader | Information Exposure (CWE-200)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43579</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by an Information Exposure vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47111 | Acrobat Reader | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47111</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, causing a disruption in service. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47112 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47112</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30235, 20.005.30763, 25.001.20521 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30327 | InCopy | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30327</link><description>InCopy versions 20.2, 19.5.3 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47107 | InCopy | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47107</link><description>InCopy versions 20.2, 19.5.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5972 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System manage-subadmins.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5972</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-subadmins.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5973 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System add-table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5973</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-table.php. The manipulation of the argument tableno leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5971 | code-projects School Fees Payment System ajx.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects School Fees Payment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajx.php. The manipulation of the argument name_startsWith leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36576 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. A high privileged attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36576</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Server-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36577 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36577</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Script injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5943 | MicroDicom DICOM Viewer Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5943</link><description>MicroDicom 

DICOM Viewer suffers from an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. Remote attackers are able to exploit this issue to potentially execute arbitrary code on affected installations of DICOM Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit the vulnerability in that the user must either visit a malicious website or open a malicious DICOM file locally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0052 | FlashBlade DOS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0052</link><description>Improper input validation performed during the authentication process of FlashBlade could lead to a system Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2474 | Vulnerability in PCX Image Codec Impacts QNX Software Development Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2474</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the PCX image codec in QNX SDP versions 8.0, 7.1 and 7.0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service condition or execute code in the context of the process using the image codec.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36578 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36578</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36580 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36580</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Script injection</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37394 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Dashboards of REDCap 13.1.9 allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37394</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Dashboards of REDCap 13.1.9 allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary web script or HTML by injecting a crafted payload into the 'Dashboard title' and 'Dashboard content' text boxes. This can lead to the execution of malicious scripts when the dashboard is viewed. Users are recommended to update to version 14.2.1 or later to mitigate this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0051 | FlashArray DOS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0051</link><description>Improper input validation performed during the authentication process of FlashArray could lead to a system Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2884 | Out-of-Bounds read vulnerability in TCG TPM2.0 reference implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2884</link><description>TCG TPM2.0 Reference implementation's CryptHmacSign helper function is vulnerable to Out-of-Bounds read due to the lack of validation the signature scheme with the signature key's algorithm. See Errata 1.83 of TCG standard TPM2.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36574 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36574</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure and Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43581 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43581</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 5.0 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43588 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43588</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 5.0 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37395 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Public Survey function of REDCap 13.1.9 allows authenticated users to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37395</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Public Survey function of REDCap 13.1.9 allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary web script or HTML by injecting a crafted payload into the 'Survey Title' and 'Survey Instructions' fields. This vulnerability could be exploited by attackers to execute malicious scripts when the survey is accessed through its public link. It is advised to update to version 14.2.1 or later to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37396 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar function of REDCap 13.1.9 allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37396</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar function of REDCap 13.1.9 allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary web script or HTML by injecting a crafted payload into the 'Notes' field of a calendar event. This could lead to the execution of malicious scripts when the event is viewed. Updating to version 14.2.1 or later is recommended to remediate this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36575 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Exposure of Sensitive Information Through Data Queries vulnerability. An u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36575</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions prior to WMS 5.2, contain an Exposure of Sensitive Information Through Data Queries vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43706 | Kibana Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43706</link><description>Improper authorization in Kibana can lead to privilege abuse via a direct HTTP request to a Synthetic monitor endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24065 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24065</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24068 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24068</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24069 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24069</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29828 | Windows Schannel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29828</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32710 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32710</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32712 | Win32k Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32712</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32713 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32713</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32714 | Windows Installer Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32714</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32715 | Remote Desktop Protocol Client Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32715</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32716 | Windows Media Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32716</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32718 | Windows SMB Client Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32718</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32719 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32719</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32720 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32720</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32721 | Windows Recovery Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32721</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32722 | Windows Storage Port Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32722</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32724 | Local Security Authority Subsystem Service (LSASS) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32724</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32725 | DHCP Server Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32725</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33050 | DHCP Server Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33050</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33052 | Windows DWM Core Library Information Disclosure  Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33052</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33053 | Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WEBDAV) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33053</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33055 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33055</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33056 | Windows Local Security Authority (LSA) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33056</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33057 | Windows Local Security Authority (LSA) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33057</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33058 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33058</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33059 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33059</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33060 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33060</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33061 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33061</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33062 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33062</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33063 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33063</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33064 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33064</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33065 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33065</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33066 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33066</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33067 | Windows Task Scheduler Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33067</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33068 | Windows Standards-Based Storage Management Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33068</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33069 | Windows App Control for Business Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33069</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33070 | Windows Netlogon Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33070</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33071 | Windows KDC Proxy Service (KPSSVC) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33071</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33073 | Windows SMB Client Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33073</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33075 | Windows Installer Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33075</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47160 | Windows Shortcut Files Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47160</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47162 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47162</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47163 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47163</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47164 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47164</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47165 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47165</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47166 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47166</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47167 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47167</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47168 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47168</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47169 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47169</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47170 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47170</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47171 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47171</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47172 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47172</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47173 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47173</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47174 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47174</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47175 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47175</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47176 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47176</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47953 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47953</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47955 | Windows Remote Access Connection Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47955</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47956 | Windows Security App Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47956</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47957 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47957</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47962 | Windows SDK Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47962</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47968 | Microsoft AutoUpdate (MAU) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47968</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47969 | Windows Virtualization-Based Security (VBS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47969</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47977 | Nuance Digital Engagement Platform Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47977</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5970 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System add-subadmin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5970</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57190 | Erxes &lt;1.6.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An attacker can bypass authentication by providing a "User" HTTP header that contain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57190</link><description>Erxes &lt;1.6.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An attacker can bypass authentication by providing a "User" HTTP header that contains any user, allowing them to talk to any GraphQL endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29184 | An incomplete cleanup vulnerability [CWE-459] in FortiOS 7.2 all versions and before  &amp; FortiProxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2 and before 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29184</link><description>An incomplete cleanup vulnerability [CWE-459] in FortiOS 7.2 all versions and before  &amp; FortiProxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2 and before 7.0.8 allows a VDOM privileged attacker to add SSH key files on the system silently via crafted CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48786 | A server-side request forgery vulnerability [CWE-918] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.2 and before 7.2.6 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48786</link><description>A server-side request forgery vulnerability [CWE-918] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.2 and before 7.2.6 may allow an authenticated attacker to perform internal requests via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32119 | An improper authentication vulnerability [CWE-287] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS version 7.4.0 and before 7.2.4 allows an unauthenticated attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32119</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability [CWE-287] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS version 7.4.0 and before 7.2.4 allows an unauthenticated attacker with the knowledge of the targeted user's FCTUID and VDOM to perform operations such as uploading or tagging on behalf of the targeted user via specially crafted TCP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45329 | A authorization bypass through user-controlled key in Fortinet FortiPortal versions 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, and versions 7.0.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45329</link><description>A authorization bypass through user-controlled key in Fortinet FortiPortal versions 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.8 may allow an authenticated attacker to view unauthorized device information via key modification in API requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50562 | An Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] in FortiOS SSL-VPN version 7.6.0, version 7.4.6 and below, version 7.2.10 and bel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50562</link><description>An Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] in FortiOS SSL-VPN version 7.6.0, version 7.4.6 and below, version 7.2.10 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions may allow an attacker in possession of a cookie used to log in the SSL-VPN portal to log in again, although the session has expired or was logged out.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50568 | A channel accessible by non-endpoint vulnerability [CWE-300] in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.7 and before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50568</link><description>A channel accessible by non-endpoint vulnerability [CWE-300] in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.7 and before 7.0.14 &amp; FortiProxy version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.9 and before 7.0.16 allows an unauthenticated attacker with the knowledge of device specific data to spoof the identity of a downstream device of the security fabric via crafted TCP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54019 | A improper validation of certificate with host mismatch in Fortinet FortiClientWindows version 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, and 7.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54019</link><description>A improper validation of certificate with host mismatch in Fortinet FortiClientWindows version 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, and 7.0 all versions allow an unauthorized attacker to redirect VPN connections via DNS spoofing or another form of redirection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57189 | In Erxes &lt;1.6.2, an authenticated attacker can write to arbitrary files on the system using a Path Traversal vulnerability in the importHist...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57189</link><description>In Erxes &lt;1.6.2, an authenticated attacker can write to arbitrary files on the system using a Path Traversal vulnerability in the importHistoriesCreate GraphQL mutation handler.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22251 | An improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints vulnerability [CWE-923] in FortiOS 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22251</link><description>An improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints vulnerability [CWE-923] in FortiOS 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions may allow an unauthenticated attacker to inject unauthorized sessions via crafted FGSP session synchronization packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22254 | An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability [CWE-269] affecting Fortinet FortiOS version 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22254</link><description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability [CWE-269] affecting Fortinet FortiOS version 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0 through 7.0.16 and before 6.4.15, FortiProxy version 7.6.0 through 7.6.1 and before 7.4.7 &amp; FortiWeb version 7.6.0 through 7.6.1 and before 7.4.6 allows an authenticated attacker with at least read-only admin permissions to gain super-admin privileges via crafted requests to Node.js websocket module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22256 | A improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges in Fortinet FortiPAM 1.4.0 through 1.4.1, 1.3.0, 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22256</link><description>A improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges in Fortinet FortiPAM 1.4.0 through 1.4.1, 1.3.0, 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1.0.0 through 1.0.3, FortiSRA 1.4.0 through 1.4.1 allows attacker to improper access control via specially crafted HTTP requests</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24471 | An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiOS version 7.6.1 and below, version 7.4.7 and below may allow an EAP veri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24471</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiOS version 7.6.1 and below, version 7.4.7 and below may allow an EAP verified remote user to connect from FortiClient via revoked certificate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25250 | An Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in FortiOS version 7.6.0, version 7.4.7 and below, 7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25250</link><description>An Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in FortiOS version 7.6.0, version 7.4.7 and below, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions SSL-VPN web-mode may allow an authenticated user to access full SSL-VPN settings via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31104 | An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiADC 7.6.0 throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31104</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiADC 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, 7.1.0 through 7.1.4, 7.0 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6.1 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33112 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33112</link><description>IBM AIX 7.3 and IBM VIOS 4.1.1 Perl implementation could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability to execute arbitrary code due to improper neutralization of pathname input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47108 | Substance3D - Painter | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47108</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 11.0.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5969 | D-Link DIR-632 HTTP POST Request biurl_grou FUN_00425fd8 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5969</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-632 FW103B08 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function FUN_00425fd8 of the file /biurl_grou of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20599 | Improper register access control in ASP may allow a privileged attacker to perform unauthorized access to ASP’s Crypto Co-Processor (CCP) re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20599</link><description>Improper register access control in ASP may allow a privileged attacker to perform unauthorized access to ASP’s Crypto Co-Processor (CCP) registers from x86, resulting in potential loss of control of cryptographic key pointer/index, leading to loss of integrity or confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57186 | In erxes &lt;1.6.2, an unauthenticated attacker can read arbitrary files from the system using a Path Traversal vulnerability in the /read-file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57186</link><description>In erxes &lt;1.6.2, an unauthenticated attacker can read arbitrary files from the system using a Path Traversal vulnerability in the /read-file endpoint handler.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30317 | InDesign Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30317</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30321 | InDesign Desktop | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30321</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, causing disruption in service. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43558 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43558</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43589 | InDesign Desktop | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43589</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43590 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43590</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43593 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43593</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47104 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47104</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47105 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47105</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47106 | InDesign Desktop | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47106</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.2, ID19.5.3 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27206 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27206</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.8, 2.4.7-p5, 2.4.6-p10, 2.4.5-p12, 2.4.4-p13 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain limited write access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27207 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27207</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.8, 2.4.7-p5, 2.4.6-p10, 2.4.5-p12, 2.4.4-p13 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in privilege escalation. A low privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43585 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Authorization (CWE-285)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43585</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.8, 2.4.7-p5, 2.4.6-p10, 2.4.5-p12, 2.4.4-p13 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized access leading to a limited impact to confidentiality and a high impact to integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43586 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43586</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.8, 2.4.7-p5, 2.4.6-p10, 2.4.5-p12, 2.4.4-p13 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in privilege escalation. A low privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized elevated access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47110 | Adobe Commerce | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47110</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.8, 2.4.7-p5, 2.4.6-p10, 2.4.5-p12, 2.4.4-p13 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a high privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4653 | Remote Code Execution leads to Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in the backup name field may allow OS command injection. This issue affects Pandora ITSM 5.0.105.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4678 | Remote Code Execution leads to Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in the chromium_path variable may allow OS command injection. This issue affects Pandora ITSM 5.0.105.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49143 | Nautobot may allows uploaded media files to be accessible without authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49143</link><description>Nautobot is a Network Source of Truth and Network Automation Platform. Prior to v2.4.10 and v1.6.32 , files uploaded by users to Nautobot's MEDIA_ROOT directory, including DeviceType image attachments as well as images attached to a Location, Device, or Rack, are served to users via a URL endpoint that was not enforcing user authentication. As a consequence, such files can be retrieved by anonymous users who know or can guess the correct URL for a given file. Nautobot v2.4.10 and v1.6.32 address this issue by adding enforcement of Nautobot user authentication to this endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49142 | Nautobot vulnerable to secrets exposure and data manipulation through Jinja2 templating</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49142</link><description>Nautobot is a Network Source of Truth and Network Automation Platform. All users of Nautobot versions prior to 2.4.10 or prior to 1.6.32 are potentially affected. Due to insufficient security configuration of the Jinja2 templating feature used in computed fields, custom links, etc. in Nautobot, a malicious user could configure this feature set in ways that could expose the value of Secrets defined in Nautobot when the templated content is rendered or that could call Python APIs to modify data within Nautobot when the templated content is rendered, bypassing the object permissions assigned to the viewing user. Nautobot versions 1.6.32 and 2.4.10 will include fixes for the vulnerability. The vulnerability can be partially mitigated by configuring object permissions appropriately to limit certain actions to only trusted users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48879 | OctoPrint Vulnerable to Denial of Service through malformed HTTP request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48879</link><description>OctoPrint versions up until and including 1.11.1 contain a vulnerability that allows any unauthenticated attacker to send a manipulated broken multipart/form-data request to OctoPrint and through that make the web server component become unresponsive. The issue can be triggered by a broken multipart/form-data request lacking an end boundary to any of OctoPrint's endpoints implemented through the octoprint.server.util.tornado.UploadStorageFallbackHandler request handler. The request handler will get stuck in an endless busy loop, looking for a part of the request that will never come. As Tornado is single-threaded, that will effectively block the whole web server. The vulnerability has been patched in version 1.11.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48937 | matrix-sdk-crypto vulnerable to sender of encrypted events being spoofed by homeserver administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48937</link><description>matrix-rust-sdk is an implementation of a Matrix client-server library in Rust. matrix-sdk-crypto since version 0.8.0 and up to 0.11.0 does not correctly validate the sender of an encrypted event. Accordingly, a malicious homeserver operator can modify events served to clients, making those events appear to the recipient as if they were sent by another user. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.11.1 and 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41797 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41797</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC324-4 (6GK5328-4TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC324-4 EEC (6GK5328-4TS00-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC332 (6GK5332-0GA00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC416-8 (6GK5424-8TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC424-4 (6GK5428-4TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XC432 (6GK5432-0GR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XCH328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XCM324 (6GK5324-8TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XCM328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XCM332 (6GK5332-0GA01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR326-8 EEC (6GK5334-2TS00-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRH334 (24 V DC, 8xFO, CC) (6GK5334-2TS01-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (24V DC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.1). Affected devices contain an incorrect authorization check vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with "guest" role to invoke an internal "do system" command which exceeds their privileges. This command allows the execution of certain low-risk actions, the most critical of which is clearing the local system log.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30220 | GeoTools, GeoServer, and GeoNetwork XML External Entity (XXE) Processing Vulnerability in XSD schema handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30220</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. GeoTools Schema class use of Eclipse XSD library to represent schema data structure is vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) exploit. This impacts whoever exposes XML processing with gt-xsd-core involved in parsing, when the documents carry a reference to an external XML schema. The gt-xsd-core Schemas class is not using the EntityResolver provided by the ParserHandler (if any was configured). This also impacts users of gt-wfs-ng DataStore where the ENTITY_RESOLVER connection parameter was not being used as intended. This vulnerability is fixed in GeoTools 33.1, 32.3, 31.7, and 28.6.1, GeoServer 2.27.1, 2.26.3, and 2.25.7, and GeoNetwork 4.4.8 and 4.2.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40567 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40567</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC324-4 (6GK5328-4TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC324-4 EEC (6GK5328-4TS00-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC332 (6GK5332-0GA00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC416-8 (6GK5424-8TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC424-4 (6GK5428-4TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC432 (6GK5432-0GR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCH328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM324 (6GK5324-8TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM332 (6GK5332-0GA01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 EEC (6GK5334-2TS00-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRH334 (24 V DC, 8xFO, CC) (6GK5334-2TS01-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24V DC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2). The "Load Rollback" functionality in the web interface of affected products contains an incorrect authorization check vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with "guest" role to make the affected product roll back configuration changes made by privileged users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40568 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40568</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC324-4 (6GK5328-4TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC324-4 EEC (6GK5328-4TS00-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC332 (6GK5332-0GA00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC416-8 (6GK5424-8TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC424-4 (6GK5428-4TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC432 (6GK5432-0GR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCH328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM324 (6GK5324-8TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM332 (6GK5332-0GA01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 EEC (6GK5334-2TS00-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRH334 (24 V DC, 8xFO, CC) (6GK5334-2TS01-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24V DC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2). An internal session termination functionality in the web interface of affected products contains an incorrect authorization check vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with "guest" role to terminate legitimate users' sessions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40569 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40569</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC316-8 (6GK5324-8TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC324-4 (6GK5328-4TS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC324-4 EEC (6GK5328-4TS00-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC332 (6GK5332-0GA00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC416-8 (6GK5424-8TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC424-4 (6GK5428-4TR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XC432 (6GK5432-0GR00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCH328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2EC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM324 (6GK5324-8TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM328 (6GK5328-4TS01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XCM332 (6GK5332-0GA01-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR302-32 (6GK5334-5TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR322-12 (6GK5334-3TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 (6GK5334-2TS00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR326-8 EEC (6GK5334-2TS00-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR502-32 (6GK5534-5TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR522-12 (6GK5534-3TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XR526-8 (6GK5534-2TR00-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRH334 (24 V DC, 8xFO, CC) (6GK5334-2TS01-2ER3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-3AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24 V DC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (24V DC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-2AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 12xFO) (6GK5334-3TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230 V AC, 8xFO) (6GK5334-2TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2), SCALANCE XRM334 (2x230V AC, 2x10G, 24xSFP, 8xSFP+) (6GK5334-5TS01-4AR3) (All versions &lt; V3.2). The "Load Configuration from Local PC" functionality in the web interface of affected products contains a race condition vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to make the affected product load an attacker controlled configuration instead of the legitimate one. Successful exploitation requires that a legitimate administrator invokes the functionality and the attacker wins the race condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40585 | A vulnerability has been identified in Energy Services (All versions with G5DFR). Affected solutions using G5DFR contain default credentials...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40585</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Energy Services (All versions with G5DFR). Affected solutions using G5DFR contain default credentials. This could allow an attacker to gain control of G5DFR component and tamper with outputs from the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40591 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40591</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1400 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1500 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1501 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1510 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1511 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1512 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1524 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1536 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5). The 'Log Viewers' tool in the web interface of affected devices is vulnerable to command injection due to missing server side input sanitation. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute the 'tail' command with root privileges and disclose contents of all files in the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44043 | Keyoti SearchUnit prior to 9.0.0. is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in /Keyoti_SearchEngine_Web_Common/SearchService.svc/G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44043</link><description>Keyoti SearchUnit prior to 9.0.0. is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in /Keyoti_SearchEngine_Web_Common/SearchService.svc/GetResults and /Keyoti_SearchEngine_Web_Common/SearchService.svc/GetLocationAndContentCategories. An attacker can specify their own SMB server as the indexDirectory value when making POST requests to the affected components. In doing so an attacker can get the SearchUnit server to read and write configuration and log files from/to the attackers server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44044 | Keyoti SearchUnit prior to 9.0.0. is vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE). An attacker who can force a vulnerable SearchUnit host into pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44044</link><description>Keyoti SearchUnit prior to 9.0.0. is vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE). An attacker who can force a vulnerable SearchUnit host into parsing maliciously crafted XML and/or DTD files can exfiltrate some files from the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48067 | OctoPrint vulnerable to possible file extraction via upload endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48067</link><description>OctoPrint provides a web interface for controlling consumer 3D printers. OctoPrint versions up until and including 1.11.1 contain a vulnerability that allows an attacker with the FILE_UPLOAD permission to exfiltrate files from the host that OctoPrint has read access to, by moving them into the upload folder where they then can be downloaded from. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37100 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized User in HPE Aruba Networking Private 5G Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37100</link><description>A vulnerability in the APIs of HPE Aruba Networking Private 5G Core could potentially expose sensitive information to unauthorized users. 
A successful exploitation could allow an attacker to iteratively navigate through the filesystem and ultimately download protected system files containing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30145 | GeoServer has an Infinite Loop Vulnerability in Jiffle process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30145</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Malicious Jiffle scripts can be executed by GeoServer, either as a rendering transformation in WMS dynamic styles or as a WPS process, that can enter an infinite loop to trigger denial of service. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.27.0, 2.26.3, and 2.25.7. This vulnerability can be mitigated by disabling WMS dynamic styling and  the Jiffle process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27505 | GeoServer Missing Authorization on REST API Index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27505</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. It is possible to bypass the default REST API security and access the index page. The REST API security handles rest and its subpaths but not rest with an extension (e.g., rest.html). The REST API index can disclose whether certain extensions are installed. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.26.3 and 2.25.6. As a workaround, in ${GEOSERVER_DATA_DIR}/security/config.xml, change the paths for the rest filter to /rest.*,/rest/** and change the paths for the gwc filter to /gwc/rest.*,/gwc/rest/** and restart GeoServer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38524 | GWC Home Page communicate version and revision information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38524</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. org.geowebcache.GeoWebCacheDispatcher.handleFrontPage(HttpServletRequest, HttpServletResponse) has no check to hide potentially sensitive information from users except for a hidden system property to hide the storage locations that defaults to showing the locations. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.26.2 and 2.25.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40625 | GeoServer Coverage REST API Allows Server Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40625</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. The Coverage rest api /workspaces/{workspaceName}/coveragestores/{storeName}/{method}.{format} allows attackers to upload files with a specified url (with {method} equals 'url') with no restrict. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.26.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5335 | Privilege Ecalation due to Untrusted Search Path Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5335</link><description>A maliciously crafted binary file when downloaded could lead to escalation of privileges to NT AUTHORITY/SYSTEM due to an untrusted search path being utilized in the Autodesk Installer application. Exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34711 | GeoServer has improper ENTITY_RESOLUTION_ALLOWLIST URI validation in XML Processing (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34711</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. An improper URI validation vulnerability exists that enables an unauthorized attacker to perform XML External Entities (XEE) attack, then send GET request to any HTTP server. By default, GeoServer use PreventLocalEntityResolver class from GeoTools to filter out malicious URIs in XML entities before resolving them. The URI must match the regex (?i)(jar:file|http|vfs)[^?#;]*\\.xsd. But the regex leaves a chance for attackers to request to any HTTP server or limited file. Attacker can abuse this to scan internal networks and gain information about them then exploit further. GeoServer 2.25.0 and greater default to the use of ENTITY_RESOLUTION_ALLOWLIST and does not require you to provide a system property.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22455 | A hardcoded key in Ivanti Workspace Control before version 10.19.0.0 allows a local authenticated attacker to decrypt stored SQL credentials...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22455</link><description>A hardcoded key in Ivanti Workspace Control before version 10.19.0.0 allows a local authenticated attacker to decrypt stored SQL credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22463 | A hardcoded key in Ivanti Workspace Control before version 10.19.10.0 allows a local authenticated attacker to decrypt the stored environmen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22463</link><description>A hardcoded key in Ivanti Workspace Control before version 10.19.10.0 allows a local authenticated attacker to decrypt the stored environment password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26394 | SolarWinds SWOSH Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26394</link><description>SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted

 is susceptible to an open redirection vulnerability. The URL is not properly sanitized, and an attacker could manipulate the string to redirect a user to a malicious site. The attack complexity is high, and authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26395 | SolarWinds SWOSH DOM-based reflective XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26395</link><description>SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted

 was susceptible to a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to an unsanitized field in the URL. The attack requires authentication using an administrator-level account and user interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5353 | A hardcoded key in Ivanti Workspace Control before version 10.19.10.0 allows a local authenticated attacker to decrypt stored SQL credential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5353</link><description>A hardcoded key in Ivanti Workspace Control before version 10.19.10.0 allows a local authenticated attacker to decrypt stored SQL credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29198 | GeoServer Vulnerable to Unauthenticated SSRF via TestWfsPost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29198</link><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. It possible to achieve Service Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Demo request endpoint if Proxy Base URL has not been set. Upgrading to GeoServer 2.24.4, or 2.25.2, removes the TestWfsPost servlet resolving this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46612 | The Panel Designer dashboard in Airleader Master and Easy before 6.36 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a wizard/wor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46612</link><description>The Panel Designer dashboard in Airleader Master and Easy before 6.36 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a wizard/workspace.jsp unrestricted file upload. To exploit this, the attacker must login to the administrator console (default credentials are weak and easily guessable) and upload a JSP file via the Panel Designer dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49454 | WordPress TinySalt &amp;lt; 3.10.0 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49454</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in LoftOcean TinySalt allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects TinySalt: from n/a before 3.10.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49455 | WordPress TinySalt &amp;lt; 3.10.0 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49455</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in LoftOcean TinySalt allows Object Injection.This issue affects TinySalt: from n/a before 3.10.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49507 | WordPress CozyStay &amp;lt; 1.7.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49507</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in LoftOcean CozyStay allows Object Injection.This issue affects CozyStay: from n/a before 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49509 | WordPress Audio Editor &amp;amp; Recorder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49509</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Roland Beaussant Audio Editor &amp; Recorder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Audio Editor &amp; Recorder: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49510 | WordPress Min Max Step Quantity Limits Manager for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49510</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPFactory Min Max Step Quantity Limits Manager for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Min Max Step Quantity Limits Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49511 | WordPress Civi Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to User Deactivation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49511</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in uxper Civi Framework allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Civi Framework: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43699 | Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows bypass of field level security controls for O...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43699</link><description>Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows bypass of field level security controls for OmniUICard objects. 

This impacts OmniStudio: before Spring 2025</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43698 | Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows bypass of field level security controls for S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43698</link><description>Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows bypass of field level security controls for Salesforce objects. 
This impacts OmniStudio: before Spring 2025</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43697 | Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (DataMapper) allows exposure of encrypted data.
This impacts Omn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43697</link><description>Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (DataMapper) allows exposure of encrypted data.
This impacts OmniStudio: before Spring 2025</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2918 | Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2918</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43701 | Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows exposure of Custom Settings data. 

This impa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43701</link><description>Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows exposure of Custom Settings data. 

This impacts OmniStudio: before version 254.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4577 | Smash Balloon Custom Facebook Feed &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `data-color` Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4577</link><description>The Smash Balloon Social Post Feed – Simple Social Feeds for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the data-color attribute in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4774 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.11.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4774</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the data-countdown attribute of Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.11.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43700 | Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows exposure of encrypted data. 

This impacts Om...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43700</link><description>Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Salesforce OmniStudio (FlexCards) allows exposure of encrypted data. 

This impacts OmniStudio versions prior to Spring 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41657 | AUMA: Incorrect delivery status of the Bluetooth configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41657</link><description>Due to an undocumented active bluetooth stack on products delivered within the period 01.01.2024 to 09.05.2025 fingerprinting is possible by an unauthenticated adjacent attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13089 | Authenticated RCE in update functionality in Guardian/CMC before 24.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13089</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability within the update functionality may allow an authenticated administrator to execute unauthorized arbitrary OS commands.



Users with administrative privileges may upload update packages to upgrade the versions of Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC.

While these updates are signed and their signatures are validated prior to installation, an improper signature validation check has been identified.

This issue could potentially enable users to execute commands remotely on the appliance, thereby impacting confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13090 | Privilege escalation in Guardian/CMC before 24.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13090</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability may enable a service account to elevate its privileges.



The sudo rules configured for a local service account were excessively permissive, potentially allowing administrative access if a malicious actor could execute arbitrary commands as that account.

It is important to note that no such vector has been identified in this instance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40655 | SQL injection vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40655</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the name parameter in /antcatalogue.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40656 | SQL injection vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40656</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the cod parameter in /administer/node-selection/data.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40657 | SQL injection vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40657</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the codform parameter in /modules/forms/collectform.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40658 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40658</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access the private area setting the option parameter equal to 0, 1 or 2 in /administer/selectionnode/framesSelection.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40659 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40659</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access the private area setting the option parameter equal to 0, 1 or 2 in /administer/selectionnode/framesSelectionNetworks.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40660 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40660</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access the private area setting the option parameter equal to 0, 1 or 2 in /administer/select node/data.asp?mode=catalogue&amp;amp;id1=1&amp;amp;id2=1session=&amp;amp;cod=1&amp;amp;networks=0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40661 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40661</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access the private area setting the option parameter equal to 0, 1 or 2 in /administer/selectionnode/selection.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40662 | Absolute path disclosure vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40662</link><description>Absolute path disclosure vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to view the contents of webroot/file, if navigating to a non-existent file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40654 | SQL injection vulnerability in DM Corporative CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40654</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in DM Corporative CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the name and cod parameters in /antbuspre.asp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3117 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability
exists impacting configuration fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3117</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability
exists impacting configuration file paths that could cause an unvalidated data injected by authenticated
malicious user leading to modify or read data in a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4681 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Instant Privilege Access allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4681</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Instant Privilege Access allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects upKeeper Instant Privilege Access: before 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3116 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial of Service when an
authenticated malicious user sends special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3116</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial of Service when an
authenticated malicious user sends special malformed HTTPS request containing improper formatted body
data to the controller.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3905 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability
exists impacting PLC system varia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3905</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability
exists impacting PLC system variables that could cause an unvalidated data injected by authenticated
malicious user leading to modify or read data in a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4680 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Instant Privilege Access allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4680</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Instant Privilege Access allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects upKeeper Instant Privilege Access: before 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3112 | CWE-400: Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability exists that could cause Denial of Service when an
authenticated malicious user send...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3112</link><description>CWE-400: Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability exists that could cause Denial of Service when an
authenticated malicious user sends manipulated HTTPS Content-Length header to the webserver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3898 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial of Service when an
authenticated malicious user sends HTTPS r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3898</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial of Service when an
authenticated malicious user sends HTTPS request containing invalid data type to the webserver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3899 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability
exists in Certificates page on We...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3899</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability
exists in Certificates page on Webserver that could cause an unvalidated data injected by authenticated
malicious user leading to modify or read data in a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5740 | CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability exists that
could cause arbitrary file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5740</link><description>CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability exists that
could cause arbitrary file writes when an unauthenticated user on the web server manipulates file path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5741 | CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability exists that
could cause arbitrary file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5741</link><description>CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability exists that
could cause arbitrary file reads from the charging station. The exploitation of this vulnerability does require an
authenticated session of the web server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5742 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5742</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an authenticated user modifies configuration parameters on the web server</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5743 | CWE-78: I Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')
vulnerability exists that could cause r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5743</link><description>CWE-78: I Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')
vulnerability exists that could cause remote control over the charging station when an authenticated user
modifies configuration parameters on the web server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27817 | Apache Kafka Client: Arbitrary file read and SSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27817</link><description>A possible arbitrary file read and SSRF vulnerability has been identified in Apache Kafka Client. Apache Kafka Clients accept configuration data for setting the SASL/OAUTHBEARER connection with the brokers, including "sasl.oauthbearer.token.endpoint.url" and "sasl.oauthbearer.jwks.endpoint.url". Apache Kafka allows clients to read an arbitrary file and return the content in the error log, or sending requests to an unintended location. In applications where Apache Kafka Clients configurations can be specified by an untrusted party, attackers may use the "sasl.oauthbearer.token.endpoint.url" and "sasl.oauthbearer.jwks.endpoint.url" configuratin to read arbitrary contents of the disk and environment variables or make requests to an unintended location. In particular, this flaw may be used in Apache Kafka Connect to escalate from REST API access to filesystem/environment/URL access, which may be undesirable in certain environments, including SaaS products. 

Since Apache Kafka 3.9.1/4.0.0, we have added a system property ("-Dorg.apache.kafka.sasl.oauthbearer.allowed.urls") to set the allowed urls in SASL JAAS configuration. In 3.9.1, it accepts all urls by default for backward compatibility. However in 4.0.0 and newer, the default value is empty list and users have to set the allowed urls explicitly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27818 | Apache Kafka: Possible RCE attack via SASL JAAS LdapLoginModule configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27818</link><description>A possible security vulnerability has been identified in Apache Kafka.
This requires access to a alterConfig to the cluster resource, or Kafka Connect worker, and the ability to create/modify connectors on it with an arbitrary Kafka client SASL JAAS config
and a SASL-based security protocol, which has been possible on Kafka clusters since Apache Kafka 2.0.0 (Kafka Connect 2.3.0).
When configuring the broker via config file or AlterConfig command, or connector via the Kafka Kafka Connect REST API, an authenticated operator can set the `sasl.jaas.config`
property for any of the connector's Kafka clients to "com.sun.security.auth.module.LdapLoginModule", which can be done via the
`producer.override.sasl.jaas.config`, `consumer.override.sasl.jaas.config`, or `admin.override.sasl.jaas.config` properties.
This will allow the server to connect to the attacker's LDAP server
and deserialize the LDAP response, which the attacker can use to execute java deserialization gadget chains on the Kafka connect server.
Attacker can cause unrestricted deserialization of untrusted data (or) RCE vulnerability when there are gadgets in the classpath.

Since Apache Kafka 3.0.0, users are allowed to specify these properties in connector configurations for Kafka Connect clusters running with out-of-the-box
configurations. Before Apache Kafka 3.0.0, users may not specify these properties unless the Kafka Connect cluster has been reconfigured with a connector
client override policy that permits them.

Since Apache Kafka 3.9.1/4.0.0, we have added a system property ("-Dorg.apache.kafka.disallowed.login.modules") to disable the problematic login modules usage
in SASL JAAS configuration. Also by default "com.sun.security.auth.module.JndiLoginModule,com.sun.security.auth.module.LdapLoginModule" are disabled in Apache Kafka Connect 3.9.1/4.0.0. 

We advise the Kafka users to validate connector configurations and only allow trusted LDAP configurations. Also examine connector dependencies for 
vulnerable versions and either upgrade their connectors, upgrading that specific dependency, or removing the connectors as options for remediation. Finally,
in addition to leveraging the "org.apache.kafka.disallowed.login.modules" system property, Kafka Connect users can also implement their own connector
client config override policy, which can be used to control which Kafka client properties can be overridden directly in a connector config and which cannot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27819 | Apache Kafka: Possible RCE/Denial of service attack via SASL JAAS JndiLoginModule configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27819</link><description>In CVE-2023-25194, we announced the RCE/Denial of service attack via SASL JAAS JndiLoginModule configuration in Kafka Connect API. But not only Kafka Connect API is vulnerable to this attack, the Apache Kafka brokers also have this vulnerability. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs to be able to connect to the Kafka cluster and have the AlterConfigs permission on the cluster resource.


Since Apache Kafka 3.4.0, we have added a system property ("-Dorg.apache.kafka.disallowed.login.modules") to disable the problematic login modules usage in SASL JAAS configuration. Also by default "com.sun.security.auth.module.JndiLoginModule" is disabled in Apache Kafka 3.4.0, and "com.sun.security.auth.module.JndiLoginModule,com.sun.security.auth.module.LdapLoginModule" is disabled by default in in Apache Kafka 3.9.1/4.0.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5945 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Centreon centreon-web (Backup co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5945</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Centreon centreon-web (Backup configuration modules) allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects centreon-web: Cloud 25.03, from 24.10.0 before 24.10.9, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.15, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.24.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1041 | Avaya Call Management System RCE vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1041</link><description>An improper input validation discovered in 

Avaya Call Management System
could allow an unauthorized 

remote command via a specially crafted web request. Affected versions include 18.x, 19.x prior to 19.2.0.7, and 20.x prior to 20.0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4840 | Likes and Dislikes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4840</link><description>The inprosysmedia-likes-dislikes-post WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4954 | Axle Demo Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Author+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4954</link><description>The Axle Demo Importer WordPress plugin through 1.0.3 does not validate files to be uploaded, which could allow authenticated users (author and above) to upload arbitrary files such as PHP on the server</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5952 | Zend.To NSSDropoff.php exec os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5952</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Zend.To up to 6.10-6 Beta. This issue affects the function exec of the file NSSDropoff.php. The manipulation of the argument file_1 leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 6.10-7 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. This affects a rather old version of the software. The vendor recommends updating to the latest release.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 05:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5935 | Open5GS AMF/MME emm-sm.c common_register_state denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5935</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function common_register_state of the file src/mme/emm-sm.c of the component AMF/MME. The manipulation of the argument ran_ue_id leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 62cb99755243c9c38e4c060c5d8d0e158fe8cdd5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3076 | Elementor Pro &amp;lt;= 3.29.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3076</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘button_text’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.29.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4387 | Abandoned Cart Pro for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 9.16.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4387</link><description>The Abandoned Cart Pro for WooCommerce plugin contains an authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability due to missing file type validation in the wcap_add_to_cart_popup_upload_files function in all versions up to, and including, 9.16.0. This makes it possible for an authenticated attacker, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may allow for either remote or local code execution depending on the server configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4601 | RH - Real Estate WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 4.4.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4601</link><description>The "RH - Real Estate WordPress Theme" theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.0. This is due to the theme not properly restricting user roles that can be updated as part of the inspiry_update_profile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to set their role to that of an administrator. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.4.0, and fully patched in version 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5925 | Bunny’s Print CSS &amp;lt;= 0.95 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5925</link><description>The Bunny’s Print CSS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.95. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the pcss_options_subpanel() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5912 | D-Link DIR-632 HTTP POST Request do_file stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5912</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-632 FW103B08. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function do_file of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5913 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Record Management System search-vehicle.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5913</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinputdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5934 | Netgear EX3700 mtd sub_41619C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5934</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear EX3700 up to 1.0.0.88. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function sub_41619C of the file /mtd. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.0.0.98 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5911 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formDMZ buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5911</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1200T up to 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formDMZ of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5910 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formWsc buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5910</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200T up to 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formWsc of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5909 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formReflashClientTbl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5909</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200T up to 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formReflashClientTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5908 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formIpQoS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5908</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200T up to 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23192 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence (BI Workspace)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23192</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence (BI Workspace) allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft and store malicious script within a workspace. When the victim accesses the workspace, the script will execute in their browser enabling the attacker to potentially access sensitive session information, modify or make browser information unavailable. This leads to a high impact on confidentiality and low impact on integrity, availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31325 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Keyword Documentation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31325</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Keyword Documentation), an unauthenticated attacker could inject malicious JavaScript into a web page through an unprotected parameter. When a victim accesses the affected page, the script executes in their browser, providing the attacker limited access to restricted information. The vulnerability does not affect data integrity or availability and operates entirely within the context of the client's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42977 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42977</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer contains a Directory Traversal vulnerability caused by insufficient validation of input paths provided by a high-privileged user. This allows an attacker to read or modify arbitrary files, resulting in a high impact on confidentiality and a low impact on integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42982 | Information Disclosure in SAP GRC (AC Plugin)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42982</link><description>SAP GRC allows a non-administrative user to access and initiate transaction which could allow them to modify or control the transmitted system credentials. This causes high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42983 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Business Warehouse and SAP Plug-In Basis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42983</link><description>SAP Business Warehouse and SAP Plug-In Basis allows an authenticated attacker to drop arbitrary SAP database tables, potentially resulting in a loss of data or rendering the system unusable. On successful exploitation, an attacker can completely delete database entries but is not able to read any data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42984 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Central Purchase Contract application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42984</link><description>SAP S/4HANA Manage Central Purchase Contract does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user. Due to this, an attacker could execute the function import on the entity making it inaccessible for unrestricted user. This has low impact on confidentiality and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42987 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Processing Rules - For Bank Statement)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42987</link><description>SAP Manage Processing Rules (For Bank Statement) allows an attacker with basic privileges to edit shared rules of any user by tampering the request parameter. Due to missing authorization check, the attacker can edit rules that should be restricted, compromising the integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42988 | Server-Side Request Forgery in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42988</link><description>Under certain conditions, SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to enumerate HTTP endpoints in the internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. This disclosure of information could further enable the researcher to cause SSRF. It has no impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42989 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42989</link><description>RFC inbound processing�does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation the attacker could critically impact both integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42990 | HTML Injection in Unprotected SAPUI5 applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42990</link><description>Unprotected SAPUI5 applications allow an attacker with basic privileges to inject malicious HTML code into a webpage, with the goal of redirecting users to the attacker controlled URL. This issue could impact the integrity of the application. Confidentiality or Availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42991 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4HANA (Bank Account Application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42991</link><description>SAP S/4HANA (Bank Account Application) does not perform necessary authorization checks. This allows an authenticated 'approver' user to delete attachment from bank account application of other user, leading to a low impact on integrity, with no impact on the confidentiality of the data or the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42993 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP S/4HANA (Enterprise Event Enablement)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42993</link><description>Due to a missing authorization check vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA (Enterprise Event Enablement), an attacker with access to the Inbound Binding Configuration could create an RFC destination and assign an arbitrary high-privilege user. This allows the attacker to consume events via the RFC destination, leading to code execution under the privileges of the assigned high-privilege user. While the vulnerability has a low impact on Availability, it significantly poses a high risk to both Confidentiality and Integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42994 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP MDM Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42994</link><description>SAP MDM Server ReadString function allows an attacker to send specially crafted packets which could trigger a memory read access violation in the server process that would then fail and exit unexpectedly causing high impact on availability with no impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42995 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP MDM Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42995</link><description>SAP MDM Server Read function allows an attacker to send specially crafted packets which could trigger a memory read access violation in the server process that would then fail and exit unexpectedly causing high impact on availability with no impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42996 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP MDM Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42996</link><description>SAP MDM Server allows an attacker to gain control of existing client sessions and execute certain functions without having to re-authenticate giving the ability to access or modify non-sensitive information or consume sufficient resources which could degrade the performance of the server causing low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availibility of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42998 | Security misconfiguration vulnerability in SAP Business One Integration Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42998</link><description>The security settings in the SAP Business One Integration Framework are not adequately checked, allowing attackers to bypass the 403 Forbidden error and access restricted pages. This leads to low impact on confidentiality of the application, there is no impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5906 | code-projects Laundry System data missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5906</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Laundry System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /data/. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5907 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5907</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK EX1200T up to 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0036 | In AMD Versal Adaptive SoC devices, the incorrect configuration of the SSS during runtime (post-boot) cryptographic operations could cause d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0036</link><description>In AMD Versal Adaptive SoC devices, the incorrect configuration of the SSS during runtime (post-boot) cryptographic operations could cause data to be incorrectly written to and read from invalid locations as well as returning incorrect cryptographic data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5904 | TOTOLINK T10 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setWiFiMeshName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5904</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5207. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWiFiMeshName of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument device_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5905 | TOTOLINK T10 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setWiFiRepeaterCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5905</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5207. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWiFiRepeaterCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0037 | In AMD Versal Adaptive SoC devices, the lack of address validation when executing PLM runtime services through the PLM firmware can allow ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0037</link><description>In AMD Versal Adaptive SoC devices, the lack of address validation when executing PLM runtime services through the PLM firmware can allow access to isolated or protected memory spaces, resulting in the loss of integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5903 | TOTOLINK T10 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setWiFiAclRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5903</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5207. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setWiFiAclRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 23:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5902 | TOTOLINK T10 POST Request cstecgi.cgi setUpgradeFW buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5902</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5207 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument slaveIpList leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 23:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30183 | CyberData 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30183</link><description>CyberData 011209 Intercom
 does not properly store or protect web server admin credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30515 | CyberData 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30515</link><description>CyberData 011209 Intercom
 
could allow an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files to multiple locations within the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5901 | TOTOLINK T10 POST Request cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5901</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5207 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26468 | CyberData 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26468</link><description>CyberData 
011209 


Intercom exposes features that could allow an unauthenticated to gain 
access and cause a denial-of-service condition or system disruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30507 | CyberData 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30507</link><description>CyberData 011209 Intercom could allow an unauthenticated user to gather sensitive information through blind SQL injections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30184 | CyberData 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30184</link><description>CyberData 011209 Intercom could allow an unauthenticated user access to the Web Interface through an alternate path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5899 | GNU PSPP pspp-convert.c parse_variables_option free of memory not on the heap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5899</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in GNU PSPP 82fb509fb2fedd33e7ac0c46ca99e108bb3bdffb. Affected by this vulnerability is the function parse_variables_option of the file utilities/pspp-convert.c. The manipulation leads to free of memory not on the heap. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5900 | Tenda AC9 cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5900</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Tenda AC9 15.03.02.13. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5898 | GNU PSPP pspp-convert.c parse_variables_option out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5898</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in GNU PSPP 82fb509fb2fedd33e7ac0c46ca99e108bb3bdffb. Affected is the function parse_variables_option of the file utilities/pspp-convert.c. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds write. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49140 | Pion Interceptor&amp;#x27;s improper RTP padding handling allows remote crash for SFU users (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49140</link><description>Pion Interceptor is a framework for building RTP/RTCP communication software. Versions v0.1.36 through v0.1.38 contain a bug in a RTP packet factory that can be exploited to trigger a panic with Pion based SFU via crafted RTP packets, This only affect users that use pion/interceptor. Users should upgrade to v0.1.39 or later, which validates that: `padLen &gt; 0 &amp;&amp; padLen &lt;= payloadLength` and return error  on overflow, avoiding panic. If upgrading is not possible, apply the patch from the pull request manually or drop packets whose P-bit is set but whose padLen is zero or larger than the remaining payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49138 | HAX CMS vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via saveOutline API Location Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49138</link><description>HAX CMS PHP allows users to manage their microsite universe with a PHP backend. Prior to version 11.0.0, an authenticated Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability in the HAXCMS saveOutline endpoint allows a low-privileged user to read arbitrary files on the server by manipulating the location field written into site.json. This enables attackers to exfiltrate sensitive system files such as /etc/passwd, application secrets, or configuration files accessible to the web server (www-data). The vulnerability stems from the way the HAXCMS backend handles the location field in the site's outline. When a user sends a POST request to /system/api/saveOutline, the backend stores the provided location value directly into the site.json file associated with the site, without validating or sanitizing the input. Later the location parameter is interpreted by the CMS to resolve and load the content for a given node. If the location field contains a relative path like `../../../etc/passwd`, the application will attempt to read and render that file. Version 11.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49139 | @haxtheweb/haxcms-nodejs Iframe Phishing vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49139</link><description>HAX CMS PHP allows users to manage their microsite universe with a PHP backend. Prior to version 11.0.0, in the HAX site editor, users can create a website block to load another site in an iframe. The application allows users to supply a target URL in the website block. When the HAX site is visited, the client's browser will query the supplied URL. An authenticated attacker can create a HAX site with a website block pointing at an attacker-controlled server running Responder or a similar tool. The attacker can then conduct a phishing attack by convincing another user to visit their malicious HAX site to harvest credentials. Version 11.0.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49141 | HaxCMS-PHP Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49141</link><description>HAX CMS PHP allows users to manage their microsite universe with a PHP backend. Prior to version 11.0.3, the `gitImportSite` functionality obtains a URL string from a POST request and insufficiently validates user input. The `set_remote` function later passes this input into `proc_open`, yielding OS command injection. An authenticated attacker can craft a URL string that bypasses the validation checks employed by the `filter_var` and `strpos` functions in order to execute arbitrary OS commands on the backend server. The attacker can exfiltrate command output via an HTTP request. Version 11.0.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49137 | Hax CMS Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49137</link><description>HAX CMS PHP allows users to manage their microsite universe with a PHP backend. Prior to version 11.0.0, the application does not sufficiently sanitize user input, allowing for the execution of arbitrary JavaScript code. The 'saveNode' and 'saveManifest' endpoints take user input and store it in the JSON schema for the site. This content is then rendered in the generated HAX site. Although the application does not allow users to supply a `script` tag, it does allow the use of other HTML tags to run JavaScript. Version 11.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5897 | vuejs vue-cli Markdown Code HtmlPwaPlugin.js HtmlPwaPlugin redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5897</link><description>A vulnerability was found in vuejs vue-cli up to 5.0.8. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function HtmlPwaPlugin of the file packages/@vue/cli-plugin-pwa/lib/HtmlPwaPlugin.js of the component Markdown Code Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49004 | Hijacking Caido instance during the initial setup via DNS Rebinding to achieve RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49004</link><description>Caido is a web security auditing toolkit. Prior to version 0.48.0, due to the lack of protection for DNS rebinding, Caido can be loaded on an attacker-controlled domain. This allows a malicious website to hijack the authentication flow of Caido and achieve code execution. A malicious website loaded in the browser can hijack the locally running Caido instance and achieve remote command execution during the initial setup. Even if the Caido instance is already configured, an attacker can initiate the authentication flow by performing DNS rebinding. In this case, the victim needs to authorize the request on dashboard.caido.io. Users should upgrade to version 0.48.0 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5896 | tarojs taro index.js redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5896</link><description>A vulnerability was found in tarojs taro up to 4.1.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file taro/packages/css-to-react-native/src/index.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 4.1.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is c2e321a8b6fc873427c466c69f41ed0b5e8814bf. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5895 | Metabase dom.js parseDataUri redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5895</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Metabase 54.10. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function parseDataUri of the file frontend/src/metabase/lib/dom.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 4454ebbdc7719016bf80ca0f34859ce5cee9f6b0. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5914 | Libarchive: double free at archive_read_format_rar_seek_data() in archive_read_support_format_rar.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5914</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the libarchive library, specifically within the archive_read_format_rar_seek_data() function. This flaw involves an integer overflow that can ultimately lead to a double-free condition. Exploiting a double-free vulnerability can result in memory corruption, enabling an attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5915 | Libarchive: heap buffer over read in copy_from_lzss_window() at archive_read_support_format_rar.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5915</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the libarchive library. This flaw can lead to a heap buffer over-read due to the size of a filter block potentially exceeding the Lempel-Ziv-Storer-Schieber (LZSS) window. This means the library may attempt to read beyond the allocated memory buffer, which can result in unpredictable program behavior, crashes (denial of service), or the disclosure of sensitive information from adjacent memory regions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5916 | Libarchive: integer overflow while reading warc files at archive_read_support_format_warc.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5916</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the libarchive library. This flaw involves an integer overflow that can be triggered when processing a Web Archive (WARC) file that claims to have more than INT64_MAX - 4 content bytes. An attacker could craft a malicious WARC archive to induce this overflow, potentially leading to unpredictable program behavior, memory corruption, or a denial-of-service condition within applications that process such archives using libarchive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5917 | Libarchive: off by one error in build_ustar_entry_name() at archive_write_set_format_pax.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5917</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the libarchive library. This flaw involves an 'off-by-one' miscalculation when handling prefixes and suffixes for file names. This can lead to a 1-byte write overflow. While seemingly small, such an overflow can corrupt adjacent memory, leading to unpredictable program behavior, crashes, or in specific circumstances, could be leveraged as a building block for more sophisticated exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5918 | Libarchive: reading past eof may be triggered for piped file streams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5918</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the libarchive library. This flaw can be triggered when file streams are piped into bsdtar, potentially allowing for reading past the end of the file. This out-of-bounds read can lead to unintended consequences, including unpredictable program behavior, memory corruption, or a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5892 | RocketChat parseMessage.js parseMessage redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5892</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in RocketChat up to 7.6.1. This issue affects the function parseMessage of the file /apps/meteor/app/irc/server/servers/RFC2813/parseMessage.js. The manipulation of the argument line leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5891 | Unitech pm2 Config.js redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5891</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Unitech pm2 up to 6.0.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /lib/tools/Config.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5890 | actions toolkit glob internal-pattern.ts globEscape redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5890</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in actions toolkit 0.5.0. This affects the function globEscape of the file toolkit/packages/glob/src/internal-pattern.ts of the component glob. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5889 | juliangruber brace-expansion index.js expand redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5889</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juliangruber brace-expansion up to 1.1.11. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function expand of the file index.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is a5b98a4f30d7813266b221435e1eaaf25a1b0ac5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47081 | Requests vulnerable to .netrc credentials leak via malicious URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47081</link><description>Requests is a HTTP library. Due to a URL parsing issue, Requests releases prior to 2.32.4 may leak .netrc credentials to third parties for specific maliciously-crafted URLs. Users should upgrade to version 2.32.4 to receive a fix. For older versions of Requests, use of the .netrc file can be disabled with `trust_env=False` on one's Requests Session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49652 | Improper access control allows arbitrary account creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49652</link><description>Missing Authentication in the registration feature of Lablup's BackendAI allows arbitrary users to create user accounts that can access private data even when registration is disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49653 | Exposure of sensitive Information allows account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49653</link><description>Exposure of sensitive data in active sessions in Lablup's BackendAI allows attackers to retrieve credentials for users on the management platform.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5888 | jsnjfz WebStack-Guns cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5888</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jsnjfz WebStack-Guns 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49651 | Missing Authorization for Interactive Sessions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49651</link><description>Missing Authorization in Lablup's BackendAI allows attackers to takeover all active sessions; Accessing, stealing, or altering any data accessible in the session. This vulnerability exists in all current versions of BackendAI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29627 | An issue in KeeperChat IOS Application v.5.8.8 allows a physically proximate attacker to escalate privileges via the Biometric Authenticatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29627</link><description>An issue in KeeperChat IOS Application v.5.8.8 allows a physically proximate attacker to escalate privileges via the Biometric Authentication Module</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46041 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Anchor CMS v0.12.7 allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript via the page descrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46041</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Anchor CMS v0.12.7 allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript via the page description field in the page creation interface (/admin/pages/add).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45001 | react-native-keys 0.7.11 is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure (remote) as encryption cipher and Base64 chunks are stored as pla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45001</link><description>react-native-keys 0.7.11 is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure (remote) as encryption cipher and Base64 chunks are stored as plaintext in the compiled native binary. Attackers can extract these secrets using basic static analysis tools.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5887 | jsnjfz WebStack-Guns File Upload UserMgrController.java cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5887</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jsnjfz WebStack-Guns 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file UserMgrController.java of the component File Upload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46452 | A Host Header injection vulnerability in the password reset function of VigyBag Open Source Online Shop commit 3f0e21b allows attackers to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46452</link><description>A Host Header injection vulnerability in the password reset function of VigyBag Open Source Online Shop commit 3f0e21b allows attackers to redirect victim users to a malicious site via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45002 | Vigybag v1.0 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the upload profile picture function under my profile.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45002</link><description>Vigybag v1.0 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the upload profile picture function under my profile.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49136 | listmonk&amp;#x27;s Sprig template Injection vulnerability leads to reading of Environment Variable for low privilege user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49136</link><description>listmonk is a standalone, self-hosted, newsletter and mailing list manager. Starting in version 4.0.0 and prior to version 5.0.2, the `env` and `expandenv` template functions which is enabled by default in Sprig enables capturing of env variables on host. While this may not be a problem on single-user (super admin) installations, on multi-user installations, this allows non-super-admin users with campaign or template permissions to use the `{{ env }}` template expression to capture sensitive environment variables. Users should upgrade to v5.0.2 to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25999 | WordPress BodyCenter - Gym, Fitness WooCommerce WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25999</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in snstheme BodyCenter - Gym, Fitness WooCommerce WordPress Theme allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects BodyCenter - Gym, Fitness WooCommerce WordPress Theme: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26005 | WordPress Fitrush &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26005</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BZOTheme Fitrush allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Fitrush: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23974 | WordPress One-Login &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23974</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in ifkooo One-Login allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects One-Login: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24767 | WordPress TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.19 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24767</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in facturaone TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24768 | WordPress Nitan &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24768</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in snstheme Nitan allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Nitan: from n/a through 2.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24770 | WordPress CraftXtore &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24770</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BZOTheme CraftXtore allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects CraftXtore: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26592 | WordPress Inset &amp;lt;= 1.18.0 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26592</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Inset allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Inset: from n/a through 1.18.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27362 | WordPress Petito &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27362</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BZOTheme Petito allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Petito: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28888 | WordPress GiftXtore &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28888</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BZOTheme GiftXtore allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects GiftXtore: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28944 | WordPress Avaz &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28944</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in snstheme Avaz allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Avaz: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28945 | WordPress Valen - Sport, Fashion WooCommerce WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28945</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in snstheme Valen - Sport, Fashion WooCommerce WordPress Theme allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Valen - Sport, Fashion WooCommerce WordPress Theme: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28992 | WordPress SNS Anton &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28992</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in snstheme SNS Anton allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects SNS Anton: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31019 | WordPress Password Policy Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31019</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in miniOrange Password Policy Manager allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Password Policy Manager: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31022 | WordPress PayU India plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.5 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31022</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in PayU India PayU India allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects PayU India: from n/a through 3.8.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31039 | WordPress Category Icon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31039</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in pixelgrade Category Icon allows XML Entity Linking. This issue affects Category Icon: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31045 | WordPress elfsight Contact Form widget &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31045</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in elfsight elfsight Contact Form widget allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects elfsight Contact Form widget: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31050 | WordPress Apptha Slider Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31050</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in appthaplugins Apptha Slider Gallery allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Apptha Slider Gallery: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31052 | WordPress The Fashion - Model Agency One Page Beauty Theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31052</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton The Fashion - Model Agency One Page Beauty Theme allows Object Injection. This issue affects The Fashion - Model Agency One Page Beauty Theme: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31057 | WordPress Universal Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LambertGroup Universal Video Player allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Universal Video Player: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31058 | WordPress Revolution Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31058</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LambertGroup Revolution Video Player allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Revolution Video Player: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31059 | WordPress WBW Product Table PRO &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31059</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in woobewoo WBW Product Table PRO allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WBW Product Table PRO: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31061 | WordPress Wishlist plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31061</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in redqteam Wishlist allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31396 | WordPress FLAP - Business WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31396</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton FLAP - Business WordPress Theme allows Object Injection. This issue affects FLAP - Business WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31398 | WordPress PIMP - Creative MultiPurpose &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31398</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton PIMP - Creative MultiPurpose allows Object Injection. This issue affects PIMP - Creative MultiPurpose: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31424 | WordPress WP Lead Capturing Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31424</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in kamleshyadav WP Lead Capturing Pages allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Lead Capturing Pages: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31426 | WordPress Sticky Radio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31426</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LambertGroup Sticky Radio Player allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Sticky Radio Player: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31429 | WordPress PressGrid - Frontend Publish Reaction &amp;amp; Multimedia Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Deserialization of untrusted data Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31429</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton PressGrid - Frontend Publish Reaction &amp; Multimedia Theme allows Object Injection. This issue affects PressGrid - Frontend Publish Reaction &amp; Multimedia Theme: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31635 | WordPress CLEVER &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31635</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in LambertGroup CLEVER allows Path Traversal. This issue affects CLEVER: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31638 | WordPress Spare &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themeton Spare allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Spare: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31917 | WordPress Universal Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31917</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LambertGroup Universal Video Player allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Universal Video Player: from n/a through 3.8.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31920 | WordPress WP Guppy &amp;lt;= 4.3.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31920</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AmentoTech WP Guppy allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Guppy: from n/a through 4.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31925 | WordPress SHOUT plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31925</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LambertGroup SHOUT allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects SHOUT: from n/a through 3.5.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5886 | Emlog article.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5886</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Emlog up to 2.5.7 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/article.php. The manipulation of the argument active_post leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32291 | WordPress SUMO Affiliates Pro &amp;lt;= 10.7.0 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32291</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in FantasticPlugins SUMO Affiliates Pro allows Using Malicious Files. This issue affects SUMO Affiliates Pro: from n/a through 10.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32305 | WordPress FlatNews theme &amp;lt;= 5.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sneeit FlatNews allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FlatNews: from n/a through 5.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32308 | WordPress Team Builder &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32308</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in looks_awesome Team Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Team Builder: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32595 | WordPress Krowd &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32595</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Krowd allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Krowd: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39473 | WordPress Seofy Core &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39473</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WebGeniusLab Seofy Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Seofy Core: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39475 | WordPress Arlo &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39475</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Frenify Arlo allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Arlo: from n/a through 6.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39476 | WordPress Revo theme &amp;lt;= 4.0.26 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39476</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in magentech Revo allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Revo: from n/a through 4.0.26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39539 | WordPress Soho Hotel &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in quitenicestuff Soho Hotel allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Soho Hotel: from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45055 | Silverpeas 6.4.2 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the event management module. An authenticated user can upload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45055</link><description>Silverpeas 6.4.2 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the event management module. An authenticated user can upload a malicious SVG file as an event attachment, which, when viewed by an administrator, executes embedded JavaScript in the admin's session. This allows attackers to escalate privileges by creating a new administrator account. The vulnerability arises from insufficient sanitization of SVG files and weak CSRF protections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46178 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in askquery.php via the eid parameter in the CloudClassroom PHP Project. This allows remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46178</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in askquery.php via the eid parameter in the CloudClassroom PHP Project. This allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a victim s browser session by sending a crafted URL, leading to session hijacking or defacement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47463 | WordPress Stock Locations for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47463</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Stock Locations for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Stock Locations for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.8.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47477 | WordPress Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule plugin &amp;lt;= 1.22.23 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47477</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in revmakx Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule: from n/a through 1.22.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47487 | WordPress MC Woocommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47487</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in moreconvert MC Woocommerce Wishlist allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MC Woocommerce Wishlist: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47511 | WordPress Welcart e-Commerce &amp;lt;= 2.11.13 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47511</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in nanbu Welcart e-Commerce allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Welcart e-Commerce: from n/a through 2.11.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47527 | WordPress Icegram Collect – Easy Form, Lead Collection and Subscription plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.18 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47527</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Icegram Icegram Collect – Easy Form, Lead Collection and Subscription plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Icegram Collect – Easy Form, Lead Collection and Subscription plugin: from n/a through 1.3.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47561 | WordPress MapSVG &amp;lt;=  8.5.34 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47561</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.34.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47598 | WordPress History Log by click5 &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in click5 History Log by click5 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects History Log by click5: from n/a through 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47608 | WordPress Recover abandoned cart for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.5 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47608</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in sonalsinha21 Recover abandoned cart for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Recover abandoned cart for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47651 | WordPress Infility Global &amp;lt;= 2.12.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Infility Infility Global allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Infility Global: from n/a through 2.12.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48122 | WordPress Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light &amp;lt;= 2.4.37 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Holest Engineering Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light: from n/a through 2.4.37.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48123 | WordPress Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light &amp;lt;= 2.4.37 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48123</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Holest Engineering Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light allows Code Injection. This issue affects Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light: from n/a through 2.4.37.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48124 | WordPress Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light &amp;lt;= 2.4.37 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48124</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Holest Engineering Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light: from n/a through 2.4.37.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48125 | WordPress WP Event Manager &amp;lt;= 3.1.49 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48125</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WP Event Manager WP Event Manager allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Event Manager: from n/a through 3.1.49.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48126 | WordPress Essential Real Estate &amp;lt;= 5.2.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48126</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in g5theme Essential Real Estate allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Essential Real Estate: from n/a through 5.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48129 | WordPress Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light &amp;lt;= 2.4.37 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48129</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Holest Engineering Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light: from n/a through 2.4.37.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48130 | WordPress Spice Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.0.7.2 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48130</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in spicethemes Spice Blocks allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Spice Blocks: from n/a through 2.0.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48139 | WordPress StyleAI &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48139</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in relentlo StyleAI allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects StyleAI: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48140 | WordPress MetalpriceAPI &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48140</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in metalpriceapi MetalpriceAPI allows Code Injection. This issue affects MetalpriceAPI: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48141 | WordPress Multi CryptoCurrency Payments &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48141</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Alex Zaytseff Multi CryptoCurrency Payments allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Multi CryptoCurrency Payments: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48143 | WordPress Formulario de contacto SalesUp! plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48143</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in salesup2019 Formulario de contacto SalesUp! allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Formulario de contacto SalesUp!: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48147 | WordPress CryptoCloud - Crypto Payment Gateway &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48147</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Crypto Cloud CryptoCloud - Crypto Payment Gateway allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CryptoCloud - Crypto Payment Gateway: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48261 | WordPress MultiVendorX &amp;lt;= 4.2.22 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48261</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in MultiVendorX MultiVendorX allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects MultiVendorX: from n/a through 4.2.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48267 | WordPress WP Pipes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48267</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in ThimPress WP Pipes allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WP Pipes: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48279 | WordPress WC MyParcel Belgium plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.5-beta - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48279</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Richard Perdaan WC MyParcel Belgium allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WC MyParcel Belgium: from 4.5.5 through beta.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48281 | WordPress MyStyle Custom Product Designer &amp;lt;= 3.21.1 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48281</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in mystyleplatform MyStyle Custom Product Designer allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects MyStyle Custom Product Designer: from n/a through 3.21.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49265 | WordPress Membership For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49265</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Swings Membership For WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Membership For WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49275 | WordPress Blogbyte &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49275</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Blogbyte allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Blogbyte: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49276 | WordPress Blogmine &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49276</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Blogmine allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Blogmine: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49277 | WordPress Blogprise &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49277</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Blogprise allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Blogprise: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49278 | WordPress Blogty &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49278</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Blogty allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Blogty: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49279 | WordPress Blogvy &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49279</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Blogvy allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Blogvy: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49280 | WordPress Magty &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49280</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magty allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magty: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49281 | WordPress Magways &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49281</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magways allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magways: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49282 | WordPress Magze &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49282</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magze allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magze: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49295 | WordPress MediClinic &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49295</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Mikado-Themes MediClinic allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects MediClinic: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49296 | WordPress GrandPrix &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49296</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Mikado-Themes GrandPrix allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects GrandPrix: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49297 | WordPress Grill and Chow &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49297</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Grill and Chow allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Grill and Chow: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5885 | Konica Minolta bizhub cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5885</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Konica Minolta bizhub up to 20250202 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5884 | Konica Minolta bizhub Display MFP Information List cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5884</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Konica Minolta bizhub up to 20250202. This affects an unknown part of the component Display MFP Information List. The manipulation of the argument Model Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5881 | code-projects Chat System confirm_password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5881</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chat System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/confirm_password.php. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5880 | Whistle get-temp-file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5880</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Whistle 2.9.98 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cgi-bin/sessions/get-temp-file. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5879 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM File Upload AdminSysConfigController.java cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5879</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM 9.0. This affects an unknown part of the file AdminSysConfigController.java of the component File Upload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48877 | Discourse vulnerable to auto-executing of third-party code in embedded CodePen iframe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48877</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.4.4 of the `stable` branch, version 3.5.0.beta5 of the `beta` branch, and version 3.5.0.beta6-dev of the `tests-passed` branch, Codepen is present in the default `allowed_iframes` site setting, and it can potentially auto-run arbitrary JS in the iframe scope, which is unintended. This issue is patched in version 3.4.4 of the `stable` branch, version 3.5.0.beta5 of the `beta` branch, and version 3.5.0.beta6-dev of the `tests-passed` branch. As a workaround, the Codepen prefix can be removed from a site's `allowed_iframes`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49006 | Wasp has case insensitive OAuth ID vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49006</link><description>Wasp (Web Application Specification) is a Rails-like framework for React, Node.js, and Prisma. Prior to version 0.16.6, Wasp authentication has a vulnerability in the OAuth authentication implementation (affecting only Keycloak with a specific config). Wasp currently lowercases OAuth user IDs before storing / fetching them. This behavior violates OAuth and OpenID Connect specifications and can result in user impersonation, account collisions, and privilege escalation. In practice, out of the OAuth providers that Wasp auth supports, only Keycloak is affected. Keycloak uses a lowercase UUID by default, but users can configure it to be case sensitive, making it affected. Google, GitHub, and Discord use numerical IDs, making them not affected. Users should update their Wasp version to `0.16.6` which has a fix for the problematic behavior. Users using Keycloak can work around the issue by not using a case sensitive user ID in their realm configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49013 | WilderForge vulnerable to code Injection via GitHub Actions Workflows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49013</link><description>WilderForge is a Wildermyth coremodding API. A critical vulnerability has been identified in multiple projects across the WilderForge organization. The issue arises from unsafe usage of `${{ github.event.review.body }}` and other user controlled variables directly inside shell script contexts in GitHub Actions workflows. This introduces a code injection vulnerability: a malicious actor submitting a crafted pull request review containing shell metacharacters or commands could execute arbitrary shell code on the GitHub Actions runner. This can lead to arbitrary command execution with the permissions of the workflow, potentially compromising CI infrastructure, secrets, and build outputs. Developers who maintain or contribute to the repos WilderForge/WilderForge, WilderForge/ExampleMod, WilderForge/WilderWorkspace, WilderForge/WildermythGameProvider, WilderForge/AutoSplitter, WilderForge/SpASM, WilderForge/thrixlvault, WilderForge/MassHash, and/or WilderForge/DLC_Disabler; as well as users who fork any of the above repositories and reuse affected GitHub Actions workflows, are affected. End users of any the above software and users who only install pre-built releases or artifacts are not affected. This vulnerability does not impact runtime behavior of the software or compiled outputs unless those outputs were produced during exploitation of this vulnerability. A current workaround is to disable GitHub Actions in affected repositories, or remove the affected workflows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49130 | Laravel Translation Manager Vulnerable to Stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49130</link><description>Laravel Translation Manager is a package to manage Laravel translation files. Prior to version 0.6.8, the application is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks due to incorrect input validation and sanitization of user-input data. An attacker can inject arbitrary HTML code, including JavaScript scripts, into the page processed by the user's browser, allowing them to steal sensitive data, hijack user sessions, or conduct other malicious activities. Only authenticated users with access to the translation manager are impacted. The issue is fixed in version 0.6.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49131 | FastGPT Sandbox Vulnerable to Sandbox Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49131</link><description>FastGPT is an open-source project that provides a platform for building, deploying, and operating AI-driven workflows and conversational agents. The Sandbox container (fastgpt-sandbox) is a specialized, isolated environment used by FastGPT to safely execute user-submitted or dynamically generated code in isolation. The sandbox before version 4.9.11 has insufficient isolation and inadequate restrictions on code execution by allowing overly permissive syscalls, which allows attackers to escape the intended sandbox boundaries. Attackers could exploit this to read and overwrite arbitrary files and bypass Python module import restrictions. This is patched in version 4.9.11 by restricting the allowed system calls to a safer subset and additional descriptive error messaging.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40668 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40668</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an attacker, with low privilege level, to change the password of other users through a POST request using the parameters idUser, PasswordActual, PasswordNew and PasswordNewRepeat in /PC/WebService.aspx/validateChangePassword%C3%B1a. To exploit the vulnerability the PasswordActual parameter must be empty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40669 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40669</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unprivileged attacker to modify the permissions held by each of the application's users, including the user himself by sending a POST request to /PC/Options.aspx?Command=2&amp;amp;Page=-1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40670 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40670</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unprivileged attacker to create a user and assign it many privileges by sending a POST request to /PC/frmGestionUser.aspx/updateUser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48053 | Discourse vulnerable to DoS via large URL payload in PM to a bot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48053</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.4.4 of the `stable` branch, version 3.5.0.beta5 of the `beta` branch, and version 3.5.0.beta6-dev of the `tests-passed` branch, sending a malicious URL in a PM to a bot user can cause a reduced the availability of a Discourse instance. This issue is patched in version 3.4.4 of the `stable` branch, version 3.5.0.beta5 of the `beta` branch, and version 3.5.0.beta6-dev of the `tests-passed` branch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48062 | Discourse vulnerable to HTML injection when inviting to topic via email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48062</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.4.4 of the `stable` branch, version 3.5.0.beta5 of the `beta` branch, and version 3.5.0.beta6-dev of the `tests-passed` branch, certain invites via email may result in HTML injection in the email body if the topic title includes HTML. This includes inviting someone (without an account) to a PM and inviting someone (without an account) to a topic with a custom message. This issue is patched in version 3.4.4 of the `stable` branch, version 3.5.0.beta5 of the `beta` branch, and version 3.5.0.beta6-dev of the `tests-passed` branch. This can be worked around if the relevant templates are overridden without `{topic_title}`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5877 | Fengoffice Feng Office Document Upload ApplicationDataObject.class.php xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5877</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Fengoffice Feng Office 3.2.2.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /application/models/ApplicationDataObject.class.php of the component Document Upload Handler. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:04:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5876 | Lucky LM-520-SC/LM-520-FSC/LM-520-FSC-SAM missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5876</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Lucky LM-520-SC, LM-520-FSC and LM-520-FSC-SAM up to 20250321. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5875 | TP-Link TL-IPC544EP-W4 main sub_69064 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5875</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TP-Link TL-IPC544EP-W4 1.0.9 Build 240428 Rel 69493n. Affected is the function sub_69064 of the file /bin/main. The manipulation of the argument text leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41444 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41444</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8510 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in the alerts module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36528 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36528</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8510 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in Service Account Auditing reports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27709 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27709</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8510 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in the Service Account Auditing reports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5874 | Redash getattr python.py run_query sandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5874</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Redash up to 10.1.0/25.1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function run_query of the file /query_runner/python.py of the component getattr Handler. The manipulation leads to sandbox issue. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41437 | Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41437</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine OpManager, NetFlow Analyzer, Network Configuration Manager, Firewall Analyzer and OpUtils versions 128565 and below are vulnerable to Reflected XSS on the login page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3835 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3835</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5721 and prior are vulnerable to Remote code execution in the Content Search module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5873 | eCharge Hardy Barth Salia PLCC Web UI firmware.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5873</link><description>A vulnerability was found in eCharge Hardy Barth Salia PLCC 2.2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /firmware.php of the component Web UI. The manipulation of the argument media leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5872 | eGauge EG3000 Energy Monitor Setting missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5872</link><description>A vulnerability was found in eGauge EG3000 Energy Monitor 3.6.3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40675 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Bagisto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40675</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been found in Bagisto v2.0.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending the victim a malicious URL using the parameter 'query' in '/search'. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5871 | Papendorf SOL Connect Center Web Interface missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5871</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Papendorf SOL Connect Center 3.3.0.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5870 | TRENDnet TV-IP121W Web Interface setup.cgi improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5870</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TRENDnet TV-IP121W 1.1.1 Build 36 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/setup.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5869 | RT-Thread lwp_syscall.c sys_recvfrom memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5869</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in RT-Thread 5.1.0. Affected is the function sys_recvfrom of the file rt-thread/components/lwp/lwp_syscall.c. The manipulation of the argument from leads to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5868 | RT-Thread lwp_syscall.c sys_thread_sigprocmask array index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5868</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in RT-Thread 5.1.0. This issue affects the function sys_thread_sigprocmask of the file rt-thread/components/lwp/lwp_syscall.c. The manipulation of the argument how leads to improper validation of array index.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5894 | Honding Technology Smart Parking Management System - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5894</link><description>Smart Parking Management System from Honding Technology has a Missing Authorization vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to access a specific functionality to create administrator accounts, and subsequently log into the system using those accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5867 | RT-Thread lwp_syscall.c csys_sendto null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5867</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in RT-Thread 5.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function csys_sendto of the file rt-thread/components/lwp/lwp_syscall.c. The manipulation of the argument to leads to null pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5866 | RT-Thread lwp_syscall.c sys_sigprocmask array index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5866</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in RT-Thread 5.1.0. This affects the function sys_sigprocmask of the file rt-thread/components/lwp/lwp_syscall.c. The manipulation of the argument how leads to improper validation of array index.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5893 | Honding Technology Smart Parking Management System - Exposure of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5893</link><description>Smart Parking Management System from Honding Technology has an Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access a specific page and obtain plaintext administrator credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5865 | RT-Thread Parameter lwp_syscall.c sys_select memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RT-Thread 5.1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sys_select of the file rt-thread/components/lwp/lwp_syscall.c of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument timeout leads to memory corruption. The vendor explains, that "[t]he timeout parameter should be checked to check if it can be accessed correctly in kernel mode and used temporarily in kernel memory."</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25207 | Rhcl: authpolicy callbacks result in denial of service in authorino severity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25207</link><description>The Authorino service in the Red Hat Connectivity Link is the authorization service for zero trust API security. Authorino allows the users with developer persona to add callbacks to be executed to HTTP endpoints once the authorization process is completed. It was found that an attacker with developer persona access can add a large number of those callbacks to be executed by Authorino and as the authentication policy is enforced by a single instance of the service, this leada to a Denial of Service in Authorino while processing the post-authorization callbacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25208 | Rhcl: authorino denial of service through authpolicy with sharedsecretref severity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25208</link><description>A Developer persona can bring down the Authorino service, preventing the evaluation of all AuthPolicies on the cluster</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25209 | Rhcl: sharedsecretref can be used to leak secrets severity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25209</link><description>The AuthPolicy metadata on Red Hat Connectivity Link contains an object which stores secretes, however it assumes those secretes are already in the kuadrant-system instead of copying it to the referred namespace. This creates space for a malicious actor with a developer persona access to leak those secrets over HTTP connection, as long the attacker knows the name of the targeted secrets and those secrets are limited to one line only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3581 | Newsletter &amp;lt; 8.8.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3581</link><description>The Newsletter  WordPress plugin before 8.8.5 does not validate and escape some of its Widget options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3582 | Newsletter &amp;lt; 8.8.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3582</link><description>The Newsletter  WordPress plugin before 8.85 does not sanitise and escape some of its Form settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47711 | Nbdkit: nbdkit-server: off-by-one error when processing block status may lead to a denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47711</link><description>There's a flaw in the nbdkit server when handling responses from its plugins regarding the status of data blocks. If a client makes a specific request for a very large data range, and a plugin responds with an even larger single block, the nbdkit server can encounter a critical internal error, leading to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47712 | Nbd: nbdkit: integer overflow triggers an assertion resulting in denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47712</link><description>A flaw exists in the nbdkit "blocksize" filter that can be triggered by a specific type of client request. When a client requests block status information for a very large data range, exceeding a certain limit, it causes an internal error in the nbdkit, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4652 | Broadstreet &amp;lt; 1.51.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4652</link><description>The Broadstreet WordPress plugin before 1.51.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5864 | Tenda TDSEE App Password Reset Confirmation Code ConfirmSmsCode excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5864</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TDSEE App up to 1.7.12. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /app/ConfirmSmsCode of the component Password Reset Confirmation Code Handler. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.7.15 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5863 | Tenda AC5 SetRebootTimer formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5863</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC5 15.03.06.47. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetRebootTimer. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 05:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5862 | Tenda AC7 setPptpUserList formSetPPTPUserList buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5862</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetPPTPUserList of the file /goform/setPptpUserList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 05:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5861 | Tenda AC7 AdvSetLanip fromadvsetlanip buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5861</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function fromadvsetlanip of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanMask leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5860 | PHPGurukul Maid Hiring Management System search-booking-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5860</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Maid Hiring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/search-booking-request.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5859 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System test-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5859</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /test-details.php. The manipulation of the argument assignto leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 03:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5857 | code-projects Patient Record Management System urinalysis_record.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5857</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /urinalysis_record.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 03:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5858 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System patient-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5858</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /patient-report.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 03:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5856 | PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5856</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /registration.php. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 02:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5855 | Tenda AC6 SetRebootTimer formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5855</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16. This affects the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetRebootTimer. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 02:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5854 | Tenda AC6 AdvSetLanip fromadvsetlanip buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5854</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16. Affected by this issue is the function fromadvsetlanip of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanMask leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 02:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5852 | Tenda AC6 setPptpUserList formSetPPTPUserList buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5852</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16. Affected is the function formSetPPTPUserList of the file /goform/setPptpUserList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5853 | Tenda AC6 SetRemoteWebCfg formSetSafeWanWebMan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5853</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetSafeWanWebMan of the file /goform/SetRemoteWebCfg. The manipulation of the argument remoteIp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5851 | Tenda AC15 HTTP POST Request AdvSetLanip fromadvsetlanip buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5851</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC15 15.03.05.19_multi. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function fromadvsetlanip of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument lanMask leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5850 | Tenda AC15 HTTP POST Request SetLEDCf formsetschedled buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5850</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC15 15.03.05.19_multi. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formsetschedled of the file /goform/SetLEDCf of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument Time leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5849 | Tenda AC15 HTTP POST Request SetRemoteWebCfg formSetSafeWanWebMan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5849</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC15 15.03.05.19_multi. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formSetSafeWanWebMan of the file /goform/SetRemoteWebCfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument remoteIp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 22:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5848 | Tenda AC15 HTTP POST Request setPptpUserList formSetPPTPUserList buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5848</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC15 15.03.05.19_multi and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetPPTPUserList of the file /goform/setPptpUserList of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35004 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MFIP Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35004</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MFIP command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35005 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MFMAC Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35005</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MFMAC command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35006 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MFPORTFWD Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35006</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MFPORTFWD command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35007 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MFRULE Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35007</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MFRULE command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35008 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MMNAME Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35008</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MMNAME command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35009 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MNNETSP Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35009</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MNNETSP command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35010 | Microhard Bullet-LTE and IPn4Gii AT+MNPINGTM Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35010</link><description>Products that incorporate the Microhard BulletLTE-NA2 and IPn4Gii-NA2 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection issue in the AT+MNPINGTM command that can lead to privilege escalation. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.1 (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N). This issue has not been generally fixed at the time of this CVE record's first publishing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32455 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna router_command.sh (in the run_cmd argument) Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32455</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, router_command.sh (in the run_cmd argument), that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32456 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna router_command.sh (in the put_file_to_qtn argument) Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32456</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, router_command.sh (in the put_file_to_qtn argument), that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32457 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna router_command.sh (in the get_file_from_qtn argument) Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32457</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, router_command.sh (in the get_file_from_qtn argument), that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32458 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna router_command.sh (in the get_syslog_from_qtn argument) Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32458</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, router_command.sh (in the get_syslog_from_qtn argument), that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32459 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna router_command.sh (in the sync_time argument) Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32459</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, router_command.sh (in the sync_time argument), that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3459 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna transmit_file Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3459</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, transmit_file, that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3460 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna set_tx_pow Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3460</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset ships with a local control script, set_tx_pow, that is vulnerable to command injection. This is an instance of CWE-88, "Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection')," and is estimated as a CVSS 7.7 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3461 | ON Semiconductor Quantenna Telnet Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3461</link><description>The Quantenna Wi-Fi chips ship with an unauthenticated telnet interface by default. This is an instance of CWE-306, "Missing Authentication for Critical Function," and is estimated as a CVSS 9.1 ( CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3-1#CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N) .
This issue affects Quantenna Wi-Fi chipset through version 8.0.0.28 of the latest SDK, and appears to be unpatched at the time of this CVE record's first publishing, though the vendor has released a best practices guide for implementors of this chipset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5847 | Tenda AC9 HTTP POST Request SetRemoteWebCfg formSetSafeWanWebMan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5847</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC9 15.03.02.13 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetSafeWanWebMan of the file /goform/SetRemoteWebCfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument remoteIp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20063 | arkui_ace_engine has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20063</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21082 | arkui_ace_engine has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21082</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23235 | arkcompiler_ets_runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23235</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through  out-of-bounds read.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24493 | kernel_liteos_a has a race condition vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24493</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through race condition.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25217 | arkui_ace_enginehas a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25217</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26691 | telephony_call_manager has an improper preservation of permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26691</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through get permission.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26693 | security_access_token has an improper preservation of permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26693</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through get permission.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27131 | kernel_liteos_m has an improper input vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27131</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27242 | Ssecurity_component_manager has an improper input vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27242</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through   improper input.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27247 | Pasteboard has an improper preservation of permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27247</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through get permission.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27563 | security_access_token has an improper preservation of permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27563</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through get permission.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38003 | can: bcm: add missing rcu read protection for procfs content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38003</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: bcm: add missing rcu read protection for procfs content

When the procfs content is generated for a bcm_op which is in the process
to be removed the procfs output might show unreliable data (UAF).

As the removal of bcm_op's is already implemented with rcu handling this
patch adds the missing rcu_read_lock() and makes sure the list entries
are properly removed under rcu protection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38004 | can: bcm: add locking for bcm_op runtime updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38004</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: bcm: add locking for bcm_op runtime updates

The CAN broadcast manager (CAN BCM) can send a sequence of CAN frames via
hrtimer. The content and also the length of the sequence can be changed
resp reduced at runtime where the 'currframe' counter is then set to zero.

Although this appeared to be a safe operation the updates of 'currframe'
can be triggered from user space and hrtimer context in bcm_can_tx().
Anderson Nascimento created a proof of concept that triggered a KASAN
slab-out-of-bounds read access which can be prevented with a spin_lock_bh.

At the rework of bcm_can_tx() the 'count' variable has been moved into
the protected section as this variable can be modified from both contexts
too.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>