<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:29:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-24430 | A reachable assertion in the mme_ue_find_by_imsi function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24430</link><description>A reachable assertion in the mme_ue_find_by_imsi function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0395 | When the assert() function in the GNU C Library versions 2.13 to 2.40 fails, it does not allocate enough space for the assertion failure mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0395</link><description>When the assert() function in the GNU C Library versions 2.13 to 2.40 fails, it does not allocate enough space for the assertion failure message string and size information, which may lead to a buffer overflow if the message string size aligns to page size.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13447 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Email Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13447</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the hotel_booking_load_order_user AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve a list of registered user emails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13495 | GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via gamipress_ajax_get_logs Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13495</link><description>The The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via the gamipress_ajax_get_logs() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13496 | GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13496</link><description>The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13499 | GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via gamipress_do_shortcode() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13499</link><description>The The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via gamipress_do_shortcode() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23439 | A externally controlled reference to a resource in another sphere in Fortinet FortiManager before version 7.4.3, FortiMail before version 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23439</link><description>A externally controlled reference to a resource in another sphere in Fortinet FortiManager before version 7.4.3, FortiMail before version 7.0.3, FortiAnalyzer before version 7.4.3, FortiVoice version 7.0.0, 7.0.1 and before 6.4.8, FortiProxy before version 7.0.4, FortiRecorder version 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 and before 6.0.10, FortiAuthenticator version 6.4.0 through 6.4.1 and before 6.3.3, FortiNDR version 7.2.0 before 7.1.0, FortiWLC before version 8.6.4, FortiPortal before version 6.0.9, FortiOS version 7.2.0 and before 7.0.5, FortiADC version 7.0.0 through 7.0.1 and before 6.2.3 , FortiDDoS before version 5.5.1, FortiDDoS-F before version 6.3.3, FortiTester before version 7.2.1, FortiSOAR before version 7.2.2 and FortiSwitch before version 6.3.3 allows attacker to poison web caches via crafted HTTP requests, where the `Host` header points to an arbitrary webserver</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 09:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13319 | Themify Builder &amp;lt;= 7.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13319</link><description>The Themify Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13360 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13360</link><description>The AI Power: Complete AI Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.96 via the wpaicg_troubleshoot_add_vector(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13361 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13361</link><description>The AI Power: Complete AI Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpaicg_save_image_media function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.96. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload image files and embed shortcode attributes in the image_alt value that will execute when sending a POST request to the attachment page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0428 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via wpaicg_export_prompts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0428</link><description>The "AI Power: Complete AI Pack" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.8.96 via deserialization of untrusted input from the $form['post_content'] variable through the wpaicg_export_prompts function. This allows authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0429 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via wpaicg_export_ai_forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0429</link><description>The "AI Power: Complete AI Pack" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.8.96 via deserialization of untrusted input from the $form['post_content'] variable through the wpaicg_export_ai_forms() function. This allows authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12117 | Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.13.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12117</link><description>The Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter of the Button block in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12857 | AdForest &amp;lt;= 5.1.8 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12857</link><description>The AdForest theme for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.8. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to logging them in as that user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to authenticate as any user as long as they have configured OTP login by phone number.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13406 | XML for Google Merchant Center &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13406</link><description>The XML for Google Merchant Center plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'feed_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23237 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23237</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. If a user logs in to CLI of the affected product, an arbitrary OS command may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 06:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20617 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20617</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by an attacker who can access the affected product with an administrative account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22450 | Inclusion of undocumented features issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. A remote attacker may disable the LAN-side f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22450</link><description>Inclusion of undocumented features issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. A remote attacker may disable the LAN-side firewall function of the affected products, and open specific ports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12879 | WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot &amp;lt;= 13.5.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Simple Text Response Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12879</link><description>The WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'qc_wp_latest_update_check_pro' function in all versions up to, and including, 13.5.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create Simple Text Responses to chat queries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11218 | Podman: buildah: container breakout by using --jobs=2 and a race condition when building a malicious containerfile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11218</link><description>A vulnerability was found in `podman build` and `buildah.` This issue occurs in a container breakout by using --jobs=2 and a race condition when building a malicious Containerfile. SELinux might mitigate it, but even with SELinux on, it still allows the enumeration of files and directories on the host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13584 | Picture Gallery – Frontend Image Uploads, AJAX Photo List &amp;lt;= 1.5.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13584</link><description>The Picture Gallery – Frontend Image Uploads, AJAX Photo List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_pictures' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13590 | Ketchup Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 0.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13590</link><description>The Ketchup Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spacer' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13426 | WP-Polls &amp;lt;= 2.77.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13426</link><description>The WP-Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via COOKIE in all versions up to, and including, 2.77.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries. Those queries are stored and results are not displayed to the attacker, which means they cannot be exploited to obtain any additional information about the database. However, a properly configured payload allows for the injection of malicious JavaScript resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23083 | With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23083</link><description>With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only to workers but also exposes internal workers, where an instance of them can be fetched, and its constructor can be grabbed and reinstated for malicious usage. 

This vulnerability affects Permission Model users (--permission) on Node.js v20, v22, and v23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23087 | This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23087</link><description>This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported and do not receive updates, including security patches. The continued use of EOL versions may expose systems to potential security risks due to unaddressed software vulnerabilities or dependencies (CWE-1104: Use of Unmaintained Third-Party Components).

Users are advised to upgrade to actively supported versions of Node.js to ensure continued security updates and support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23088 | This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23088</link><description>This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported and do not receive updates, including security patches. The continued use of EOL versions may expose systems to potential security risks due to unaddressed software vulnerabilities or dependencies (CWE-1104: Use of Unmaintained Third-Party Components).

Users are advised to upgrade to actively supported versions of Node.js to ensure continued security updates and support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23089 | This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23089</link><description>This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported and do not receive updates, including security patches. The continued use of EOL versions may expose systems to potential security risks due to unaddressed software vulnerabilities or dependencies (CWE-1104: Use of Unmaintained Third-Party Components).

Users are advised to upgrade to actively supported versions of Node.js to ensure continued security updates and support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23090 | With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23090</link><description>With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only to workers
 but also exposes internal workers, where an instance of them can be fetched, and its constructor can be grabbed and reinstated for malicious usage.

This vulnerability affects Permission Model users (--permission) on Node.js v20, v22, and v23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0625 | CampCodes School Management Software Attachment resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0625</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Attachment Handler. The manipulation leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 01:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37039 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37039</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allow network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Initial UE Message` packet missing an expected `RRC Establishment Clause` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13091 | WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot &amp;lt;= 13.5.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13091</link><description>The WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'qcld_wpcfb_file_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 13.5.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Note: The exploit requires thee ChatBot Conversational Forms plugin and the Conversational Form Builder Pro addon plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37033 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37033</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Initial UE Message` packet missing an expected `EUTRAN_CGI` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37034 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37034</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Initial UE Message` packet missing an expected `TAI` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37035 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37035</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `S1Setup Request` packet missing an expected `Global eNB ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37036 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37036</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Uplink NAS Transport` packet missing an expected `ENB_UE_S1AP_ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37037 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37037</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `S1Setup Request` packet missing an expected `Supported TAs` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37038 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37038</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Uplink NAS Transport` packet missing an expected `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40108 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to access media content belonging to another user due to a missing permission check. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40108</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to access media content belonging to another user due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40132 | In setActualDefaultRingtoneUri of RingtoneManager.java, there is a possible way to bypass content providers read permissions due to a missin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40132</link><description>In setActualDefaultRingtoneUri of RingtoneManager.java, there is a possible way to bypass content providers read permissions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34730 | In multiple locations, there is a possible bypass of user consent to enabling new Bluetooth HIDs due to a logic error in the code. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34730</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible bypass of user consent to enabling new Bluetooth HIDs due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43095 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to obtain any system permission due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43095</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to obtain any system permission due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43096 | In build_read_multi_rsp of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43096</link><description>In build_read_multi_rsp of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43763 | In build_read_multi_rsp of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible denial of service due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43763</link><description>In build_read_multi_rsp of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible denial of service due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43765 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to obtain access to a folder due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43765</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to obtain access to a folder due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43770 | In gatts_process_find_info of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43770</link><description>In gatts_process_find_info of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43771 | In gatts_process_read_req of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43771</link><description>In gatts_process_read_req of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49724 | In multiple functions of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass permissions and launch protected activities due to a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49724</link><description>In multiple functions of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass permissions and launch protected activities due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49732 | In multiple functions of CompanionDeviceManagerService.java, there is a possible way to grant permissions without user consent due to a miss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49732</link><description>In multiple functions of CompanionDeviceManagerService.java, there is a possible way to grant permissions without user consent due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49733 | In reload of ServiceListing.java , there is a possible way to allow a malicious app to hide an NLS from Settings due to a logic error in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49733</link><description>In reload of ServiceListing.java , there is a possible way to allow a malicious app to hide an NLS from Settings due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49734 | In multiple functions of ConnectivityService.java, there is a possible way for a Wi-Fi AP to determine what site a device has connected to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49734</link><description>In multiple functions of ConnectivityService.java, there is a possible way for a Wi-Fi AP to determine what site a device has connected to through a VPN due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49735 | In multiple locations, there is a possible failure to persist permissions settings due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49735</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible failure to persist permissions settings due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49736 | In onClick of MainClear.java, there is a possible way to trigger factory reset without explicit user consent due to a logic error in the cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49736</link><description>In onClick of MainClear.java, there is a possible way to trigger factory reset without explicit user consent due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49737 | In applyTaskFragmentOperation of WindowOrganizerController.java, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities as the system UID du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49737</link><description>In applyTaskFragmentOperation of WindowOrganizerController.java, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities as the system UID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49738 | In writeInplace of Parcel.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49738</link><description>In writeInplace of Parcel.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49742 | In onCreate of NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity.java , there is a possible way to hide an app with notification access in Settings due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49742</link><description>In onCreate of NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity.java , there is a possible way to hide an app with notification access in Settings due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49744 | In  checkKeyIntentParceledCorrectly of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass parcel mismatch mitigation  due to unsa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49744</link><description>In  checkKeyIntentParceledCorrectly of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass parcel mismatch mitigation  due to unsafe deserialization. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49745 | In growData of Parcel.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49745</link><description>In growData of Parcel.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49747 | In gatts_process_read_by_type_req of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49747</link><description>In gatts_process_read_by_type_req of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49748 | In gatts_process_primary_service_req of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49748</link><description>In gatts_process_primary_service_req of gatt_sr.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49749 | In DGifSlurp of dgif_lib.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remote code execution wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49749</link><description>In DGifSlurp of dgif_lib.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37028 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37028</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `E-RAB Modification Indication` packet missing an expected `eNB_UE_S1AP_ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37030 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37030</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Initial UE Message` packet missing an expected `eNB_UE_S1AP_ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37031 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37031</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `eNB Configuration Transfer` packet missing its required `Target eNB ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37025 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37025</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `Reset` packet missing an expected `ResetType` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37026 | A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37026</link><description>A Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `E-RAB Release Response` packet missing an expected `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37027 | Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37027</link><description>Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) in Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows network-adjacent attackers to crash the MME via an S1AP `E-RAB Modification Indication` packet missing an expected `eNB_UE_S1AP_ID` field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24417 | The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24417</link><description>The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the decode_protocol_configuration_options function at /3gpp/3gpp_24.008_sm_ies.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24421 | A type confusion in the nas_message_decode function of Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24421</link><description>A type confusion in the nas_message_decode function of Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24422 | The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a stack overfl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24422</link><description>The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the decode_protocol_configuration_options function at /3gpp/3gpp_24.008_sm_ies.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24423 | The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24423</link><description>The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the decode_esm_message_container function at /nas/ies/EsmMessageContainer.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24418 | The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24418</link><description>The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the decode_pdn_address function at /nas/ies/PdnAddress.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24420 | A reachable assertion in the decode_linked_ti_ie function of Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24420</link><description>A reachable assertion in the decode_linked_ti_ie function of Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24424 | A reachable assertion in the decode_access_point_name_ie function of Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24424</link><description>A reachable assertion in the decode_access_point_name_ie function of Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24416 | The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24416</link><description>The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the decode_access_point_name_ie function at /3gpp/3gpp_24.008_sm_ies.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24419 | The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24419</link><description>The Linux Foundation Magma &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the decode_traffic_flow_template_packet_filter function at /3gpp/3gpp_24.008_sm_ies.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37024 | A reachable assertion in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) of Magma versions &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37024</link><description>A reachable assertion in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) of Magma versions &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows remote attackers to crash the MME with an unauthenticated cellphone by sending a NAS packet containing an `Emergency Number List` Information Element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37029 | Magma versions &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) are susceptible to an assertion-based crash when an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37029</link><description>Magma versions &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) are susceptible to an assertion-based crash when an oversized NAS packet is received. An attacker may leverage this behavior to repeatedly crash the MME via either a compromised base station or via an unauthenticated cellphone within range of a base station managed by the MME, causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37032 | A Stack-based buffer overflow in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) of Magma versions &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37032</link><description>A Stack-based buffer overflow in the Mobile Management Entity (MME) of Magma versions &lt;= 1.8.0 (fixed in v1.9 commit 08472ba98b8321f802e95f5622fa90fec2dea486) allows remote attackers to crash the MME with an unauthenticated cellphone by sending a NAS packet containing an oversized `Emergency Number List` Information Element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24427 | A reachable assertion in the amf_ue_set_suci function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24427</link><description>A reachable assertion in the amf_ue_set_suci function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24428 | A reachable assertion in the oai_nas_5gmm_decode function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24428</link><description>A reachable assertion in the oai_nas_5gmm_decode function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NGAP packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24443 | An uninitialized pointer dereference in the ngap_handle_pdu_session_resource_setup_response routine of OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24443</link><description>An uninitialized pointer dereference in the ngap_handle_pdu_session_resource_setup_response routine of OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PDU Session Resource Setup Response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50733 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in newer Lexmark devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50733</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the Web Services feature of newer
Lexmark devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24442 | A NULL pointer dereference in the ngap_app::handle_receive routine of OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24442</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in the ngap_app::handle_receive routine of OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NGAP message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24444 | Improper file descriptor handling for closed connections in OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attackers to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24444</link><description>Improper file descriptor handling for closed connections in OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by repeatedly establishing SCTP connections with the N2 interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24451 | A stack overflow in the sctp_server::sctp_receiver_thread component of OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24451</link><description>A stack overflow in the sctp_server::sctp_receiver_thread component of OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) up to v2.0.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by repeatedly establishing SCTP connections with the N2 interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24445 | OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) &lt;= 2.0.0 contains a null dereference in its handling of unsupported NGAP protocol messages which al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24445</link><description>OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF (oai-cn5g-amf) &lt;= 2.0.0 contains a null dereference in its handling of unsupported NGAP protocol messages which allows an attacker with network-adjacent access to the AMF to carry out denial of service. When a procedure code/presence field tuple is received that is unsupported, OAI indexes into a null function pointer and subsequently dereferences it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27112 | pearProjectApi v2.8.10 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the projectCode parameter at project.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27112</link><description>pearProjectApi v2.8.10 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the projectCode parameter at project.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27113 | pearProjectApi v2.8.10 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the organizationCode parameter at project.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27113</link><description>pearProjectApi v2.8.10 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the organizationCode parameter at project.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45479 | Apache Ranger: SSRF in Edit Service page - Add logic to filter requests to localhost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45479</link><description>SSRF vulnerability in Edit Service Page of Apache Ranger UI in Apache Ranger Version 2.4.0.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version Apache Ranger 2.5.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45478 | Apache Ranger: Stored XSS in Edit Service page - Add logic to validate user input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45478</link><description>Stored XSS vulnerability in Edit Service Page of Apache Ranger UI in Apache Ranger Version 2.4.0.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version Apache Ranger 2.5.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51941 | Apache Ambari: Remote Code Injection in Ambari Metrics and AMS Alerts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51941</link><description>A remote code injection vulnerability exists in the Ambari Metrics and 
AMS Alerts feature, allowing authenticated users to inject and execute 
arbitrary code. The vulnerability occurs when processing alert 
definitions, where malicious input can be injected into the alert script
 execution path. An attacker with authenticated access can exploit this 
vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the server. The issue has
 been fixed in the latest versions of Ambari.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23195 | Apache Ambari: XML External Entity (XXE) Vulnerability in Ambari/Oozie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23195</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability exists in the Ambari/Oozie 
project, allowing an attacker to inject malicious XML entities. This 
vulnerability occurs due to insecure parsing of XML input using the 
`DocumentBuilderFactory` class without disabling external entity 
resolution. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary
 files on the server or perform server-side request forgery (SSRF) 
attacks. The issue has been fixed in both Ambari 2.7.9 and the trunk 
branch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23196 | Apache Ambari: Code Injection Vulnerability in Ambari Alert Definition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23196</link><description>A code injection vulnerability exists in the Ambari Alert Definition 
feature, allowing authenticated users to inject and execute arbitrary 
shell commands. The vulnerability arises when defining alert scripts, 
where the script filename field is executed using `sh -c`. An attacker 
with authenticated access can exploit this vulnerability to inject 
malicious commands, leading to remote code execution on the server. The 
issue has been fixed in the latest versions of Ambari.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55958 | Northern.tech CFEngine Enterprise Mission Portal 3.24.0, 3.21.5, and below allows XSS. The fixed versions are 3.24.1 and 3.21.6.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55958</link><description>Northern.tech CFEngine Enterprise Mission Portal 3.24.0, 3.21.5, and below allows XSS. The fixed versions are 3.24.1 and 3.21.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55959 | Northern.tech Mender Client 4.x before 4.0.5 has Insecure Permissions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55959</link><description>Northern.tech Mender Client 4.x before 4.0.5 has Insecure Permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21245 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21245</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48392 | OrangeScrum v2.0.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into user email due to lac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48392</link><description>OrangeScrum v2.0.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into user email due to lack of input validation, which could lead to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21489 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21489</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21490 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21490</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21491 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21491</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21492 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21492</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21493 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21493</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21494 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21494</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21495 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21495</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21497 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21497</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21498 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21498</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21499 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21499</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21500 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21500</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21501 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21501</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21502 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21502</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21503 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21503</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21504 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21504</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21505 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21505</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21506 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21506</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21507 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21507</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21508 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21508</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21509 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21509</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21510 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21510</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21511 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21511</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21512 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21512</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21513 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21513</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21514 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21514</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21515 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21515</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21516 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21516</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21517 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21517</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21518 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21518</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21519 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21519</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21520 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21520</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21521 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21521</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21522 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21522</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21523 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21523</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21524 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21524</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21525 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21525</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21526 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21526</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21527 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21527</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21528 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21528</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21529 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21529</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21530 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21530</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21531 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21531</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21532 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21532</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21533 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21533</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21534 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21534</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21535 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21535</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21536 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21536</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21537 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21537</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21538 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21538</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21539 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21539</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21540 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21540</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21541 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21541</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21542 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21542</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21543 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21543</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21544 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21544</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21545 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21545</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21546 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21546</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21547 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21547</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21548 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21548</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21549 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21549</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21550 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21550</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21551 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21551</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21552 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21552</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21553 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21553</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21554 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21554</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21555 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21555</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21556 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21556</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21557 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21557</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21558 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21558</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21559 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21559</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21560 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21560</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21561 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21561</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21562 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21562</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21563 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21563</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21564 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21564</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21565 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21565</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21566 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21566</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21567 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21567</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21568 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21568</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21569 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21569</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21570 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21570</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21571 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21571</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57360 | https://www.gnu.org/software/binutils/ nm &gt;=2.43 is affected by: Incorrect Access Control. The type of exploitation is: local. The component...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57360</link><description>https://www.gnu.org/software/binutils/ nm &gt;=2.43 is affected by: Incorrect Access Control. The type of exploitation is: local. The component is: `nm --without-symbol-version` function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57541 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (ipv6_protect_status) is copied to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57541</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (ipv6_protect_status) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57542 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the field id_email_check_btn.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57542</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the field id_email_check_btn.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57543 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (dhcpstart_ip) is copied to the sta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57543</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (dhcpstart_ip) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57544 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (lan_ipaddr) is copied to the stack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57544</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (lan_ipaddr) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57545 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (hidden_dhcp_num) is copied to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57545</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (hidden_dhcp_num) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57536 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via wizard_status.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57536</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via wizard_status.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57537 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (page) is copied to the stack witho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57537</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (page) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57538 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (anonymous_protect_status) is copie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57538</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (anonymous_protect_status) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57539 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via userEmail.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57539</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via userEmail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57540 | Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (action) is copied to the stack wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57540</link><description>Linksys E8450 v1.2.00.360516 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. The parsed field (action) is copied to the stack without length verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42936 | The mqlink.elf is service component in Ruijie RG-EW300N with firmware ReyeeOS 1.300.1422 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via a modifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42936</link><description>The mqlink.elf is service component in Ruijie RG-EW300N with firmware ReyeeOS 1.300.1422 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via a modified MQTT broker message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24024 | Mjolnir v1.9.0 accepts commands from any room</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24024</link><description>Mjolnir is a moderation tool for Matrix. Mjolnir v1.9.0 responds to management commands from any room the bot is member of. This can allow users who aren't operators of the bot to use the bot's functions, including server administration components if enabled. Version 1.9.1 reverts the feature that introduced the bug, and version 1.9.2 reintroduces the feature safely. Downgrading to version 1.8.3 is recommended if upgrading to 1.9.1 or higher isn't possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45908 | Homarr before v0.14.0 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Notebook widget.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45908</link><description>Homarr before v0.14.0 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Notebook widget.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55504 | An issue in RAR Extractor - Unarchiver Free and Pro v.6.4.0 allows local attackers to inject arbitrary code potentially leading to remote co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55504</link><description>An issue in RAR Extractor - Unarchiver Free and Pro v.6.4.0 allows local attackers to inject arbitrary code potentially leading to remote control and unauthorized access to sensitive user data via the exploit_combined.dylib component on MacOS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51417 | An issue in System.Linq.Dynamic.Core Latest version v.1.4.6 allows remote access to properties on reflection types and static properties/fie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51417</link><description>An issue in System.Linq.Dynamic.Core Latest version v.1.4.6 allows remote access to properties on reflection types and static properties/fields.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23369 | Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature in GitHub Enterprise Server Allows Signature Spoofing by Improper Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23369</link><description>An improper verification of cryptographic signature vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed signature spoofing for unauthorized internal users.  Instances not utilizing SAML single sign-on or where the attacker is not already an existing user were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12.14, 3.13.10, 3.14.7, 3.15.2, and 3.16.0. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54795 | SpagoBI v3.5.1 contains multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the create/edit forms of the worksheet designer functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54795</link><description>SpagoBI v3.5.1 contains multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the create/edit forms of the worksheet designer function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54792 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been found in SpagoBI v3.5.1 in the user administration panel. An authenticated user c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54792</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been found in SpagoBI v3.5.1 in the user administration panel. An authenticated user can lead another user into executing unwanted actions inside the application they are logged in, like adding, editing or deleting users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54794 | The script input feature of SpagoBI 3.5.1 allows arbitrary code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54794</link><description>The script input feature of SpagoBI 3.5.1 allows arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24020 | WeGIA Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24020</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. An Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the `control.php` endpoint of versions up to and including 3.2.10 of the WeGIA application. The vulnerability allows the `nextPage` parameter to be manipulated, redirecting authenticated users to arbitrary external URLs without validation. The issue stems from the lack of validation for the `nextPage` parameter, which accepts external URLs as redirection destinations. This vulnerability can be exploited to perform phishing attacks or redirect users to malicious websites. Version 3.2.11 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22150 | Undici Uses Insufficiently Random Values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22150</link><description>Undici is an HTTP/1.1 client. Starting in version 4.5.0 and prior to versions 5.28.5, 6.21.1, and 7.2.3, undici uses `Math.random()` to choose the boundary for a multipart/form-data request. It is known that the output of `Math.random()` can be predicted if several of its generated values are known. If there is a mechanism in an app that sends multipart requests to an attacker-controlled website, they can use this to leak the necessary values. Therefore, an attacker can tamper with the requests going to the backend APIs if certain conditions are met. This is fixed in versions 5.28.5, 6.21.1, and 7.2.3. As a workaround, do not issue multipart requests to attacker controlled servers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24019 | YesWiki vulnerable to authenticated arbitrary file deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24019</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. In versions up to and including 4.4.5, it is possible for any authenticated user, through the use of the filemanager to delete any file owned by the user running the FastCGI Process Manager (FPM) on the host without any limitation on the filesystem's scope. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to arbitrarily remove content from the Wiki resulting in partial loss of data and defacement/deterioration of the website. In the context of a container installation of YesWiki without any modification, the `yeswiki` files (for example .php) are not owned by the same user (root) as the one running the FPM process (www-data). However in a standard installation, www-data may also be the owner of the PHP files, allowing a malicious user to completely cut the access to the wiki by deleting all important PHP files (like index.php or core files of YesWiki). Version 4.5.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22267 | WordPress Weaver Themes Shortcode Compatibility Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22267</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bruce Wampler Weaver Themes Shortcode Compatibility allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Weaver Themes Shortcode Compatibility: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22276 | WordPress Related Post Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22276</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Enguerran Weiss Related Post Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Related Post Shortcode: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22661 | WordPress Online Payments plugin &amp;lt;= 3.20.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22661</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vcita.com Online Payments – Get Paid with PayPal, Square &amp; Stripe allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Online Payments – Get Paid with PayPal, Square &amp; Stripe: from n/a through 3.20.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22721 | WordPress ApplyOnline plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22721</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Farhan Noor ApplyOnline – Application Form Builder and Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ApplyOnline – Application Form Builder and Manager: from n/a through 2.6.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22722 | WordPress Widget Options plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.8 - Broken Access Control to Notice Dimissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22722</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Widget Options Team Widget Options allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Widget Options: from n/a through 4.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23454 | WordPress Nature FlipBook WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23454</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in flashmaniac Nature FlipBook allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Nature FlipBook: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23461 | WordPress Social2Blog plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.990 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23461</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Andrea Dotta, Jacopo Campani, di xkoll.com Social2Blog allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Social2Blog: from n/a through 0.2.990.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23477 | WordPress Realty Workstation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.45 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23477</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Realty Workstation Realty Workstation allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Realty Workstation: from n/a through 1.0.45.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23489 | WordPress WP-Announcements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23489</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brian Messenlehner of WebDevStudios WP-Announcements allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP-Announcements: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23551 | WordPress SexBundle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in P. Razvan SexBundle allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects SexBundle: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23580 | WordPress BizLibrary plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23580</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matthew Garvin BizLibrary allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BizLibrary: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23994 | WordPress Estatebud – Properties &amp;amp; Listings plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23994</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Estatebud Estatebud – Properties &amp; Listings allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Estatebud – Properties &amp; Listings: from n/a through 5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23996 | WordPress AnyRoad plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23996</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in anyroad.com AnyRoad allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects AnyRoad: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24456 | In JetBrains Hub before 2024.3.55417 privilege escalation was possible via LDAP authentication mapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24456</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2024.3.55417 privilege escalation was possible via LDAP authentication mapping</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24457 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.55417 permanent tokens could be exposed in logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24457</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.55417 permanent tokens could be exposed in logs</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24458 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.55417 account takeover was possible via spoofed email and Helpdesk integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24458</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.55417 account takeover was possible via spoofed email and Helpdesk integration</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24459 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12.1 reflected XSS was possible on the Vault Connection page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24459</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12.1 reflected XSS was possible on the Vault Connection page</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24460 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12.1 improper access control allowed to see Projects’ names in the agent pool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24460</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12.1 improper access control allowed to see Projects’ names in the agent pool</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24461 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12.1 decryption of connection secrets without proper permissions was possible via Test Connection endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24461</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12.1 decryption of connection secrets without proper permissions was possible via Test Connection endpoint</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24018 | YesWiki Vulnerable to Authenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24018</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. In versions up to and including 4.4.5, it is possible for an authenticated user with rights to edit/create a page or comment to trigger a stored XSS which will be reflected on any page where the resource is loaded. The vulnerability makes use of the content edition feature and more specifically of the `{{attach}}` component allowing users to attach files/medias to a page. When a file is attached using the `{{attach}}` component, if the resource contained in the `file` attribute doesn't exist, then the server will generate a file upload button containing the filename. This vulnerability allows any malicious authenticated user that has the right to create a comment or edit a page to be able to steal accounts and therefore modify pages, comments, permissions, extract user data (emails), thus impacting the integrity, availability and confidentiality of a YesWiki instance. Version 4.5.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45687 | HTTP Server incorrectly accepting disallowed characters within header values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45687</link><description>Improper Neutralization of CRLF Sequences in HTTP Headers ('HTTP Request/Response Splitting') vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server (Grizzly, REST Management Interface modules), Payara Platform Payara Micro (Grizzly modules) allows Manipulating State, Identity Spoofing.This issue affects Payara Server: from 4.1.151 through 4.1.2.191.51, from 5.20.0 through 5.70.0, from 5.2020.2 through 5.2022.5, from 6.2022.1 through 6.2024.12, from 6.0.0 through 6.21.0; Payara Micro: from 4.1.152 through 4.1.2.191.51, from 5.20.0 through 5.70.0, from 5.2020.2 through 5.2022.5, from 6.2022.1 through 6.2024.12, from 6.0.0 through 6.21.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57036 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5032_B20200407 was found to contain a command insertion vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi main function. This vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57036</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5032_B20200407 was found to contain a command insertion vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi main function. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands by sending HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56990 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /view-medhistory.php and /admin/view-patient.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56990</link><description>PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /view-medhistory.php and /admin/view-patient.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24017 | YesWiki Vulnerable to Unauthenticated DOM Based XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24017</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Versions up to and including 4.4.5 are vulnerable to any end-user crafting a DOM based XSS on all of YesWiki's pages which is triggered when a user clicks on a malicious link. The vulnerability makes use of the search by tag feature. When a tag doesn't exist, the tag is reflected on the page and isn't properly sanitized on the server side which allows a malicious user to generate a link that will trigger an XSS on the client's side when clicked. This vulnerability allows any user to generate a malicious link that will trigger an account takeover when clicked, therefore allowing a user to steal other accounts, modify pages, comments, permissions, extract user data (emails), thus impacting the integrity, availability and confidentiality of a YesWiki instance. Version 4.5.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24011 | Umbraco CMS Vulnerable to User Enumeration Feasible Based On Management API Timing and Response Codes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24011</link><description>Umbraco is a free and open source .NET content management system. Starting in version 14.0.0 and prior to versions 14.3.2 and 15.1.2, it's possible to determine whether an account exists based on an analysis of response codes and timing of Umbraco management API responses. Versions 14.3.2 and 15.1.2 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24012 | Umbraco Backoffice Components Have XSS/HTML Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24012</link><description>Umbraco is a free and open source .NET content management system. Starting in version 14.0.0 and prior to versions 14.3.2 and 15.1.2, authenticated users are able to exploit a cross-site scripting vulnerability when viewing certain localized backoffice components. Versions 14.3.2 and 15.1.2 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0377 | HashiCorp go-slug Vulnerable to Zip Slip Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0377</link><description>HashiCorp’s go-slug library is vulnerable to a zip-slip style attack when a non-existing user-provided path is extracted from the tar entry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53829 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in CodeChecker API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53829</link><description>CodeChecker is an analyzer tooling, defect database and viewer extension for the Clang Static Analyzer and Clang Tidy. 
Cross-site request forgery allows an unauthenticated attacker to hijack the authentication of a logged in user, and use the web API with the same permissions, including but not limited to adding, removing or editing products. The attacker needs to know the ID of the available products to modify or delete them. The attacker cannot directly exfiltrate data (view) from CodeChecker, due to being limited to form-based CSRF.

This issue affects CodeChecker: through 6.24.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56997 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /doctor/index.php via the 'Email' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56997</link><description>PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /doctor/index.php via the 'Email' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56998 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit-profile.php via the parameter $address.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56998</link><description>PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit-profile.php via the parameter $address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32555 | WordPress Easy Real Estate plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32555</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in NotFound Easy Real Estate allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Easy Real Estate: from n/a through 2.2.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22262 | WordPress Bonjour Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Bonjour Bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bonjour Bar: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22706 | WordPress Social Pug: Author Box plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22706</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in iova.mihai Social Pug: Author Box allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Social Pug: Author Box: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22709 | WordPress Verge3D Publishing and E-Commerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22709</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Soft8Soft LLC Verge3D allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Verge3D: from n/a through 4.8.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22710 | WordPress Smart Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.52.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22710</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in StoreApps Smart Manager allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Smart Manager: from n/a through 8.52.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22711 | WordPress Image Source Control Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.29.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22711</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Thomas Maier Image Source Control allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Image Source Control: from n/a through 2.29.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22716 | WordPress Taskbuilder Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22716</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Taskbuilder Team Taskbuilder allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Taskbuilder: from n/a through 3.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22717 | WordPress My Tickets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22717</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Joe Dolson My Tickets allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects My Tickets: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22718 | WordPress FAT Event Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22718</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Roninwp FAT Event Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FAT Event Lite: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22719 | WordPress VikAppointments Services Booking Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.16 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22719</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in E4J s.r.l. VikAppointments Services Booking Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects VikAppointments Services Booking Calendar: from n/a through 1.2.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22723 | WordPress Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22723</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22727 | WordPress MailChimp Subscribe Form plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22727</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PluginOps MailChimp Subscribe Forms  allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MailChimp Subscribe Forms : from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22732 | WordPress Ad Blocking Detector plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22732</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Admiral Ad Blocking Detector allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ad Blocking Detector: from n/a through 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22733 | WordPress My auctions allegro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.18 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22733</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPHocus My auctions allegro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects My auctions allegro: from n/a through 3.6.18.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22825 | WordPress Flexible PDF Coupons plugin &amp;lt; 1.10.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22825</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Desk Flexible PDF Coupons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Flexible PDF Coupons: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23997 | WordPress Tamara Checkout plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23997</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in dev@tamara.co Tamara Checkout allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tamara Checkout: from n/a through 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23998 | WordPress UltraLight theme &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23998</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rara Theme UltraLight allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects UltraLight: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24001 | WordPress PPO Call To Actions plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24001</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PPO Việt Nam (ppo.vn) PPO Call To Actions allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects PPO Call To Actions: from n/a through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49300 | WordPress Hero Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49300</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Hero Mega Menu - Responsive WordPress Menu Plugin allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Hero Mega Menu - Responsive WordPress Menu Plugin: from n/a through 1.16.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49303 | WordPress Hero Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Hero Mega Menu - Responsive WordPress Menu Plugin allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Hero Mega Menu - Responsive WordPress Menu Plugin: from n/a through 1.16.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49333 | WordPress Hero Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49333</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Hero Mega Menu - Responsive WordPress Menu Plugin allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Hero Mega Menu - Responsive WordPress Menu Plugin: from n/a through 1.16.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49655 | WordPress ARPrice plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound ARPrice allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ARPrice: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49666 | WordPress ARPrice plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound ARPrice allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ARPrice: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49688 | WordPress ARPrice plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49688</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NotFound ARPrice allows Object Injection. This issue affects ARPrice: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49699 | WordPress ARPrice plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49699</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NotFound ARPrice allows Object Injection. This issue affects ARPrice: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49700 | WordPress ARPrice plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound ARPrice allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ARPrice: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51818 | WordPress Fancy Product Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51818</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Fancy Product Designer. This issue affects Fancy Product Designer: from n/a through 6.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51888 | WordPress Homey Login Register Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51888</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in NotFound Homey Login Register allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Homey Login Register: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51919 | WordPress Fancy Product Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51919</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NotFound Fancy Product Designer. This issue affects Fancy Product Designer: from n/a through 6.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56277 | WordPress Poll Maker Plugin &amp;lt; 5.5.5 - HTML Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56277</link><description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output vulnerability in Poll Maker Team Poll Maker. This issue affects Poll Maker: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22311 | WordPress Private Messages for UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22311</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound Private Messages for UserPro. This issue affects Private Messages for UserPro: from n/a through 4.10.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22318 | WordPress Standard Box Sizes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22318</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Eniture Technology Standard Box Sizes – for WooCommerce. This issue affects Standard Box Sizes – for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22322 | WordPress Private Messages for UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22322</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Private Messages for UserPro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Private Messages for UserPro: from n/a through 4.10.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22553 | WordPress Multiple Carousel Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Multiple Carousel allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Multiple Carousel: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22735 | WordPress Tag Cloud Plugin - Tag Groups plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22735</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in TaxoPress WordPress Tag Cloud Plugin – Tag Groups allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress Tag Cloud Plugin – Tag Groups: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22763 | WordPress Brizy Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22763</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Brizy Pro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Brizy Pro: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57939 | riscv: Fix sleeping in invalid context in die()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57939</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: Fix sleeping in invalid context in die()

die() can be called in exception handler, and therefore cannot sleep.
However, die() takes spinlock_t which can sleep with PREEMPT_RT enabled.
That causes the following warning:

BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at kernel/locking/spinlock_rt.c:48
in_atomic(): 1, irqs_disabled(): 1, non_block: 0, pid: 285, name: mutex
preempt_count: 110001, expected: 0
RCU nest depth: 0, expected: 0
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 285 Comm: mutex Not tainted 6.12.0-rc7-00022-ge19049cf7d56-dirty #234
Hardware name: riscv-virtio,qemu (DT)
Call Trace:
    dump_backtrace+0x1c/0x24
    show_stack+0x2c/0x38
    dump_stack_lvl+0x5a/0x72
    dump_stack+0x14/0x1c
    __might_resched+0x130/0x13a
    rt_spin_lock+0x2a/0x5c
    die+0x24/0x112
    do_trap_insn_illegal+0xa0/0xea
    _new_vmalloc_restore_context_a0+0xcc/0xd8
Oops - illegal instruction [#1]

Switch to use raw_spinlock_t, which does not sleep even with PREEMPT_RT
enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57940 | exfat: fix the infinite loop in exfat_readdir()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57940</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

exfat: fix the infinite loop in exfat_readdir()

If the file system is corrupted so that a cluster is linked to
itself in the cluster chain, and there is an unused directory
entry in the cluster, 'dentry' will not be incremented, causing
condition 'dentry &lt; max_dentries' unable to prevent an infinite
loop.

This infinite loop causes s_lock not to be released, and other
tasks will hang, such as exfat_sync_fs().

This commit stops traversing the cluster chain when there is unused
directory entry in the cluster to avoid this infinite loop.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57941 | netfs: Fix the (non-)cancellation of copy when cache is temporarily disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57941</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfs: Fix the (non-)cancellation of copy when cache is temporarily disabled

When the caching for a cookie is temporarily disabled (e.g. due to a DIO
write on that file), future copying to the cache for that file is disabled
until all fds open on that file are closed.  However, if netfslib is using
the deprecated PG_private_2 method (such as is currently used by ceph), and
decides it wants to copy to the cache, netfs_advance_write() will just bail
at the first check seeing that the cache stream is unavailable, and
indicate that it dealt with all the content.

This means that we have no subrequests to provide notifications to drive
the state machine or even to pin the request and the request just gets
discarded, leaving the folios with PG_private_2 set.

Fix this by jumping directly to cancel the request if the cache is not
available.  That way, we don't remove mark3 from the folio_queue list and
netfs_pgpriv2_cancel() will clean up the folios.

This was found by running the generic/013 xfstest against ceph with an
active cache and the "-o fsc" option passed to ceph.  That would usually
hang</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57942 | netfs: Fix ceph copy to cache on write-begin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57942</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfs: Fix ceph copy to cache on write-begin

At the end of netfs_unlock_read_folio() in which folios are marked
appropriately for copying to the cache (either with by being marked dirty
and having their private data set or by having PG_private_2 set) and then
unlocked, the folio_queue struct has the entry pointing to the folio
cleared.  This presents a problem for netfs_pgpriv2_write_to_the_cache(),
which is used to write folios marked with PG_private_2 to the cache as it
expects to be able to trawl the folio_queue list thereafter to find the
relevant folios, leading to a hang.

Fix this by not clearing the folio_queue entry if we're going to do the
deprecated copy-to-cache.  The clearance will be done instead as the folios
are written to the cache.

This can be reproduced by starting cachefiles, mounting a ceph filesystem
with "-o fsc" and writing to it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57943 | exfat: fix the new buffer was not zeroed before writing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57943</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

exfat: fix the new buffer was not zeroed before writing

Before writing, if a buffer_head marked as new, its data must
be zeroed, otherwise uninitialized data in the page cache will
be written.

So this commit uses folio_zero_new_buffers() to zero the new
buffers before -&gt;write_end().</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57944 | iio: adc: ti-ads1298: Add NULL check in ads1298_init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57944</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iio: adc: ti-ads1298: Add NULL check in ads1298_init

devm_kasprintf() can return a NULL pointer on failure. A check on the
return value of such a call in ads1298_init() is missing. Add it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57945 | riscv: mm: Fix the out of bound issue of vmemmap address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57945</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: mm: Fix the out of bound issue of vmemmap address

In sparse vmemmap model, the virtual address of vmemmap is calculated as:
((struct page *)VMEMMAP_START - (phys_ram_base &gt;&gt; PAGE_SHIFT)).
And the struct page's va can be calculated with an offset:
(vmemmap + (pfn)).

However, when initializing struct pages, kernel actually starts from the
first page from the same section that phys_ram_base belongs to. If the
first page's physical address is not (phys_ram_base &gt;&gt; PAGE_SHIFT), then
we get an va below VMEMMAP_START when calculating va for it's struct page.

For example, if phys_ram_base starts from 0x82000000 with pfn 0x82000, the
first page in the same section is actually pfn 0x80000. During
init_unavailable_range(), we will initialize struct page for pfn 0x80000
with virtual address ((struct page *)VMEMMAP_START - 0x2000), which is
below VMEMMAP_START as well as PCI_IO_END.

This commit fixes this bug by introducing a new variable
'vmemmap_start_pfn' which is aligned with memory section size and using
it to calculate vmemmap address instead of phys_ram_base.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57946 | virtio-blk: don&amp;#x27;t keep queue frozen during system suspend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57946</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

virtio-blk: don't keep queue frozen during system suspend

Commit 4ce6e2db00de ("virtio-blk: Ensure no requests in virtqueues before
deleting vqs.") replaces queue quiesce with queue freeze in virtio-blk's
PM callbacks. And the motivation is to drain inflight IOs before suspending.

block layer's queue freeze looks very handy, but it is also easy to cause
deadlock, such as, any attempt to call into bio_queue_enter() may run into
deadlock if the queue is frozen in current context. There are all kinds
of -&gt;suspend() called in suspend context, so keeping queue frozen in the
whole suspend context isn't one good idea. And Marek reported lockdep
warning[1] caused by virtio-blk's freeze queue in virtblk_freeze().

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/linux-block/ca16370e-d646-4eee-b9cc-87277c89c43c@samsung.com/

Given the motivation is to drain in-flight IOs, it can be done by calling
freeze &amp; unfreeze, meantime restore to previous behavior by keeping queue
quiesced during suspend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21656 | hwmon: (drivetemp) Fix driver producing garbage data when SCSI errors occur</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21656</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hwmon: (drivetemp) Fix driver producing garbage data when SCSI errors occur

scsi_execute_cmd() function can return both negative (linux codes) and
positive (scsi_cmnd result field) error codes.

Currently the driver just passes error codes of scsi_execute_cmd() to
hwmon core, which is incorrect because hwmon only checks for negative
error codes. This leads to hwmon reporting uninitialized data to
userspace in case of SCSI errors (for example if the disk drive was
disconnected).

This patch checks scsi_execute_cmd() output and returns -EIO if it's
error code is positive.

[groeck: Avoid inline variable declaration for portability]</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21657 | sched_ext: Replace rq_lock() to raw_spin_rq_lock() in scx_ops_bypass()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21657</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sched_ext: Replace rq_lock() to raw_spin_rq_lock() in scx_ops_bypass()

scx_ops_bypass() iterates all CPUs to re-enqueue all the scx tasks.
For each CPU, it acquires a lock using rq_lock() regardless of whether
a CPU is offline or the CPU is currently running a task in a higher
scheduler class (e.g., deadline). The rq_lock() is supposed to be used
for online CPUs, and the use of rq_lock() may trigger an unnecessary
warning in rq_pin_lock(). Therefore, replace rq_lock() to
raw_spin_rq_lock() in scx_ops_bypass().

Without this change, we observe the following warning:

===== START =====
[    6.615205] rq-&gt;balance_callback &amp;&amp; rq-&gt;balance_callback != &amp;amp;balance_push_callback
[    6.615208] WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 0 at kernel/sched/sched.h:1730 __schedule+0x1130/0x1c90
=====  END  =====</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21658 | btrfs: avoid NULL pointer dereference if no valid extent tree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21658</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: avoid NULL pointer dereference if no valid extent tree

[BUG]
Syzbot reported a crash with the following call trace:

  BTRFS info (device loop0): scrub: started on devid 1
  BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000208
  #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
  PGD 106e70067 P4D 106e70067 PUD 107143067 PMD 0
  Oops: Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
  CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 689 Comm: repro Kdump: loaded Tainted: G           O       6.13.0-rc4-custom+ #206
  Tainted: [O]=OOT_MODULE
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS unknown 02/02/2022
  RIP: 0010:find_first_extent_item+0x26/0x1f0 [btrfs]
  Call Trace:
   
   scrub_find_fill_first_stripe+0x13d/0x3b0 [btrfs]
   scrub_simple_mirror+0x175/0x260 [btrfs]
   scrub_stripe+0x5d4/0x6c0 [btrfs]
   scrub_chunk+0xbb/0x170 [btrfs]
   scrub_enumerate_chunks+0x2f4/0x5f0 [btrfs]
   btrfs_scrub_dev+0x240/0x600 [btrfs]
   btrfs_ioctl+0x1dc8/0x2fa0 [btrfs]
   ? do_sys_openat2+0xa5/0xf0
   __x64_sys_ioctl+0x97/0xc0
   do_syscall_64+0x4f/0x120
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e
   

[CAUSE]
The reproducer is using a corrupted image where extent tree root is
corrupted, thus forcing to use "rescue=all,ro" mount option to mount the
image.

Then it triggered a scrub, but since scrub relies on extent tree to find
where the data/metadata extents are, scrub_find_fill_first_stripe()
relies on an non-empty extent root.

But unfortunately scrub_find_fill_first_stripe() doesn't really expect
an NULL pointer for extent root, it use extent_root to grab fs_info and
triggered a NULL pointer dereference.

[FIX]
Add an extra check for a valid extent root at the beginning of
scrub_find_fill_first_stripe().

The new error path is introduced by 42437a6386ff ("btrfs: introduce
mount option rescue=ignorebadroots"), but that's pretty old, and later
commit b979547513ff ("btrfs: scrub: introduce helper to find and fill
sector info for a scrub_stripe") changed how we do scrub.

So for kernels older than 6.6, the fix will need manual backport.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21659 | netdev: prevent accessing NAPI instances from another namespace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21659</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netdev: prevent accessing NAPI instances from another namespace

The NAPI IDs were not fully exposed to user space prior to the netlink
API, so they were never namespaced. The netlink API must ensure that
at the very least NAPI instance belongs to the same netns as the owner
of the genl sock.

napi_by_id() can become static now, but it needs to move because of
dev_get_by_napi_id().</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21660 | ksmbd: fix unexpectedly changed path in ksmbd_vfs_kern_path_locked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21660</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix unexpectedly changed path in ksmbd_vfs_kern_path_locked

When `ksmbd_vfs_kern_path_locked` met an error and it is not the last
entry, it will exit without restoring changed path buffer. But later this
buffer may be used as the filename for creation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21661 | gpio: virtuser: fix missing lookup table cleanups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21661</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpio: virtuser: fix missing lookup table cleanups

When a virtuser device is created via configfs and the probe fails due
to an incorrect lookup table, the table is not removed. This prevents
subsequent probe attempts from succeeding, even if the issue is
corrected, unless the device is released. Additionally, cleanup is also
needed in the less likely case of platform_device_register_full()
failure.

Besides, a consistent memory leak in lookup_table-&gt;dev_id was spotted
using kmemleak by toggling the live state between 0 and 1 with a correct
lookup table.

Introduce gpio_virtuser_remove_lookup_table() as the counterpart to the
existing gpio_virtuser_make_lookup_table() and call it from all
necessary points to ensure proper cleanup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21662 | net/mlx5: Fix variable not being completed when function returns</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21662</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5: Fix variable not being completed when function returns

When cmd_alloc_index(), fails cmd_work_handler() needs
to complete ent-&gt;slotted before returning early.
Otherwise the task which issued the command may hang:

   mlx5_core 0000:01:00.0: cmd_work_handler:877:(pid 3880418): failed to allocate command entry
   INFO: task kworker/13:2:4055883 blocked for more than 120 seconds.
         Not tainted 4.19.90-25.44.v2101.ky10.aarch64 #1
   "echo 0 &gt; /proc/sys/kernel/hung_task_timeout_secs" disables this message.
   kworker/13:2    D    0 4055883      2 0x00000228
   Workqueue: events mlx5e_tx_dim_work [mlx5_core]
   Call trace:
      __switch_to+0xe8/0x150
      __schedule+0x2a8/0x9b8
      schedule+0x2c/0x88
      schedule_timeout+0x204/0x478
      wait_for_common+0x154/0x250
      wait_for_completion+0x28/0x38
      cmd_exec+0x7a0/0xa00 [mlx5_core]
      mlx5_cmd_exec+0x54/0x80 [mlx5_core]
      mlx5_core_modify_cq+0x6c/0x80 [mlx5_core]
      mlx5_core_modify_cq_moderation+0xa0/0xb8 [mlx5_core]
      mlx5e_tx_dim_work+0x54/0x68 [mlx5_core]
      process_one_work+0x1b0/0x448
      worker_thread+0x54/0x468
      kthread+0x134/0x138
      ret_from_fork+0x10/0x18</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21663 | net: stmmac: dwmac-tegra: Read iommu stream id from device tree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: stmmac: dwmac-tegra: Read iommu stream id from device tree

Nvidia's Tegra MGBE controllers require the IOMMU "Stream ID" (SID) to be
written to the MGBE_WRAP_AXI_ASID0_CTRL register.

The current driver is hard coded to use MGBE0's SID for all controllers.
This causes softirq time outs and kernel panics when using controllers
other than MGBE0.

Example dmesg errors when an ethernet cable is connected to MGBE1:

[  116.133290] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: Link is Up - 1Gbps/Full - flow control rx/tx
[  121.851283] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: NETDEV WATCHDOG: CPU: 5: transmit queue 0 timed out 5690 ms
[  121.851782] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: Reset adapter.
[  121.892464] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: Register MEM_TYPE_PAGE_POOL RxQ-0
[  121.905920] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: PHY [stmmac-1:00] driver [Aquantia AQR113] (irq=171)
[  121.907356] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: Enabling Safety Features
[  121.907578] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: IEEE 1588-2008 Advanced Timestamp supported
[  121.908399] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: registered PTP clock
[  121.908582] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: configuring for phy/10gbase-r link mode
[  125.961292] tegra-mgbe 6910000.ethernet eth1: Link is Up - 1Gbps/Full - flow control rx/tx
[  181.921198] rcu: INFO: rcu_preempt detected stalls on CPUs/tasks:
[  181.921404] rcu: 	7-....: (1 GPs behind) idle=540c/1/0x4000000000000002 softirq=1748/1749 fqs=2337
[  181.921684] rcu: 	(detected by 4, t=6002 jiffies, g=1357, q=1254 ncpus=8)
[  181.921878] Sending NMI from CPU 4 to CPUs 7:
[  181.921886] NMI backtrace for cpu 7
[  181.922131] CPU: 7 UID: 0 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/7 Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.13.0-rc3+ #6
[  181.922390] Hardware name: NVIDIA CTI Forge + Orin AGX/Jetson, BIOS 202402.1-Unknown 10/28/2024
[  181.922658] pstate: 40400009 (nZcv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[  181.922847] pc : handle_softirqs+0x98/0x368
[  181.922978] lr : __do_softirq+0x18/0x20
[  181.923095] sp : ffff80008003bf50
[  181.923189] x29: ffff80008003bf50 x28: 0000000000000008 x27: 0000000000000000
[  181.923379] x26: ffffce78ea277000 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: 0000001c61befda0
[  181.924486] x23: 0000000060400009 x22: ffffce78e99918bc x21: ffff80008018bd70
[  181.925568] x20: ffffce78e8bb00d8 x19: ffff80008018bc20 x18: 0000000000000000
[  181.926655] x17: ffff318ebe7d3000 x16: ffff800080038000 x15: 0000000000000000
[  181.931455] x14: ffff000080816680 x13: ffff318ebe7d3000 x12: 000000003464d91d
[  181.938628] x11: 0000000000000040 x10: ffff000080165a70 x9 : ffffce78e8bb0160
[  181.945804] x8 : ffff8000827b3160 x7 : f9157b241586f343 x6 : eeb6502a01c81c74
[  181.953068] x5 : a4acfcdd2e8096bb x4 : ffffce78ea277340 x3 : 00000000ffffd1e1
[  181.960329] x2 : 0000000000000101 x1 : ffffce78ea277340 x0 : ffff318ebe7d3000
[  181.967591] Call trace:
[  181.970043]  handle_softirqs+0x98/0x368 (P)
[  181.974240]  __do_softirq+0x18/0x20
[  181.977743]  ____do_softirq+0x14/0x28
[  181.981415]  call_on_irq_stack+0x24/0x30
[  181.985180]  do_softirq_own_stack+0x20/0x30
[  181.989379]  __irq_exit_rcu+0x114/0x140
[  181.993142]  irq_exit_rcu+0x14/0x28
[  181.996816]  el1_interrupt+0x44/0xb8
[  182.000316]  el1h_64_irq_handler+0x14/0x20
[  182.004343]  el1h_64_irq+0x80/0x88
[  182.007755]  cpuidle_enter_state+0xc4/0x4a8 (P)
[  182.012305]  cpuidle_enter+0x3c/0x58
[  182.015980]  cpuidle_idle_call+0x128/0x1c0
[  182.020005]  do_idle+0xe0/0xf0
[  182.023155]  cpu_startup_entry+0x3c/0x48
[  182.026917]  secondary_start_kernel+0xdc/0x120
[  182.031379]  __secondary_switched+0x74/0x78
[  212.971162] rcu: INFO: rcu_preempt detected expedited stalls on CPUs/tasks: { 7-.... } 6103 jiffies s: 417 root: 0x80/.
[  212.985935] rcu: blocking rcu_node structures (internal RCU debug):
[  212.992758] Sending NMI from CPU 0 to CPUs 7:
[  212.998539] NMI backtrace for cpu 7
[  213.004304] CPU: 7 UID: 0 PI
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21664 | dm thin: make get_first_thin use rcu-safe list first function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dm thin: make get_first_thin use rcu-safe list first function

The documentation in rculist.h explains the absence of list_empty_rcu()
and cautions programmers against relying on a list_empty() -&gt;
list_first() sequence in RCU safe code.  This is because each of these
functions performs its own READ_ONCE() of the list head.  This can lead
to a situation where the list_empty() sees a valid list entry, but the
subsequent list_first() sees a different view of list head state after a
modification.

In the case of dm-thin, this author had a production box crash from a GP
fault in the process_deferred_bios path.  This function saw a valid list
head in get_first_thin() but when it subsequently dereferenced that and
turned it into a thin_c, it got the inside of the struct pool, since the
list was now empty and referring to itself.  The kernel on which this
occurred printed both a warning about a refcount_t being saturated, and
a UBSAN error for an out-of-bounds cpuid access in the queued spinlock,
prior to the fault itself.  When the resulting kdump was examined, it
was possible to see another thread patiently waiting in thin_dtr's
synchronize_rcu.

The thin_dtr call managed to pull the thin_c out of the active thins
list (and have it be the last entry in the active_thins list) at just
the wrong moment which lead to this crash.

Fortunately, the fix here is straight forward.  Switch get_first_thin()
function to use list_first_or_null_rcu() which performs just a single
READ_ONCE() and returns NULL if the list is already empty.

This was run against the devicemapper test suite's thin-provisioning
suites for delete and suspend and no regressions were observed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57937 | mm: reinstate ability to map write-sealed memfd mappings read-only</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57937</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: reinstate ability to map write-sealed memfd mappings read-only

Patch series "mm: reinstate ability to map write-sealed memfd mappings
read-only".

In commit 158978945f31 ("mm: perform the mapping_map_writable() check
after call_mmap()") (and preceding changes in the same series) it became
possible to mmap() F_SEAL_WRITE sealed memfd mappings read-only.

Commit 5de195060b2e ("mm: resolve faulty mmap_region() error path
behaviour") unintentionally undid this logic by moving the
mapping_map_writable() check before the shmem_mmap() hook is invoked,
thereby regressing this change.

This series reworks how we both permit write-sealed mappings being mapped
read-only and disallow mprotect() from undoing the write-seal, fixing this
regression.

We also add a regression test to ensure that we do not accidentally
regress this in future.

Thanks to Julian Orth for reporting this regression.


This patch (of 2):

In commit 158978945f31 ("mm: perform the mapping_map_writable() check
after call_mmap()") (and preceding changes in the same series) it became
possible to mmap() F_SEAL_WRITE sealed memfd mappings read-only.

This was previously unnecessarily disallowed, despite the man page
documentation indicating that it would be, thereby limiting the usefulness
of F_SEAL_WRITE logic.

We fixed this by adapting logic that existed for the F_SEAL_FUTURE_WRITE
seal (one which disallows future writes to the memfd) to also be used for
F_SEAL_WRITE.

For background - the F_SEAL_FUTURE_WRITE seal clears VM_MAYWRITE for a
read-only mapping to disallow mprotect() from overriding the seal - an
operation performed by seal_check_write(), invoked from shmem_mmap(), the
f_op-&gt;mmap() hook used by shmem mappings.

By extending this to F_SEAL_WRITE and critically - checking
mapping_map_writable() to determine if we may map the memfd AFTER we
invoke shmem_mmap() - the desired logic becomes possible.  This is because
mapping_map_writable() explicitly checks for VM_MAYWRITE, which we will
have cleared.

Commit 5de195060b2e ("mm: resolve faulty mmap_region() error path
behaviour") unintentionally undid this logic by moving the
mapping_map_writable() check before the shmem_mmap() hook is invoked,
thereby regressing this change.

We reinstate this functionality by moving the check out of shmem_mmap()
and instead performing it in do_mmap() at the point at which VMA flags are
being determined, which seems in any case to be a more appropriate place
in which to make this determination.

In order to achieve this we rework memfd seal logic to allow us access to
this information using existing logic and eliminate the clearing of
VM_MAYWRITE from seal_check_write() which we are performing in do_mmap()
instead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57938 | net/sctp: Prevent autoclose integer overflow in sctp_association_init()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57938</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sctp: Prevent autoclose integer overflow in sctp_association_init()

While by default max_autoclose equals to INT_MAX / HZ, one may set
net.sctp.max_autoclose to UINT_MAX. There is code in
sctp_association_init() that can consequently trigger overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57930 | tracing: Have process_string() also allow arrays</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57930</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tracing: Have process_string() also allow arrays

In order to catch a common bug where a TRACE_EVENT() TP_fast_assign()
assigns an address of an allocated string to the ring buffer and then
references it in TP_printk(), which can be executed hours later when the
string is free, the function test_event_printk() runs on all events as
they are registered to make sure there's no unwanted dereferencing.

It calls process_string() to handle cases in TP_printk() format that has
"%s". It returns whether or not the string is safe. But it can have some
false positives.

For instance, xe_bo_move() has:

 TP_printk("move_lacks_source:%s, migrate object %p [size %zu] from %s to %s device_id:%s",
            __entry-&gt;move_lacks_source ? "yes" : "no", __entry-&gt;bo, __entry-&gt;size,
            xe_mem_type_to_name[__entry-&gt;old_placement],
            xe_mem_type_to_name[__entry-&gt;new_placement], __get_str(device_id))

Where the "%s" references into xe_mem_type_to_name[]. This is an array of
pointers that should be safe for the event to access. Instead of flagging
this as a bad reference, if a reference points to an array, where the
record field is the index, consider it safe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57931 | selinux: ignore unknown extended permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57931</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

selinux: ignore unknown extended permissions

When evaluating extended permissions, ignore unknown permissions instead
of calling BUG(). This commit ensures that future permissions can be
added without interfering with older kernels.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57932 | gve: guard XDP xmit NDO on existence of xdp queues</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57932</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gve: guard XDP xmit NDO on existence of xdp queues

In GVE, dedicated XDP queues only exist when an XDP program is installed
and the interface is up. As such, the NDO XDP XMIT callback should
return early if either of these conditions are false.

In the case of no loaded XDP program, priv-&gt;num_xdp_queues=0 which can
cause a divide-by-zero error, and in the case of interface down,
num_xdp_queues remains untouched to persist XDP queue count for the next
interface up, but the TX pointer itself would be NULL.

The XDP xmit callback also needs to synchronize with a device
transitioning from open to close. This synchronization will happen via
the GVE_PRIV_FLAGS_NAPI_ENABLED bit along with a synchronize_net() call,
which waits for any RCU critical sections at call-time to complete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57933 | gve: guard XSK operations on the existence of queues</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57933</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gve: guard XSK operations on the existence of queues

This patch predicates the enabling and disabling of XSK pools on the
existence of queues. As it stands, if the interface is down, disabling
or enabling XSK pools would result in a crash, as the RX queue pointer
would be NULL. XSK pool registration will occur as part of the next
interface up.

Similarly, xsk_wakeup needs be guarded against queues disappearing
while the function is executing, so a check against the
GVE_PRIV_FLAGS_NAPI_ENABLED flag is added to synchronize with the
disabling of the bit and the synchronize_net() in gve_turndown.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57934 | fgraph: Add READ_ONCE() when accessing fgraph_array[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57934</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fgraph: Add READ_ONCE() when accessing fgraph_array[]

In __ftrace_return_to_handler(), a loop iterates over the fgraph_array[]
elements, which are fgraph_ops. The loop checks if an element is a
fgraph_stub to prevent using a fgraph_stub afterward.

However, if the compiler reloads fgraph_array[] after this check, it might
race with an update to fgraph_array[] that introduces a fgraph_stub. This
could result in the stub being processed, but the stub contains a null
"func_hash" field, leading to a NULL pointer dereference.

To ensure that the gops compared against the fgraph_stub matches the gops
processed later, add a READ_ONCE(). A similar patch appears in commit
63a8dfb ("function_graph: Add READ_ONCE() when accessing fgraph_array[]").</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57935 | RDMA/hns: Fix accessing invalid dip_ctx during destroying QP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57935</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/hns: Fix accessing invalid dip_ctx during destroying QP

If it fails to modify QP to RTR, dip_ctx will not be attached. And
during detroying QP, the invalid dip_ctx pointer will be accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57936 | RDMA/bnxt_re: Fix max SGEs for the Work Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57936</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/bnxt_re: Fix max SGEs for the Work Request

Gen P7 supports up to 13 SGEs for now. WQE software structure
can hold only 6 now. Since the max send sge is reported as
13, the stack can give requests up to 13 SGEs. This is causing
traffic failures and system crashes.

Use the define for max SGE supported for variable size. This
will work for both static and variable WQEs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0615 | Input validation vulnerability in Qualifio&amp;#x27;s Wheel of Fortune</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0615</link><description>Input validation vulnerability in Qualifio's Wheel of Fortune. This vulnerability allows an attacker to modify an email to contain the ‘+’ symbol to access the application and win prizes as many times as wanted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0614 | Input validation vulnerability in Qualifio&amp;#x27;s Wheel of Fortune</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0614</link><description>Input validation vulnerability in Qualifio's Wheel of Fortune. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to modify a single email to contain upper and lower case characters in order to access the application and win prizes as many times as wanted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11226 | FireCask Like &amp;amp; Share Button &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via width Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11226</link><description>The FireCask Like &amp; Share Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'width' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13230 | Social Share, Social Login and Social Comments Plugin – Super Socializer &amp;lt;= 7.14 - Unauthenticated Limited SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;SuperSocializerKey&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13230</link><description>The Social Share, Social Login and Social Comments Plugin – Super Socializer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Limited SQL Injection via the ‘SuperSocializerKey’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.14 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional values into the already existing query that can be used to extract user metadata from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13444 | wp-greet &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13444</link><description>The wp-greet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52973 | Kibana allocation of resources without limits or throttling leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52973</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling in Kibana can lead to a crash caused by a specially crafted request to /api/log_entries/summary. This can be carried out by users with read access to the Observability-Logs feature in Kibana.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0450 | Betheme &amp;lt;= 27.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom JS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0450</link><description>The Betheme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom JS functionality in all versions up to, and including, 27.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37284 | Elastic Defend Improper Handling of Alternate Encoding Leads to Crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37284</link><description>Improper handling of alternate encoding occurs when Elastic Defend on Windows systems attempts to scan a file or process encoded as a multibyte character. This leads to an uncaught exception causing Elastic Defend to crash which in turn will prevent it from quarantining the file and/or killing the process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43709 | Elasticsearch allocation of resources without limits or throttling leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43709</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling in Elasticsearch can lead to an OutOfMemoryError exception resulting in a crash via a specially crafted query using an SQL function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6466 | NEC Corporation's WebSAM DeploymentManager v6.0 to v6.80 allows an attacker to reset configurations or restart products via network with X-F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6466</link><description>NEC Corporation's WebSAM DeploymentManager v6.0 to v6.80 allows an attacker to reset configurations or restart products via network with X-FRAME-OPTIONS is not specified.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23184 | Apache CXF: Denial of Service vulnerability with temporary files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23184</link><description>A potential denial of service vulnerability is present in versions of Apache CXF before 3.5.10, 3.6.5 and 4.0.6. In some edge cases, the CachedOutputStream instances may not be closed and, if backed by temporary files, may fill up the file system (it applies to servers and clients).</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12005 | WP-BibTeX &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored and Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12005</link><description>The WP-BibTeX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wp_bibtex_option_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 09:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12104 | Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp;amp; Project Management – Atarim &amp;lt;= 4.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Project Page/File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12104</link><description>The Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp; Project Management – Atarim plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the wpf_delete_file and wpf_delete_file functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete project pages and files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 09:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13404 | Link Library &amp;lt;= 7.7.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13404</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'searchll' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 09:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10936 | String Locator &amp;lt;= 2.6.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10936</link><description>The String locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'recursive_unserialize_replace' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must perform a search and replace action to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 08:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0371 | Jet Elements &amp;lt;= 2.7.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0371</link><description>The JetElements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 08:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23086 | On most desktop platforms, Brave Browser versions 1.70.x-1.73.x included a feature to show a site's origin on the OS-provided file selector ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23086</link><description>On most desktop platforms, Brave Browser versions 1.70.x-1.73.x included a feature to show a site's origin on the OS-provided file selector dialog when a site prompts the user to upload or download a file. However the origin was not correctly inferred in some cases. When combined with an open redirector vulnerability on a trusted site, this could allow a malicious site to initiate a download whose origin in the file select dialog appears as the trusted site which initiated the redirect.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 04:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13536 | 1003 Mortgage Application &amp;lt;= 1.87 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13536</link><description>The 1003 Mortgage Application plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.87. This is due the /inc/class/fnm/export.php file being publicly accessible with error logging enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 04:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45091 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45091</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.0 through 7.0.5.24, 7.1 through 7.1.2.10, and 7.2 through 7.2.3.13 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user with access to HTTP request logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24014 | segmentation fault in win_line() in Vim &amp;lt; 9.1.1043</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24014</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. A segmentation fault was found in Vim before 9.1.1043. In silent Ex mode (-s -e), Vim typically doesn't show a screen and just operates silently in batch mode. However, it is still possible to trigger the function that handles the scrolling of a gui version of Vim by feeding some binary characters to Vim. The function that handles the scrolling however may be triggering a redraw, which will access the ScreenLines pointer, even so this variable hasn't been allocated (since there is no screen). This vulnerability is fixed in 9.1.1043.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13454 | Weak encryption algorithm in Easy-RSA version 3.0.5 through 3.1.7 allows a local attacker to more easily bruteforce the private CA key when ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13454</link><description>Weak encryption algorithm in Easy-RSA version 3.0.5 through 3.1.7 allows a local attacker to more easily bruteforce the private CA key when created using OpenSSL 3</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 21:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23214 | Cosmos userbase checking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23214</link><description>Cosmos provides users the ability self-host a home server by acting as a secure gateway to your application, as well as a server manager. By monitoring the error code returned in the login, it is possible to figure out whether a user exist or not in the database. Patched in 0.17.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 18:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22347 | IBM UrbanCode Velocity information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22347</link><description>IBM DevOps Velocity 5.0.0 and IBM UrbanCode Velocity 4.0.0 through 4.0. 25 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22348 | IBM UrbanCode Velocity cross-origin resource sharing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22348</link><description>IBM DevOps Velocity 5.0.0 and IBM UrbanCode Velocity 4.0.0 through 4.0. 25 uses Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) which could allow an attacker to carry out privileged actions and retrieve sensitive information as the domain name is not being limited to only trusted domains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22349 | IBM UrbanCode Velocity information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22349</link><description>IBM DevOps Velocity 5.0.0 and IBM UrbanCode Velocity 4.0.0 through 4.0. 25 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23221 | Fedify has an Infinite loop and Blind SSRF found inside the Webfinger mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23221</link><description>Fedify is a TypeScript library for building federated server apps powered by ActivityPub and other standards. This vulnerability allows a user to maneuver the Webfinger mechanism to perform a GET request to any internal resource on any Host, Port, URL combination regardless of present security mechanisms, and forcing the victim’s server into an infinite loop causing Denial of Service. Moreover, this issue can also be maneuvered into performing a Blind SSRF attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.14, 1.1.11, 1.2.11, and 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24013 | CodeIgniter validation of header name and value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24013</link><description>CodeIgniter is a PHP full-stack web framework. Prior to 4.5.8, CodeIgniter lacked proper header validation for its name and value. The potential attacker can construct deliberately malformed headers with Header class. This could disrupt application functionality, potentially causing errors or generating invalid HTTP requests. In some cases, these malformed requests might lead to a DoS scenario if a remote service’s web application firewall interprets them as malicious and blocks further communication with the application. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.5.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23220 | WeGIA has a SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;adicionar_raca.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;raca&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23220</link><description>WeGIA is an open source web manager with a focus on the Portuguese language and charitable institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the WeGIA application, specifically in the adicionar_raca.php endpoint. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands in the database, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive information. During the exploit, it was possible to perform a complete dump of the application's database, highlighting the severity of the flaw. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24010 | Vite allows any websites to send any requests to the development server and read the response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24010</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for javascript. Vite allowed any websites to send any requests to the development server and read the response due to default CORS settings and lack of validation on the Origin header for WebSocket connections. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.0.9, 5.4.12, and 4.5.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23044 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) allows creating admin account with POST request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23044</link><description>PwnDoc is a penetration test report generator. There is no CSRF protection in pwndoc, allowing attackers to send requests on a logged-in user's behalf. This includes GET and POST requests due to the missing SameSite= attribute on cookies and the ability to refresh cookies. Commit 14acb704891245bf1703ce6296d62112e85aa995 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23218 | WeGIA has a SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;adicionar_especie.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;especie&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23218</link><description>WeGIA is an open source web manager with a focus on the Portuguese language and charitable institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the WeGIA application, specifically in the adicionar_especie.php endpoint. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands in the database, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive information. During the exploit, it was possible to perform a complete dump of the application's database, highlighting the severity of the flaw. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23219 | WeGIA has a SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;adicionar_cor.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;cor&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23219</link><description>WeGIA is an open source web manager with a focus on the Portuguese language and charitable institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the WeGIA application, specifically in the adicionar_cor.php endpoint. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands in the database, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive information. During the exploit, it was possible to perform a complete dump of the application's database, highlighting the severity of the flaw. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22620 | gix-worktree-state nonexclusive checkout sets executable files world-writable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22620</link><description>gitoxide is an implementation of git written in Rust. Prior to 0.17.0, gix-worktree-state specifies 0777 permissions when checking out executable files, intending that the umask will restrict them appropriately. But one of the strategies it uses to set permissions is not subject to the umask. This causes files in a repository to be world-writable in some situations. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.17.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22131 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in generateNavigation() function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22131</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the code which translates the XLSX file into a HTML representation and displays it in the response.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51738 | Sunshine improperly enforces pairing protocol request order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51738</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. In 0.23.1 and earlier, Sunshine's pairing protocol implementation does not validate request order and is thereby vulnerable to a MITM attack, potentially allowing an unauthenticated attacker to pair a client by hijacking a legitimate pairing attempt. This bug may also be used by a remote attacker to crash Sunshine. This vulnerability is fixed in 2025.118.151840.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45647 | IBM Security Verify Access unverified password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45647</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow could an unverified user to change the password of an expired user without prior knowledge of that password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21655 | io_uring/eventfd: ensure io_eventfd_signal() defers another RCU period</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21655</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/eventfd: ensure io_eventfd_signal() defers another RCU period

io_eventfd_do_signal() is invoked from an RCU callback, but when
dropping the reference to the io_ev_fd, it calls io_eventfd_free()
directly if the refcount drops to zero. This isn't correct, as any
potential freeing of the io_ev_fd should be deferred another RCU grace
period.

Just call io_eventfd_put() rather than open-code the dec-and-test and
free, which will correctly defer it another RCU grace period.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 13:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24337 | WriteFreely through 0.15.1, when MySQL is used, allows local users to discover credentials by reading config.ini.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24337</link><description>WriteFreely through 0.15.1, when MySQL is used, allows local users to discover credentials by reading config.ini.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 13:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13176 | Timing side-channel in ECDSA signature computation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13176</link><description>Issue summary: A timing side-channel which could potentially allow recovering
the private key exists in the ECDSA signature computation.

Impact summary: A timing side-channel in ECDSA signature computations
could allow recovering the private key by an attacker. However, measuring
the timing would require either local access to the signing application or
a very fast network connection with low latency.

There is a timing signal of around 300 nanoseconds when the top word of
the inverted ECDSA nonce value is zero. This can happen with significant
probability only for some of the supported elliptic curves. In particular
the NIST P-521 curve is affected. To be able to measure this leak, the attacker
process must either be located in the same physical computer or must
have a very fast network connection with low latency. For that reason
the severity of this vulnerability is Low.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 13:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0479 | Security Misconfiguration Vulnerability in CP Plus Router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0479</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CP Plus Router due to insecure handling of cookie flags used within its web interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting data transmissions during an HTTP session on the vulnerable system.
 
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information and compromise the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 11:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52923 | netfilter: nf_tables: adapt set backend to use GC transaction API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52923</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: adapt set backend to use GC transaction API

Use the GC transaction API to replace the old and buggy gc API and the
busy mark approach.

No set elements are removed from async garbage collection anymore,
instead the _DEAD bit is set on so the set element is not visible from
lookup path anymore. Async GC enqueues transaction work that might be
aborted and retried later.

rbtree and pipapo set backends does not set on the _DEAD bit from the
sync GC path since this runs in control plane path where mutex is held.
In this case, set elements are deactivated, removed and then released
via RCU callback, sync GC never fails.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0581 | CampCodes School Management Software Chat History send cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0581</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /chat/group/send of the component Chat History. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0582 | itsourcecode Farm Management System add-pig.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0582</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Farm Management System up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add-pig.php. The manipulation of the argument pigphoto leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0579 | Shiprocket Module REST API Module restapi sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shiprocket Module 3/4 on OpenCart. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php?route=extension/shiprocket/module/restapi of the component REST API Module. The manipulation of the argument x-username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0580 | Shiprocket Module REST API Module rest_api authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shiprocket Module 3 on OpenCart. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?route=extension/module/rest_api&amp;amp;action=getOrders of the component REST API Module. The manipulation of the argument contentHash leads to incorrect authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0586 | aEnrich Technology a+HRD - Insecure Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0586</link><description>The a+HRD from aEnrich Technology has an Insecure Deserialization vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with database modification privileges and regular system privileges to perform arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13524 | obsproject OBS Studio untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13524</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in obsproject OBS Studio up to 30.0.2 on Windows and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The vendor disagrees that this issue is "something worth reporting, as every attack surface requires privileged access/user compromise".</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0584 | aEnrich Technology a+HRD - Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0584</link><description>The a+HRD from aEnrich Technology has a Server-side Request Forgery, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to probe internal network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0585 | aEnrich Technology a+HRD - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0585</link><description>The a+HRD from aEnrich Technology has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0583 | aEnrich Technology a+HRD - Reflected Cross-site Scripting(XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0583</link><description>The a+HRD from aEnrich Technology has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0578 | Facile Sistemas Cloud Apps Password Reset forgotpassword cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0578</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Facile Sistemas Cloud Apps up to 20250107. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /account/forgotpassword of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation of the argument reterros leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>