<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-24396 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24396</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the search bar component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6874 | Zigbee Unauthenticated DoS via NWK Sequence number manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6874</link><description>Prior to v7.4.0, Ember ZNet is vulnerable to a denial of service attack through manipulation of the NWK sequence number</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24258 | mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddSubMenu function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24258</link><description>mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddSubMenu function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24259 | mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddMenuEntry function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24259</link><description>mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddMenuEntry function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24260 | media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_subscribe_remove function at /uac/sip-uac-sub...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24260</link><description>media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_subscribe_remove function at /uac/sip-uac-subscribe.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24262 | media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_uac_stop_timer function at /uac/sip-uac-trans...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24262</link><description>media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_uac_stop_timer function at /uac/sip-uac-transaction.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24263 | Lotos WebServer v0.1.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the response_append_status_line function at /lotos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24263</link><description>Lotos WebServer v0.1.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the response_append_status_line function at /lotos/src/response.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24265 | gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the dst_props variable in the gf_filter_pid_merge_properties_internal function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24265</link><description>gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the dst_props variable in the gf_filter_pid_merge_properties_internal function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24266 | gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the dasher_configure_pid function at /src/filters/dasher.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24266</link><description>gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the dasher_configure_pid function at /src/filters/dasher.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24267 | gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the gfio_blob variable in the gf_fileio_from_blob function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24267</link><description>gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the gfio_blob variable in the gf_fileio_from_blob function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6028 | SDM Web interface vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6028</link><description>A reflected
cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SVG version of System
Diagnostics Manager of B&amp;R Automation Runtime versions &lt;= G4.93 that
enables a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context
of the attacked user’s browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0953 | QR Code Scanner does not prompt before navigating user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0953</link><description>When a user scans a QR Code with the QR Code Scanner feature, the user is not prompted before being navigated to the page specified in the code.  This may surprise the user and potentially direct them to unwanted content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47355 | The com.eypcnnapps.quickreboot (aka Eyuep Can Yilmaz {ROOT] Quick Reboot) application 1.0.8 for Android has exposed broadcast receivers for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47355</link><description>The com.eypcnnapps.quickreboot (aka Eyuep Can Yilmaz {ROOT] Quick Reboot) application 1.0.8 for Android has exposed broadcast receivers for PowerOff, Reboot, and Recovery (e.g., com.eypcnnapps.quickreboot.widget.PowerOff) that are susceptible to unauthorized broadcasts because of missing input validation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0323 | FTP uses unsecure encryption mechanisms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0323</link><description>Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Runtime (SDM modules).



The FTP server used on the B&amp;R
Automation Runtime supports unsecure encryption mechanisms, such as SSLv3,
TLSv1.0 and TLS1.1. An network-based attacker can exploit the flaws to conduct
man-in-the-middle attacks or to decrypt communications between the affected product
clients.  

This issue affects Automation Runtime: from 14.0 before 14.93.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23054 | An issue in Plone Docker Official Image 5.2.13 (5221) open-source software that could allow for remote code execution due to a package liste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23054</link><description>An issue in Plone Docker Official Image 5.2.13 (5221) open-source software that could allow for remote code execution due to a package listed in ++plone++static/components not existing in the public package index (npm).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24397 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24397</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the ReportName field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24469 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the delete_post .php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24469</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the delete_post .php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24468 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_customblock.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24468</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_customblock.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7216 | Cpio: extraction allows symlinks which enables remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7216</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in the CPIO utility. This issue could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to trick a user into opening a specially crafted archive. During the extraction process, the archiver could follow symlinks outside of the intended directory, which could be utilized to run arbitrary commands on the target system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24768 | 1Panel set-cookie is missing the Secure keyword</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24768</link><description>1Panel is an open source Linux server operation and maintenance management panel. The HTTPS cookie that comes with the panel does not have the Secure keyword, which may cause the cookie to be sent in plain text if accessed using HTTP. This issue has been patched in version 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52138 | Path traversal via crafted cpio archives in Engrampa archivers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52138</link><description>Engrampa is an archive manager for the MATE environment. Engrampa is found to be vulnerable to a Path Traversal vulnerability that can be leveraged to achieve full Remote Command Execution (RCE) on the target. While handling CPIO archives, the Engrampa Archive manager follows symlink, cpio by default will follow stored symlinks while extracting and the Archiver will not check the symlink location, which leads to arbitrary file writes to unintended locations. When the victim extracts the archive, the attacker can craft a malicious cpio or ISO archive to achieve RCE on the target system. This vulnerability was fixed in commit 63d5dfa.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24762 | FastAPI vulnerable to content-type header Regular expression Denial of Service (ReDoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24762</link><description>FastAPI is a web framework for building APIs with Python 3.8+ based on standard Python type hints. When using form data, `python-multipart` uses a Regular Expression to parse the HTTP `Content-Type` header, including options. An attacker could send a custom-made `Content-Type` option that is very difficult for the RegEx to process, consuming CPU resources and stalling indefinitely (minutes or more) while holding the main event loop. This means that process can't handle any more requests. It's a ReDoS(Regular expression Denial of Service), it only applies to those reading form data, using `python-multipart`. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.109.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 14:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23108 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23108</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7.1.1 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.2 and 6.7.0 through 6.7.8 and 6.6.0 through 6.6.3 and 6.5.0 through 6.5.2 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via via crafted API requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23109 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23109</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7.1.1 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.2 and 6.7.0 through 6.7.8 and 6.6.0 through 6.6.3 and 6.5.0 through 6.5.2 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via via crafted API requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1225 | QiboSoft QiboCMS X1 Pay.php rmb_pay deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1225</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in QiboSoft QiboCMS X1 up to 1.0.6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function rmb_pay of the file /application/index/controller/Pay.php. The manipulation of the argument callback_class leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252847. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5249 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5249</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper memory processing operations to exploit a software race condition. If the system’s memory is carefully prepared by the user, then this in turn cause a use-after-free.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r35p0 through r40p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r35p0 through r40p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5643 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5643</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations. Depending on the configuration of the Mali GPU Kernel Driver, and if the system’s memory is carefully prepared by the user, then this in turn could write to memory outside of buffer bounds.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r45p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r45p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r45p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 09:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4436 | 3DPrint Lite &amp;lt; 1.9.1.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4436</link><description>The 3DPrint Lite WordPress plugin before 1.9.1.5 does not have any authorisation and does not check the uploaded file in its p3dlite_handle_upload AJAX action , allowing unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary file to the web server. However, there is a .htaccess, preventing the file to be accessed on Web servers such as Apache.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22667 | Vim before 9.0.2142 has a stack-based buffer overflow because did_set_langmap in map.c calls sprintf to write to the error buffer that is pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22667</link><description>Vim before 9.0.2142 has a stack-based buffer overflow because did_set_langmap in map.c calls sprintf to write to the error buffer that is passed down to the option callback functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24864 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel media/dvb-core in dvbdmx_write()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24864</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's media/dvb-core in dvbdmx_write() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24857 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel bluetooth in conn_info_{min,max}_age_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24857</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's net/bluetooth device driver in conn_info_{min,max}_age_set() function. This can result in integrity overflow issue, possibly leading to bluetooth connection abnormality or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24858 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel net/bluetooth in {conn,adv}_{min,max}_interval_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24858</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's net/bluetooth in {conn,adv}_{min,max}_interval_set() function. This can result in I2cap connection or broadcast abnormality issue, possibly leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24855 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel scsi device driver lpfc_unregister_fcf_rescan()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24855</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's scsi device driver in lpfc_unregister_fcf_rescan() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24859 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel bluetooth sniff_{min,max}_interval_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24859</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's net/bluetooth in sniff_{min,max}_interval_set() function. This can result in a bluetooth sniffing exception issue, possibly leading denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24860 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel bluetooth driver in {min,max}_key_size_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24860</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's bluetooth device driver in {min,max}_key_size_set() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24861 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel media/xc4000 xc4000_get_frequency()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24861</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's media/xc4000 device driver in xc4000 xc4000_get_frequency() function. This can result in return value overflow issue, possibly leading to malfunction or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22386 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel drm/exynos exynos_drm_crtc_atomic_disable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22386</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's drm/exynos device driver in exynos_drm_crtc_atomic_disable() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23196 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel sound/hda snd_hdac_regmap_sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23196</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's sound/hda  device driver in snd_hdac_regmap_sync() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7077 | Sharp NEC Displays (P403, P463, P553, P703, P801, X554UN, X464UN, X554UNS, X464UNV, X474HB, X464UNS, X554UNV, X555UNS, X555UNV, X754HB, X554...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7077</link><description>Sharp NEC Displays (P403, P463, P553, P703, P801, X554UN, X464UN, X554UNS, X464UNV, X474HB, X464UNS, X554UNV, X555UNS, X555UNV, X754HB, X554HB, E705, E805, E905, UN551S, UN551VS, X551UHD, X651UHD, X841UHD, X981UHD, MD551C8) allows an attacker execute remote code by sending unintended parameters in http request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24838 | WordPress Five Star Restaurant Reviews Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24838</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Five Star Plugins Five Star Restaurant Reviews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Five Star Restaurant Reviews: from n/a through 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24839 | WordPress Structured Content Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24839</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gordon Böhme, Antonio Leutsch Structured Content (JSON-LD) #wpsc allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Structured Content (JSON-LD) #wpsc: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24841 | WordPress Add Customer for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24841</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dan's Art Add Customer for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Add Customer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24846 | WordPress Mighty Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24846</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MightyThemes Mighty Addons for Elementor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mighty Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24847 | WordPress CalculatorPro Calculators Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24847</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jgadbois CalculatorPro Calculators allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CalculatorPro Calculators: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24848 | WordPress PT Sign Ups Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24848</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MJS Software PT Sign Ups – Beautiful volunteer sign ups and management made easy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PT Sign Ups – Beautiful volunteer sign ups and management made easy: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24865 | WordPress Scroll Triggered Box Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24865</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Noah Kagan Scroll Triggered Box allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Scroll Triggered Box: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24866 | WordPress Biteship Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.24 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24866</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Biteship Biteship: Plugin Ongkos Kirim Kurir Instant, Reguler, Kargo allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Biteship: Plugin Ongkos Kirim Kurir Instant, Reguler, Kargo: from n/a through 2.2.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20001 | In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20001</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961601; Issue ID: DTV03961601.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20002 | In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20002</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961715; Issue ID: DTV03961715.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20003 | In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20003</link><description>In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent invalid NR RRC Connection Setup message, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01191612; Issue ID: MOLY01191612 (MSV-981).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20004 | In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20004</link><description>In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent invalid NR RRC Connection Setup message, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01191612; Issue ID: MOLY01195812 (MSV-985).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20006 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20006</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08477148; Issue ID: ALPS08477148.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20007 | In mp3 decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20007</link><description>In mp3 decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441369; Issue ID: ALPS08441369.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20009 | In alac decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20009</link><description>In alac decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441150; Issue ID: ALPS08441150.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20010 | In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20010</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08358560; Issue ID: ALPS08358560.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20011 | In alac decoder, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20011</link><description>In alac decoder, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441146; Issue ID: ALPS08441146.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20012 | In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20012</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08358566; Issue ID: ALPS08358566.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20013 | In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20013</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08471742; Issue ID: ALPS08308608.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20015 | In telephony, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20015</link><description>In telephony, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441419; Issue ID: ALPS08441419.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20016 | In ged, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20016</link><description>In ged, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation Patch ID: ALPS07835901; Issue ID: ALPS07835901.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24870 | WordPress Advanced iFrame Plugin &amp;lt;= 2023.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24870</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Dempfle Advanced iFrame allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced iFrame: from n/a through 2023.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51504 | WordPress Dan&amp;#x27;s Embedder for Google Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51504</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dan Dulaney Dan's Embedder for Google Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Dan's Embedder for Google Calendar: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5677 | Insufficient input validation in VAPIX API tcptext.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5677</link><description>Brandon
Rothel from QED Secure Solutions has found that the VAPIX API tcptest.cgi
did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible remote code
execution. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an
operator- or administrator-privileged service account. The impact of exploiting
this vulnerability is lower with operator-privileges compared to
administrator-privileges service accounts. Axis has released patched AXIS OS
versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory
for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5800 | Insufficient input validation in VAPIX API create_overlay.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5800</link><description>Vintage,
member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API create_overlay.cgi
did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible remote code
execution. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an
operator- or administrator-privileged service account. Axis has released patched AXIS OS
versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory
for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25089 | Malwarebytes Binisoft Windows Firewall Control before 6.9.9.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via gRPC named pipes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25089</link><description>Malwarebytes Binisoft Windows Firewall Control before 6.9.9.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via gRPC named pipes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 21:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46902 | An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. Path...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46902</link><description>An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. Path validation is mishandled, and thus an admin can read or delete files in violation of expected access controls.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 20:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46903 | An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46903</link><description>An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. An admin can delete required user accounts (in violation of expected access control).</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52425 | libexpat through 2.5.0 allows a denial of service (resource consumption) because many full reparsings are required in the case of a large to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52425</link><description>libexpat through 2.5.0 allows a denial of service (resource consumption) because many full reparsings are required in the case of a large token for which multiple buffer fills are needed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52426 | libexpat through 2.5.0 allows recursive XML Entity Expansion if XML_DTD is undefined at compile time.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52426</link><description>libexpat through 2.5.0 allows recursive XML Entity Expansion if XML_DTD is undefined at compile time.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4435 | Yarn: untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4435</link><description>An untrusted search path vulnerability was found in Yarn. When a victim runs certain Yarn commands in a directory with attacker-controlled content, malicious commands could be executed in unexpected ways.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36773 | Artifex Ghostscript before 9.53.0 has an out-of-bounds write and use-after-free in devices/vector/gdevtxtw.c (for txtwrite) because a single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36773</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 9.53.0 has an out-of-bounds write and use-after-free in devices/vector/gdevtxtw.c (for txtwrite) because a single character code in a PDF document can map to more than one Unicode code point (e.g., for a ligature).</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25098 | blockmason credit-protocol UCAC CreditProtocol.sol executeUcacTx denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25098</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in blockmason credit-protocol. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function executeUcacTx of the file contracts/CreditProtocol.sol of the component UCAC Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 082e01f18707ef995e80ebe97fcedb229a55efc5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252799. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25062 | An issue was discovered in libxml2 before 2.11.7 and 2.12.x before 2.12.5. When using the XML Reader interface with DTD validation and XIncl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25062</link><description>An issue was discovered in libxml2 before 2.11.7 and 2.12.x before 2.12.5. When using the XML Reader interface with DTD validation and XInclude expansion enabled, processing crafted XML documents can lead to an xmlValidatePopElement use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6240 | Kernel: marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage in the rsa decryption operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6240</link><description>A Marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage was found in the RSA decryption operation in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a network attacker to decrypt ciphertexts or forge signatures, limiting the services that use that private key.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 14:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25159 | mpedraza2020 Intranet del Monterroso cargos.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25159</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mpedraza2020 Intranet del Monterroso up to 4.50.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file config/cargos.php. The manipulation of the argument dni_profe leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 4.51.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 678190bee1dfd64b54a2b0e88abfd009e78adce8. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-252717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10129 | planet-freo auth.inc.php comparison</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in planet-freo up to 20150116 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/inc/auth.inc.php. The manipulation of the argument auth leads to incorrect comparison. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 6ad38c58a45642eb8c7844e2f272ef199f59550d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252716.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 04:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33851 | IBM PowerVM Hypervisor information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33851</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW950.00 through FW950.90, FW1020.00 through FW1020.40, and FW1030.00 through FW1030.30 could reveal sensitive partition data to a system administrator.  IBM X-Force ID:  257135.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50947 | IBM Business Automation Workflow cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50947</link><description>IBM Business Automation Workflow 22.0.2, 23.0.1, and 23.0.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  275665.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1215 | SourceCodester CRUD without Page Reload fetch_data.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1215</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester CRUD without Page Reload 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file fetch_data.php. The manipulation of the argument username/city leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252782 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0853 | OCSP verification bypass with TLS session reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0853</link><description>curl inadvertently kept the SSL session ID for connections in its cache even when the verify status (*OCSP stapling*) test failed. A subsequent transfer to
the same hostname could then succeed if the session ID cache was still fresh, which then skipped the verify status check.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 13:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1064 | Improper Neutralization of HTTP Headers for Scripting Syntax in Crafty Controller 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1064</link><description>A host header injection vulnerability in the HTTP handler component of Crafty Controller allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trigger a Denial of Service (DoS) condition via a modified host header</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 09:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49950 | The Jinja templating in Logpoint SIEM 6.10.0 through 7.x before 7.3.0 does not correctly sanitize log data being displayed when using a cust...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49950</link><description>The Jinja templating in Logpoint SIEM 6.10.0 through 7.x before 7.3.0 does not correctly sanitize log data being displayed when using a custom Jinja template in the Alert view. A remote attacker can craft a cross-site scripting (XSS) payload and send it to any system or device that sends logs to the SIEM. If an alert is created, the payload will execute upon the alert data being viewed with that template, which can lead to sensitive data disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43183 | Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows read-only users to arbitrarily change t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43183</link><description>Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows read-only users to arbitrarily change the password of an admin and hijack their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44031 | Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily save sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44031</link><description>Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily save sensitive files in insecure locations via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0895 | The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via outline settings in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0895</link><description>The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via outline settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied data. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0909 | The Anonymous Restricted Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0909</link><description>The Anonymous Restricted Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to insufficient restrictions through the REST API on the posts/pages that protections are being place on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access protected content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23550 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch (UCD) may be vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23550</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch (UCD) could disclose sensitive user information when installing the Windows agent.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37528 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37528</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attack to exploit an application parameter during execution of the Save Report.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1200 | Jspxcms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1200</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /template/1/default/. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31004 | IBM Security Access Manager Container gain access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31004</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote attacker to gain access to the underlying system using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  254765.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31006 | IBM Security Access Manager Container denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31006</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to a denial of service attacks on the DSC server.  IBM X-Force ID:  254776.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32327 | IBM Security Access Manager Container XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32327</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  254783.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32329 | IBM Security Access Manager Container improper file validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32329</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a user to download files from an incorrect repository due to improper file validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  254972.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43016 | IBM Security Access Manager Container unauthorized access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43016</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote user to log into the server due to a user account with an empty password.  IBM X-Force ID:  266154.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30999 | IBM Security Access Manager denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30999</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service due to uncontrolled resource consumption.  IBM X-Force ID:  254651.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31005 | IBM Security Access Manager Container privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31005</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to an improper security configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  254767.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1199 | CodeAstro Employee Task Management System attendance-info.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1199</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file \employee-tasks-php\attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument aten_id leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252697 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>