<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-5807 | SQLi in TRtek Software&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5807</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TRtek Software Education Portal allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Education Portal: before 3.2023.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44376 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44376</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'add2' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44377 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44377</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'add3' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5570 | User Enumeration in Inohom&amp;#x27;s Home Manager Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5570</link><description>Improper Protection for Outbound Error Messages and Alert Signals vulnerability in Inohom Home Manager Gateway allows Account Footprinting.This issue affects Home Manager Gateway: before v.1.27.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5705 | The VK Filter Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vk_filter_search' shortcode in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5705</link><description>The VK Filter Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vk_filter_search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5820 | The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5820</link><description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the addedit functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5821 | The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing nonce ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5821</link><description>The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the deleteselected function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete sliders in bulk via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5774 | The Animated Counters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5774</link><description>The Animated Counters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5817 | The Neon text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's neontext_box shortcode in all versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5817</link><description>The Neon text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's neontext_box shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes (color). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46199 | WordPress Triberr Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46199</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Triberr plugin &lt;= 4.1.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44220 | SonicWall NetExtender Windows (32-bit and 64-bit) client 10.2.336 and earlier versions have a DLL Search Order Hijacking vulnerability in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44220</link><description>SonicWall NetExtender Windows (32-bit and 64-bit) client 10.2.336 and earlier versions have a DLL Search Order Hijacking vulnerability in the start-up DLL component. Successful exploitation via a local attacker could result in command execution in the target system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46192 | WordPress Internal Link Building Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46192</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Internet Marketing Ninjas Internal Link Building plugin &lt;= 1.2.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46194 | WordPress Archivist – Custom Archive Templates Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46194</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Eric Teubert Archivist – Custom Archive Templates plugin &lt;= 1.7.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46093 | WordPress Webmaster Tools Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46093</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LionScripts.Com Webmaster Tools plugin &lt;= 2.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46153 | WordPress User Feedback Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46153</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in UserFeedback Team User Feedback plugin &lt;= 1.0.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44219 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability in SonicWall Directory Services Connector Windows MSI client 4.1.21 and earlier versions allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44219</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability in SonicWall Directory Services Connector Windows MSI client 4.1.21 and earlier versions allows a local low-privileged user to gain system privileges through running the recovery feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46091 | WordPress Category SEO Meta Tags Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46091</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bala Krishna, Sergey Yakovlev Category SEO Meta Tags plugin &lt;= 2.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34059 | open-vm-tools contains a file descriptor hijack vulnerability in the vmware-user-suid-wrapper. A malicious actor with non-root privileges ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34059</link><description>open-vm-tools contains a file descriptor hijack vulnerability in the vmware-user-suid-wrapper. A malicious actor with non-root privileges may be able to hijack the 
/dev/uinput file descriptor allowing them to simulate user inputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34057 | VMware Tools contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with local user access to a guest virtual machine may el...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34057</link><description>VMware Tools contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with local user access to a guest virtual machine may elevate privileges within the virtual machine.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34058 | VMware Tools contains a SAML token signature bypass vulnerability. A malicious actor that has been granted  Guest Operation Privileges https...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34058</link><description>VMware Tools contains a SAML token signature bypass vulnerability. A malicious actor that has been granted  Guest Operation Privileges https://docs.vmware.com/en/VMware-vSphere/8.0/vsphere-security/GUID-6A952214-0E5E-4CCF-9D2A-90948FF643EC.html  in a target virtual machine may be able to elevate their privileges if that target virtual machine has been assigned a more privileged  Guest Alias https://vdc-download.vmware.com/vmwb-repository/dcr-public/d1902b0e-d479-46bf-8ac9-cee0e31e8ec0/07ce8dbd-db48-4261-9b8f-c6d3ad8ba472/vim.vm.guest.AliasManager.html .</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46815 | An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. An Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability has been identified in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46815</link><description>An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. An Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability has been identified in the Notes module. By using a crafted request, custom PHP code can be injected via the Notes module because of missing input validation. An attacker with regular user privileges can exploit this.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46816 | An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. A Server Site Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability has been id...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46816</link><description>An issue was discovered in SugarCRM 12 before 12.0.4 and 13 before 13.0.2. A Server Site Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability has been identified in the GecControl action. By using a crafted request, custom PHP code can be injected via the GetControl action because of missing input validation. An attacker with regular user privileges can exploit this.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46818 | An issue was discovered in ISPConfig before 3.2.11p1. PHP code injection can be achieved in the language file editor by an admin if admin_al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46818</link><description>An issue was discovered in ISPConfig before 3.2.11p1. PHP code injection can be achieved in the language file editor by an admin if admin_allow_langedit is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5051 | The CallRail Phone Call Tracking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'callrail_form' shortcode in vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5051</link><description>The CallRail Phone Call Tracking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'callrail_form' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 0.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'form_id' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46503 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the reader manag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46503</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the reader management and book input modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46504 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46504</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PwnCYN YXBOOKCMS v.1.0.2 allows a physically proximate attacker to execute arbitrary code via the library name function in the general settings component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45498 | VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45498</link><description>VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45499 | VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45499</link><description>VinChin Backup &amp; Recovery v5.0.*, v6.0.*, v6.7.*, and v7.0.* was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46813 | An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel before 6.5.9, exploitable by local users with userspace access to MMIO registers. Incorrect acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46813</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel before 6.5.9, exploitable by local users with userspace access to MMIO registers. Incorrect access checking in the #VC handler and instruction emulation of the SEV-ES emulation of MMIO accesses could lead to arbitrary write access to kernel memory (and thus privilege escalation). This depends on a race condition through which userspace can replace an instruction before the #VC handler reads it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44375 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44375</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'add1' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44162 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44162</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'contact' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43738 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43738</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'email' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5814 | SourceCodester Task Reminder System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5814</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Reminder System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_reminder. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-243645 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5812 | flusity CMS upload.php handleFileUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5812</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in flusity CMS and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function handleFileUpload of the file core/tools/upload.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243643.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5813 | SourceCodester Task Reminder System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5813</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Reminder System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_reminder. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243644.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46376 | Zentao Biz version 8.7 and before is vulnerable to Information Disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46376</link><description>Zentao Biz version 8.7 and before is vulnerable to Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46375 | ZenTao Biz version 4.1.3 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46375</link><description>ZenTao Biz version 4.1.3 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5810 | flusity CMS posts.php loadPostAddForm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5810</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in flusity CMS. This issue affects the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_post_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-243641 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5811 | flusity CMS posts.php loadPostAddForm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5811</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in flusity CMS. Affected is the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument menu_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-243642 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46505 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in FanCMS v.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the content1 parameter in the demo.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46505</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in FanCMS v.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the content1 parameter in the demo.php file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46491 | ZenTao Biz version 4.1.3 and before has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Version Library.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46491</link><description>ZenTao Biz version 4.1.3 and before has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Version Library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46374 | ZenTao Enterprise Edition version 4.1.3 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46374</link><description>ZenTao Enterprise Edition version 4.1.3 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42188 | IceCMS v2.0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42188</link><description>IceCMS v2.0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27170 | Xpand IT Write-back manager v2.3.1 allows attackers to perform a directory traversal via modification of the siteName parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27170</link><description>Xpand IT Write-back manager v2.3.1 allows attackers to perform a directory traversal via modification of the siteName parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 22:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43737 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43737</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'fnm' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 22:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44268 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44268</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'gender' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 22:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42406 | SQL injection vulnerability in D-Link Online behavior audit gateway DAR-7000 V31R02B1413C allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42406</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in D-Link Online behavior audit gateway DAR-7000 V31R02B1413C allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the editrole.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43352 | An issue in CMSmadesimple v.2.2.18 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Content Manager Menu compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43352</link><description>An issue in CMSmadesimple v.2.2.18 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Content Manager Menu component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38328 | An issue was discovered in eGroupWare 17.1.20190111. An Improper Password Storage vulnerability affects the setup panel of under setup/manag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38328</link><description>An issue was discovered in eGroupWare 17.1.20190111. An Improper Password Storage vulnerability affects the setup panel of under setup/manageheader.php, which allows authenticated remote attackers with administrator credentials to read a cleartext database password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-17878 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in certain ABUS TVIP cameras allows attackers to gain control of the program via crafted string sent to sprint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17878</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in certain ABUS TVIP cameras allows attackers to gain control of the program via crafted string sent to sprintf() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-17879 | An issue was discovered on certain ABUS TVIP cameras. The CGI scripts allow remote attackers to execute code via system() as root. There are...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17879</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain ABUS TVIP cameras. The CGI scripts allow remote attackers to execute code via system() as root. There are several injection points in various scripts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-17558 | Hardcoded manufacturer credentials and an OS command injection vulnerability in the /cgi-bin/mft/ directory on ABUS TVIP TVIP20050 LM.1.6.18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17558</link><description>Hardcoded manufacturer credentials and an OS command injection vulnerability in the /cgi-bin/mft/ directory on ABUS TVIP TVIP20050 LM.1.6.18, TVIP10051 LM.1.6.18, TVIP11050 MG.1.6.03.05, TVIP20550 LM.1.6.18, TVIP10050 LM.1.6.18, TVIP11550 MG.1.6.03, TVIP21050 MG.1.6.03, and TVIP51550 MG.1.6.03 cameras allow remote attackers to execute code as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-17559 | Due to incorrect access control, unauthenticated remote attackers can view the /video.mjpg video stream of certain ABUS TVIP cameras.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17559</link><description>Due to incorrect access control, unauthenticated remote attackers can view the /video.mjpg video stream of certain ABUS TVIP cameras.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-16739 | An issue was discovered on certain ABUS TVIP devices. Due to a path traversal in /opt/cgi/admin/filewrite, an attacker can write to files, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16739</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain ABUS TVIP devices. Due to a path traversal in /opt/cgi/admin/filewrite, an attacker can write to files, and thus execute code arbitrarily with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5805 | SourceCodester Simple Real Estate Portal System view_estate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5805</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Real Estate Portal System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_estate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243618 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39726 | An issue in Mintty v.3.6.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted commands to the terminal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39726</link><description>An issue in Mintty v.3.6.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted commands to the terminal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33558 | An information disclosure vulnerability in the component users-grid-data.php of Ocomon before v4.0.1 allows attackers to obtain sensitive in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33558</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the component users-grid-data.php of Ocomon before v4.0.1 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information such as e-mails and usernames.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33559 | A local file inclusion vulnerability via the lang parameter in OcoMon before v4.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by supplying ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33559</link><description>A local file inclusion vulnerability via the lang parameter in OcoMon before v4.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by supplying a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46665 | Improper Access Control in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46665</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass vulnerability due to an attacker modifying passwords in a POST request and gain unauthorized access to the affected device with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46663 | Improper Access Control in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46663</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 is vulnerable to an attacker bypassing authorization and accessing resources behind protected pages. The application interface allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46664 | Improper Access Control in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46664</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 is vulnerable to an improper access control vulnerability when the application provides direct access to objects based on user-supplied input. As a result of this vulnerability attackers can bypass authorization and access resources behind protected pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46747 | BIG-IP Configuration utility unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46747</link><description>Undisclosed requests may bypass configuration utility authentication, allowing an attacker with network access to the BIG-IP system through the management port and/or self IP addresses to execute arbitrary system commands.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46748 | BIG-IP Configuration utility authenticated SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46748</link><description>An authenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Configuration utility which 

may allow an authenticated attacker with network access to the Configuration utility through the BIG-IP management port and/or self IP addresses to execute arbitrary system commands.

 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46661 | Improper Access Control in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46661</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 is vulnerable to an attacker escalating their privileges by modifying passwords in POST requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46662 | Improper Access Control in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46662</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability due to improper access control enforcement. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this via a specially crafted request to gain access to sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5804 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5804</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-243617 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0897 | Session FIxation in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0897</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 is vulnerable to a session hijack vulnerability due to the cookie being vulnerable to a brute force attack, lack of SSL, and the session being visible in requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 19:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5754 | Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts in Sielco PolyEco1000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5754</link><description>Sielco PolyEco1000 uses a weak set of default administrative credentials that can be easily guessed in remote password attacks and gain full control of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 19:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39427 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39427</link><description>In Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, and Cobalt Share v12 SP0 Build (1204.77), the affected applications lack proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing XE files. This could lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 19:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39936 | Ashlar-Vellum Graphite Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39936</link><description>In Ashlar-Vellum Graphite v13.0.48, the affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing VC6 files. This could lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 19:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44267 | Online Art Gallery v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44267</link><description>Online Art Gallery v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'lnm' parameter of the header.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 19:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31416 | Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes (ECK) secret token configuration issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31416</link><description>Secret token configuration is never applied when using ECK &lt;2.8 with APM Server &gt;=8.0. This could lead to anonymous requests to an APM Server being accepted and the data ingested into this APM deployment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31417 | Elasticsearch Insertion of sensitive information in audit logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31417</link><description>Elasticsearch generally filters out sensitive information and credentials before logging to the audit log. It was found that this filtering was not applied when requests to Elasticsearch use certain deprecated URIs for APIs. The impact of this flaw is that sensitive information such as passwords and tokens might be printed in cleartext in Elasticsearch audit logs. Note that audit logging is disabled by default and needs to be explicitly enabled and even when audit logging is enabled, request bodies that could contain sensitive information are not printed to the audit log unless explicitly configured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31418 | Elasticsearch uncontrolled resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31418</link><description>An issue has been identified with how Elasticsearch handled incoming requests on the HTTP layer. An unauthenticated user could force an Elasticsearch node to exit with an OutOfMemory error by sending a moderate number of malformed HTTP requests. The issue was identified by Elastic Engineering and we have no indication that the issue is known or that it is being exploited in the wild.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5795 | CodeAstro POS System Profile Picture profil unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5795</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro POS System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /profil of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-243601 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5796 | CodeAstro POS System Logo setting unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5796</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro POS System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /setting of the component Logo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46435 | Sourcecodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via mpms/?p=services/view_service&amp;id.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46435</link><description>Sourcecodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via mpms/?p=services/view_service&amp;id.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31419 | Elasticsearch StackOverflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31419</link><description>A flaw was discovered in Elasticsearch, affecting the _search API that allowed a specially crafted query string to cause a Stack Overflow and ultimately a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5793 | flusity CMS Dashboard customblock.php loadCustomBlocCreateForm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5793</link><description>A vulnerability was found in flusity CMS and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function loadCustomBlocCreateForm of the file /core/tools/customblock.php of the component Dashboard. The manipulation of the argument customblock_place leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 81252bc764e1de2422e79e36194bba1289e7a0a5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243599.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5794 | PHPGurukul Online Railway Catering System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Railway Catering System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243600.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43208 | NextGen Healthcare Mirth Connect before version 4.4.1 is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution. Note that this vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43208</link><description>NextGen Healthcare Mirth Connect before version 4.4.1 is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution. Note that this vulnerability is caused by the incomplete patch of CVE-2023-37679.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5624 | Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5624</link><description>Under certain conditions, Nessus Network Monitor was found to not properly enforce input validation. This could allow an admin user to alter parameters that could potentially allow a blindSQL injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5792 | SourceCodester Sticky Notes App delete-note.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5792</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Sticky Notes App 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file endpoint/delete-note.php. The manipulation of the argument note leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5623 | Privilege Escalation </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5623</link><description>NNM failed to properly set ACLs on its installation directory, which could allow a low privileged user to run arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges where NNM is installed to a non-standard location</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5791 | SourceCodester Sticky Notes App add-note.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5791</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Sticky Notes App 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file endpoint/add-note.php. The manipulation of the argument noteTitle/noteContent leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-243597 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41966 | Sielco Radio Link and Analog FM Transmitters Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41966</link><description>The application suffers from a privilege escalation vulnerability. A 
user with read permissions can elevate privileges by sending a HTTP POST
 to set a parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42769 | Sielco Radio Link and Analog FM Transmitters Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42769</link><description>The cookie session ID is of insufficient length and can be exploited by 
brute force, which may allow a remote attacker to obtain a valid 
session, bypass authentication, and manipulate the transmitter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45228 | Sielco Radio Link and Analog FM Transmitters  Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45228</link><description>The application suffers from improper access control when editing users.
 A user with read permissions can manipulate users, passwords, and 
permissions by sending a single HTTP POST request with modified 
parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45317 | Sielco Radio Link and Analog FM Transmitters Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45317</link><description>The application interface allows users to perform certain actions via 
HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the 
requests. This can be exploited to perform certain actions with 
administrative privileges if a logged-in user visits a malicious web 
site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46666 | Elastic Sharepoint Online Python Connector Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46666</link><description>An issue was discovered when using Document Level Security and the SPO "Limited Access" functionality in Elastic Sharepoint Online Python Connector. If a user is assigned limited access permissions to an item on a Sharepoint site then that user would have read permissions to all content on the Sharepoint site through Elasticsearch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5622 | Privilege Escalation </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5622</link><description>Under certain conditions, Nessus Network Monitor could allow a low privileged user to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM on Windows hosts by replacing a specially crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5789 | Dragon Path 707GR1 Ping Diagnostics cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5789</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Dragon Path 707GR1 up to 20231022. Affected is an unknown function of the component Ping Diagnostics. The manipulation of the argument Host Address with the input &gt;&gt;&lt;img/src/onerror=alert(1)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5790 | SourceCodester File Manager App add-file.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5790</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester File Manager App 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file endpoint/add-file.php. The manipulation of the argument uploadedFileName leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243595.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5786 | GeoServer GeoWebCache rest.html direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GeoServer GeoWebCache up to 1.15.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /geoserver/gwc/rest.html. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243592.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5787 | Shaanxi Chanming Education Technology Score Query System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5787</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shaanxi Chanming Education Technology Score Query System 5.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument stuIdCard leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-243593 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45867 | ILIAS (2013-09-12 release) contains a medium-criticality Directory Traversal local file inclusion vulnerability in the ScormAicc module. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45867</link><description>ILIAS (2013-09-12 release) contains a medium-criticality Directory Traversal local file inclusion vulnerability in the ScormAicc module. An attacker with a privileged account, typically holding the tutor role, can exploit this to gain unauthorized access to and potentially retrieve confidential files stored on the web server. The attacker can access files that are readable by the web server user www-data; this may include sensitive configuration files and documents located outside the documentRoot. The vulnerability is exploited by an attacker who manipulates the file parameter in a URL, inserting directory traversal sequences in order to access unauthorized files. This manipulation allows the attacker to retrieve sensitive files, such as /etc/passwd, potentially compromising the system's security. This issue poses a significant risk to confidentiality and is remotely exploitable over the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45868 | The Learning Module in ILIAS 7.25 (2023-09-12 release) allows an attacker (with basic user privileges) to achieve a high-impact Directory Tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45868</link><description>The Learning Module in ILIAS 7.25 (2023-09-12 release) allows an attacker (with basic user privileges) to achieve a high-impact Directory Traversal attack on confidentiality and availability. By exploiting this network-based vulnerability, the attacker can move specified directories, normally outside the documentRoot, to a publicly accessible location via the PHP function rename(). This results in a total loss of confidentiality, exposing sensitive resources, and potentially denying access to the affected component and the operating system's components. To exploit this, an attacker must manipulate a POST request during the creation of an exercise unit, by modifying the old_name and new_name parameters via directory traversal. However, it's essential to note that, when exploiting this vulnerability, the specified directory will be relocated from its original location, rendering all files obtained from there unavailable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45869 | ILIAS 7.25 (2023-09-12) allows any authenticated user to execute arbitrary operating system commands remotely, when a highly privileged acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45869</link><description>ILIAS 7.25 (2023-09-12) allows any authenticated user to execute arbitrary operating system commands remotely, when a highly privileged account accesses an XSS payload. The injected commands are executed via the exec() function in the execQuoted() method of the ilUtil class (/Services/Utilities/classes/class.ilUtil.php) This allows attackers to inject malicious commands into the system, potentially compromising the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of the ILIAS installation and the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5785 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway addaddress_interpret.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5785</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /protocol/firewall/addaddress_interpret.php. The manipulation of the argument messagecontent leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243591. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46449 | Sourcecodester Free and Open Source inventory management system v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An arbitrary user can change...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46449</link><description>Sourcecodester Free and Open Source inventory management system v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An arbitrary user can change the password of another user and takeover the account via IDOR in the password change function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46450 | Sourcecodester Free and Open Source inventory management system 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Add supplier functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46450</link><description>Sourcecodester Free and Open Source inventory management system 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Add supplier function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46234 | browserify-sign vulnerable via an upper bound check issue in `dsaVerify` that leads to a signature forgery attack </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46234</link><description>browserify-sign is a package to duplicate the functionality of node's crypto public key functions, much of this is based on Fedor Indutny's work on indutny/tls.js. An upper bound check issue in `dsaVerify` function allows an attacker to construct signatures that can be successfully verified by any public key, thus leading to a signature forgery attack. All places in this project that involve DSA verification of user-input signatures will be affected by this vulnerability. This issue has been patched in version 4.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5784 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway uploadfirewall.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5784</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /protocol/firewall/uploadfirewall.php. The manipulation of the argument messagecontent leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243590 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46238 | XSS with User Avatar image in ZITADEL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46238</link><description>ZITADEL is an identity infrastructure management system. ZITADEL users can upload their own avatar image using various image types including SVG. SVG can include scripts, such as javascript, which can be executed during rendering. Due to a missing security header, an attacker could inject code to an SVG to gain access to the victim’s account in certain scenarios. A victim would need to directly open the malicious image in the browser, where a single session in ZITADEL needs to be active for this exploit to work. If the possible victim had multiple or no active sessions in ZITADEL, the attack would not succeed. This issue has been patched in version 2.39.2 and 2.38.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5783 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5783</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/system/approve_center/flow_sort/flow/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument id/sort_parent leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-243589 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5782 | Tongda OA 2017 General News delete_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5782</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage/delete_query.php of the component General News. The manipulation of the argument NEWS_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243588. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 13:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46090 | WordPress Spider Facebook Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46090</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WebDorado WDSocialWidgets plugin &lt;= 1.0.15 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41095 | Keys Stored in Plaintext on Secure Vault High for Silabs OpenThread devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41095</link><description>Missing Encryption of Security Keys vulnerability in Silicon Labs OpenThread SDK on 32 bit, ARM (SecureVault High modules) allows potential modification or extraction of network credentials stored in flash.
This issue affects Silicon Labs OpenThread SDK: 2.3.1 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41096 | Keys Stored in Plaintext on Secure Vault High for Silabs Ember ZNet devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41096</link><description>Missing Encryption of Security Keys vulnerability in Silicon Labs Ember ZNet SDK on 32 bit, ARM (SecureVault High modules)
 allows potential modification or extraction of network credentials stored in flash.


This issue affects Silicon Labs Ember ZNet SDK: 7.3.1 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46088 | WordPress WP Full Stripe Free Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46088</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Mammothology WP Full Stripe Free plugin &lt;= 1.6.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5781 | Tongda OA 2017 delete_webmail.php DELETE_STR sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5781</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA 2017 11.10. This issue affects the function DELETE_STR of the file general/system/res_manage/monitor/delete_webmail.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243587. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-17477 | Incorrect LDAP ACLs in ucs-school-ldap-acls-master in UCS@school before 4.4v5-errata allow remote teachers, staff, and school administrators...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17477</link><description>Incorrect LDAP ACLs in ucs-school-ldap-acls-master in UCS@school before 4.4v5-errata allow remote teachers, staff, and school administrators to read LDAP password hashes (sambaNTPassword, krb5Key, sambaPasswordHistory, and pwhistory) via LDAP search requests. For example, a teacher can gain administrator access via an NTLM hash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32116 | WordPress Custom post types Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32116</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in TotalPress.Org Custom post types, Custom Fields &amp; more plugin &lt;= 4.0.12 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46081 | WordPress Lava Directory Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.34 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46081</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Lavacode Lava Directory Manager plugin &lt;= 1.1.34 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46094 | WordPress Conversios.io Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46094</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Conversios Track Google Analytics 4, Facebook Pixel &amp; Conversions API via Google Tag Manager for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 6.5.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46076 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.102 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46076</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in RedNao WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder, Create invoices, packing slips and more plugin &lt;= 1.2.102 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46077 | WordPress The Awesome Feed – Custom Feed Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46077</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Arrow Plugins The Awesome Feed – Custom Feed plugin &lt;= 2.2.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30492 | WordPress Minimum Purchase for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30492</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Vark Minimum Purchase for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 2.0.0.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46075 | WordPress Contact Form Builder, Contact Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46075</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in wpdevart Contact Form Builder, Contact Widget plugin &lt;= 2.1.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5780 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5780</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA 2017 11.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file general/system/approve_center/flow_guide/flow_type/set_print/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243586 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46074 | WordPress FreshMail For WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46074</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Borbis Media FreshMail For WordPress plugin &lt;= 2.3.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5802 | WordPress WP Knowledgebase Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5802</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mihai Iova WordPress Knowledge base &amp; Documentation Plugin – WP Knowledgebase plugin &lt;= 1.3.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46072 | WordPress Add Shortcodes Actions And Filters Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46072</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Michael Simpson Add Shortcodes Actions And Filters plugin &lt;= 2.0.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5798 | Assistant &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Editor+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5798</link><description>The Assistant WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not validate a parameter before making a request to it via wp_remote_get(), which could allow users with a role as low as Editor to perform SSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46754 | The admin panel for Obl.ong before 1.1.2 allows authorization bypass because the email OTP feature accepts arbitrary numerical values.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46754</link><description>The admin panel for Obl.ong before 1.1.2 allows authorization bypass because the email OTP feature accepts arbitrary numerical values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46752 | An issue was discovered in FRRouting FRR through 9.0.1. It mishandles malformed MP_REACH_NLRI data, leading to a crash.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46752</link><description>An issue was discovered in FRRouting FRR through 9.0.1. It mishandles malformed MP_REACH_NLRI data, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46753 | An issue was discovered in FRRouting FRR through 9.0.1. A crash can occur for a crafted BGP UPDATE message without mandatory attributes, e.g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46753</link><description>An issue was discovered in FRRouting FRR through 9.0.1. A crash can occur for a crafted BGP UPDATE message without mandatory attributes, e.g., one with only an unknown transit attribute.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5139 | Potential buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zephyr STM32 Crypto driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5139</link><description>Potential buffer overflow vulnerability at the following location in the Zephyr STM32 Crypto driver</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31421 | Beats, Elastic Agent, APM Server, and Fleet Server Improper Certificate Validation issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31421</link><description>It was discovered that when acting as TLS clients, Beats, Elastic Agent, APM Server, and Fleet Server did not verify whether the server certificate is valid for the target IP address; however, certificate signature validation is still performed. More specifically, when the client is configured to connect to an IP address (instead of a hostname) it does not validate the server certificate's IP SAN values against that IP address and certificate validation fails, and therefore the connection is not blocked as expected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31422 | Kibana Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31422</link><description>An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby sensitive information is recorded in Kibana logs in the event of an error. The issue impacts only Kibana version 8.10.0 when logging in the JSON layout or when the pattern layout is configured to log the %meta pattern. Elastic has released Kibana 8.10.1 which resolves this issue. The error object recorded in the log contains request information, which can include sensitive data, such as authentication credentials, cookies, authorization headers, query params, request paths, and other metadata. Some examples of sensitive data which can be included in the logs are account credentials for kibana_system, kibana-metricbeat, or Kibana end-users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46667 | Fleet Server Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46667</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fleet Server &gt;= v8.10.0 and &lt; v8.10.3 where Agent enrolment tokens are being inserted into the Fleet Server’s log file in plain text. These enrolment tokens could allow someone to enrol an agent into an agent policy, and potentially use that to retrieve other secrets in the policy including for Elasticsearch and third-party services. Alternatively a threat actor could potentially enrol agents to the clusters and send arbitrary events to Elasticsearch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46668 | Elastic Endpoint Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46668</link><description>If Elastic Endpoint (v7.9.0 - v8.10.3) is configured to use a non-default option in which the logging level is explicitly set to debug, and when Elastic Agent is simultaneously configured to collect and send those logs to Elasticsearch, then Elastic Agent API keys can be viewed in Elasticsearch in plaintext. These API keys could be used to write arbitrary data and read Elastic Endpoint user artifacts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43906 | Xolo CMS v0.11 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43906</link><description>Xolo CMS v0.11 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30967 | Gotham Orbital Simulator path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30967</link><description>Gotham Orbital-Simulator service prior to 0.692.0 was found to be vulnerable to a Path traversal issue allowing an unauthenticated user to read arbitrary files on the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30969 | Palantir Tiles missing authentication on API endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30969</link><description>The Palantir Tiles1 service was  found to be vulnerable to an API wide issue where the service was not performing authentication/authorization on all the endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43905 | Incorrect access control in writercms v1.1.0 allows attackers to directly obtain backend account passwords via unspecified vectors.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43905</link><description>Incorrect access control in writercms v1.1.0 allows attackers to directly obtain backend account passwords via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46345 | Catdoc v0.95 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component xls2csv at src/xlsparse.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46345</link><description>Catdoc v0.95 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component xls2csv at src/xlsparse.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46584 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PHPGurukul Nipah virus (NiV) " Testing Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46584</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PHPGurukul Nipah virus (NiV) " Testing Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted request to the new-user-testing.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 22:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46583 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPGurukul Nipah virus (NiV) " Testing Management System v.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46583</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPGurukul Nipah virus (NiV) " Testing Management System v.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload injected into the State field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 22:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38845 | An issue in Anglaise Company Anglaise.Company v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38845</link><description>An issue in Anglaise Company Anglaise.Company v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38849 | An issue in tire-sales Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38849</link><description>An issue in tire-sales Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38847 | An issue in CHRISTINA JAPAN Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38847</link><description>An issue in CHRISTINA JAPAN Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38846 | An issue in Marbre Lapin Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38846</link><description>An issue in Marbre Lapin Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38848 | An issue in rmc R Beauty CLINIC Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38848</link><description>An issue in rmc R Beauty CLINIC Line v.13.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46232 | era-compiler-vyper First Immutable Variable Initialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46232</link><description>era-compiler-vyper is the EraVM Vyper compiler for zkSync Era, a layer 2 rollup that uses zero-knowledge proofs to scale Ethereum. Prior to era-compiler-vype version 1.3.10, a bug prevented the initialization of the first immutable variable for Vyper contracts meeting certain criteria. The problem arises when there is a String or Array with more 256-bit words allocated than initialized. It results in the second word’s index unset, that is effectively set to 0, so the first immutable value with the actual 0 index is overwritten in the ImmutableSimulator. Version 1.3.10 fixes this issue by setting all indexes in advance. The problem will go away, but it will get more expensive if the user allocates a lot of uninitialized space, e.g. `String[4096]`. Upgrading and redeploying affected contracts is the only way of working around the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46137 | twisted.web has disordered HTTP pipeline response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46137</link><description>Twisted is an event-based framework for internet applications. Prior to version 23.10.0rc1, when sending multiple HTTP requests in one TCP packet, twisted.web will process the requests asynchronously without guaranteeing the response order. If one of the endpoints is controlled by an attacker, the attacker can delay the response on purpose to manipulate the response of the second request when a victim launched two requests using HTTP pipeline. Version 23.10.0rc1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46133 | crypto-es PBKDF2 1,000 times weaker than specified in 1993 and 1.3M times weaker than current standard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46133</link><description>CryptoES is a cryptography algorithms library compatible with ES6 and TypeScript. Prior to version 2.1.0, CryptoES PBKDF2 is 1,000 times weaker than originally specified in 1993, and at least 1,300,000 times weaker than current industry standard. This is because it both defaults to SHA1, a cryptographic hash algorithm considered insecure since at least 2005, and defaults to one single iteration, a 'strength' or 'difficulty' value specified at 1,000 when specified in 1993. PBKDF2 relies on iteration count as a countermeasure to preimage and collision attacks. If used to protect passwords, the impact is high. If used to generate signatures, the impact is high. Version 2.1.0 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, configure CryptoES to use SHA256 with at least 250,000 iterations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46134 | D-Tale vulnerable to Remote Code Execution through the Custom Filter Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46134</link><description>D-Tale is the combination of a Flask back-end and a React front-end to view &amp; analyze Pandas data structures. Prior to version 3.7.0, users hosting D-Tale publicly can be vulnerable to remote code execution, allowing attackers to run malicious code on the server. This issue has been patched in version 3.7.0 by turning off "Custom Filter" input by default. The only workaround for versions earlier than 3.7.0 is to only host D-Tale to trusted users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46233 | crypto-js PBKDF2 1,000 times weaker than specified in 1993 and 1.3M times weaker than current standard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46233</link><description>crypto-js is a JavaScript library of crypto standards. Prior to version 4.2.0, crypto-js PBKDF2 is 1,000 times weaker than originally specified in 1993, and at least 1,300,000 times weaker than current industry standard. This is because it both defaults to SHA1, a cryptographic hash algorithm considered insecure since at least 2005, and defaults to one single iteration, a 'strength' or 'difficulty' value specified at 1,000 when specified in 1993. PBKDF2 relies on iteration count as a countermeasure to preimage and collision attacks. If used to protect passwords, the impact is high. If used to generate signatures, the impact is high. Version 4.2.0 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, configure crypto-js to use SHA256 with at least 250,000 iterations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45137 | XWiki Platform XSS with edit right in the create document form for existing pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45137</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web` starting in version 3.1-milestone-2 and prior to version 13.4-rc-1, as well as `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web-templates` prior to versions 14.10.12 and 15.5-rc-1, are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. When trying to create a document that already exists, XWiki displays an error message in the form for creating it. Due to missing escaping, this error message is vulnerable to raw HTML injection and thus XSS. The injected code is the document reference of the existing document so this requires that the attacker first creates a non-empty document whose name contains the attack code. This has been patched in `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web` version 13.4-rc-1 and `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web-templates` versions 14.10.12 and 15.5-rc-1 by adding the appropriate escaping. The vulnerable template file `createinline.vm` is part of XWiki's WAR and can be patched by manually applying the changes from the fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 20:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5367 | Out-of-bounds write in xichangedeviceproperty/rrchangeoutputproperty</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5367</link><description>A out-of-bounds write flaw was found in the xorg-x11-server. This issue occurs due to an incorrect calculation of a buffer offset when copying data stored in the heap in the XIChangeDeviceProperty function in Xi/xiproperty.c and in RRChangeOutputProperty function in randr/rrproperty.c, allowing for possible escalation of privileges or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5380 | Use-after-free bug in destroywindow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5380</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the xorg-x11-server. An X server crash may occur in a very specific and legacy configuration (a multi-screen setup with multiple protocol screens, also known as Zaphod mode) if the pointer is warped from within a window on one screen to the root window of the other screen and if the original window is destroyed followed by another window being destroyed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5574 | Use-after-free bug in damagedestroy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5574</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in xorg-x11-server-Xvfb. This issue occurs in Xvfb with a very specific and legacy configuration (a multi-screen setup with multiple protocol screens, also known as Zaphod mode). If the pointer is warped from a screen 1 to a screen 0, a use-after-free issue may be triggered during shutdown or reset of the Xvfb server, allowing for possible escalation of privileges or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45136 | XWiki Platform web templates vulnerable to reflected XSS in the create document form if name validation is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45136</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When document names are validated according to a name strategy (disabled by default), XWiki starting in version 12.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 12.10.12 and 15.5-rc-1 is vulnerable to a reflected cross-site scripting attack in the page creation form. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary actions with the rights of the user opening the malicious link. Depending on the rights of the user, this may allow remote code execution and full read and write access to the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.12 and 15.5-rc-1 by adding appropriate escaping. The vulnerable template file `createinline.vm` is part of XWiki's WAR and can be patched by manually applying the changes from the fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46408 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_ The 41DD80 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46408</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_ The 41DD80 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46409 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_ 41CC04 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46409</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_ 41CC04 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46410 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_ The 416F60 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46410</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_ The 416F60 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46411 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_415258 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46411</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_415258 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46412 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_41D998 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46412</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_41D998 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46413 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_4155DC function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46413</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the sub_4155DC function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46414 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_ 41D494 function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46414</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_ 41D494 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46415 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_41E588 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46415</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_41E588 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46416 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_ The 41A414 func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46416</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_ The 41A414 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46417 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_415498 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46417</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_415498 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46418 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_412688 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46418</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_412688 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46419 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_415730 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46419</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_415730 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46420 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_41590C function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46420</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_41590C function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46421 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_411D00 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46421</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_411D00 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46422 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_411994 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46422</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_411994 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46423 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_417094 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46423</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_417094 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46424 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_422BD4 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46424</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the sub_422BD4 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45135 | XWiki users can be tricked to execute scripts as the create page action doesn&amp;#x27;t display the page&amp;#x27;s title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45135</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web` versions 7.2-milestone-2 until 14.10.12 and `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web-templates` prior to versions 14.10.12 and 15.5-rc-1, it is possible to pass a title to the page creation action that isn't displayed at first but then executed in the second step. This can be used by an attacker to trick a victim to execute code, allowing script execution if the victim has script right or remote code execution including full access to the XWiki instance if the victim has programming right.

For the attack to work, the attacker needs to convince the victim to visit a link like `&lt;xwiki-host&gt;/xwiki/bin/create/NonExistingSpace/WebHome?title=$services.logging.getLogger(%22foo%22).error(%22Script%20executed!%22)` where `&lt;xwiki-host&gt;`  is the URL of the Wiki installation and to then click on the "Create" button on that page. The page looks like a regular XWiki page that the victim would also see when clicking the button to create a page that doesn't exist yet, the malicious code is not displayed anywhere on that page. After clicking the "Create" button, the malicious title would be displayed but at this point, the code has already been executed and the attacker could use this code also to hide the attack, e.g., by redirecting the victim again to the same page with an innocent title. It thus seems plausible that this attack could work if the attacker can place a fake "create page" button on a page which is possible with edit right.

This has been patched in `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web` version 14.10.12 and `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web-templates` versions 14.10.12 and 15.5-rc-1 by displaying the title already in the first step such that the victim can notice the attack before continuing. It is possible to manually patch the modified files from the patch in an existing installation. For the JavaScript change, the minified JavaScript file would need to be obtained from a build of XWiki and replaced accordingly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4886 | Ingress-nginx `path` sanitization can be bypassed with `log_format` directive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4886</link><description>Ingress-nginx `path` sanitization can be bypassed with `log_format` directive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5043 | Ingress nginx annotation injection causes arbitrary command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5043</link><description>Ingress nginx annotation injection causes arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5044 | Code injection via nginx.ingress.kubernetes.io/permanent-redirect annotation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5044</link><description>Code injection via nginx.ingress.kubernetes.io/permanent-redirect annotation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45134 | XWiki Platform XSS vulnerability from account in the create page form via template provider</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45134</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web` starting in version 3.1-milestone-1 and prior to 13.4-rc-1, `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web-templates` prior to versions 14.10.2 and 15.5-rc-1, and `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-web-standard` starting in version 2.4-milestone-2 and prior to version 3.1-milestone-1 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An attacker can create a template provider on any document that is part of the wiki (could be the attacker's user profile) that contains malicious code. This code is executed when this template provider is selected during document creation which can be triggered by sending the user to a URL. For the attacker, the only requirement is to have an account as by default the own user profile is editable. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary actions with the rights of the user opening the malicious link. Depending on the rights of the user, this may allow remote code execution and full read and write access to the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web` 13.4-rc-1, `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-web-templates` 14.10.2 and 15.5-rc-1, and `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-web-standard` 3.1-milestone-1 by adding the appropriate escaping. The vulnerable template file createinline.vm is part of XWiki's WAR and can be patched by manually applying the changes from the fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32359 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2. A user's pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32359</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2. A user's password may be read aloud by VoiceOver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40401 | The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An attacker may be able to access p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40401</link><description>The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An attacker may be able to access passkeys without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40404 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40404</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40405 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40405</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40408 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40408</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. Hide My Email may be deactivated unexpectedly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40413 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, watchOS 10...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40413</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40416 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40416</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. Processing an image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40421 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40421</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40423 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40423</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40425 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.1. An app wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40425</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.1. An app with root privileges may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40444 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access user-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40444</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40445 | The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A device may persistently fail to lock.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40445</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A device may persistently fail to lock.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40447 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40447</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.1, Safari 17.1, tvOS 17.1. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40449 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40449</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41072 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41072</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41077 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access protected user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41077</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41254 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41254</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41975 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41975</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. A website may be able to access the microphone without the microphone use indicator being shown.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41976 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41976</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.1, Safari 17.1, tvOS 17.1. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41977 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2. Visiting a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41977</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2. Visiting a malicious website may reveal browsing history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41982 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41982</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to use Siri to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41983 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, Safari 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41983</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, Safari 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41988 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 17.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41988</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to use Siri to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41989 | The issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41989</link><description>The issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker may be able to execute arbitrary code as root from the Lock Screen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41997 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41997</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to use Siri to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42438 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. Visiting a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42438</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to user interface spoofing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42841 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42841</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42842 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42842</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42844 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42844</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. A website may be able to access sensitive user data when resolving symlinks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42845 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. Ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42845</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. Photos in the Hidden Photos Album may be viewed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42846 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, tvOS 17.1, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42846</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, tvOS 17.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A device may be passively tracked by its Wi-Fi MAC address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42847 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker may be abl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42847</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker may be able to access passkeys without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42849 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, watchOS 10.1,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42849</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker that has already achieved kernel code execution may be able to bypass kernel memory mitigations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42850 | The issue was addressed with improved permissions logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access sensitive us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42850</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved permissions logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42852 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42852</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.1, Safari 17.1, tvOS 17.1. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42854 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42854</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service to Endpoint Security clients.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42856 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42856</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. Processing a file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42857 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42857</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42861 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker with knowledge of a standa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42861</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker with knowledge of a standard user's credentials can unlock another standard user's locked screen on the same Mac.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37913 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-office-importer vulnerable to arbitrary server side file writing from account through office converter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37913</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Starting in version 3.5-milestone-1 and prior to versions 14.10.8 and 15.3-rc-1, triggering the office converter with a specially crafted file name allows writing the attachment's content to an attacker-controlled location on the server as long as the Java process has write access to that location. In particular in the combination with attachment moving, a feature introduced in XWiki 14.0, this is easy to reproduce but it also possible to reproduce in versions as old as XWiki 3.5 by uploading the attachment through the REST API which doesn't remove `/` or `\` from the filename. As the mime type of the attachment doesn't matter for the exploitation, this could e.g., be used to replace the `jar`-file of an extension which would allow executing arbitrary Java code and thus impact the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.8 and 15.3RC1. There are no known workarounds apart from disabling the office converter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 18:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37912 | XWiki Rendering&amp;#x27;s footnote macro vulnerable to privilege escalation via the footnote macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37912</link><description>XWiki Rendering is a generic Rendering system that converts textual input in a given syntax into another syntax. Prior to version 14.10.6 of `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-core-rendering-macro-footnotes` and `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-rendering-macro-footnotes` and prior to version 15.1-rc-1 of `org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-rendering-macro-footnotes`, the footnote macro executed its content in a potentially different context than the one in which it was defined. In particular in combination with the include macro, this allows privilege escalation from a simple user account in XWiki to programming rights and thus remote code execution, impacting the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.6 and 15.1-rc-1. There is no workaround apart from upgrading to a fixed version of the footnote macro.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37910 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-attachment-api vulnerable to Missing Authorization on Attachment Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37910</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Starting with the introduction of attachment move support in version 14.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.4.8, 14.10.4, and 15.0-rc-1, an attacker with edit access on any document (can be the user profile which is editable by default) can move any attachment of any other document to this attacker-controlled document. This allows the attacker to access and possibly publish any attachment of which the name is known, regardless if the attacker has view or edit rights on the source document of this attachment. Further, the attachment is deleted from the source document. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.4.8, 14.10.4, and 15.0 RC1. There is no workaround apart from upgrading to a fixed version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37911 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-oldcore may leak data through deleted and re-created documents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37911</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Starting in version 9.4-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.8 and 15.3-rc-1, when a document has been deleted and re-created, it is possible for users with view right on the re-created document but not on the deleted document to view the contents of the deleted document. Such a situation might arise when rights were added to the deleted document. This can be exploited through the diff feature and, partially, through the REST API by using versions such as `deleted:1` (where the number counts the deletions in the wiki and is thus guessable). Given sufficient rights, the attacker can also re-create the deleted document, thus extending the scope to any deleted document as long as the attacker has edit right in the location of the deleted document. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.8 and 15.3 RC1 by properly checking rights when deleted revisions of a document are accessed. The only workaround is to regularly clean deleted documents to minimize the potential exposure. Extra care should be taken when deleting sensitive documents that are protected individually (and not, e.g., by being placed in a protected space) or deleting a protected space as a whole.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37909 | Privilege escalation (PR)/remote code execution from account through Menu.UIExtensionSheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37909</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Starting in version 5.1-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.8 and 15.3-rc-1, any user who can edit their own user profile can execute arbitrary script macros including Groovy and Python macros that allow remote code execution including unrestricted read and write access to all wiki contents. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.8 and 15.3-rc-1 by adding proper escaping. As a workaround, the patch can be manually applied to the document `Menu.UIExtensionSheet`; only three lines need to be changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5671 | HP Print and Scan Doctor for Windows may potentially be vulnerable to escalation of privilege. HP is releasing software updates to mitigate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5671</link><description>HP Print and Scan Doctor for Windows may potentially be vulnerable to escalation of privilege. HP is releasing software updates to mitigate the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37908 | org.xwiki.rendering:xwiki-rendering-xml Improper Neutralization of Invalid Characters in Identifiers in Web Pages vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37908</link><description>XWiki Rendering is a generic Rendering system that converts textual input in a given syntax into another syntax. The cleaning of attributes during XHTML rendering, introduced in version 14.6-rc-1, allowed the injection of arbitrary HTML code and thus cross-site scripting via invalid attribute names. This can be exploited, e.g., via the link syntax in any content that supports XWiki syntax like comments in XWiki. When a user moves the mouse over a malicious link, the malicious JavaScript code is executed in the context of the user session. When this user is a privileged user who has programming rights, this allows server-side code execution with programming rights, impacting the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the XWiki instance. While this attribute was correctly recognized as not allowed, the attribute was still printed with a prefix `data-xwiki-translated-attribute-` without further cleaning or validation. This problem has been patched in XWiki 14.10.4 and 15.0 RC1 by removing characters not allowed in data attributes and then validating the cleaned attribute again. There are no known workarounds apart from upgrading to a version including the fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5472 | Use after free in Profiles in Google Chrome prior to 118.0.5993.117 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5472</link><description>Use after free in Profiles in Google Chrome prior to 118.0.5993.117 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34446 | iTop XSS vulnerability on pages/preferences.php </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34446</link><description>iTop is an open source, web-based IT service management platform. Prior to versions 3.0.4 and 3.1.0, when displaying `pages/preferences.php`, cross site scripting is possible. This issue is fixed in versions 3.0.4 and 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34447 | iTop XSS vulnerability on pages/UI.php </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34447</link><description>iTop is an open source, web-based IT service management platform. Prior to versions 3.0.4 and 3.1.0, on `pages/UI.php`, cross site scripting is possible. This issue is fixed in versions 3.0.4 and 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46523 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function upgradeInfoRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46523</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function upgradeInfoRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46396 | Audimex 15.0.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /audimex/cgi-bin/wal.fcgi via company parameter search filters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46396</link><description>Audimex 15.0.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /audimex/cgi-bin/wal.fcgi via company parameter search filters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42490 |  EisBaer Scada - CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42490</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42492 |  EisBaer Scada - CWE-321: Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42492</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-321: Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42493 |  EisBaer Scada - CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42493</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42494 |  EisBaer Scada - CWE-749: Exposed Dangerous Method or Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42494</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-749: Exposed Dangerous Method or Function</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30912 | A remote code execution issue exists in HPE OneView.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30912</link><description>A remote code execution issue exists in HPE OneView.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42488 |  EisBaer Scada - CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42488</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal')</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42489 |  EisBaer Scada - CWE-732: Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42489</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-732: Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42491 | EisBaer Scada - CWE-285: Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42491</link><description>EisBaer Scada - CWE-285: Improper Authorization</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45220 | The Android Client application, when enrolled with the define method 1(the user manually inserts the server ip address), use HTTP protocol t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45220</link><description>The Android Client application, when enrolled with the define method 1(the user manually inserts the server ip address), use HTTP protocol to retrieve  sensitive information (ip address and credentials to connect to a remote MQTT broker entity) instead of HTTPS and this feature is not configurable by the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45321 | The Android Client application, when enrolled with the define  method 1 (the user manually inserts the server ip address), use HTTP protocol...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45321</link><description>The Android Client application, when enrolled with the define  method 1 (the user manually inserts the server ip address), use HTTP protocol to retrieve sensitive information (ip address and credentials to connect to a remote MQTT broker entity) instead of HTTPS and this feature is not configurable by the user. Due to the lack of encryption of HTTP,this issue allows an attacker placed in the same subnet network of the HMI device to intercept username and password necessary to authenticate to the MQTT server responsible to implement the remote management protocol.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45851 | The Android Client application, when enrolled to the AppHub server,connects to an MQTT broker without enforcing any server authentication. &#13;...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45851</link><description>The Android Client application, when enrolled to the AppHub server,connects to an MQTT broker without enforcing any server authentication. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This issue allows an attacker to force the Android Client application to connect to a malicious MQTT broker, enabling it to send fake messages to the HMI device</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46102 | The Android Client application, when enrolled to the AppHub server, connects to an MQTT&#13;
broker to exchange messages and receive commands to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46102</link><description>The Android Client application, when enrolled to the AppHub server, connects to an MQTT&#13;
broker to exchange messages and receive commands to execute on the HMI device.&#13;
The protocol builds on top of MQTT to implement the remote management of the device is encrypted with a hard-coded DES symmetric key, that can be retrieved reversing both the Android Client application and the server-side web application.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This issue allows an attacker able to control a malicious MQTT broker on the same subnet&#13;
network of the device, to craft malicious messages and send them to the HMI device, executing arbitrary commands on the device itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41255 | The vulnerability allows an unprivileged user with access to the subnet of the TPC-110W device to gain a root shell on the device itself abu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41255</link><description>The vulnerability allows an unprivileged user with access to the subnet of the TPC-110W device to gain a root shell on the device itself abusing the lack of authentication &#13;
of the ‘su’ binary file installed on the device that can be accessed through the ADB (Android Debug Bridge) protocol  exposed on the network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41372 | The vulnerability allows an unprivileged (untrusted) third- party application to arbitrary modify the server settings of the Android Client ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41372</link><description>The vulnerability allows an unprivileged (untrusted) third- party application to arbitrary modify the server settings of the Android Client application, inducing it to connect to an attacker - controlled malicious server.This is possible by forging a valid broadcast intent encrypted with a hardcoded RSA key pair</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41960 | The vulnerability allows an unprivileged(untrusted) third-party application to interact with a content-provider unsafely exposed by the Andr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41960</link><description>The vulnerability allows an unprivileged(untrusted) third-party application to interact with a content-provider unsafely exposed by the Android Agent application, potentially modifying sensitive settings of the Android Client application itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46650 | Jenkins GitHub Plugin 1.37.3 and earlier does not escape the GitHub project URL on the build page when showing changes, resulting in a store...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46650</link><description>Jenkins GitHub Plugin 1.37.3 and earlier does not escape the GitHub project URL on the build page when showing changes, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers with Item/Configure permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46651 | Jenkins Warnings Plugin 10.5.0 and earlier does not set the appropriate context for credentials lookup, allowing attackers with Item/Configu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46651</link><description>Jenkins Warnings Plugin 10.5.0 and earlier does not set the appropriate context for credentials lookup, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to access and capture credentials they are not entitled to. This fix has been backported to 10.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46652 | A missing permission check in Jenkins lambdatest-automation Plugin 1.20.9 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to enume...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46652</link><description>A missing permission check in Jenkins lambdatest-automation Plugin 1.20.9 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to enumerate credentials IDs of LAMBDATEST credentials stored in Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46653 | Jenkins lambdatest-automation Plugin 1.20.10 and earlier logs LAMBDATEST Credentials access token at the INFO level, potentially resulting i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46653</link><description>Jenkins lambdatest-automation Plugin 1.20.10 and earlier logs LAMBDATEST Credentials access token at the INFO level, potentially resulting in its exposure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46654 | Jenkins CloudBees CD Plugin 1.1.32 and earlier follows symbolic links to locations outside of the expected directory during the cleanup proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46654</link><description>Jenkins CloudBees CD Plugin 1.1.32 and earlier follows symbolic links to locations outside of the expected directory during the cleanup process of the 'CloudBees CD - Publish Artifact' post-build step, allowing attackers able to configure jobs to delete arbitrary files on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46655 | Jenkins CloudBees CD Plugin 1.1.32 and earlier follows symbolic links to locations outside of the directory from which artifacts are publish...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46655</link><description>Jenkins CloudBees CD Plugin 1.1.32 and earlier follows symbolic links to locations outside of the directory from which artifacts are published during the 'CloudBees CD - Publish Artifact' post-build step, allowing attackers able to configure jobs to publish arbitrary files from the Jenkins controller file system to the previously configured CloudBees CD server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46656 | Jenkins Multibranch Scan Webhook Trigger Plugin 1.0.9 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46656</link><description>Jenkins Multibranch Scan Webhook Trigger Plugin 1.0.9 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook token are equal, potentially allowing attackers to use statistical methods to obtain a valid webhook token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46657 | Jenkins Gogs Plugin 1.0.15 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46657</link><description>Jenkins Gogs Plugin 1.0.15 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook token are equal, potentially allowing attackers to use statistical methods to obtain a valid webhook token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46658 | Jenkins MSTeams Webhook Trigger Plugin 0.1.1 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46658</link><description>Jenkins MSTeams Webhook Trigger Plugin 0.1.1 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook token are equal, potentially allowing attackers to use statistical methods to obtain a valid webhook token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46659 | Jenkins Edgewall Trac Plugin 1.13 and earlier does not escape the Trac website URL on the build page, resulting in a stored cross-site scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46659</link><description>Jenkins Edgewall Trac Plugin 1.13 and earlier does not escape the Trac website URL on the build page, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers with Item/Configure permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46660 | Jenkins Zanata Plugin 0.6 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46660</link><description>Jenkins Zanata Plugin 0.6 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook token hashes are equal, potentially allowing attackers to use statistical methods to obtain a valid webhook token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43488 | The vulnerability allows a low privileged (untrusted) application to&#13;
modify a critical system property that should be denied, in order to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43488</link><description>The vulnerability allows a low privileged (untrusted) application to&#13;
modify a critical system property that should be denied, in order to enable the ADB (Android Debug Bridge) protocol to be exposed on the network, exploiting it to gain a privileged shell on the device without requiring the physical access through USB.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45844 | The vulnerability allows a low privileged user that have access to the device when locked in Kiosk mode to install an arbitrary Android appl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45844</link><description>The vulnerability allows a low privileged user that have access to the device when locked in Kiosk mode to install an arbitrary Android application and leverage it to have access to critical device settings such as the device power management or eventually the device secure settings (ADB debug).</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5717 | Out-of-bounds write in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s Linux Kernel Performance Events (perf) component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5717</link><description>A heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the Linux kernel's Linux Kernel Performance Events (perf) component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

If perf_read_group() is called while an event's sibling_list is smaller than its child's sibling_list, it can increment or write to memory locations outside of the allocated buffer.

We recommend upgrading past commit 32671e3799ca2e4590773fd0e63aaa4229e50c06.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46518 | Mercury A15 V1.0 20230818_1.0.3 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the component cloudDeviceTokenSuccCB.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46518</link><description>Mercury A15 V1.0 20230818_1.0.3 was discovered to contain a command execution vulnerability via the component cloudDeviceTokenSuccCB.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46520 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function uninstallPluginReqHand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46520</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function uninstallPluginReqHandle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46521 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function RegisterRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46521</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function RegisterRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46522 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function deviceInfoRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46522</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function deviceInfoRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46525 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function loginRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46525</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function loginRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46526 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function resetCloudPwdRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46526</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function resetCloudPwdRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46527 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function bindRequestHandle.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46527</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function bindRequestHandle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46534 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function modifyAccPwdRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46534</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function modifyAccPwdRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46535 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function getResetVeriRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46535</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function getResetVeriRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46536 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function chkRegVeriRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46536</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function chkRegVeriRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46537 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function getRegVeriRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46537</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function getRegVeriRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46538 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function chkResetVeriRegister.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46538</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function chkResetVeriRegister.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46539 | TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function registerRequestHandle.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46539</link><description>TP-LINK TL-WR886N V7.0_3.0.14_Build_221115_Rel.56908n.bin was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function registerRequestHandle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46540 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formNtp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46540</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formNtp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46541 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formIpv6Setup.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46541</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formIpv6Setup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46542 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMeshUploadConfig.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46542</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMeshUploadConfig.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46543 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWlSiteSurvey.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46543</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWlSiteSurvey.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46544 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWirelessTbl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46544</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWirelessTbl.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46545 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWsc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46545</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWsc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46546 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formStats.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46546</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formStats.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46547 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSysLog.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46547</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSysLog.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46548 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWlanRedirect.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46548</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formWlanRedirect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46549 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSetLg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46549</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formSetLg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46550 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMapDelDevice.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46550</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMapDelDevice.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46551 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formReflashClientTbl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46551</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formReflashClientTbl.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46552 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMultiAP.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46552</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMultiAP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46553 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formParentControl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46553</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formParentControl.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46554 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMapDel.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46554</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMapDel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46555 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formPortFw.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46555</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formPortFw.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46556 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formFilter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46556</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formFilter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46557 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMultiAPVLAN.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46557</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMultiAPVLAN.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46558 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMapDelDevice.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46558</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formMapDelDevice.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46559 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formIPv6Addr.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46559</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formIPv6Addr.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46560 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formTcpipSetup.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46560</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formTcpipSetup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46562 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formDosCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46562</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formDosCfg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46563 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formIpQoS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46563</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formIpQoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46564 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formDMZ.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46564</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formDMZ.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1356 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1356</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting in the StudentSearch component in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows hijacking of a user’s browsing session by attackers who have convinced the said user to click on a malicious link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4692 | Out-of-bounds write at fs/ntfs.c may lead to unsigned code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4692</link><description>An out-of-bounds write flaw was found in grub2's NTFS filesystem driver. This issue may allow an attacker to present a specially crafted NTFS filesystem image, leading to grub's heap metadata corruption. In some circumstances, the attack may also corrupt the UEFI firmware heap metadata. As a result, arbitrary code execution and secure boot protection bypass may be achieved.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4693 | Out-of-bounds read at fs/ntfs.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4693</link><description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found on grub2's NTFS filesystem driver. This issue may allow a physically present attacker to present a specially crafted NTFS file system image to read arbitrary memory locations. A successful attack allows sensitive data cached in memory or EFI variable values to be leaked, presenting a high Confidentiality risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27259 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27259</link><description>Missing authentication in the GetAssignmentsDue      method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction of sensitive student and teacher data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27260 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27260</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetAssignmentsDue        method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27261 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27261</link><description>Missing authentication in the DeleteAssignments         method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows deletion of data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27262 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27262</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetAssignmentsDue        method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27375 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27375</link><description>Missing authentication in the StudentPopupDetails_ContactDetails       method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction of sensitive student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27376 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27376</link><description>Missing authentication in the StudentPopupDetails_StudentDetails       method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction of sensitive student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27377 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27377</link><description>Missing authentication in the StudentPopupDetails_EmergencyContactDetails        method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction of sensitive student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27256 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27256</link><description>Missing authentication in the GetLogFiles   method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows retrieval of sensitive log files by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27257 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27257</link><description>Missing authentication in the GetActiveToiletPasses    method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows retrieval of student information by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27258 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27258</link><description>Missing authentication in the GetStudentGroupStudents     method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows retrieval of student and teacher data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26581 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26581</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetVisitors  method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26582 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26582</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetExcursionDetails   method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26583 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26583</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetCurrentPeriod    method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26584 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26584</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetStudentInconsistencies     method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27254 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27254</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetRoomChanges      method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27255 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27255</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the DeleteRoomChanges       method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26580 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26580</link><description>Unauthenticated arbitrary file read in the IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.013 allows the retrieval of any file present on the web server by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26578 | Arbitrary File Upload to Web Root In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26578</link><description>Arbitrary file upload to web root in the IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.013 allows authenticated attackers to upload dangerous files to web root such as ASP or ASPX, gaining command execution on the affected server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26579 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26579</link><description>Missing authentication in the DeleteStaff method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.013 allows deletion of staff information by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26575 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26575</link><description>Missing authentication in the SearchStudentsStaff  method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction sensitive student and teacher data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26576 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26576</link><description>Missing authentication in the SearchStudentsRFID   method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction sensitive student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26577 | Stored Cross-site Scripting In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26577</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting in the IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows attackers to hijack the browsing session of the logged in user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26574 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26574</link><description>Missing authentication in the SearchStudents method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction sensitive student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26573 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26573</link><description>Missing authentication in the SetDB method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows denial of service or theft of database login credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26571 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26571</link><description>Missing authentication in the SetStudentNotes  method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows modification of student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26572 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26572</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetExcursionList method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26568 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26568</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the GetStudentGroupStudents method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26569 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26569</link><description>Unauthenticated SQL injection in the StudentPopupDetails_Timetable method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction or modification of all data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26570 | Missing Authentication In IDAttend’s IDWeb Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26570</link><description>Missing authentication in the StudentPopupDetails_Timetable method in IDAttend’s IDWeb application 3.1.052 and earlier allows extraction sensitive student data by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3010 | Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. 

The WorldMap panel plugin, versions before 1.0.4 contains a DOM XSS v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3010</link><description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. 

The WorldMap panel plugin, versions before 1.0.4 contains a DOM XSS vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5311 | The WP EXtra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the register() fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5311</link><description>The WP EXtra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the register() function in versions up to, and including, 6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to modify the contents of the .htaccess files located in a site's root directory or /wp-content and /wp-includes folders and achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43961 | An issue in Dromara SaToken version 1.3.50RC and before when using Spring dynamic controllers, a specially crafted request may cause an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43961</link><description>An issue in Dromara SaToken version 1.3.50RC and before when using Spring dynamic controllers, a specially crafted request may cause an authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44794 | An issue in Dromara SaToken version 1.36.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted payload to the URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44794</link><description>An issue in Dromara SaToken version 1.36.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted payload to the URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46358 | In the module "Referral and Affiliation Program" (referralbyphone) version 3.5.1 and before from Snegurka for PrestaShop, a guest can perfor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46358</link><description>In the module "Referral and Affiliation Program" (referralbyphone) version 3.5.1 and before from Snegurka for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. Method `ReferralByPhoneDefaultModuleFrontController::ajaxProcessCartRuleValidate` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34048 | VMware vCenter Server Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34048</link><description>vCenter Server contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the implementation of the DCERPC protocol. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger an out-of-bounds write potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34056 | VMware vCenter Server Partial Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34056</link><description>vCenter Server contains a partial information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges to vCenter Server may leverage this issue to access unauthorized data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46347 | In the module "Step by Step products Pack" (ndk_steppingpack) version 1.5.6 and before from NDK Design for PrestaShop, a guest can perform S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46347</link><description>In the module "Step by Step products Pack" (ndk_steppingpack) version 1.5.6 and before from NDK Design for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `NdkSpack::getPacks()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46346 | In the module "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel, XML) Export PRO" (exportproducts) in versions up to 4.1.1 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46346</link><description>In the module "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel, XML) Export PRO" (exportproducts) in versions up to 4.1.1 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal information without restriction by performing a path traversal attack. Due to a lack of permissions control and a lack of control in the path name construction, a guest can perform a path traversal to view all files on the information system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46158 | IBM WebSphere Application Server session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46158</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 23.0.0.9 through 23.0.0.10 could provide weaker than expected security due to improper resource expiration handling.  IBM X-Force ID:  268775.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34085 | User Attribute Disclosure via DynamoDB Data Stores</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34085</link><description>When an AWS DynamoDB table is used for user attribute storage, it is possible to retrieve the attributes of another user using a maliciously crafted request</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39219 | Admin Console Denial of Service via Java class enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39219</link><description>PingFederate Administrative Console dependency contains a weakness where console becomes unresponsive with crafted Java class loading enumeration requests</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37283 | Authentication Bypass via HTML Form &amp;amp; Identifier First Adapter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37283</link><description>Under a very specific and highly unrecommended configuration, authentication bypass is possible in the PingFederate Identifier First Adapter</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38041 | A logged in user may elevate its permissions by abusing a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition. When a particular process fl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38041</link><description>A logged in user may elevate its permissions by abusing a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition. When a particular process flow is initiated, an attacker can exploit this condition to gain unauthorized elevated privileges on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41721 | Instances of UniFi Network Application that (i) are run on a UniFi Gateway Console, and (ii) are versions 7.5.176. and earlier, implement de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41721</link><description>Instances of UniFi Network Application that (i) are run on a UniFi Gateway Console, and (ii) are versions 7.5.176. and earlier, implement device adoption with improper access control logic, creating a risk of access to device configuration information by a malicious actor with preexisting access to the network.

Affected Products:
UDM
UDM-PRO
UDM-SE
UDR
UDW
 
Mitigation:
Update UniFi Network to Version 7.5.187 or later.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46135 | Panic in SignedPayload::from_payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46135</link><description>rs-stellar-strkey is a Rust lib for encode/decode of Stellar Strkeys. A panic vulnerability occurs when a specially crafted payload is used.`inner_payload_len` should not above 64. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.0.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46119 | Parse Server may crash when uploading file without extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46119</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. Parse Server crashes when uploading a file without extension. This vulnerability has been patched in versions 5.5.6 and 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46123 | jumpserver is vulnerable to password brute-force protection bypass via arbitrary IP values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46123</link><description>jumpserver is an open source bastion machine, professional operation and maintenance security audit system that complies with 4A specifications. A flaw in the Core API allows attackers to bypass password brute-force protections by spoofing arbitrary IP addresses. By exploiting this vulnerability, attackers can effectively make unlimited password attempts by altering their apparent IP address for each request. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>