<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2489 | Insecure storage of sensitive information in NTFS Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2489</link><description>Insecure information storage vulnerability in NTFS Tools version 3.5.1. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to know the application password, stored in /Users/user/Library/Application Support/ntfs-tool/config.json.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2494 | Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2494</link><description>Unrestricted file upload to Softdial Contact Center of Sytel Ltd. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to upload files to the server via the ‘/softdial/phpconsole/upload.php’ endpoint, which is protected by basic HTTP authentication. The files are uploaded to a directory exposed by the web application, which could result in code execution, giving the attacker full control over the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2495 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2495</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Softdial Contact Center of Sytel Ltd. This vulnerability allows an attacker to upload XML files to the server with JavaScript code injected via the ‘/softdial/scheduler/save.php’ resource. The injected code will execute when the uploaded file is loaded via the ‘/softdial/scheduler/load.php’ resource and can redirect the victim to malicious sites or steal their login information to spoof their identity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2493 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2493</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Softdial Contact Center of Sytel Ltd. This vulnerability allows an attacker to manipulate the ‘id’ parameter of the ‘/softdial/scheduler/load.php’ endpoint to navigate beyond the intended directory. This can allow unauthorised access to sensitive files outside the expected scope, posing a security risk.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23943 | MB connect line: Cloud API access due to a lack of authentication for a critical function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23943</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain access to the cloud API due to a lack of authentication for a critical function in the affected devices. Availability is not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41975 | CODESYS (Edge) Gateway for Windows insecure default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41975</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain limited information of the PLC network but the user management of the PLCs prevents the actual access to the PLCs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0694 | CODESYS Control V3 removable media path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0694</link><description>Insufficient path validation in CODESYS Control allows low privileged attackers with physical access to gain full filesystem access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23942 | MB connect line: Configuration File on the client workstation is not encrypted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23942</link><description>A local user may find a configuration file on the client workstation with unencrypted sensitive data. This allows an attacker to impersonate the device or prevent the device from accessing the cloud portal which leads to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1468 | CODESYS Control V3 - OPC UA Server Authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1468</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain access to sensitive information including authentication information when using CODESYS OPC UA Server with the non-default Basic128Rsa15 security policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0755 | MongoDB C Driver bson library may be susceptible to buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0755</link><description>The various bson_append functions in the MongoDB C driver library may be susceptible to buffer overflow when performing operations that could result in a final BSON document which exceeds the maximum allowable size (INT32_MAX), resulting in a segmentation fault and possible application crash. This issue affected libbson versions prior to 1.27.5, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.1 and MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.16</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24306 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24306</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0.0_1101. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25220 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25220</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in +F FS010M versions prior to V2.0.1_1101. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a remote authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2262 | Logo Slider &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2262</link><description>The The Logo Slider – Logo Showcase, Logo Carousel, Logo Gallery and Client Logo Presentation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.3. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2473 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System Sign In index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2473</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Sign In. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2471 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System boat-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2471</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boat-details.php. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2472 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System Sign In index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2472</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Sign In. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29912 | CryptoLib Has Heap Buffer Overflow Due to Unsigned Integer Underflow in Crypto_TC_ProcessSecurity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29912</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. In versions 1.3.3 and prior, an unsigned integer underflow in the `Crypto_TC_ProcessSecurity` function of CryptoLib leads to a heap buffer overflow. The vulnerability is triggered when the `fl` (frame length) field in a Telecommand (TC) packet is set to 0. This underflow causes the frame length to be interpreted as 65535, resulting in out-of-bounds memory access. This critical vulnerability can be exploited to cause a denial of service (DoS) or potentially achieve remote code execution. Users of CryptoLib are advised to apply the recommended patch or avoid processing untrusted TC packets until a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29913 | CryptoLib&amp;#x27;s Crypto_TC_Prep_AAD Has Buffer Overflow Due to Integer Underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29913</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. A critical heap buffer overflow vulnerability was identified in the `Crypto_TC_Prep_AAD` function of CryptoLib versions 1.3.3 and prior. This vulnerability allows an attacker to trigger a Denial of Service (DoS) or potentially execute arbitrary code (RCE) by providing a maliciously crafted telecommand (TC) frame that causes an unsigned integer underflow. The vulnerability lies in the function `Crypto_TC_Prep_AAD`, specifically during the computation of `tc_mac_start_index`. The affected code incorrectly calculates the MAC start index without ensuring it remains within the bounds of the `ingest` buffer. When `tc_mac_start_index` underflows due to an incorrect length calculation, the function attempts to access an out-of-bounds memory location, leading to a segmentation fault. The vulnerability is still present in the repository as of commit `d3cc420ace96d02a5b7e83d88cbd2e48010d5723`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2420 | 猫宁i Morning cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2420</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in 猫宁i Morning up to bc782730c74ff080494f145cc363a0b4f43f7d3e. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29911 | CryptoLib Has Heap Buffer Overflow in Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29911</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. A critical heap buffer overflow vulnerability was identified in the `Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity` function of CryptoLib versions 1.3.3 and prior. This vulnerability allows an attacker to trigger a Denial of Service (DoS) or potentially execute arbitrary code (RCE) by providing a maliciously crafted AOS frame with an insufficient length. The vulnerability lies in the function `Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity`, specifically during the processing of the Frame Error Control Field (FECF). The affected code attempts to read from the `p_ingest` buffer at indices `current_managed_parameters_struct.max_frame_size - 2` and `current_managed_parameters_struct.max_frame_size - 1` without verifying if `len_ingest` is sufficiently large. This leads to a heap buffer overflow when `len_ingest` is smaller than `max_frame_size`. As of time of publication, no known patched versions exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29910 | CryptoLib&amp;#x27;s crypto_handle_incrementing_nontransmitted_counter Function has Memory Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29910</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. A memory leak vulnerability was identified in the `crypto_handle_incrementing_nontransmitted_counter` function of CryptoLib versions 1.3.3 and prior. This vulnerability can lead to resource exhaustion and degraded system performance over time, particularly in long-running processes or systems processing large volumes of data. The vulnerability is present in the `crypto_handle_incrementing_nontransmitted_counter` function within `crypto_tc.c`. The function allocates memory using `malloc` without ensuring the allocated memory is always freed. This issue can lead to resource exhaustion, reduced system performance, and potentially a Denial of Service (DoS) in environments where CryptoLib is used in long-running processes or with large volumes of data. Any system using CryptoLib, especially those handling high-throughput or continuous data streams, could be impacted. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29909 | CryptoLib&amp;#x27;s Crypto_TC_ApplySecurity() Has a Heap Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29909</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. In versions 1.3.3 and prior, a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in CryptoLib's `Crypto_TC_ApplySecurity()` allows an attacker to craft a malicious TC frame that causes out-of-bounds memory writes. This can result in denial of service (DoS) or, under certain conditions, remote code execution (RCE). Any application or system that relies on CryptoLib for Telecommand (TC) processing and does not strictly validate incoming TC frames is at risk. This includes satellite ground stations or mission control software where attackers can inject malformed frames. A patch is available at commit c7e8a8745ff4b5e9bd7e500e91358e86d5abedcc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2419 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertFeedback.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2419</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /InsertFeedback.php. The manipulation of the argument txtName/txtEmail/txtMobile/txtFeedback leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29781 | Bare Metal Operator (BMO) can expose any secret from other namespaces via BMCEventSubscription CRD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29781</link><description>The Bare Metal Operator (BMO) implements a Kubernetes API for managing bare metal hosts in Metal3. Baremetal Operator enables users to load Secret from arbitrary namespaces upon deployment of the namespace scoped Custom Resource `BMCEventSubscription`. Prior to versions 0.8.1 and 0.9.1, an adversary Kubernetes account with only namespace level roles (e.g. a tenant controlling a namespace) may create a `BMCEventSubscription` in his authorized namespace and then load Secrets from his unauthorized namespaces to his authorized namespace via the Baremetal Operator, causing Secret Leakage. The patch makes BMO refuse to read Secrets from other namespace than where the corresponding BMH resource is. The patch does not change the `BMCEventSubscription` API in BMO, but stricter validation will fail the request at admission time. It will also prevent the controller reading such Secrets, in case the BMCES CR has already been deployed. The issue exists for all versions of BMO, and is patched in BMO releases v0.9.1 and v0.8.1. Prior upgrading to patched BMO version, duplicate any existing Secret pointed to by `BMCEventSubscription`'s `httpHeadersRef` to the same namespace where the corresponding BMH exists. After upgrade, remove the old Secrets. As a workaround, the operator can configure BMO RBAC to be namespace scoped, instead of cluster scoped, to prevent BMO from accessing Secrets from other namespaces, and/or use `WATCH_NAMESPACE` configuration option to limit BMO to single namespace.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40635 | containerd has an integer overflow in User ID handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40635</link><description>containerd is an open-source container runtime. A bug was found in containerd prior to versions 1.6.38, 1.7.27, and 2.0.4 where containers launched with a User set as a `UID:GID` larger than the maximum 32-bit signed integer can cause an overflow condition where the container ultimately runs as root (UID 0). This could cause unexpected behavior for environments that require containers to run as a non-root user. This bug has been fixed in containerd 1.6.38, 1.7.27, and 2.04. As a workaround, ensure that only trusted images are used and that only trusted users have permissions to import images.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2398 | China Mobile P22g-CIac CLI su Command default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2398</link><description>A vulnerability was found in China Mobile P22g-CIac, ZXWT-MIG-P4G4V, ZXWT-MIG-P8G8V, GT3200-4G4P and GT3200-8G8P up to 20250305. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component CLI su Command Handler. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2397 | China Mobile P22g-CIac Telnet Service improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2397</link><description>A vulnerability was found in China Mobile P22g-CIac, ZXWT-MIG-P4G4V, ZXWT-MIG-P8G8V, GT3200-4G4P and GT3200-8G8P up to 20250305. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2393 | code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System salut_del.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2393</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/salut_del.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29426 | Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/class.php via the id and cy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29426</link><description>Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/class.php via the id and cys parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26393 | SolarWinds Service Desk Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26393</link><description>SolarWinds Service Desk is affected by a broken access control vulnerability. The issue allows authenticated users to escalate privileges, leading to unauthorized data manipulation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2392 | code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System activate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2392</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/activate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44276 | This issue was addressed by using HTTPS when sending information over the network. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. A user i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44276</link><description>This issue was addressed by using HTTPS when sending information over the network. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. A user in a privileged network position may be able to leak sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54525 | A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54525</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. Restoring a maliciously crafted backup file may lead to modification of protected system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54559 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54559</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54565 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54565</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24185 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24185</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing a maliciously crafted file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25914 | SQL injection vulnerability in Online Exam Mastering System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the fid parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25914</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Online Exam Mastering System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the fid parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2391 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System Admin Login Page admin_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2391</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/admin_login.php of the component Admin Login Page. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0495 | Secrets leakage to telemetry endpoint via cache backend configuration via buildx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0495</link><description>Buildx is a Docker CLI plugin that extends build capabilities using BuildKit.

Cache backends support credentials by setting secrets directly as attribute values in cache-to/cache-from configuration. When supplied as user input, these secure values may be inadvertently captured in OpenTelemetry traces as part of the arguments and flags for the traced CLI command. OpenTelemetry traces are also saved in BuildKit daemon's history records.


This vulnerability does not impact secrets passed to the Github cache backend via environment variables or registry authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8510 | N-central Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8510</link><description>N-central is vulnerable to a path traversal that allows unintended access to the Apache Tomcat WEB-INF directory. Customer data is not exposed. 

This vulnerability is present in all deployments of N-central prior to N-central 2024.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2390 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System add_donor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2390</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user_dashboard/add_donor.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29425 | Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in exam_save.php via the parameters member and firs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29425</link><description>Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in exam_save.php via the parameters member and first.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26042 | Uptime Kuma &gt;== 1.23.0 has a ReDoS vulnerability, specifically when an administrator creates a notification through the web service. If a st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26042</link><description>Uptime Kuma &gt;== 1.23.0 has a ReDoS vulnerability, specifically when an administrator creates a notification through the web service. If a string is provided it triggers catastrophic backtracking in the regular expression, leading to a ReDoS attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29427 | Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in profile.php via the member_first a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29427</link><description>Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in profile.php via the member_first and member_last parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2389 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System add_city.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2389</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_city.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44866 | A buffer overflow in the GuitarPro1::read function of MuseScore Studio v4.3.2 allows attackers to to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44866</link><description>A buffer overflow in the GuitarPro1::read function of MuseScore Studio v4.3.2 allows attackers to to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via opening a crafted GuitarPro file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48831 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.6.x, contain(s) a Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48831</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.6.x, contain(s) a Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2388 | Keytop 路内停车收费系统 API getParks improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2388</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keytop 路内停车收费系统 2.7.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /saas/commonApi/park/getParks of the component API. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22472 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22472</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22473 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22473</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49559 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Use of Default Password vulnerability. A lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49559</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Use of Default Password vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49561 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49561</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29429 | Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/program.php via the id, cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29429</link><description>Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/program.php via the id, code, and name parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2387 | SourceCodester Online Food Ordering System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2387</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Food Ordering System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=add_to_cart. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48017 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48017</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26125 | An exposed ioctl in the IMFForceDelete driver of IObit Malware Fighter v12.1.0 allows attackers to arbitrarily delete files and escalate pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26125</link><description>An exposed ioctl in the IMFForceDelete driver of IObit Malware Fighter v12.1.0 allows attackers to arbitrarily delete files and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29430 | Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/room.php via the id and rom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29430</link><description>Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/room.php via the id and rome parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48015 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48015</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48828 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Privilege Management vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48828</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Privilege Management vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22474 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22474</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Server-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48830 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48830</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29431 | Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/department.php via the id, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29431</link><description>Code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /pages/department.php via the id, code, and name parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2386 | PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System serviceman-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2386</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /serviceman-search.php. The manipulation of the argument location leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48013 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48013</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.4.x, 10.5.5.x, 10.5.6.x, 10.6.0.x, contain(s) an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25684 | A lack of validation in the path parameter (/download) of GL-INet Beryl AX GL-MT3000 v4.7.0 allows attackers to download arbitrary files fro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25684</link><description>A lack of validation in the path parameter (/download) of GL-INet Beryl AX GL-MT3000 v4.7.0 allows attackers to download arbitrary files from the device's file system via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25685 | An issue was discovered in GL-INet Beryl AX GL-MT3000 v4.7.0. Attackers are able to download arbitrary files from the device's file system v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25685</link><description>An issue was discovered in GL-INet Beryl AX GL-MT3000 v4.7.0. Attackers are able to download arbitrary files from the device's file system via adding symbolic links on an external drive used as a samba share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2241 | Hive: exposure of vcenter credentials via clusterprovision in hive / mce / acm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2241</link><description>A flaw was found in Hive, a component of Multicluster Engine (MCE) and Advanced Cluster Management (ACM). This vulnerability causes VCenter credentials to be exposed in the ClusterProvision object after provisioning a VSphere cluster. Users with read access to ClusterProvision objects can extract sensitive credentials even if they do not have direct access to Kubernetes Secrets. This issue can lead to unauthorized VCenter access, cluster management, and privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2385 | code-projects Modern Bag login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2385</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Modern Bag 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument userEmail/userPassword leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2384 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System Parameter InsertCustomer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2384</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /InsertCustomer.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument txtName/txtAddress/cmbCity/txtEmail/cmbGender/txtBirthDate/txtUserName2/txtPassword2 leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2383 | PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2383</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /doctor/search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30143 | Rule 3000216 (before version 2) in Akamai App &amp; API Protector (with Akamai ASE) before 2024-12-10 does not properly consider JavaScript vari...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30143</link><description>Rule 3000216 (before version 2) in Akamai App &amp; API Protector (with Akamai ASE) before 2024-12-10 does not properly consider JavaScript variable assignment to built-in functions and properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1774 | Logs manipulation in BotSense</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1774</link><description>Incorrect string encoding vulnerability in NASK - PIB BotSense allows injection of an additional field separator character or value in the content of some fields of the generated event. A field with additional field separator characters or values can be included in the "extraData" field.This issue affects BotSense in versions before 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2382 | PHPGurukul Online Banquet Booking System booking-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2382</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Banquet Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/booking-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25650 | An issue in the storage of NFC card data in Dorset DG 201 Digital Lock H5_433WBSK_v2.2_220605 allows attackers to produce cloned NFC cards t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25650</link><description>An issue in the storage of NFC card data in Dorset DG 201 Digital Lock H5_433WBSK_v2.2_220605 allows attackers to produce cloned NFC cards to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27512 | Zincati allows unprivileged access to rpm-ostree D-Bus `Deploy()` and `FinalizeDeployment()` methods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27512</link><description>Zincati is an auto-update agent for Fedora CoreOS hosts. Zincati ships a polkit rule which allows the `zincati` system user to use the actions `org.projectatomic.rpmostree1.deploy` to deploy updates to the system and `org.projectatomic.rpmostree1.finalize-deployment` to reboot the system into the deployed update. Since Zincati v0.0.24, this polkit rule contains a logic error which broadens access of those polkit actions to any unprivileged user rather than just the `zincati` system user. In practice, this means that any unprivileged user with access to the system D-Bus socket is able to deploy older Fedora CoreOS versions (which may have other known vulnerabilities). Note that rpm-ostree enforces that the selected version must be from the same branch the system is currently on so this cannot directly be used to deploy an attacker-controlled update payload. This primarily impacts users running untrusted workloads with access to the system D-Bus socket. Note that in general, untrusted workloads should not be given this access, whether containerized or not. By default, containers do not have access to the system D-Bus socket. The logic error is fixed in Zincati v0.0.30. A workaround is to manually add a following polkit rule, instructions for which are available in the GitHub Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2381 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System search-pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2381</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/search-pass.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1398 | macOS TCC Bypass via Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1398</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.10.0 explicitly declared unnecessary macOS entitlements which allows an attacker with remote access to bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC) via code injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25612 | FS Inc S3150-8T2F prior to version S3150-8T2F_2.2.0D_135103 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Time Range Configuration func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25612</link><description>FS Inc S3150-8T2F prior to version S3150-8T2F_2.2.0D_135103 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Time Range Configuration functionality of the administration interface. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript into the "Time Range Name" field, which is improperly sanitized. When this input is saved, it is later executed in the browser of any user accessing the affected page, including administrators, resulting in arbitrary script execution in the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25621 | Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, which allows teachers to take attendance of fellow teachers. This affected e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25621</link><description>Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, which allows teachers to take attendance of fellow teachers. This affected endpoint is /courses/teacher/index?teacher_id=2&amp;amp;semester_id=1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25618 | Incorrect Access Control in Unifiedtransform 2.0 leads to Privilege Escalation allowing the change of Section Name and Room Number by Teache...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25618</link><description>Incorrect Access Control in Unifiedtransform 2.0 leads to Privilege Escalation allowing the change of Section Name and Room Number by Teachers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26127 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Send for Approval function of FileCloud v23.241.2 allows attackers to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26127</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Send for Approval function of FileCloud v23.241.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2380 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2380</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0598 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Relations in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0598</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Relations in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0599 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Document Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0599</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Document Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0600 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Product Explorer in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0600</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Product Explorer in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0601 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Issue Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0601</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Issue Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0826 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3D Navigate in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0826</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3D Navigate in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0827 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DPlay in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0827</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DPlay in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0828 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Engineering Release in ENOVIA Product Engineering Specialist from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0828</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Engineering Release in ENOVIA Product Engineering Specialist from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0829 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3D Markup in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0829</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3D Markup in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0830 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Meeting Management in ENOVIA Change Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0830</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Meeting Management in ENOVIA Change Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0832 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Project Gantt in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0832</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Project Gantt in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0833 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Route Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0833</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Route Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6697 | An Improper Neutralization of Input vulnerability affecting FortiGate version 6.2.0 through 6.2.1, 6.0.0 through 6.0.6 in the hostname param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6697</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input vulnerability affecting FortiGate version 6.2.0 through 6.2.1, 6.0.0 through 6.0.6 in the hostname parameter of a DHCP packet under DHCP monitor page may allow an unauthenticated attacker in the same network as the FortiGate to perform a Stored Cross Site Scripting attack (XSS) by sending a crafted DHCP packet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-9295 | FortiOS 6.2 running AV engine version 6.00142 and below, FortiOS 6.4 running AV engine version 6.00144 and below and FortiClient 6.2 running...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9295</link><description>FortiOS 6.2 running AV engine version 6.00142 and below, FortiOS 6.4 running AV engine version 6.00144 and below and FortiClient 6.2 running AV engine version 6.00137 and below may not immediately detect certain types of malformed or non-standard RAR archives, potentially containing malicious files. Based on the samples provided, FortiClient will detect the malicious files upon trying extraction by real-time scanning and FortiGate will detect the malicious archive if Virus Outbreak Prevention is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9055 | DPA Countermeasures need reseeding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9055</link><description>The DPA countermeasures on Silicon Labs' Series 2 devices are not reseeded periodically as they should be. This may allow an attacker to eventually extract secret keys through a DPA attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0595 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0595</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0596 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Bookmark Editor in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0596</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Bookmark Editor in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2379 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System create-pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2379</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /create-pass.php. The manipulation of the argument visname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29787 | zip Vulnerable to Incorrect Path Canonicalization During Archive Extraction, Leading to Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29787</link><description>`zip` is a zip library for rust which supports reading and writing of simple ZIP files. In the archive extraction routine of affected versions of the `zip` crate starting with version 1.3.0 and prior to version 2.3.0, symbolic links earlier in the archive are allowed to be used for later files in the archive without validation of the final canonicalized path, allowing maliciously crafted archives to overwrite arbitrary files in the file system when extracted. Users who extract untrusted archive files using the following high-level API method may be affected and critical files on the system may be overwritten with arbitrary file permissions, which can potentially lead to code execution. Version 2.3.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29788 | Sylius PayPal Plugin Payment Amount Manipulation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29788</link><description>The Syliud PayPal Plugin is the Sylius Core Team’s plugin for the PayPal Commerce Platform. A vulnerability in versions prior to 1.6.1, 1.7.1, and 2.0.1 allows users to manipulate the final payment amount processed by PayPal. If a user modifies the item quantity in their shopping cart after initiating the PayPal Express Checkout process, PayPal will not receive the updated total amount. As a result, PayPal captures only the initially transmitted amount, while Sylius incorrectly considers the order fully paid based on the modified total. This flaw can be exploited both accidentally and intentionally, potentially enabling fraud by allowing customers to pay less than the actual order value. Attackers can intentionally pay less than the actual total order amount, business owners may suffer financial losses due to underpaid orders, and integrity of payment processing is compromised. The issue is fixed in versions 1.6.1, 1.7.1, 2.0.1, and above. To resolve the problem in the end application without updating to the newest patches, there is a need to overwrite `ProcessPayPalOrderAction`, `CompletePayPalOrderFromPaymentPageAction`, and `CaptureAction` with modified logic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-15706 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation in the SSL VPN portal of FortiProxy version 2.0.0, version 1.2.9 and below an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15706</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation in the SSL VPN portal of FortiProxy version 2.0.0, version 1.2.9 and below and FortiOS version 6.2.1 and below, version 6.0.8 and below, version 5.6.12 may allow a remote authenticated attacker to perform a stored cross site scripting attack (XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-17659 | A use of hard-coded cryptographic key vulnerability in FortiSIEM version 5.2.6 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain SSH acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17659</link><description>A use of hard-coded cryptographic key vulnerability in FortiSIEM version 5.2.6 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain SSH access to the supervisor as the restricted user "tunneluser" by leveraging knowledge of the private key from another installation or a firmware image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-29010 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability in FortiOS version 6.2.4 and below, version 6.0.10 and belowmay ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29010</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability in FortiOS version 6.2.4 and below, version 6.0.10 and belowmay allow remote authenticated actors to read the SSL VPN events log entries of users in other VDOMs by  executing "get vpn ssl monitor" from the CLI. The sensitive data includes usernames, user groups, and IP address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22126 | A use of hard-coded password vulnerability in FortiWLC version 8.5.2 and below, version 8.4.8 and below, version 8.3.3 to 8.3.2, version 8.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22126</link><description>A use of hard-coded password vulnerability in FortiWLC version 8.5.2 and below, version 8.4.8 and below, version 8.3.3 to 8.3.2, version 8.2.7 to 8.2.6 may allow a local, authenticated attacker to connect to the managed Access Point (Meru AP and FortiAP-U) as root using the default hard-coded username and password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26087 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation in FortiWLC version 8.6.0, version 8.5.3 and below, version 8.4.8 and below, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26087</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation in FortiWLC version 8.6.0, version 8.5.3 and below, version 8.4.8 and below, version 8.3.3 web interface may allow both authenticated remote attackers and non-authenticated attackers in the same network as the appliance to perform a stored cross site scripting attack (XSS) via injecting malicious payloads in different locations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-32584 | An improper access control (CWE-284) vulnerability in FortiWLC version 8.6.0, version 8.5.3 and below, version 8.4.8 and below, version 8.3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32584</link><description>An improper access control (CWE-284) vulnerability in FortiWLC version 8.6.0, version 8.5.3 and below, version 8.4.8 and below, version 8.3.3 and below, version 8.2.7 to 8.2.4, version 8.1.3 may allow an unauthenticated and remote attacker to access certain areas of the web management CGI functionality by just specifying the correct URL.  The vulnerability applies only to limited CGI resources and might allow the unauthorized party to access configuration details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54027 | A Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability [CWE-321] in FortiSandbox version 4.4.6 and below, version 4.2.7 and below, version 4.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54027</link><description>A Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability [CWE-321] in FortiSandbox version 4.4.6 and below, version 4.2.7 and below, version 4.0.5 and below, version 3.2.4 and below, version 3.1.5 and below, version 3.0.7 to 3.0.5 may allow a privileged attacker with super-admin profile and CLI access to read sensitive data via CLI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27102 | Agate vulnerable to HTML injection in user signup - Administrator phishing risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27102</link><description>Agate is central authentication server software for OBiBa epidemiology applications. Prior to version 3.3.0, when registering for an Agate account, arbitrary HTML code can be injected into a user's first and last name. This HTML is then rendered in the email sent to administrative users. The Agate service account sends this email and appears trustworthy, making this a significant risk for phishing attacks. Administrative users are impacted, as they can be targeted by unauthenticated users. Version 3.3.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29786 | Memory Exhaustion in Expr Parser with Unrestricted Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29786</link><description>Expr is an expression language and expression evaluation for Go. Prior to version 1.17.0, if the Expr expression parser is given an unbounded input string, it will attempt to compile the entire string and generate an Abstract Syntax Tree (AST) node for each part of the expression. In scenarios where input size isn’t limited, a malicious or inadvertent extremely large expression can consume excessive memory as the parser builds a huge AST. This can ultimately lead to*excessive memory usage and an Out-Of-Memory (OOM) crash of the process. This issue is relatively uncommon and will only manifest when there are no restrictions on the input size, i.e. the expression length is allowed to grow arbitrarily large. In typical use cases where inputs are bounded or validated, this problem would not occur. The problem has been patched in the latest versions of the Expr library. The fix introduces compile-time limits on the number of AST nodes and memory usage during parsing, preventing any single expression from exhausting resources. Users should upgrade to Expr version 1.17.0 or later, as this release includes the new node budget and memory limit safeguards. Upgrading to v1.17.0 ensures that extremely deep or large expressions are detected and safely aborted during compilation, avoiding the OOM condition. For users who cannot immediately upgrade, the recommended workaround is to impose an input size restriction before parsing. In practice, this means validating or limiting the length of expression strings that your application will accept. For example, set a maximum allowable number of characters (or nodes) for any expression and reject or truncate inputs that exceed this limit. By ensuring no unbounded-length expression is ever fed into the parser, one can prevent the parser from constructing a pathologically large AST and avoid potential memory exhaustion. In short, pre-validate and cap input size as a safeguard in the absence of the patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2378 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System download-medical-cards.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2378</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /download-medical-cards.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2377 | SourceCodester Vehicle Management System confirmbooking.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /confirmbooking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting product names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2401 | Buffer overflow in Immunity Debugger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2401</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in Immunity Debugger affecting version 1.85, its exploitation could allow a local attacker to execute arbitrary code, due to the lack of proper boundary checking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2376 | viames Pair Framework PHP Object UserRemember.php getCookieContent deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2376</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in viames Pair Framework up to 1.9.11 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getCookieContent of the file /src/UserRemember.php of the component PHP Object Handler. The manipulation of the argument cookieName leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 12:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2375 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System Admin Profile Page profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2375</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /profile.php of the component Admin Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 11:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2374 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2374</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument aid/adminname/mobilenumber/email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 11:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2373 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System check_availability.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2373</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /check_availability.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnumber/employeeid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2202 | Broken access control vulnerability in the Innovación y Cualificación local administration plugin ajax.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2202</link><description>Broken access control vulnerability in the Innovación y Cualificación local administration plugin ajax.php. This vulnerability allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information about other users such as id, name, login and email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2199 | SQL injection vulnerability in the Innovación y Cualificación local administration plugin ajax.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2199</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the Innovación y Cualificación local administration plugin ajax.php. This vulnerability allows an attacker to obtain, update and delete data from the database by injecting an SQL query in ‘searchActionsToUpdate’, ‘searchSpecialitiesPending’, ‘searchSpecialitiesLinked’, ‘searchUsersToUpdateProfile’, ‘training_action_data’, ‘showContinuingTrainingCourses’ and ‘showUsersToEdit’ in /local/administration/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2200 | SQL injection vulnerability in the Innovación y Cualificación local administration plugin ajax.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2200</link><description>QL injection vulnerability in the IcProgress Innovación y Cualificación plugin. This vulnerability allows an attacker to obtain, update and delete data from the database by injecting an SQL query on the parameters user, id, idGroup, start_date and end_date in the endpoint /report/icprogreso/generar_blocks.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2201 | Broken access control vulnerability in the Innovación y Cualificación local administration plugin ajax.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2201</link><description>Broken access control vulnerability in the IcProgress Innovación y Cualificación plugin. This vulnerability allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information about other users such as public IP addresses, messages with other users and more.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2372 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System Password Recovery Page password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2372</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /password-recovery.php of the component Password Recovery Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2371 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System Registered Mobile Number Search registered-user-testing.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2371</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registered-user-testing.php of the component Registered Mobile Number Search. The manipulation of the argument regmobilenumber leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12971 | QuickShell Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12971</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command vulnerability allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Pandora FMS from 700 to 777.6</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12992 | Remote Code Execution leads to Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12992</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command vulnerability allows OS Command Injection via RCE. 

This issue affects Pandora FMS from 700 to 777.6

.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2370 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setWiFiExtenderConfig stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1800T up to 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWiFiExtenderConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument apcliSsid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2369 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setPasswordCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1800T up to 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setPasswordCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument admpass leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 08:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2368 | WebAssembly wabt Malformed File binary-reader-interp.cc OnExport heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WebAssembly wabt 1.0.36 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function wabt::interp::(anonymous namespace)::BinaryReaderInterp::OnExport of the file wabt/src/interp/binary-reader-interp.cc of the component Malformed File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 08:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2367 | Oiwtech OIW-2431APGN-HP Personal Script Submenu formScript os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2367</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Oiwtech OIW-2431APGN-HP 2.5.3-B20131128 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formScript of the component Personal Script Submenu. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1724 | Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1724</link><description>Zohocorp's ManageEngine Analytics Plus and Zoho Analytics on-premise versions older than 6130 are vulnerable to an AD only account takeover because of a hardcoded sensitive token.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2366 | gougucms Add Department Page add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2366</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in gougucms 4.08.18. This affects the function add of the file /admin/department/add of the component Add Department Page. The manipulation of the argument title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2365 | crmeb_java WeChatMessageController.java webHook xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2365</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in crmeb_java up to 1.3.4. Affected by this issue is the function webHook of the file WeChatMessageController.java. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2364 | lenve VBlog ArticleService.java addNewArticle cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2364</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in lenve VBlog up to 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function addNewArticle of the file blogserver/src/main/java/org/sang/service/ArticleService.java. The manipulation of the argument mdContent/htmlContent leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2396 | e-Excellence U-Office Force - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2396</link><description>The U-Office Force from e-Excellence has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2395 | e-Excellence U-Office Force - Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2395</link><description>The U-Office Force from e-Excellence has an Improper Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to use a particular API and alter cookies to log in as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2363 | lenve VBlog ArticleController.java uploadImg path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2363</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in lenve VBlog up to 1.0.0. Affected is the function uploadImg of the file blogserver/src/main/java/org/sang/controller/ArticleController.java. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2362 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2362</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnum leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2361 | Mercurial SCM Web Interface cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2361</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mercurial SCM 4.5.3/71.19.145.211. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2360 | D-Link DIR-823G UPnP Service HNAP1 SetUpnpSettings improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2360</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-823G 1.0.2B05_20181207. Affected by this vulnerability is the function SetUpnpSettings of the file /HNAP1/ of the component UPnP Service. The manipulation of the argument SOAPAction leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2359 | D-Link DIR-823G DDNS Service HNAP1 SetDDNSSettings improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2359</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DIR-823G 1.0.2B05_20181207. Affected is the function SetDDNSSettings of the file /HNAP1/ of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation of the argument SOAPAction leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2358 | Shenzhen Mingyuan Cloud Technology Mingyuan Real Estate ERP System HTTP Header Service.asmx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2358</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shenzhen Mingyuan Cloud Technology Mingyuan Real Estate ERP System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Kfxt/Service.asmx of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2357 | DCMTK dcmjpls JPEG-LS Decoder memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2357</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DCMTK 3.6.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component dcmjpls JPEG-LS Decoder. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 3239a7915. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2356 | BlackVue App API deviceDelete get request method with sensitive query strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlackVue App 3.65 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function deviceDelete of the component API Handler. The manipulation leads to use of get request method with sensitive query strings. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2355 | BlackVue App API Endpoint credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlackVue App 3.65 on Android and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component API Endpoint Handler. The manipulation of the argument BCS_TOKEN/SECRET_KEY leads to unprotected storage of credentials. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2354 | VAM Virtual Airlines Manager index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2354</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in VAM Virtual Airlines Manager 2.6.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /vam/index.php. The manipulation of the argument registry_id/plane_icao/hub_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30089 | gurk (aka gurk-rs) through 0.6.3 mishandles ANSI escape sequences.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30089</link><description>gurk (aka gurk-rs) through 0.6.3 mishandles ANSI escape sequences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2353 | VAM Virtual Airlines Manager HTTP GET Parameter index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in VAM Virtual Airlines Manager up to 2.6.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /vam/index.php of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID/registry_id/plane_icao leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 23:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2352 | StarSea99 starsea-mall Backend save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2352</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in StarSea99 starsea-mall 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/indexConfigs/save of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument categoryName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 23:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2351 | DayCloud StudentManage Login Endpoint adminScoreUrl sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2351</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in DayCloud StudentManage 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/adminScoreUrl of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument query leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 22:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2350 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 upload_file unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /action/upload_file. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2349 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 Password Hash passwd weak password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2349</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/passwd of the component Password Hash Handler. The manipulation leads to password hash with insufficient computational effort. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2348 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 HTTP/RTSP event information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /mnt/extsd/event/ of the component HTTP/RTSP. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2347 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 Device Registration default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Device Registration. The manipulation of the argument Password with the input qwertyuiop leads to use of default password. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2346 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 Domain origin validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2346</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Domain Handler. The manipulation of the argument Domain Name leads to origin validation error. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2345 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2345</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as very critical, was found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2344 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 API Endpoint missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2344</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2343 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 Device Pairing hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2343</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Device Pairing. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2342 | IROAD X5 Mobile App API Endpoint hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2342</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in IROAD X5 Mobile App up to 5.2.5 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 16:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2341 | IROAD Dash Cam X5 SSID default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2341</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 up to 20250203. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component SSID. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 14:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2340 | otale Tale Blog Site Settings save saveOptions cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2340</link><description>A vulnerability was found in otale Tale Blog 2.0.5. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function saveOptions of the file /options/save of the component Site Settings. The manipulation of the argument Site Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2339 | otale Tale Blog logs improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in otale Tale Blog 2.0.5. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /%61dmin/api/logs. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2338 | tbeu matio io.c strdup_vprintf heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2338</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in tbeu matio 1.5.28. Affected is the function strdup_vprintf of the file src/io.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 12:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2337 | tbeu matio mat.c Mat_VarPrint heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in tbeu matio 1.5.28. This issue affects the function Mat_VarPrint of the file src/mat.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 09:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13126 | Download Manager &amp;lt; 3.3.07 - Unauthenticated Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13126</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.3.07 doesn't prevent directory listing on web servers that don't use htaccess, allowing unauthorized access of files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13602 | Poll Maker &amp;lt; 5.5.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13602</link><description>The Poll Maker  WordPress plugin before 5.5.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1619 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1619</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1620 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1620</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1621 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1621</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1622 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1622</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1623 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1623</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1624 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1624</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24856 | An issue was discovered in the oidc (aka OpenID Connect Authentication) extension before 4.0.0 for TYPO3. The account linking logic allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24856</link><description>An issue was discovered in the oidc (aka OpenID Connect Authentication) extension before 4.0.0 for TYPO3. The account linking logic allows a pre-hijacking attack, leading to Account Takeover. The attack can only be exploited if the following requirements are met: (1) an attacker can anticipate the e-mail address of the user, (2) an attacker can register a public frontend user account using that e-mail address before the user's first OIDC login, and (3) the IDP returns an email field containing the e-mail address of the user,</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58103 | Square Wire before 5.2.0 does not enforce a recursion limit on nested groups in ByteArrayProtoReader32.kt and ProtoReader.kt.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58103</link><description>Square Wire before 5.2.0 does not enforce a recursion limit on nested groups in ByteArrayProtoReader32.kt and ProtoReader.kt.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30077 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.28 allows an index out-of-range panic in asn1/aper GetBitString via a zero value of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30077</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.28 allows an index out-of-range panic in asn1/aper GetBitString via a zero value of numBits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2335 | Drivin Soluções API registerSchool cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Drivin Soluções up to 20250226. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/school/registerSchool of the component API Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30076 | Koha before 24.11.02 allows admins to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the tools/scheduler.pl report parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30076</link><description>Koha before 24.11.02 allows admins to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the tools/scheduler.pl report parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30074 | Alludo Parallels Desktop before 19.4.2 and 20.x before 20.2.2 for macOS on Intel platforms allows privilege escalation to root via the VM cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30074</link><description>Alludo Parallels Desktop before 19.4.2 and 20.x before 20.2.2 for macOS on Intel platforms allows privilege escalation to root via the VM creation routine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 02:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-49737 | In X.Org X server 20.11 through 21.1.16, when a client application uses easystroke for mouse gestures, the main thread modifies various data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-49737</link><description>In X.Org X server 20.11 through 21.1.16, when a client application uses easystroke for mouse gestures, the main thread modifies various data structures used by the input thread without acquiring a lock, aka a race condition. In particular, AttachDevice in dix/devices.c does not acquire an input lock.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 01:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>