<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-49321 | Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because scanning a crafted file takes a long time, and causes the scanner to hang. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49321</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because scanning a crafted file takes a long time, and causes the scanner to hang. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant 1.0.35-1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49322 | Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because there is an unpack handler crash that can lead to a scanning engine crash. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49322</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service because there is an unpack handler crash that can lead to a scanning engine crash. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant 1.0.35-1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6300 | SourceCodester Best Courier Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6300</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument page with the input &lt;/TiTlE&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(1)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6301 | SourceCodester Best Courier Management System GET Parameter parcel_list.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6301</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file parcel_list.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id with the input &lt;/TiTlE&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(1)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246127.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6298 | Apryse iText PdfDocument.java main array index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6298</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Apryse iText 8.0.2. This vulnerability affects the function main of the file PdfDocument.java. The manipulation leads to improper validation of array index. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246124. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6299 | Apryse iText Reference Table PdfDocument.java memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6299</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Apryse iText 8.0.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file PdfDocument.java of the component Reference Table Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246125 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6297 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System Search Report Page patient-search-report.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6297</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file patient-search-report.php of the component Search Report Page. The manipulation of the argument Search By Patient Name with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246123.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 22:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6296 | osCommerce Instant Message compare cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6296</link><description>A vulnerability was found in osCommerce 4. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /catalog/compare of the component Instant Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument compare with the input 40dz4iq"&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt;zohkx leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-246122 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 21:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49312 | Precision Bridge PrecisionBridge.exe (aka the thick client) before 7.3.21 allows an integrity violation in which the same license key is use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49312</link><description>Precision Bridge PrecisionBridge.exe (aka the thick client) before 7.3.21 allows an integrity violation in which the same license key is used on multiple systems, via vectors involving a Process Hacker memory dump, error message inspection, and modification of a MAC address.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 21:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6293 | Prototype Pollution in robinbuschmann/sequelize-typescript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6293</link><description>Prototype Pollution in GitHub repository robinbuschmann/sequelize-typescript prior to 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 20:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49298 | OpenZFS through 2.1.13 and 2.2.x through 2.2.1, in certain scenarios involving applications that try to rely on efficient copying of file da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49298</link><description>OpenZFS through 2.1.13 and 2.2.x through 2.2.1, in certain scenarios involving applications that try to rely on efficient copying of file data, can replace file contents with zero-valued bytes and thus potentially disable security mechanisms. NOTE: this issue is not always security related, but can be security related in realistic situations. A possible example is cp, from a recent GNU Core Utilities (coreutils) version, when attempting to preserve a rule set for denying unauthorized access. (One might use cp when configuring access control, such as with the /etc/hosts.deny file specified in the IBM Support reference.) NOTE: this issue occurs less often in version 2.2.1, and in versions before 2.1.4, because of the default configuration in those versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 19:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6277 | Libtiff: out-of-memory in tiffopen via a craft file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6277</link><description>An out-of-memory flaw was found in libtiff. Passing a crafted tiff file to TIFFOpen() API may allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a craft input with size smaller than 379 KB.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48707 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in codeigniter4/shield</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48707</link><description>CodeIgniter Shield is an authentication and authorization provider for CodeIgniter 4. The `secretKey` value is an important key for HMAC SHA256 authentication and in affected versions was stored in the database in cleartext form. If a malicious person somehow had access to the data in the database, they could use the key and secretKey for HMAC SHA256 authentication to send requests impersonating that corresponding user. This issue has been addressed in version 1.0.0-beta.8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 17:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48312 | Authentication bypass using an empty token in capsule-proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48312</link><description>capsule-proxy is a reverse proxy for the capsule operator project. Affected versions are subject to a privilege escalation vulnerability which is based on a missing check if the user is authenticated based on the `TokenReview` result. All the clusters running with the `anonymous-auth` Kubernetes API Server setting disable (set to `false`) are affected since it would be possible to bypass the token review mechanism, interacting with the upper Kubernetes API Server. This privilege escalation cannot be exploited if you're relying only on client certificates (SSL/TLS). This vulnerability has been addressed in version 0.4.6. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 17:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48708 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log in codeigniter4/shield</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48708</link><description>CodeIgniter Shield is an authentication and authorization provider for CodeIgniter 4. In affected versions successful login attempts are recorded with the raw tokens stored in the log table. If a malicious person somehow views the data in the log table they can obtain a raw token which can then be used to send a request with that user's authority. This issue has been addressed in version 1.0.0-beta.8. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable logging for successful login attempts by the configuration files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 17:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48711 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability in google-translate-api-browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48711</link><description>google-translate-api-browser is an npm package which interfaces with the google translate web api. A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability is present in applications utilizing the `google-translate-api-browser` package and exposing the `translateOptions` to the end user. An attacker can set a malicious `tld`, causing the application to return unsafe URLs pointing towards local resources. The `translateOptions.tld` field is not properly sanitized before being placed in the Google translate URL. This can allow an attacker with control over the `translateOptions` to set the `tld` to a payload such as `@127.0.0.1`. This causes the full URL to become `https://translate.google.@127.0.0.1/...`, where `translate.google.` is the username used to connect to localhost. An attacker can send requests within internal networks and the local host. Should any HTTPS application be present on the internal network with a vulnerability exploitable via a GET call, then it would be possible to exploit this using this vulnerability. This issue has been addressed in release version 4.1.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 17:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48712 | User authorization bug leading to privilege escalation in warpgate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48712</link><description>Warpgate is an open source SSH, HTTPS and MySQL bastion host for Linux. In affected versions there is a privilege escalation vulnerability through a non-admin user's account. Limited users can impersonate another user's account if only single-factor authentication is configured. If a user knows an admin username, opens the login screen and attempts to authenticate with an incorrect password they can subsequently enter a valid non-admin username and password they will be logged in as the admin user. All installations prior to version 0.9.0 are affected. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 17:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6276 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6276</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. This affects an unknown part of the file general/wiki/cp/ct/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument PROJ_ID_STR leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-246105 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6275 | TOTVS Fluig Platform mobileredir openApp.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6275</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTVS Fluig Platform 1.6.x/1.7.x/1.8.0/1.8.1. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /mobileredir/openApp.jsp of the component mobileredir. The manipulation of the argument redirectUrl/user with the input "&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(document.domain)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246104. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6274 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S80 PHP File updatelib.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6274</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S80 up to 20231108. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/updatelib.php of the component PHP File Handler. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246103. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46575 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Meshery before 0.6.179 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46575</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Meshery before 0.6.179 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the order parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6251 | CSRF in delete_user_message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6251</link><description>Cross-site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Checkmk &lt; 2.2.0p15, &lt; 2.1.0p37, &lt;= 2.0.0p39 allow an authenticated attacker to delete user-messages for individual users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48796 | Apache dolphinscheduler sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48796</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler.

The information exposed to unauthorized actors may include sensitive data such as database credentials.

Users who can't upgrade to the fixed version can also set environment variable `MANAGEMENT_ENDPOINTS_WEB_EXPOSURE_INCLUDE=health,metrics,prometheus` to workaround this, or add the following section in the `application.yaml` file

```
management:
  endpoints:
    web:
      exposure:
        include: health,metrics,prometheus
```

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: from 3.0.0 before 3.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44303 | RVTools, Version 3.9.2 and above, contain a sensitive data exposure vulnerability in the password encryption utility (RVToolsPasswordEncrypt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44303</link><description>RVTools, Version 3.9.2 and above, contain a sensitive data exposure vulnerability in the password encryption utility (RVToolsPasswordEncryption.exe) and main application (RVTools.exe). A remote unauthenticated attacker with access to stored encrypted passwords from a users' system could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of encrypted passwords in clear text. This vulnerability is caused by an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-27688.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 02:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33706 | SysAid before 23.2.15 allows Indirect Object Reference (IDOR) attacks to read ticket data via a modified sid parameter to EmailHtmlSourceIfr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33706</link><description>SysAid before 23.2.15 allows Indirect Object Reference (IDOR) attacks to read ticket data via a modified sid parameter to EmailHtmlSourceIframe.jsp or a modified srID parameter to ShowMessage.jsp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>