<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 23:43:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-42027 | IBM CICS TX cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42027</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard 11.1, Advanced 10.1, 11.1, and TXSeries for Multiplatforms 8.1, 8.2, 9.1 are vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  266057.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 23:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39048 | An information leak in Tokudaya.honten v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39048</link><description>An information leak in Tokudaya.honten v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39053 | An information leak in Hattoriya v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39053</link><description>An information leak in Hattoriya v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39054 | An information leak in Tokudaya.ekimae_mc v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39054</link><description>An information leak in Tokudaya.ekimae_mc v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39057 | An information leak in hirochanKAKIwaiting v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39057</link><description>An information leak in hirochanKAKIwaiting v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31579 | Dromara Lamp-Cloud before v3.8.1 was discovered to use a hardcoded cryptographic key when creating and verifying a Json Web Token. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31579</link><description>Dromara Lamp-Cloud before v3.8.1 was discovered to use a hardcoded cryptographic key when creating and verifying a Json Web Token. This vulnerability allows attackers to authenticate to the application via a crafted JWT token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39042 | An information leak in Gyouza-newhushimi v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39042</link><description>An information leak in Gyouza-newhushimi v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39047 | An information leak in shouzu sweets oz v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39047</link><description>An information leak in shouzu sweets oz v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39050 | An information leak in Daiky-value.Fukueten v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39050</link><description>An information leak in Daiky-value.Fukueten v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39051 | An information leak in VISION MEAT WORKS Track Diner 10/10mbl v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39051</link><description>An information leak in VISION MEAT WORKS Track Diner 10/10mbl v13.6.1 allows attackers to obtain the channel access token and send crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42299 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in OpenImageIO oiio v.2.4.12.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42299</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in OpenImageIO oiio v.2.4.12.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via the read_subimage_data function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43194 | Submitty before v22.06.00 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An attacker can delete any post in the forum by modifying request param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43194</link><description>Submitty before v22.06.00 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An attacker can delete any post in the forum by modifying request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46352 | In the module "Pixel Plus: Events + CAPI + Pixel Catalog for Facebook Module" (facebookconversiontrackingplus) up to version 2.4.9 from Smar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46352</link><description>In the module "Pixel Plus: Events + CAPI + Pixel Catalog for Facebook Module" (facebookconversiontrackingplus) up to version 2.4.9 from Smart Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal information without restriction. Due to a lack of permissions control, a guest can access exports from the module which can lead to a leak of personal information from ps_customer table such as name / surname / email.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46958 | An issue in lmxcms v.1.41 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the admin.php file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46958</link><description>An issue in lmxcms v.1.41 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the admin.php file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39283 | An SMM memory corruption vulnerability in the SMM driver (SMRAM write) in CsmInt10HookSmm in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39283</link><description>An SMM memory corruption vulnerability in the SMM driver (SMRAM write) in CsmInt10HookSmm in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5 allows attackers to send arbitrary data to SMM which could lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39284 | An issue was discovered in IhisiServicesSmm in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5. There are arbitrary calls to SetVariable with u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39284</link><description>An issue was discovered in IhisiServicesSmm in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5. There are arbitrary calls to SetVariable with unsanitized arguments in the SMI handler.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5929 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System manage_academic.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5929</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/students/manage_academic.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244329 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 20:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5930 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System manage_academic.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5930</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/students/manage_academic.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-244330 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 20:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5927 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System manage_course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5927</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/courses/manage_course.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244327.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5928 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System manage_department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5928</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/departments/manage_department.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244328.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5925 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System Master.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5925</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Master.php. The manipulation of the argument f leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244325 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5926 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System update_status.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5926</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/students/update_status.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-244326 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31017 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31017</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker may be able to write arbitrary data to privileged locations by using reparse points. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31018 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31018</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause a NULL-pointer dereference, which may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31019 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31019</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in wksServicePlugin.dll, where the driver implementation does not restrict or incorrectly restricts access from the named pipe server to a connecting client, which may lead to potential impersonation to the client's secure context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31020 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31020</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause improper access control, which may lead to denial of service or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31021 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31021</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager (vGPU plugin), where a malicious user in the guest VM can cause a NULL-pointer dereference, which may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31022 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31022</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a NULL-pointer dereference may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31023 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31023</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause a pointer dereference of an untrusted value, which may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31026 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31026</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager (vGPU plugin), where a NULL-pointer dereference may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31027 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31027</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability that allows Windows users with low levels of privilege to escalate privileges when an administrator is updating GPU drivers, which may lead to escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31016 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31016</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an uncontrolled search path element may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5923 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5923</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244323.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5924 | Campcodes Simple Student Information System view_course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5924</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/courses/view_course.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244324.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5846 | Use of Password Hash With Insufficient Computational Effort in Franklin Fueling System TS-550</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5846</link><description>Franklin Fueling System TS-550 versions prior to 1.9.23.8960 are vulnerable to attackers decoding admin credentials, resulting in unauthenticated access to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5035 | Cookie Without Secure Flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5035</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in PT-G503 Series firmware versions prior to v5.2, where the Secure attribute for sensitive cookies in HTTPS sessions is not set, which could cause the cookie to be transmitted in plaintext over an HTTP session. The vulnerability may lead to security risks, potentially exposing user session data to unauthorized access and manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46925 | Reportico 7.1.21 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46925</link><description>Reportico 7.1.21 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4217 | Session cookies attribute not set properly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4217</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in PT-G503 Series versions prior to v5.2, where the session cookies attribute is not set properly in the affected application. The vulnerability may lead to security risks, potentially exposing user session data to unauthorized access and manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4900 | Potential buffer overflow in php_cli_server_startup_workers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4900</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHP where setting the environment variable PHP_CLI_SERVER_WORKERS to a large value leads to a heap buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 15:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38471 | Reachable assertion in dbus_set_host_name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38471</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the dbus_set_host_name function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38472 | Reachable assertion in avahi_rdata_parse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38472</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the avahi_rdata_parse() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38473 | Reachable assertion in avahi_alternative_host_name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38473</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the avahi_alternative_host_name() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38470 | Reachable assertion in avahi_escape_label</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38470</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the avahi_escape_label() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38469 | Reachable assertion in avahi_dns_packet_append_record</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38469</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi, where a reachable assertion exists in avahi_dns_packet_append_record.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46725 | FoodCoopShop Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46725</link><description>FoodCoopShop is open source software for food coops and local shops. Versions prior to 3.6.1 are vulnerable to server-side request forgery. In the Network module, a manufacturer account can use the `/api/updateProducts.json` endpoint to make the server send a request to an arbitrary host. This means that the server can be used as a proxy into the internal network where the server is. Furthermore, the checks on a valid image are not adequate, leading to a time of check time of use issue. For example, by using a custom server that returns 200 on HEAD requests, then return a valid image on first GET request and then a 302 redirect to final target on second GET request, the server will copy whatever file is at the redirect destination, making this a full SSRF. Version 3.6.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45338 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45338</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'id' parameter of the routers/add-ticket.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45343 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45343</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'ticket_id' parameter of the routers/ticket-message.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45345 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45345</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The '*_deleted' parameter of the routers/user-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45346 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45346</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The '*_role' parameter of the routers/user-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45347 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45347</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The '*_verified' parameter of the routers/user-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45341 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45341</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The '*_price' parameter of the routers/menu-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45344 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45344</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The '*_balance' parameter of the routers/user-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45342 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45342</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'phone' parameter of the routers/register-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45340 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45340</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'phone' parameter of the routers/details-router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42802 | GLPI vulnerable to unallowed PHP script execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42802</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. Starting in version 10.0.7 and prior to version 10.0.10, an unverified object instantiation allows one to upload malicious PHP files to unwanted directories. Depending on web server configuration and available system libraries, malicious PHP files can then be executed through a web server request. Version 10.0.10 fixes this issue. As a workaround, remove write access on `/ajax` and `/front` files to the web server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45339 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45339</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'type' parameter of the routers/add-ticket.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5919 | SourceCodester Company Website CMS Create Blog Page createblog unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5919</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Company Website CMS 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/createblog of the component Create Blog Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-244310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45331 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45331</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'contact' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45332 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45332</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'deleted' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45333 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45333</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'verified' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45334 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45334</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'status' parameter of the routers/edit-orders.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45335 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45335</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'id' parameter of the routers/edit-orders.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45336 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45336</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'password' parameter of the routers/router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45337 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45337</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the routers/router.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45324 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45324</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'price' parameter of the routers/add-item.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45325 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45325</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'address' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45326 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45326</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'email' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45327 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45327</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'name' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45328 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45328</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'password' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45329 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45329</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'role' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45330 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45330</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the routers/add-users.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45323 | Online Food Ordering System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45323</link><description>Online Food Ordering System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'name' parameter of the routers/add-item.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26452 | Requests to cache an image and return its metadata could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26452</link><description>Requests to cache an image and return its metadata could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires at least access to adjacent networks of the imageconverter service, which is not exposed to public networks by default. Arbitrary SQL statements could be executed in the context of the services database user account. API requests are now properly checked for valid content and attempts to circumvent this check are being logged as error. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26453 | Requests to cache an image could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26453</link><description>Requests to cache an image could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires at least access to adjacent networks of the imageconverter service, which is not exposed to public networks by default. Arbitrary SQL statements could be executed in the context of the services database user account. API requests are now properly checked for valid content and attempts to circumvent this check are being logged as error. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26454 | Requests to fetch image metadata could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26454</link><description>Requests to fetch image metadata could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires at least access to adjacent networks of the imageconverter service, which is not exposed to public networks by default. Arbitrary SQL statements could be executed in the context of the services database user account. API requests are now properly checked for valid content and attempts to circumvent this check are being logged as error. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26455 | RMI was not requiring authentication when calling ChronosRMIService:setEventOrganizer. Attackers with local or adjacent network access could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26455</link><description>RMI was not requiring authentication when calling ChronosRMIService:setEventOrganizer. Attackers with local or adjacent network access could abuse the RMI service to modify calendar items using RMI. RMI access is restricted to localhost by default. The interface has been updated to require authenticated requests. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26456 | Users were able to set an arbitrary "product name" for OX Guard. The chosen value was not sufficiently sanitized before processing it at the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26456</link><description>Users were able to set an arbitrary "product name" for OX Guard. The chosen value was not sufficiently sanitized before processing it at the user interface, allowing for indirect cross-site scripting attacks. Accounts that were temporarily taken over could be configured to trigger persistent code execution, allowing an attacker to build a foothold. Sanitization is in place for product names now. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29043 | Presentations may contain references to images, which are user-controlled, and could include malicious script code that is being processed w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29043</link><description>Presentations may contain references to images, which are user-controlled, and could include malicious script code that is being processed when editing a document. Script code embedded in malicious documents could be executed in the context of the user editing the document when performing certain actions, like copying content. The relevant attribute does now get encoded to avoid the possibility of executing script code. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29044 | Documents operations could be manipulated to contain invalid data types, possibly script code. Script code could be injected to an operation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29044</link><description>Documents operations could be manipulated to contain invalid data types, possibly script code. Script code could be injected to an operation that would be executed for users that are actively collaborating on the same document. Operation data exchanged between collaborating parties does now get escaped to avoid code execution. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29045 | Documents operations, in this case "drawing", could be manipulated to contain invalid data types, possibly script code. Script code could be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29045</link><description>Documents operations, in this case "drawing", could be manipulated to contain invalid data types, possibly script code. Script code could be injected to an operation that would be executed for users that are actively collaborating on the same document. Operation data exchanged between collaborating parties does now gets checked for validity to avoid code execution. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29046 | Connections to external data sources, like e-mail autoconfiguration, were not terminated in case they hit a timeout, instead those connectio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29046</link><description>Connections to external data sources, like e-mail autoconfiguration, were not terminated in case they hit a timeout, instead those connections were logged. Some connections use user-controlled endpoints, which could be malicious and attempt to keep the connection open for an extended period of time. As a result users were able to trigger large amount of egress network connections, possibly exhausting network pool resources and lock up legitimate requests. A new mechanism has been introduced to cancel external connections that might access user-controlled endpoints. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29047 | Imageconverter API endpoints provided methods that were not sufficiently validating and sanitizing client input, allowing to inject arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29047</link><description>Imageconverter API endpoints provided methods that were not sufficiently validating and sanitizing client input, allowing to inject arbitrary SQL statements. An attacker with access to the adjacent network and potentially API credentials, could read and modify database content which is accessible to the imageconverter SQL user account. None No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46475 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability was discovered in ZenTao 18.3 where a user can create a project, and in the name field of the pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46475</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability was discovered in ZenTao 18.3 where a user can create a project, and in the name field of the project, they can inject malicious JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3164 | Heap out of bound read in builtin.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3164</link><description>A heap out-of-bounds read flaw was found in builtin.c in the gawk package. This issue may lead to a crash and could be used to read sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43193 | Submitty before v22.06.00 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can create a malicious link in the forum that leads to XS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43193</link><description>Submitty before v22.06.00 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can create a malicious link in the forum that leads to XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43336 | Sangoma Technologies FreePBX before cdr 15.0.18, 16.0.40, 15.0.16, and 16.0.17 was discovered to contain an access control issue via a modif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43336</link><description>Sangoma Technologies FreePBX before cdr 15.0.18, 16.0.40, 15.0.16, and 16.0.17 was discovered to contain an access control issue via a modified parameter value, e.g., changing extension=self to extension=101.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5860 | The Icons Font Loader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the upload functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5860</link><description>The Icons Font Loader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the upload function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5918 | SourceCodester Visitor Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5918</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Visitor Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244308.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43076 | Dell PowerScale OneFS 8.2.x,9.0.0.x-9.5.0.x contains a denial-of-service vulnerability. A low privilege remote attacker could potentially ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43076</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS 8.2.x,9.0.0.x-9.5.0.x contains a denial-of-service vulnerability. A low privilege remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause an out of memory (OOM) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43087 | Dell PowerScale OneFS 8.2.x, 9.0.0.x-9.5.0.x contains an improper handling of insufficient permissions. A low privileged remote attacker cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43087</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS 8.2.x, 9.0.0.x-9.5.0.x contains an improper handling of insufficient permissions. A low privileged remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5916 | Lissy93 Dashy Configuration save access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5916</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Lissy93 Dashy 2.1.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /config-manager/save of the component Configuration Handler. The manipulation of the argument config leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244305 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5917 | phpBB Smiley Pack acp_icons.php main cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5917</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in phpBB up to 3.3.10. This issue affects the function main of the file phpBB/includes/acp/acp_icons.php of the component Smiley Pack Handler. The manipulation of the argument pak leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.11 is able to address this issue. The patch is named ccf6e6c255d38692d72fcb613b113e6eaa240aac. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244307.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5606 | The ChatBot for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the FAQ Builder in versions 4.8.6 through 4.9.6 due to insufficie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5606</link><description>The ChatBot for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the FAQ Builder in versions 4.8.6 through 4.9.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled. NOTE: This vulnerability is a re-introduction of CVE-2023-4253.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5920 | Lack Of Secure Keyboard Entry Protection in MacOS Desktop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5920</link><description>Mattermost Desktop for MacOS fails to utilize the secure keyboard input functionality provided by macOS, allowing for other processes to read the keyboard input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5875 | Lack of Hardening against media exploitation from a remote origin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5875</link><description>Mattermost Desktop fails to correctly handle permissions or prompt the user for consent on certain sensitive ones allowing media exploitation from a malicious mattermost server</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5876 | Regex DoS from a malicious server enrolled in Desktop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5876</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly validate a RegExp built off the server URL path, allowing an attacker in control of an enrolled server to mount a Denial Of Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46595 | Net-NTLM leak via HTML injection in FireFlow VisualFlow workflow editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46595</link><description>Net-NTLM leak in Fireflow A32.20 and A32.50 allows an attacker to obtain victim’s domain credentials and Net-NTLM hash which can lead to relay domain attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46695 | An issue was discovered in Django 3.2 before 3.2.23, 4.1 before 4.1.13, and 4.2 before 4.2.7. The NFKC normalization is slow on Windows. As ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46695</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 3.2 before 3.2.23, 4.1 before 4.1.13, and 4.2 before 4.2.7. The NFKC normalization is slow on Windows. As a consequence, django.contrib.auth.forms.UsernameField is subject to a potential DoS (denial of service) attack via certain inputs with a very large number of Unicode characters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47204 | Unsafe YAML deserialization in yaml.Loader in transmute-core before 1.13.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Python code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47204</link><description>Unsafe YAML deserialization in yaml.Loader in transmute-core before 1.13.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Python code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5408 | Modification of node role labels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5408</link><description>A privilege escalation flaw was found in the node restriction admission plugin of the kubernetes api server of OpenShift. A remote attacker who modifies the node role label could steer workloads from the control plane and etcd nodes onto different worker nodes and gain broader access to the cluster.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45018 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45018</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the includes/login.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45019 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45019</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'category' parameter of the category.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46327 | Multiple MFPs (multifunction printers) provided by FUJIFILM Business Innovation Corp. and Xerox Corporation provide a facility to export the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46327</link><description>Multiple MFPs (multifunction printers) provided by FUJIFILM Business Innovation Corp. and Xerox Corporation provide a facility to export the contents of their Address Book with encrypted form, but the encryption strength is insufficient. With the knowledge of the encryption process and the encryption key, the information such as the server credentials may be obtained from the exported Address Book data. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45012 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45012</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'user_email' parameter of the bus_info.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45013 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45013</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'user_query' parameter of the bus_info.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45014 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45014</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'bus_id' parameter of the bus_info.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45015 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45015</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'date' parameter of the bus_info.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45016 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45016</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'source' parameter of the search.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45017 | Online Bus Booking System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45017</link><description>Online Bus Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'destination' parameter of the search.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45111 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45111</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'email' parameter of the feed.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45112 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45112</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'feedback' parameter of the feed.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45113 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45113</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'name' parameter of the feed.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45114 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45114</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'subject' parameter of the feed.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5910 | PopojiCMS Web Config install.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5910</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PopojiCMS 2.0.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file install.php of the component Web Config. The manipulation of the argument Site Title with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244229 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 23:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44954 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in BigTree CMS v.4.5.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ID parameter in the Dev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44954</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in BigTree CMS v.4.5.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ID parameter in the Developer Settings functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 22:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45203 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45203</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Open Redirect vulnerabilities. The 'q' parameter of the login.php resource allows an attacker to redirect a victim user to an arbitrary web site using a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 22:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45202 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45202</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Open Redirect vulnerabilities. The 'q' parameter of the feed.php resource allows an attacker to redirect a victim user to an arbitrary web site using a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 22:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39281 | A stack buffer overflow vulnerability discovered in AsfSecureBootDxe in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5 allows attackers to run...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39281</link><description>A stack buffer overflow vulnerability discovered in AsfSecureBootDxe in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5 allows attackers to run arbitrary code execution during the DXE phase.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45201 | Online Examination System v1.0 - Multiple Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45201</link><description>Online Examination System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Open Redirect vulnerabilities. The 'q' parameter of the admin.php resource allows an attacker to redirect a victim user to an arbitrary web site using a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 22:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44025 | SQL injection vulnerability in addify Addifyfreegifts v.1.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44025</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in addify Addifyfreegifts v.1.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the getrulebyid function in the AddifyfreegiftsModel.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46448 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in dmpop Mejiro Commit Versions Prior To 3096393 allows attackers to run arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46448</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in dmpop Mejiro Commit Versions Prior To 3096393 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string in metadata of uploaded images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46428 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in HadSky v7.12.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46428</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in HadSky v7.12.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1193 | Use-after-free in setup_async_work()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1193</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in setup_async_work in the KSMBD implementation of the in-kernel samba server and CIFS in the Linux kernel. This issue could allow an attacker to crash the system by accessing freed work.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46724 | SQUID-2023:4 Denial of Service in SSL Certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46724</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. Due to an Improper Validation of Specified Index bug, Squid versions 3.3.0.1 through 5.9 and 6.0 prior to 6.4 compiled using `--with-openssl` are vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against SSL Certificate validation. This problem allows a remote server to perform Denial of Service against Squid Proxy by initiating a TLS Handshake with a specially crafted SSL Certificate in a server certificate chain. This attack is limited to HTTPS and SSL-Bump. This bug is fixed in Squid version 6.4. In addition, patches addressing this problem for the stable releases can be found in Squid's patch archives. Those who you use a prepackaged version of Squid should refer to the package vendor for availability information on updated packages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1192 | Use-after-free in smb2_is_status_io_timeout()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1192</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in smb2_is_status_io_timeout() in CIFS in the Linux Kernel. After CIFS transfers response data to a system call, there are still local variable points to the memory region, and if the system call frees it faster than CIFS uses it, CIFS will access a free memory region, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3397 | Slab-use-after-free write in txend due to race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3397</link><description>A race condition occurred between the functions lmLogClose and txEnd in JFS, in the Linux Kernel, executed in different threads. This flaw allows a local attacker with normal user privileges to crash the system or leak internal kernel information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46482 | SQL injection vulnerability in wuzhicms v.4.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Database Backup Functionality in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46482</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in wuzhicms v.4.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Database Backup Functionality in the coreframe/app/database/admin/index.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 18:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20083 | A vulnerability in ICMPv6 inspection when configured with the Snort 2 detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20083</link><description>A vulnerability in ICMPv6 inspection when configured with the Snort 2 detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the CPU of an affected device to spike to 100 percent, which could stop all traffic processing and result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. FTD management traffic is not affected by this vulnerability. This vulnerability is due to improper error checking when parsing fields within the ICMPv6 header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted ICMPv6 packet through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: To recover from the DoS condition, the Snort 2 Detection Engine or the Cisco FTD device may need to be restarted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5358 | Improper access control in Report log filters feature in Devolutions Server 2023.2.10.0 and earlier allows attackers to retrieve logs from v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5358</link><description>Improper access control in Report log filters feature in Devolutions Server 2023.2.10.0 and earlier allows attackers to retrieve logs from vaults or entries they are not allowed to access via the report request url query parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20042 | A vulnerability in the AnyConnect SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20042</link><description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to an implementation error within the SSL/TLS session handling process that can prevent the release of a session handler under specific conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSL/TLS traffic to an affected device, increasing the probability of session handler leaks. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to eventually deplete the available session handler pool, preventing new sessions from being established and causing a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20063 | A vulnerability in the inter-device communication mechanisms between devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20063</link><description>A vulnerability in the inter-device communication mechanisms between devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software and devices that are running Cisco Firepower Management (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root permissions on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the expert mode of an affected device and submitting specific commands to a connected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of an FMC device if the attacker has administrative privileges on an associated FTD device. Alternatively, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of an FTD device if the attacker has administrative privileges on an associated FMC device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20070 | A vulnerability in the TLS 1.3 implementation of the Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20070</link><description>A vulnerability in the TLS 1.3 implementation of the Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to unexpectedly restart. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in how memory allocations are handled during a TLS 1.3 session. Under specific, time-based constraints, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS 1.3 message sequence through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. While the Snort detection engine reloads, packets going through the FTD device that are sent to the Snort detection engine will be dropped. The Snort detection engine will restart automatically. No manual intervention is required.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20071 | Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20071</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a flaw in the FTP module of the Snort detection engine. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted FTP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass FTP inspection and deliver a malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20095 | A vulnerability in the remote access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20095</link><description>A vulnerability in the remote access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of HTTPS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTPS requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause resource exhaustion, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20170 | A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20170</link><description>A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20175 | A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20175</link><description>A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Read-only-level privileges or higher on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20219 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20219</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. The attacker would need valid device credentials but does not require administrator privileges to exploit this vulnerability. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for certain configuration options. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using crafted input within the device configuration GUI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device including the underlying operating system which could also affect the availability of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20220 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20220</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid device credentials, but does not need Administrator privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for certain configuration options. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using crafted input within the device configuration GUI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device, including on the underlying operating system, which could also affect the availability of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20246 | Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in Snort access control policies that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20246</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in Snort access control policies that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when the access control policies are being populated. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a connection to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access control rules on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20247 | A vulnerability in the remote access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20247</link><description>A vulnerability in the remote access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured multiple certificate authentication policy and connect using only a valid username and password. This vulnerability is due to improper error handling during remote access VPN authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests during remote access VPN session establishment. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured multiple certificate authentication policy while retaining the privileges and permissions associated with the original connection profile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20264 | A vulnerability in the implementation of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN in Cisco A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20264</link><description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to intercept the SAML assertion of a user who is authenticating to a remote access VPN session. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the login URL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to access a site that is under the control of the attacker, allowing the attacker to modify the login URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to intercept a successful SAML assertion and use that assertion to establish a remote access VPN session toward the affected device with the identity and permissions of the hijacked user, resulting in access to the protected network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20267 | A vulnerability in the IP geolocation rules of Snort 3 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to potentially bypass IP address rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20267</link><description>A vulnerability in the IP geolocation rules of Snort 3 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to potentially bypass IP address restrictions. This vulnerability exists because the configuration for IP geolocation rules is not parsed properly. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by spoofing an IP address until they bypass the restriction. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass location-based IP address restrictions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5480 | Inappropriate implementation in Payments in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to bypass XSS preventions via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5480</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Payments in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to bypass XSS preventions via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5482 | Insufficient data validation in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5482</link><description>Insufficient data validation in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5765 | Improper access control in the password analyzer feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5765</link><description>Improper access control in the password analyzer feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker to bypass permissions via data source switching.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5766 | A remote code execution vulnerability in Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker to remotely execute code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5766</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability in Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker to remotely execute code from another windows user session on the same host via a specially crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5849 | Integer overflow in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5849</link><description>Integer overflow in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5850 | Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5850</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted domain name. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5851 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5851</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5852 | Use after free in Printing in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5852</link><description>Use after free in Printing in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5853 | Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5853</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5854 | Use after free in Profiles in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5854</link><description>Use after free in Profiles in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5855 | Use after free in Reading Mode in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5855</link><description>Use after free in Reading Mode in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5856 | Use after free in Side Panel in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5856</link><description>Use after free in Side Panel in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5857 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5857</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially execute arbitrary code via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5858 | Inappropriate implementation in WebApp Provider in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5858</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in WebApp Provider in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5859 | Incorrect security UI in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5859</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted local HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20031 | A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS certificate handling of Snort 3 Detection Engine integration with Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Softwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20031</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS certificate handling of Snort 3 Detection Engine integration with Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to restart. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an SSL/TLS certificate that is under load is accessed when it is initiating an SSL connection. Under specific, time-based constraints, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of SSL/TLS connection requests to be inspected by the Snort 3 detection engine on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to reload, resulting in either a bypass or a denial of service (DoS) condition, depending on device configuration. The Snort detection engine will restart automatically. No manual intervention is required.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20048 | A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20048</link><description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute certain unauthorized configuration commands on a Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) device that is managed by the FMC Software. This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization of configuration commands that are sent through the web service interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the FMC web services interface and sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute certain configuration commands on the targeted FTD device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials on the FMC Software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20196 | Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20196</link><description>Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a crafted file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files in specific directories on the device. The attacker could later use those files to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20255 | A vulnerability in an API of the Web Bridge feature of Cisco Meeting Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20255</link><description>A vulnerability in an API of the Web Bridge feature of Cisco Meeting Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a partial availability condition, which could cause ongoing video calls to be dropped due to the invalid packets reaching the Web Bridge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20195 | Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20195</link><description>Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a crafted file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files in specific directories on the device. The attacker could later use those files to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20213 | A vulnerability in the CDP processing feature of Cisco ISE could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20213</link><description>A vulnerability in the CDP processing feature of Cisco ISE could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of the CDP process on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when an affected device processes CDP traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CDP traffic to the device. A successful exploit could cause the CDP process to crash, impacting neighbor discovery and the ability of Cisco ISE to determine the reachability of remote devices. After a crash, the CDP process must be manually restarted using the cdp enable command in interface configuration mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20245 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20245</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to a logic error that could occur when the affected software constructs and applies per-user-override rules. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by connecting to a network through an affected device that has a vulnerable configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the interface ACL and access resources that would should be protected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20256 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20256</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to a logic error that could occur when the affected software constructs and applies per-user-override rules. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by connecting to a network through an affected device that has a vulnerable configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the interface ACL and access resources that would should be protected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20005 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20005</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20041 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20041</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20074 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20074</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20206 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20206</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20244 | A vulnerability in the internal packet processing of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Firewalls...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20244</link><description>A vulnerability in the internal packet processing of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Firewalls could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain packets when they are sent to the inspection engine. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete all 9,472 byte blocks on the device, resulting in traffic loss across the device or an unexpected reload of the device. If the device does not reload on its own, a manual reload of the device would be required to recover from this state.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20270 | A vulnerability in the interaction between the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol preprocessor and the Snort 3 detection engine for Cisco F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20270</link><description>A vulnerability in the interaction between the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol preprocessor and the Snort 3 detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper error-checking when the Snort 3 detection engine is processing SMB traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SMB packet stream through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Snort process to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20114 | A vulnerability in the file download feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20114</link><description>A vulnerability in the file download feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download arbitrary files from an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a lack of input sanitation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download arbitrary files from the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20155 | A vulnerability in a logging API in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20155</link><description>A vulnerability in a logging API in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to become unresponsive or trigger an unexpected reload. This vulnerability could also allow an attacker with valid user credentials, but not Administrator privileges, to view a system log file that they would not normally have access to. This vulnerability is due to a lack of rate-limiting of requests that are sent to a specific API that is related to an FMC log. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of HTTP requests to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition due to the FMC CPU spiking to 100 percent utilization or to the device reloading. CPU utilization would return to normal if the attack traffic was stopped before an unexpected reload was triggered.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20086 | A vulnerability in ICMPv6 processing of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20086</link><description>A vulnerability in ICMPv6 processing of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper processing of ICMPv6 messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted ICMPv6 messages to a targeted Cisco ASA or FTD system with IPv6 enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20177 | A vulnerability in the SSL file policy implementation of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software that occurs when the SSL/TLS connecti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20177</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSL file policy implementation of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software that occurs when the SSL/TLS connection is configured with a URL Category and the Snort 3 detection engine could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to unexpectedly restart. This vulnerability exists because a logic error occurs when a Snort 3 detection engine inspects an SSL/TLS connection that has either a URL Category configured on the SSL file policy or a URL Category configured on an access control policy with TLS server identity discovery enabled. Under specific, time-based constraints, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS connection through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger an unexpected reload of the Snort 3 detection engine, resulting in either a bypass or denial of service (DoS) condition, depending on device configuration. The Snort 3 detection engine will restart automatically. No manual intervention is required.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5178 | Use after free in nvmet_tcp_free_crypto in nvme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5178</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in drivers/nvme/target/tcp.c` in `nvmet_tcp_free_crypto` due to a logical bug in the NVMe-oF/TCP subsystem in the Linux kernel. This issue may allow a malicious user to cause a use-after-free and double-free problem, which may permit remote code execution or lead to local privilege escalation in case that the attacker already has local privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46911 | There is a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the choose_style_tree.do interface of Jspxcms v10.2.0 backend.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46911</link><description>There is a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the choose_style_tree.do interface of Jspxcms v10.2.0 backend.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3972 | Unsafe handling of temporary files and directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3972</link><description>A vulnerability was found in insights-client. This security issue occurs because of insecure file operations or unsafe handling of temporary files and directories that lead to local privilege escalation. Before the insights-client has been registered on the system by root, an unprivileged local user or attacker could create the /var/tmp/insights-client directory (owning the directory with read, write, and execute permissions) on the system. After the insights-client is registered by root, an attacker could then control the directory content that insights are using by putting malicious scripts into it and executing arbitrary code as root (trivially bypassing SELinux protections because insights processes are allowed to disable SELinux system-wide).</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33228 | SolarWinds Network Configuration Manager Sensitive Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33228</link><description>The SolarWinds Network Configuration Manager was susceptible to the Exposure of Sensitive Information Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows users with administrative access to SolarWinds Web Console to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33226 | Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33226</link><description>The Network Configuration Manager was susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability.  This vulnerability allows a low-level user to perform the actions with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33227 | Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33227</link><description>The Network Configuration Manager was susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability This vulnerability allows a low level user to perform the actions with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40061 | Insecure Job Execution Mechanism Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40061</link><description>Insecure
job execution mechanism vulnerability.  This
vulnerability can lead to other attacks as a result.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40062 | Incomplete List of Disallowed Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40062</link><description>SolarWinds Platform Incomplete List of Disallowed Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If executed, this vulnerability would allow a low-privileged user to execute commands with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5847 | Under certain conditions, a low privileged attacker could load a specially crafted file during installation or upgrade to escalate privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5847</link><description>Under certain conditions, a low privileged attacker could load a specially crafted file during installation or upgrade to escalate privileges on Windows and Linux hosts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5627 | Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5627</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in NPort 6000 Series, making the authentication mechanism vulnerable. This vulnerability arises from the incorrect implementation of sensitive information protection, potentially allowing malicious users to gain unauthorized access to the web service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46927 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in gf_isom_use_compact_size gpac/src/isomedia/isom_write.c:3403:3 in g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46927</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in gf_isom_use_compact_size gpac/src/isomedia/isom_write.c:3403:3 in gpac/MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46928 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_media_change_pl /afltest/gpac/src/media_tools/isom_tools.c:3293:4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46928</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_media_change_pl /afltest/gpac/src/media_tools/isom_tools.c:3293:42.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4452 | Web Server Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4452</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the EDR-810, EDR-G902, and EDR-G903 Series, making them  vulnerable to the denial-of-service vulnerability. This vulnerability stems from insufficient input validation in the URI, potentially enabling malicious users to trigger the device reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46930 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_isom_find_od_id_for_track /afltest/gpac/src/isomedia/media_odf.c:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46930</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_isom_find_od_id_for_track /afltest/gpac/src/isomedia/media_odf.c:522:14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46931 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in ffdmx_parse_side_data /afltest/gpac/src/filters/ff_dmx.c:202:14 in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46931</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in ffdmx_parse_side_data /afltest/gpac/src/filters/ff_dmx.c:202:14 in gpac/MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5625 | Patch regression for cve-2021-21419 in some red hat builds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5625</link><description>A regression was introduced in the Red Hat build of python-eventlet due to a change in the patch application strategy, resulting in a patch for CVE-2021-21419 not being applied for all builds of all products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48454 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48454</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48455 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48455</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48456 | In camera driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48456</link><description>In camera driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48457 | In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48457</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48458 | In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48458</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48459 | In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48459</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48460 | In setting service, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to local denial of service with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48460</link><description>In setting service, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48461 | In sensor driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48461</link><description>In sensor driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1714 | Bitrix24 Remote Command Execution (RCE) via Unsafe Variable Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1714</link><description>Unsafe variable extraction in bitrix/modules/main/classes/general/user_options.php in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via (1) appending arbitrary content to existing PHP files or (2) PHAR deserialization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1715 | Bitrix24 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Improper Input Neutralization on Invoice Edit Page (1 of 2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1715</link><description>A logic error when using mb_strpos() to check for potential XSS payload in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows attackers to bypass XSS sanitisation via placing HTML tags at the begining of the payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1716 | Bitrix24 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Improper Input Neutralization on Invoice Edit Page (2 of 2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1716</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Invoice Edit Page in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1717 | Bitrix24 Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Client-side Prototype Pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1717</link><description>Prototype pollution in bitrix/templates/bitrix24/components/bitrix/menu/left_vertical/script.js in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege, via polluting `__proto__[tag]` and `__proto__[text]`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1718 | Bitrix24 Denial-of-Service (DoS) via Improper File Stream Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1718</link><description>Improper file stream access in /desktop_app/file.ajax.php?action=uploadfile in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause denial-of-service via a crafted "tmp_url".</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1719 | Bitrix24 Insecure Global Variable Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1719</link><description>Global variable extraction in bitrix/modules/main/tools.php in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to (1) enumerate attachments on the server and (2) execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege, via overwriting uninitialised variables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1720 | Bitrix24 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1720</link><description>Lack of mime type response header in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows authenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege, via uploading a crafted HTML file through /desktop_app/file.ajax.php?action=uploadfile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42631 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42631</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42632 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42632</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42633 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42633</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42634 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42634</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42635 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42635</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42636 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42636</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42637 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42637</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42638 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42638</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42639 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42639</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42640 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42640</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42641 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42641</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42642 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42642</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42643 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42643</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42644 | In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42644</link><description>In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42645 | In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42645</link><description>In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42646 | In Ifaa service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42646</link><description>In Ifaa service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42647 | In Ifaa service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42647</link><description>In Ifaa service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42648 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42648</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42649 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42649</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42650 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42650</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42651 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42651</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42652 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42652</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42653 | In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42653</link><description>In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42654 | In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42654</link><description>In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42655 | In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42655</link><description>In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42750 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42750</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1713 | Bitrix24 Remote Command Execution (RCE) via Insecure Temporary File Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1713</link><description>Insecure temporary file creation in bitrix/modules/crm/lib/order/import/instagram.php in Bitrix24 22.0.300 hosted on Apache HTTP Server allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted ".htaccess" file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4198 | Dolibarr ERP CRM (&amp;lt;= 17.0.3) Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4198</link><description>Improper Access Control in Dolibarr ERP CRM &lt;= v17.0.3 allows an unauthorized authenticated user to read a database table containing customer data</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 08:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4197 | Dolibarr ERP CRM (&amp;lt;= 18.0.1) Improper Input Sanitization Authenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4197</link><description>Improper input validation in Dolibarr ERP CRM &lt;= v18.0.1 fails to strip certain PHP code from user-supplied input when creating a Website, allowing an attacker to inject and evaluate arbitrary PHP code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 08:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5516 | Poorly constructed webap requests and URI components with special characters trigger unhandled errors and exceptions, disclosing
information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5516</link><description>Poorly constructed webap requests and URI components with special characters trigger unhandled errors and exceptions, disclosing
information about the underlying technology and other sensitive information details. The website unintentionally reveals sensitive information including technical details like version Info, endpoints,
backend server, Internal IP. etc., which can potentially expose additional attack surface containing other interesting vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5515 | The responses for web queries with certain parameters disclose internal path of resources. This information can be used to learn internal st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5515</link><description>The responses for web queries with certain parameters disclose internal path of resources. This information can be used to learn internal structure of the application and to further plot attacks against
web servers and deployed web applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5514 | The response messages received from the eSOMS report generation using certain parameter queries with full file path can be
abused for enumer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5514</link><description>The response messages received from the eSOMS report generation using certain parameter queries with full file path can be
abused for enumerating the local file system structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2622 | Authenticated clients can read arbitrary files on the MAIN Computer
system using the remote procedure call (RPC) of the InspectSetup
service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2622</link><description>Authenticated clients can read arbitrary files on the MAIN Computer
system using the remote procedure call (RPC) of the InspectSetup
service endpoint. The low privilege client is then allowed to read arbitrary files that they do not have authorization to read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2621 | The McFeeder server (distributed as part of SSW package), is susceptible to an arbitrary file write vulnerability on the MAIN computer
syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2621</link><description>The McFeeder server (distributed as part of SSW package), is susceptible to an arbitrary file write vulnerability on the MAIN computer
system. This vulnerability stems from the use of an outdated version of a third-party library, which is used to extract archives uploaded to McFeeder server. An authenticated malicious client can
exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted ZIP archive via the
network to McFeeder’s service endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5889 | Insufficient Session Expiration in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5889</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5890 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5890</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5891 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5891</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5892 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5892</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5893 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5893</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5894 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/ojs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5894</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/ojs prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5895 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - DOM in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5895</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - DOM in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5896 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5896</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.4.0-4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5897 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/customLocale</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5897</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/customLocale prior to 1.2.0-1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5898 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5898</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5899 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5899</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5900 | Missing Authorization in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5900</link><description>Missing Authorization in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5901 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5901</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5902 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5902</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5903 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5903</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5904 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5904</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47094 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Account Plans tab of System Settings in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47094</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Account Plans tab of System Settings in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Plan name field while editing Account plan details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47095 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Custom fields of Edit Virtual Server under System Customization in Virtualmin 7.7 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47095</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Custom fields of Edit Virtual Server under System Customization in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Batch Label field while details of Virtual Server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47096 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Cloudmin Services Client under System Setting in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47096</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Cloudmin Services Client under System Setting in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Cloudmin services master field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47097 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Server Template under System Setting in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47097</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Server Template under System Setting in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Template name field while creating server templates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47098 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Manage Extra Admins under Administration Options in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47098</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Manage Extra Admins under Administration Options in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the real name or description field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47099 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Create Virtual Server in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47099</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Create Virtual Server in Virtualmin 7.7 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via Description field while creating the Virtual server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46278 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Cybozu Remote Service 4.1.0 to 4.1.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker to consume hu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46278</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Cybozu Remote Service 4.1.0 to 4.1.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker to consume huge storage space or cause significantly delayed communication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39695 | Insufficient session expiration in Elenos ETG150 FM Transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to arbitrarily change transmitter configuration and d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39695</link><description>Insufficient session expiration in Elenos ETG150 FM Transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to arbitrarily change transmitter configuration and data after logging out.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37833 | Improper access control in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to make arbitrary configuration edits that are only accessed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37833</link><description>Improper access control in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to make arbitrary configuration edits that are only accessed by privileged users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46378 | Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MiniCMS 1.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string appended to /mc-a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46378</link><description>Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MiniCMS 1.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string appended to /mc-admin/conf.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44486 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44486</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'address' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5306 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5306</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'city' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44484 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44484</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'firstName' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44485 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44485</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'lastName' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20886 | VMware Workspace ONE UEM console contains an open redirect vulnerability.


A malicious actor may be able to redirect a victim to an attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20886</link><description>VMware Workspace ONE UEM console contains an open redirect vulnerability.


A malicious actor may be able to redirect a victim to an attacker and retrieve their SAML response to login as the victim user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39610 | An issue in TP-Link Tapo C100 v1.1.15 Build 211130 Rel.15378n(4555) and before allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via suppl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39610</link><description>An issue in TP-Link Tapo C100 v1.1.15 Build 211130 Rel.15378n(4555) and before allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted web request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3955 | Kubernetes - Windows nodes - Insufficient input sanitization leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3955</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a user
 that can create pods on Windows nodes may be able to escalate to admin 
privileges on those nodes. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if they
 include Windows nodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43295 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Click Studios (SA) Pty Ltd Passwordstate v.Build 9785 and before allows a local attacker to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43295</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Click Studios (SA) Pty Ltd Passwordstate v.Build 9785 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3676 | Kubernetes - Windows nodes - Insufficient input sanitization leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3676</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a user
 that can create pods on Windows nodes may be able to escalate to admin 
privileges on those nodes. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if they
 include Windows nodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46485 | An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setTracerouteCfg function of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46485</link><description>An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setTracerouteCfg function of the stecgi.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46484 | An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setLedCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46484</link><description>An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setLedCfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37832 | A lack of rate limiting in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to obtain user credentials via brute force and cause other un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37832</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to obtain user credentials via brute force and cause other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37831 | An issue discovered in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to enumerate user accounts based on server responses when credent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37831</link><description>An issue discovered in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to enumerate user accounts based on server responses when credentials are submitted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45955 | An issue discovered in Nanoleaf Light strip v3.5.10 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted write binding attribute comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45955</link><description>An issue discovered in Nanoleaf Light strip v3.5.10 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted write binding attribute commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43796 | Synapse vulnerable to leak of remote user device information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43796</link><description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver Prior to versions 1.95.1 and 1.96.0rc1, cached device information of remote users can be queried from Synapse. This can be used to enumerate the remote users known to a homeserver. System administrators are encouraged to upgrade to Synapse 1.95.1 or 1.96.0rc1 to receive a patch. As a workaround, the `federation_domain_whitelist` can be used to limit federation traffic with a homeserver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5739 | Certain versions of HP PC Hardware Diagnostics Windows are potentially vulnerable to elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5739</link><description>Certain versions of HP PC Hardware Diagnostics Windows are potentially vulnerable to elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46722 | Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in PDF previews</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46722</link><description>The Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend UI for Pimcore. Prior to version 1.2.0, a cross-site scripting vulnerability has the potential to steal a user's cookie and gain unauthorized access to that user's account through the stolen cookie or redirect users to other malicious sites. Users should upgrade to version 1.2.0 to receive a patch or, as a workaround, apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46723 | lte-pic32-writer&amp;#x27;s sendto.txt may disclose URL and the API key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46723</link><description>lte-pic32-writer is a writer for PIC32 devices. In versions 0.0.1 and prior, those who use `sendto.txt` are vulnerable to attackers who known the IMEI reading the sendto.txt. The sendto.txt file can contain the SNS(such as slack and zulip) URL and API key. As of time of publication, a patch is not yet available. As workarounds, avoid using `sendto.txt` or use `.htaccess` to block access to `sendto.txt`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46256 | PX4-Autopilot Heap Buffer Overflow Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46256</link><description>PX4-Autopilot provides PX4 flight control solution for drones. In versions 1.14.0-rc1 and prior, PX4-Autopilot has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the parser function due to the absence of `parserbuf_index` value checking. A malfunction of the sensor device can cause a heap buffer overflow with leading unexpected drone behavior. Malicious applications can exploit the vulnerability even if device sensor malfunction does not occur. Up to the maximum value of an `unsigned int`, bytes sized data can be written to the heap memory area. As of time of publication, no fixed version is available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46250 | pypdf possible Infinite Loop when PdfWriter(clone_from) is used with a PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46250</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. An attacker who uses a vulnerability present in versions 3.7.0 through 3.16.4 can craft a PDF which leads to an infinite loop. This infinite loop blocks the current process and can utilize a single core of the CPU by 100%. It does not affect memory usage. That is, for example, the case when the pypdf-user manipulates an incoming malicious PDF e.g. by merging it with another PDF or by adding annotations. The issue was fixed in version 3.17.0. As a workaround, apply the patch manually by modifying `pypdf/generic/_data_structures.py`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46255 | `SPICEDB_DATASTORE_CONN_URI` is leaked when URI cannot be parsed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46255</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source, Google Zanzibar-inspired database for creating and managing security-critical application permissions. Prior to version 1.27.0-rc1, when the provided datastore URI is malformed (e.g. by having a password which contains `:`) the full URI (including the provided password) is printed, so that the password is shown in the logs. Version 1.27.0-rc1 patches this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46249 | authentik potential installation takeover when default admin user is deleted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46249</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Prior to versions 2023.8.4 and 2023.10.2, when the default admin user has been deleted, it is potentially possible for an attacker to set the password of the default admin user without any authentication. authentik uses a blueprint to create the default admin user, which can also optionally set the default admin users' password from an environment variable. When the user is deleted, the `initial-setup` flow used to configure authentik after the first installation becomes available again. authentik 2023.8.4 and 2023.10.2 fix this issue. As a workaround, ensure the default admin user (Username `akadmin`) exists and has a password set. It is recommended to use a very strong password for this user, and store it in a secure location like a password manager. It is also possible to deactivate the user to prevent any logins as akadmin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46245 | Kimai (Authenticated) SSTI to RCE by Uploading a Malicious Twig File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46245</link><description>Kimai is a web-based multi-user time-tracking application. Versions 2.1.0 and prior are vulnerable to a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) which can be escalated to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The vulnerability arises when a malicious user uploads a specially crafted Twig file, exploiting the software's PDF and HTML rendering functionalities. As of time of publication, no patches or known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46248 | Overwrite of builtin Cody commands facilitates RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46248</link><description>Cody is an artificial intelligence (AI) coding assistant. The Cody AI VSCode extension versions 0.10.0 through 0.14.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution under certain conditions. An attacker in control of a malicious repository could modify the Cody configuration file `.vscode/cody.json` and overwrite Cody commands. If a user with the extension installed opens this malicious repository and runs a Cody command such as /explain or /doc, this could allow arbitrary code execution on the user's machine. The vulnerability is rated as critical severity, but with low exploitability. It requires the user to have a malicious repository loaded and execute the overwritten command in VS Code. The issue is exploitable regardless of the user blocking code execution on a repository through VS Code Workspace Trust. The issue was found during a regular 3rd party penetration test. The maintainers of Cody do not have evidence of open source repositories having malicious `.vscode/cody.json` files to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version 0.14.1 of the Cody VSCode extension. In case users can't promptly upgrade, they should not open any untrusted repositories with the Cody extension loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46237 | FOG path traversal via unauthenticated endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46237</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Prior to version 1.5.10, an endpoint intended to offer limited enumeration abilities to authenticated users was accessible to unauthenticated users. This enabled unauthenticated users to discover files and their respective paths that were visible to the Apache user group. Version 1.5.10 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46239 | quic-go vulnerable to pointer dereference that can lead to panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46239</link><description>quic-go is an implementation of the QUIC protocol in Go. Starting in version 0.37.0 and prior to version 0.37.3, by serializing an ACK frame after the CRYTPO that allows a node to complete the handshake, a remote node could trigger a nil pointer dereference (leading to a panic) when the node attempted to drop the Handshake packet number space. An attacker can bring down a quic-go node with very minimal effort. Completing the QUIC handshake only requires sending and receiving a few packets. Version 0.37.3 contains a patch. Versions before 0.37.0 are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46240 | CodeIgniter4 vulnerable to information disclosure when detailed error report is displayed in production environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46240</link><description>CodeIgniter is a PHP full-stack web framework. Prior to CodeIgniter4 version 4.4.3, if an error or exception occurs, a detailed error report is displayed even if in the production environment. As a result, confidential information may be leaked. Version 4.4.3 contains a patch. As a workaround, replace `ini_set('display_errors', '0')` with `ini_set('display_errors', 'Off')` in `app/Config/Boot/production.php`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37966 | WordPress User Activity Log Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37966</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Solwin Infotech User Activity Log user-activity-log allows SQL Injection.This issue affects User Activity Log: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42425 | An issue in Turing Video Turing Edge+ EVC5FD v.1.38.6 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42425</link><description>An issue in Turing Video Turing Edge+ EVC5FD v.1.38.6 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the cloud connection components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22518 | All versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are affected by this unexploited vulnerability. There is no impact to confidentiality as a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22518</link><description>All versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are affected by this unexploited vulnerability. There is no impact to confidentiality as an attacker cannot exfiltrate any instance data.

Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37243 | The C:\Windows\Temp\Agent.Package.Availability\Agent.Package.Availability.exe file is automatically launched as SYSTEM when the system reboo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37243</link><description>The C:\Windows\Temp\Agent.Package.Availability\Agent.Package.Availability.exe file is automatically launched as SYSTEM when the system reboots. Since the C:\Windows\Temp\Agent.Package.Availability folder inherits permissions from C:\Windows\Temp and Agent.Package.Availability.exe is susceptible to DLL hijacking, standard users can write a malicious DLL to it and elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46236 | FOG SSRF via unauthenticated endpoint(s)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46236</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Prior to version 1.5.10, a server-side-request-forgery (SSRF) vulnerability allowed an unauthenticated user to trigger a GET request as the server to an arbitrary endpoint and URL scheme. This also allows remote access to files visible to the Apache user group. Other impacts vary based on server configuration. Version 1.5.10 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24410 | WordPress FluentForm Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.25 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24410</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Contact Form - WPManageNinja LLC Contact Form Plugin – Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms fluentform allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Contact Form Plugin – Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms: from n/a through 4.3.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36508 | WordPress Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36508</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in BestWebSoft Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft – Messages Database Plugin For WordPress contact-form-to-db allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft – Messages Database Plugin For WordPress: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46235 | FOG stored XSS on log screen via unsanitized request logging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46235</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Prior to version 1.5.10.15, due to a lack of request sanitization in the logs, a malicious request containing XSS would be stored in a log file. When an administrator of the FOG server logged in and viewed the logs, they would be parsed as HTML and displayed accordingly. Version 1.5.10.15 contains a patch. As a workaround, view logs from an external text editor rather than the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35879 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Vendors Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.78 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WooCommerce Product Vendors allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Product Vendors: from n/a through 2.1.78.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31212 | WordPress Contact Form Entries Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31212</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CRM Perks Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms contact-form-entries allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33927 | WordPress Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.19 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33927</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themeisle Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG multiple-pages-generator-by-porthas allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG: from n/a through 3.3.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40050 | Automate Vulnerable to Malicious Content Uploaded Through Embedded Compliance Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40050</link><description>Upload profile either
through API or user interface in Chef Automate prior to and including version 4.10.29 using InSpec
check command with maliciously crafted profile allows remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42658 | InSpec Archive Command Vulnerable to Maliciously Crafted Profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42658</link><description>Archive command in Chef InSpec prior to 4.56.58 and 5.22.29 allow local command execution via maliciously crafted profile.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46993 | In TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 when dealing with setLedCfg request, there is no verification for the enable parameter, which can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46993</link><description>In TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 when dealing with setLedCfg request, there is no verification for the enable parameter, which can lead to command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28777 | WordPress LearnDash LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28777</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LearnDash LearnDash LMS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects LearnDash LMS: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46992 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Attackers are able to reset serveral critical passwords w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46992</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Attackers are able to reset serveral critical passwords without authentication by visiting specific pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24000 | WordPress GamiPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24000</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GamiPress gamipress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects GamiPress: from n/a through 2.5.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46978 | TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.Attackers can reset login password &amp; WIFI passwords without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46978</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.Attackers can reset login password &amp; WIFI passwords without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46979 | TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setLedCfg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46979</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setLedCfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4250 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4250</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4251 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Booking Creation via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4251</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not have CSRF checks when creating bookings, which could allow attackers to make logged in users create unwanted bookings via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4390 | Popup box &amp;lt; 3.7.2 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4390</link><description>The Popup box WordPress plugin before 3.7.2 does not sanitize and escape some Popup fields, which could allow high-privilege users such as an administrator to inject arbitrary web scripts even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in a multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4823 | WP Meta and Date Remover &amp;lt; 2.2.0 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4823</link><description>The WP Meta and Date Remover WordPress plugin before 2.2.0 provides an AJAX endpoint for configuring the plugin settings. This endpoint has no capability checks and does not sanitize the user input, which is then later output unescaped. Allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber change them and perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4836 | WordPress File Sharing Plugin &amp;lt; 2.0.5 - Subscriber+ Sensitive Data and Files Exposure via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4836</link><description>The WordPress File Sharing Plugin WordPress plugin before 2.0.5 does not check authorization before displaying files and folders, allowing users to gain access to those filed by manipulating IDs which can easily be brute forced</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5098 | Campaign Monitor Forms &amp;lt; 2.5.6 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5098</link><description>The Campaign Monitor Forms by Optin Cat WordPress plugin before 2.5.6 does not prevent users with low privileges (like subscribers) from overwriting any options on a site with the string "true", which could lead to a variety of outcomes, including DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5211 | Fattura24 &amp;lt; 6.2.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5211</link><description>The Fattura24 WordPress plugin before 6.2.8 does not sanitize or escape the 'id' parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5229 | E2Pdf &amp;lt; 1.20.20 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scriping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5229</link><description>The E2Pdf WordPress plugin before 1.20.20 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5237 | Memberlite Shortcodes &amp;lt; 1.3.9 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5237</link><description>The Memberlite Shortcodes WordPress plugin before 1.3.9 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5238 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Reflected HTML Injection on keyword parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5238</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to an HTML Injection on the plugin in the search area of the website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5243 | Login screen manager &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5243</link><description>The Login Screen Manager WordPress plugin through 3.5.2 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5307 | Photos and Files Contest Gallery – Contact Form &amp;lt; 21.2.8.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS via HTTP Headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5307</link><description>The Photos and Files Contest Gallery WordPress plugin before 21.2.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks via certain headers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5360 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt; 1.3.79 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5360</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates WordPress plugin before 1.3.79 does not properly validate uploaded files, which could allow unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files, such as PHP and achieve RCE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5458 | CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload &amp;lt; 3.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5458</link><description>The CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload WordPress plugin before 3.0 does not sanitise uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5519 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Booking Creation via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5519</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not have CSRF checks when creating bookings, which could allow attackers to make logged in users create unwanted bookings via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25047 | WordPress RSVPMarker Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25047</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker rsvpmaker allows SQL Injection.This issue affects RSVPMaker: from n/a through 9.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46976 | TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 contains a command injection via the file_name parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46976</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 contains a command injection via the file_name parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46977 | TOTOLINK LR1200GB V9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46977</link><description>TOTOLINK LR1200GB V9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25045 | WordPress RSVPMarker Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25045</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker allows SQL Injection.This issue affects RSVPMaker: from n/a through 9.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5116 | The Live updates from Excel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ipushpull_page' shortcode in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5116</link><description>The Live updates from Excel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ipushpull_page' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-1203 | Improper file verification vulnerability in SaAT Netizen installer ver.1.2.0.424 and earlier, and SaAT Netizen ver.1.2.0.8 (Build427) and ea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1203</link><description>Improper file verification vulnerability in SaAT Netizen installer ver.1.2.0.424 and earlier, and SaAT Netizen ver.1.2.0.8 (Build427) and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to conduct a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful exploitation may result in a malicious file being downloaded and executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38994 | An issue in Univention UCS v.5.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain privileges via the check_univention_joinstatus f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38994</link><description>An issue in Univention UCS v.5.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain privileges via the check_univention_joinstatus function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5073 | The iframe forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iframe' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5073</link><description>The iframe forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iframe' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5099 | The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5099</link><description>The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the 'src' attribute of the 'csvsearch' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5114 | The idbbee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idbbee' shortcode in versions up to, and incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5114</link><description>The idbbee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idbbee' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3007 | Unauthorized Access Vulnerability in Syska SW100 Smartwatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3007</link><description>The vulnerability exists in Syska SW100 Smartwatch due to an improper implementation and/or configuration of Nordic Device Firmware Update (DFU) which is used for performing Over-The-Air (OTA) firmware updates on the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) devices. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by setting arbitrary values to handle on the vulnerable device over Bluetooth.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform firmware update, device reboot or data manipulation on the target device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40681 | WordPress Groundhogg Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.11.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40681</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Groundhogg Inc. Groundhogg plugin &lt;= 2.7.11.10 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46622 | WordPress WPPizza Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.18.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46622</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ollybach WPPizza – A Restaurant Plugin plugin &lt;= 3.18.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46313 | WordPress Zotpress Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46313</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Katie Seaborn Zotpress plugin &lt;= 7.3.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-2968 | LINE@ for Android version 1.0.0 and LINE@ for iOS version 1.0.0 are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-2968</link><description>LINE@ for Android version 1.0.0 and LINE@ for iOS version 1.0.0 are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allows non-SSL/TLS communications. As a result, any API may be invoked from a script injected by a MITM (man-in-the-middle) attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-0897 | LINE for Android version 5.0.2 and earlier and LINE for iOS version 5.0.0 and earlier are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack sinc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-0897</link><description>LINE for Android version 5.0.2 and earlier and LINE for iOS version 5.0.0 and earlier are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allows non-SSL/TLS communications. As a result, any API may be invoked from a script injected by a MITM (man-in-the-middle) attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46312 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46312</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &lt;= 1.5.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5412 | The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5412</link><description>The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5428 | The Image vertical reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5428</link><description>The Image vertical reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5429 | The Information Reel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 10.0 d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5429</link><description>The Information Reel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 10.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5430 | The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5430</link><description>The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5431 | The Left right image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5431</link><description>The Left right image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5433 | The Message ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.2 due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5433</link><description>The Message ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5434 | The Superb slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5434</link><description>The Superb slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5435 | The Up down image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5435</link><description>The Up down image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5436 | The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5436</link><description>The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5437 | The WP fade in text news plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5437</link><description>The WP fade in text news plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5438 | The wp image slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5438</link><description>The wp image slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5439 | The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5439</link><description>The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 8.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5464 | The Jquery accordion slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5464</link><description>The Jquery accordion slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 8.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5873 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pimcore/pimcore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5873</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pimcore/pimcore prior to 11.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46210 | WordPress WC Captcha Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46210</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WebCource WC Captcha plugin &lt;= 1.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46451 | Best Courier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the change username field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46451</link><description>Best Courier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the change username field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46361 | Artifex Software jbig2dec v0.20 was discovered to contain a SEGV vulnerability via jbig2_error at /jbig2dec/jbig2.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46361</link><description>Artifex Software jbig2dec v0.20 was discovered to contain a SEGV vulnerability via jbig2_error at /jbig2dec/jbig2.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45996 | SQL injection vulnerability in Senayan Library Management Systems Slims v.9 and Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45996</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Senayan Library Management Systems Slims v.9 and Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the reborrowLimit parameter in the member_type.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43139 | An issue in franfinance before v.2.0.27 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation.php, and controllers/front/val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43139</link><description>An issue in franfinance before v.2.0.27 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation.php, and controllers/front/validation.php components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36263 | Prestashop opartlimitquantity 1.4.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection. OpartlimitquantityAlertlimitModuleFrontController::displayAja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36263</link><description>Prestashop opartlimitquantity 1.4.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection. OpartlimitquantityAlertlimitModuleFrontController::displayAjaxPushAlertMessage()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47174 | Thorn SFTP gateway 3.4.x before 3.4.4 uses Pivotal Spring Framework for Java deserialization of untrusted data, which is not supported by Pi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47174</link><description>Thorn SFTP gateway 3.4.x before 3.4.4 uses Pivotal Spring Framework for Java deserialization of untrusted data, which is not supported by Pivotal, a related issue to CVE-2016-1000027. Also, within the specific context of Thorn SFTP gateway, this leads to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46356 | In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) before 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `SearchA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46356</link><description>In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) before 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `SearchApiCsv::getProducts()` has sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27846 | SQL injection vulnerability found in PrestaShop themevolty v.4.0.8 and before allow a remote attacker to gain privileges via the tvcmsblog, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27846</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability found in PrestaShop themevolty v.4.0.8 and before allow a remote attacker to gain privileges via the tvcmsblog, tvcmsvideotab, tvcmswishlist, tvcmsbrandlist, tvcmscategorychainslider, tvcmscategoryproduct, tvcmscategoryslider, tvcmspaymenticon, tvcmstestimonial components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45378 | In the module "PrestaBlog" (prestablog) version 4.4.7 and before from HDclic for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45378</link><description>In the module "PrestaBlog" (prestablog) version 4.4.7 and before from HDclic for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script ajax slider_positions.php has a sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-20110 | JHipster generator-jhipster before 2.23.0 allows a timing attack against validateToken due to a string comparison that stops at the first ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-20110</link><description>JHipster generator-jhipster before 2.23.0 allows a timing attack against validateToken due to a string comparison that stops at the first character that is different. Attackers can guess tokens by brute forcing one character at a time and observing the timing. This of course drastically reduces the search space to a linear amount of guesses based on the token length times the possible characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25155 | DOMPurify before 1.0.11 allows reverse tabnabbing in demos/hooks-target-blank-demo.html because links lack a 'rel="noopener noreferrer"' att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25155</link><description>DOMPurify before 1.0.11 allows reverse tabnabbing in demos/hooks-target-blank-demo.html because links lack a 'rel="noopener noreferrer"' attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45899 | An issue in the component SuperUserSetuserModuleFrontController:init() of idnovate superuser before v2.4.2 allows attackers to bypass authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45899</link><description>An issue in the component SuperUserSetuserModuleFrontController:init() of idnovate superuser before v2.4.2 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted HTTP call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31794 | MuPDF v1.21.1 was discovered to contain an infinite recursion in the component pdf_mark_list_push. This vulnerability allows attackers to ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31794</link><description>MuPDF v1.21.1 was discovered to contain an infinite recursion in the component pdf_mark_list_push. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46040 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in GetSimpleCMS v.3.4.0a allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the a crafted payload to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46040</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in GetSimpleCMS v.3.4.0a allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the a crafted payload to the components.php function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46139 | KernelSU signature validation mismatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46139</link><description>KernelSU is a Kernel based root solution for Android. Starting in version 0.6.1 and prior to version 0.7.0, if a KernelSU installed device is infected with a malware whose app signing block specially constructed, it can take over root privileges on the device. The vulnerable verification logic actually obtains the signature of the last block with an id of `0x7109871a`, while the verification logic during Android installation is to obtain the first one. In addition to the actual signature upgrade that has been fixed (KSU thought it was V2 but was actually V3), there is also the problem of actual signature downgrading (KSU thought it was V2 but was actually V1). Find a condition in the signature verification logic that will cause the signature not to be found error, and KernelSU does not implement the same conditions, so KSU thinks there is a V2 signature, but the APK signature verification actually uses the V1 signature. This issue is fixed in version 0.7.0. As workarounds, keep the KernelSU manager installed and avoid installing unknown apps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5861 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in microweber/microweber</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5861</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository microweber/microweber prior to 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5862 | Missing Authorization in hamza417/inure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5862</link><description>Missing Authorization in GitHub repository hamza417/inure prior to Build95.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5863 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5863</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5864 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5864</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5865 | Insufficient Session Expiration in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5865</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5866 | Sensitive Cookie in HTTPS Session Without &amp;#x27;Secure&amp;#x27; Attribute in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5866</link><description>Sensitive Cookie in HTTPS Session Without 'Secure' Attribute in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5867 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5867</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>