<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:42:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-34750 | Apache Tomcat: HTTP/2 excess header handling DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34750</link><description>Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions, Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 stream, Tomcat did not handle some cases of excessive HTTP headers correctly. This led to a miscounting of active HTTP/2 streams which in turn led to the use of an incorrect infinite timeout which allowed connections to remain open which should have been closed.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M20, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.24, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.89.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M21, 10.1.25 or 9.0.90, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39683 | ZITADEL Vulnerable to Session Information Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39683</link><description>ZITADEL is an open-source identity infrastructure tool. ZITADEL provides users the ability to list all user sessions of the current user agent (browser). Starting in version 2.53.0 and prior to versions 2.53.8, 2.54.5, and 2.55.1, due to a missing check, user sessions without that information (e.g. when created though the session service) were incorrectly listed exposing potentially other user's sessions. Versions 2.55.1, 2.54.5, and 2.53.8 contain a fix for the issue. There is no workaround since a patch is already available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36122 | Discourse doesn&amp;#x27;t limit reviewable user serializer payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36122</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, moderators using the review queue to review users may see a users email address even when the Allow moderators to view email addresses setting is disabled. This issue is patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. As possible workarounds, either prevent moderators from accessing the review queue or disable the approve suspect users site setting and the must approve users site setting to prevent users from being added to the review queue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37157 | Discourse vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery via FastImage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37157</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, a malicious actor could get the FastImage library to redirect requests to an internal Discourse IP. This issue is patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36113 | Discourse missing authorization checks for suspending admins/moderators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36113</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch, version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `beta` branch, and version 3.3.0.beta4-dev on the `tests-passed` branch, a rogue staff user could suspend other staff users preventing them from logging in to the site. The issue is patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch, version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `beta` branch, and version 3.3.0.beta4-dev on the `tests-passed` branch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33870 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. There is path traversal (via a crafted PostScript document) to arbitrary file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33870</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. There is path traversal (via a crafted PostScript document) to arbitrary files if the current directory is in the permitted paths. For example, there can be a transformation of ../../foo to ./../../foo and this will grant access if ./ is permitted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33869 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. Path traversal and command execution can occur (via a crafted PostScript docu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33869</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. Path traversal and command execution can occur (via a crafted PostScript document) because of path reduction in base/gpmisc.c. For example, restrictions on use of %pipe% can be bypassed via the aa/../%pipe%command# output filename.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29507 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 sometimes has a stack-based buffer overflow via the CIDFSubstPath and CIDFSubstFont parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29507</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 sometimes has a stack-based buffer overflow via the CIDFSubstPath and CIDFSubstFont parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33871 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. contrib/opvp/gdevopvp.c allows arbitrary code execution via a custom Driver l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33871</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. contrib/opvp/gdevopvp.c allows arbitrary code execution via a custom Driver library, exploitable via a crafted PostScript document. This occurs because the Driver parameter for opvp (and oprp) devices can have an arbitrary name for a dynamic library; this library is then loaded.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29510 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1 allows memory corruption, and SAFER sandbox bypass, via format string injection with a uniprint device.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29510</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1 allows memory corruption, and SAFER sandbox bypass, via format string injection with a uniprint device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29511 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1, when Tesseract is used for OCR, has a directory traversal issue that allows arbitrary file reading (and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29511</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1, when Tesseract is used for OCR, has a directory traversal issue that allows arbitrary file reading (and writing of error messages to arbitrary files) via OCRLanguage. For example, exploitation can use debug_file /tmp/out and user_patterns_file /etc/passwd.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35234 | Discourse vulnerable to stored-dom XSS via Facebook Oneboxes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35234</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users’ browsers by posting a specific URL containing maliciously crafted meta tags. This issue only affects sites with Content Security Polic (CSP) disabled. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. As a workaround, ensure CSP is enabled on the forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29506 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the pdfi_apply_filter() function via a long PDF filter name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29506</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the pdfi_apply_filter() function via a long PDF filter name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29508 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.0.3.0 has a heap-based pointer disclosure (observable in a constructed BaseFont name) in the function pdf_base...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29508</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.0.3.0 has a heap-based pointer disclosure (observable in a constructed BaseFont name) in the function pdf_base_font_alloc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29509 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a heap-based overflow when PDFPassword (e.g., for runpdf) has a \000 byte in the middle.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29509</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a heap-based overflow when PDFPassword (e.g., for runpdf) has a \000 byte in the middle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52169 | The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains an out-of-bounds read that allows an attacker to read beyond the i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52169</link><description>The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains an out-of-bounds read that allows an attacker to read beyond the intended buffer. The bytes read beyond the intended buffer are presented as a part of a filename listed in the file system image. This has security relevance in some known web-service use cases where untrusted users can upload files and have them extracted by a server-side 7-Zip process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52168 | The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains a heap-based buffer overflow that allows an attacker to overwrite ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52168</link><description>The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains a heap-based buffer overflow that allows an attacker to overwrite two bytes at multiple offsets beyond the allocated buffer size: buffer+512*i-2, for i=9, i=10, i=11, etc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35227 | Discourse vulnerable to DoS through Onebox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35227</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, Oneboxing against a carefully crafted malicious URL can reduce the availability of a Discourse instance. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. There are no known workarounds available for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5821 | Improper Access Control in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5821</link><description>Improper Access Control in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5887 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5887</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31223 | Fides Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Privacy Center of SERVER_SIDE_FIDES_API_URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31223</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform, and `SERVER_SIDE_FIDES_API_URL` is a server-side configuration environment variable used by the Fides Privacy Center to communicate with the Fides webserver backend. The value of this variable is a URL which typically includes a private IP address, private domain name, and/or port. A vulnerability present starting in version 2.19.0 and prior to version 2.39.2rc0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to make a HTTP GET request from the Privacy Center that discloses the value of this server-side URL. This could result in disclosure of server-side configuration giving an attacker information on server-side ports, private IP addresses, and/or private domain names. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version 2.39.2rc0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3332 | bt: host/smp: DoS caused by null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3332</link><description>A malicious BLE device can send a specific order of packet sequence to cause a DoS attack on the victim BLE device</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39844 | In ZNC before 1.9.1, remote code execution can occur in modtcl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39844</link><description>In ZNC before 1.9.1, remote code execution can occur in modtcl.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39248 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SimpCMS v0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39248</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SimpCMS v0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Title field at /admin.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39220 | BAS-IP AV-01D, AV-01MD, AV-01MFD, AV-01ED, AV-01KD, AV-01BD, AV-01KBD, AV-02D, AV-02IDE, AV-02IDR, AV-02IPD, AV-02FDE, AV-02FDR, AV-03D, AV-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39220</link><description>BAS-IP AV-01D, AV-01MD, AV-01MFD, AV-01ED, AV-01KD, AV-01BD, AV-01KBD, AV-02D, AV-02IDE, AV-02IDR, AV-02IPD, AV-02FDE, AV-02FDR, AV-03D, AV-03BD, AV-04AFD, AV-04ASD, AV-04FD, AV-04SD, AV-05FD, AV-05SD, AA-07BD, AA-07BDI, BA-04BD, BA-04MD, BA-08BD, BA-08MD, BA-12BD, BA-12MD, CR-02BD before firmware v3.9.2 allows authenticated attackers to read SIP account passwords via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6126 | Cockpit: authenticated user can kill any process when enabling pam_env&amp;#x27;s user_readenv option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6126</link><description>A flaw was found in the cockpit package. This flaw allows an authenticated user to kill any process when enabling the pam_env's user_readenv option, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6052 | XSS in SQL check parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6052</link><description>Stored XSS in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p8, 2.2.0p29, 2.1.0p45, and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows users to execute arbitrary scripts by injecting HTML elements</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39223 | An authentication bypass in the SSH service of gost v2.11.5 allows attackers to intercept communications via setting the HostKeyCallback fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39223</link><description>An authentication bypass in the SSH service of gost v2.11.5 allows attackers to intercept communications via setting the HostKeyCallback function to ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32937 | An os command injection vulnerability exists in the CWMP SelfDefinedTimeZone functionality of Grandstream GXP2135 1.0.9.129, 1.0.11.74 and 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32937</link><description>An os command injection vulnerability exists in the CWMP SelfDefinedTimeZone functionality of Grandstream GXP2135 1.0.9.129, 1.0.11.74 and 1.0.11.79. A specially crafted network packet can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a sequence of malicious packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37726 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Micro-Star International Co., Ltd MSI Center v.2.0.36.0 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37726</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Micro-Star International Co., Ltd MSI Center v.2.0.36.0 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Export System Info function in MSI.CentralServer.exe</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6471 | SourceCodester Online Tours &amp;amp; Travels Management sms_setting.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6471</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Tours &amp; Travels Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file sms_setting.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270279.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6470 | playSMS Template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6470</link><description>A vulnerability was found in playSMS 1.4.3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=feature_inboxgroup&amp;amp;op=list of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument Receiver Number with the input {{`id`}} leads to injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270278 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5672 | Red Lion Europe: mbNET.mini vulnerable to OS command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5672</link><description>A high privileged remote attacker can execute arbitrary system commands via GET requests due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6426 | Information exposure vulnerability vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6426</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version, the exploitation of which could allow a local attacker, with user privileges, to access different resources by changing the API value of the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6427 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6427</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version. An unauthenticated remote attacker can use the "message" parameter to inject a payload with dangerous JavaScript code, causing the application to loop requests on itself, which could lead to resource consumption and disable the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6469 | playSMS Template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6469</link><description>A vulnerability was found in playSMS 1.4.3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=feature_firewall&amp;amp;op=firewall_list of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument IP address with the input {{`id`} leads to injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270277 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39353 | RemoteClusterFrame payloads are audit logged in full</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39353</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 and 9.8.0 fail to sanitize the RemoteClusterFrame payloads before audit logging them which allows a high privileged attacker with access to the audit logs to read message contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39361 | Creating posts with user-defined IDs permitted in CreatePost API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39361</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.8.0, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.4, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.2 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 fail to prevent users from specifying a RemoteId for their posts which allows an attacker to specify both a remoteId and the post ID, resulting in creating a post with a user-defined post ID. This can cause some broken functionality in the channel or thread with user-defined posts</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6428 | Limited DoS due to permitting creating users with user-defined IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6428</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.8.0, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.4, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.2, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 fail to prevent specifying a RemoteId when creating a new user which allows an attacker to specify both a remoteId and the user ID, resulting in creating a user with a user-defined user ID. This can cause some broken functionality in User Management such administrative actions against the user not working.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36257 | Lack of permission check when updating the profile picture of a remote user (shared channels enabled)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36257</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 and 9.8.0, when using shared channels with multiple remote servers connected, fail to check that the remote server A requesting the server B to update the profile picture of a user is the remote that actually has the user as a local one . This allows a malicious remote A to change the profile images of users that belong to another remote server C that is connected to the server A.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39807 | Channel IDs of archived/restored channels leaked via webhook events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39807</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 and 9.8.0 fail to properly sanitize the recipients of a webhook event which allows an attacker monitoring webhook events to retrieve the channel IDs of archived or restored channels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39830 | Timing attack during remote cluster token comparison when shared channels are enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39830</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.0, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.4, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.2 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5, when shared channels are enabled, fail to use constant time comparison for remote cluster tokens which allows an attacker to retrieve the remote cluster token via a timing attack during remote cluster token comparison.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4482 | The Plus Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 5.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4482</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Countdown' widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'text_days' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6263 | WP Lightbox 2 &amp;lt;= 3.0.6.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6263</link><description>The WP Lightbox 2 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6340 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.35 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6340</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37082 | HAProxy Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link><description>Security check loophole in HAProxy release (in combination with routing release) in Cloud Foundry prior to v40.17.0 potentially allows bypass of mTLS authentication to applications hosted on Cloud Foundry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2040 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Arbitrary Group Joining via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2040</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make users join private groups via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2231 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Subscriber+ Private Group Joining via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2231</link><description>The  allows any authenticated user to join a private group due to a missing authorization check on a function</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2233 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Multiple CSRF on the Group Section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2233</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks. These include declining and accepting group invitations or leaving a group</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2234 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2234</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its Post settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2235 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Bypass Poll Voting Restrictions via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2235</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make users vote on any polls, including those they don't have access to via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2375 | WPQA &amp;lt; 6.1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2375</link><description>The WPQA Builder WordPress plugin before 6.1.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its Slider settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2376 | WPQA &amp;lt; 6.1.1 - Arbitrary Category and Tag Follow/Unfollow via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2376</link><description>The WPQA Builder WordPress plugin before 6.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38453 | The Avalara for Salesforce CPQ app before 7.0 for Salesforce allows attackers to read an API key. NOTE: the current version is 11 as of mid-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38453</link><description>The Avalara for Salesforce CPQ app before 7.0 for Salesforce allows attackers to read an API key. NOTE: the current version is 11 as of mid-2024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4543 | Snippet Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 4.1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4543</link><description>The Snippet Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation when adding or editing shortcodes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify shortcodes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 04:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39920 | The TCP protocol in RFC 9293 has a timing side channel that makes it easier for remote attackers to infer the content of one TCP connection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39920</link><description>The TCP protocol in RFC 9293 has a timing side channel that makes it easier for remote attackers to infer the content of one TCP connection from a client system (to any server), when that client system is concurrently obtaining TCP data at a slow rate from an attacker-controlled server, aka the "SnailLoad" issue. For example, the attack can begin by measuring RTTs via the TCP segments whose role is to provide an ACK control bit and an Acknowledgment Number.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32673 | Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Walrus Webassembly runtime engine allows a segmentation fault issue....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32673</link><description>Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Walrus Webassembly runtime engine allows a segmentation fault issue.

This issue affects Walrus: before 72c7230f32a0b791355bbdfc78669701024b0956.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 01:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4708 | mySCADA myPRO Use of Hard-coded Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4708</link><description>mySCADA myPRO 

uses a hard-coded password which could allow an attacker to remotely execute code on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 23:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6453 | itsourcecode Farm Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6453</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Farm Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /quarantine.php?id=3. The manipulation of the argument pigno/breed/reason leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270241 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: Original submission mentioned parameter pigno only but the VulDB data analysis team determined two additional parameters to be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24791 | Denial of service due to improper 100-continue handling in net/http</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24791</link><description>The net/http HTTP/1.1 client mishandled the case where a server responds to a request with an "Expect: 100-continue" header with a non-informational (200 or higher) status. This mishandling could leave a client connection in an invalid state, where the next request sent on the connection will fail. An attacker sending a request to a net/http/httputil.ReverseProxy proxy can exploit this mishandling to cause a denial of service by sending "Expect: 100-continue" requests which elicit a non-informational response from the backend. Each such request leaves the proxy with an invalid connection, and causes one subsequent request using that connection to fail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39326 | SkillTree CSRF Vulnerability allows an attacker to modify the Video and Captions of a Skill</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39326</link><description>SkillTree is a micro-learning gamification platform. Prior to version 2.12.6, the endpoint 
`/admin/projects/{projectname}/skills/{skillname}/video` (and probably others) is open to a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. Due to the endpoint being CSRFable e.g POST request, supports a content type that can be exploited (multipart file upload), makes a state change and has no CSRF mitigations in place (samesite flag, CSRF token). It is possible to perform a CSRF attack against a logged in admin account, allowing an attacker that can target a logged in admin of Skills Service to modify the videos, captions, and text of the skill. Version 2.12.6 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39325 | aimeos/ai-controller-frontend doesn&amp;#x27;t reset payment status in basket</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39325</link><description>aimeos/ai-controller-frontend is the  Aimeos frontend controller. Prior to versions 2024.04.2, 2023.10.9, 2022.10.8, 2021.10.8, and 2020.10.15, aimeos/ai-controller-frontend doesn't reset the payment status of a user's basket after the user completes a purchase. Versions 2024.04.2, 2023.10.9, 2022.10.8, 2021.10.8, and 2020.10.15 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39322 | aimeos/ai-admin-jsonadm improper access control vulnerability allows editors to remove required records</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39322</link><description>aimeos/ai-admin-jsonadm is the Aimeos e-commerce JSON API for administrative tasks. In versions prior to 2020.10.13, 2021.10.6, 2022.10.3, 2023.10.4, and 2024.4.2, improper access control allows editors to remove admin group and locale configuration in the Aimeos backend. Versions 2020.10.13, 2021.10.6, 2022.10.3, 2023.10.4, and 2024.4.2 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39324 | aimeos/ai-admin-graphql improper access control vulnerability allows editors to manage own services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39324</link><description>aimeos/ai-admin-graphql is the Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface. Starting in version 2022.04.1 and prior to versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.4.2, improper access control allows a editors to manage own services via GraphQL API which isn't allowed in the JQAdm front end. Versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.4.2 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39315 | Pomerium exposed OAuth2 access and ID tokens in user info endpoint response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39315</link><description>Pomerium is an identity and context-aware access proxy. Prior to version 0.26.1, the Pomerium user info page (at `/.pomerium`) unintentionally included serialized OAuth2 access and ID tokens from the logged-in user's session. These tokens are not intended to be exposed to end users. This issue may be more severe in the presence of a cross-site scripting vulnerability in an upstream application proxied through Pomerium. If an attacker could insert a malicious script onto a web page proxied through Pomerium, that script could access these tokens by making a request to the `/.pomerium` endpoint. Upstream applications that authenticate only the ID token may be vulnerable to user impersonation using a token obtained in this manner. Note that an OAuth2 access token or ID token by itself is not sufficient to hijack a user's Pomerium session. Upstream applications should not be vulnerable to user impersonation via these tokens provided the application verifies the Pomerium JWT for each request, the connection between Pomerium and the application is secured by mTLS, or the connection between Pomerium and the application is otherwise secured at the network layer. The issue is patched in Pomerium v0.26.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6452 | linlinjava litemall AdminGoodscontroller.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6452</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in linlinjava litemall up to 1.8.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file AdminGoodscontroller.java. The manipulation of the argument goodsId/goodsSn/name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270235.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30636 | Limited directory traversal vulnerability on Windows in golang.org/x/crypto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30636</link><description>httpTokenCacheKey uses path.Base to extract the expected HTTP-01 token value to lookup in the DirCache implementation. On Windows, path.Base acts differently to filepath.Base, since Windows uses a different path separator (\ vs. /), allowing a user to provide a relative path, i.e. .well-known/acme-challenge/..\..\asd becomes ..\..\asd. The extracted path is then suffixed with +http-01, joined with the cache directory, and opened. Since the controlled path is suffixed with +http-01 before opening, the impact of this is significantly limited, since it only allows reading arbitrary files on the system if and only if they have this suffix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24531 | Output of &amp;quot;go env&amp;quot; does not sanitize values in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24531</link><description>Command go env is documented as outputting a shell script containing the Go environment. However, go env doesn't sanitize values, so executing its output as a shell script can cause various bad bahaviors, including executing arbitrary commands or inserting new environment variables. This issue is relatively minor because, in general, if an attacker can set arbitrary environment variables on a system, they have better attack vectors than making "go env" print them out.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38537 | Inclusion of Untrusted polyfill.io Code Vulnerability in fides.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38537</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. `fides.js`, a client-side script used to interact with the consent management features of Fides, used the `polyfill.io` domain in a very limited edge case, when it detected a legacy browser such as IE11 that did not support the fetch standard. Therefore it was possible for users of legacy, pre-2017 browsers who navigate to a page serving `fides.js` to download and execute malicious scripts from the `polyfill.io` domain when the domain was compromised and serving malware. No exploitation of `fides.js` via `polyfill.io` has been identified as of time of publication.

The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.39.1`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. On Thursday, June 27, 2024, Cloudflare and Namecheap intervened at a domain level to ensure `polyfill.io` and its subdomains could not resolve to the compromised service, rendering this vulnerability unexploitable. Prior to the domain level intervention, there were no server-side workarounds and the confidentiality, integrity, and availability impacts of this vulnerability were high. Clients could ensure they were not affected by using a modern browser that supported the fetch standard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25477 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25477</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 leaks driver logs that contain addresses of kernel mode objects, weakening KASLR.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25478 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25478</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 provides read and write access to the PCI configuration space of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25479 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25479</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 allows for the leakage of kernel memory from both the stack and the heap.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25480 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25480</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 allows writing to kernel memory beyond the SystemBuffer of the IRP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39894 | OpenSSH 9.5 through 9.7 before 9.8 sometimes allows timing attacks against echo-off password entry (e.g., for su and Sudo) because of an Obs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39894</link><description>OpenSSH 9.5 through 9.7 before 9.8 sometimes allows timing attacks against echo-off password entry (e.g., for su and Sudo) because of an ObscureKeystrokeTiming logic error. Similarly, other timing attacks against keystroke entry could occur.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39206 | An issue discovered in MSP360 Backup Agent v7.8.5.15 and v7.9.4.84 allows attackers to obtain network share credentials used in a backup due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39206</link><description>An issue discovered in MSP360 Backup Agent v7.8.5.15 and v7.9.4.84 allows attackers to obtain network share credentials used in a backup due to enginesettings.list being encrypted with a hard coded key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39891 | In the Twilio Authy API, accessed by Authy Android before 25.1.0 and Authy iOS before 26.1.0, an unauthenticated endpoint provided access to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39891</link><description>In the Twilio Authy API, accessed by Authy Android before 25.1.0 and Authy iOS before 26.1.0, an unauthenticated endpoint provided access to certain phone-number data. (Authy accounts were not compromised, however.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6381 | MongoDB C Driver bson_strfreev may be susceptible to integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6381</link><description>The bson_strfreev function in the MongoDB C driver library may be susceptible to an integer overflow where the function will try to free memory at a negative offset. This may result in memory corruption. This issue affected libbson versions prior to 1.26.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6382 | Adversarial unsanitized input may cause MongoDB Rust Driver to issue unintended commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6382</link><description>Incorrect handling of certain string inputs may result in MongoDB Rust driver constructing unintended server commands. This may cause unexpected application behavior including data modification. This issue affects MongoDB Rust Driver 2.0 versions prior to 2.8.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39323 | aimeos/ai-admin-graphql improper access control vulnerability allows an editor to modify admin account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39323</link><description>aimeos/ai-admin-graphql is the Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface. Starting in version 2022.04.01 and prior to versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.04.6, an improper access control vulnerability allows an editor to modify and take over an admin account in the back end. Versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.04.6 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39316 | Rack ReDoS Vulnerability in HTTP Accept Headers Parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39316</link><description>Rack is a modular Ruby web server interface. Starting in version 3.1.0 and prior to version 3.1.5, Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the `Rack::Request::Helpers` module when parsing HTTP Accept headers. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker sending specially crafted `Accept-Encoding` or `Accept-Language` headers, causing the server to spend excessive time processing the request and leading to a Denial of Service (DoS). The fix for CVE-2024-26146 was not applied to the main branch and thus while the issue was fixed for the Rack v3.0 release series, it was not fixed in the v3.1 release series until v3.1.5. Users of versions on the 3.1 branch should upgrade to version 3.1.5 to receive the fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4467 | Qemu: &amp;#x27;qemu-img info&amp;#x27; leads to host file read/write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4467</link><description>A flaw was found in the QEMU disk image utility (qemu-img) 'info' command. A specially crafted image file containing a `json:{}` value describing block devices in QMP could cause the qemu-img process on the host to consume large amounts of memory or CPU time, leading to denial of service or read/write to an existing external file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5865 | Arbitrary File Reading in Centrify PAS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5865</link><description>Vulnerability in Delinea Centrify PAS v. 21.3 and possibly others. The application is prone to the path traversal vulnerability allowing arbitrary files reading outside the web publish directory. Versions 23.1-HF7 and on have the patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5866 | Arbitrary Directory Listing in Centrify PAS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5866</link><description>Vulnerability in Delinea Centrify PAS v. 21.3 and possibly others. The application is prone to the path traversal vulnerability allowing listing of arbitrary directory outside the root directory of the web application. Versions 23.1-HF7 and on have the patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3826 | Broken SAML Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3826</link><description>In versions of Akana in versions prior to and including 2022.1.3 validation is broken when using the SAML Single Sign-On (SSO) functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26314 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 6.0.0 through 16.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26314</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 6.0.0 through 16.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25087 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.7.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25087</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.7.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25088 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25088</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25086 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.2.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25086</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.2.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22105 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22105</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22106 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, or cause a De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22106</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, or cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22103 | Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22103</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22104 | Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22104</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51778 | Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51778</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22102 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22102</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51777 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51777</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51776 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51776</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4897 | Remote Code Execution in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4897</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui, in its latest version, is vulnerable to remote code execution due to an insecure dependency on llama-cpp-python version llama_cpp_python-0.2.61+cpuavx2-cp311-cp311-manylinux_2_31_x86_64. The vulnerability arises from the application's 'binding_zoo' feature, which allows attackers to upload and interact with a malicious model file hosted on hugging-face, leading to remote code execution. The issue is linked to a known vulnerability in llama-cpp-python, CVE-2024-34359, which has not been patched in lollms-webui as of commit b454f40a. The vulnerability is exploitable through the application's handling of model files in the 'bindings_zoo' feature, specifically when processing gguf format model files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32932 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Reversible User Credential - stored web interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32932</link><description>Under certain circumstances the web interface users credentials may be recovered by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32757 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Linux Credential Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32757</link><description>Under certain circumstances unnecessary user details are provided within system logs</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32756 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Reversible User Credential - Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32756</link><description>Under certain circumstances the Linux users credentials may be recovered by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34122 | T5 Acrobat Vulnerability - Exploitable crash in DecodeTile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34122</link><description>Acrobat for Edge versions 126.0.2592.68 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38519 | yt-dlp file system modification and RCE through improper file-extension sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38519</link><description>`yt-dlp` is a command-line audio/video downloader. Prior to version 2024.07.01, `yt-dlp` does not limit the extensions of downloaded files, which could lead to aribitrary filenames being created in the download folder (and path traversal on Windows). Since `yt-dlp` also reads config from the working directory (and on Windows executables will be executed from the yt-dlp directory) this could lead to arbitrary code being executed. `yt-dlp` version 2024.07.01 fixes this issue by whitelisting the allowed extensions. This might mean some very uncommon extensions might not get downloaded, however it will also limit the possible exploitation surface. In addition to upgrading, have `.%(ext)s` at the end of the output template and make sure the user trusts the websites that they are downloading from. Also, make sure to never download to a directory within PATH or other sensitive locations like one's user directory, `system32`, or other binaries locations. For users who are not able to upgrade, keep the default output template (`-o "%(title)s [%(id)s].%(ext)s`); make sure the extension of the media to download is a common video/audio/sub/... one; try to avoid the generic extractor; and/or use `--ignore-config --config-location ...` to not load config from common locations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32755 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Log Filter Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32755</link><description>Under certain circumstances the web interface will accept characters unrelated to the expected input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36404 | GeoTools Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in evaluating XPath expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36404</link><description>GeoTools is an open source Java library that provides tools for geospatial data. Prior to versions 31.2, 30.4, and 29.6, Remote Code Execution (RCE) is possible if an application uses certain GeoTools functionality to evaluate XPath expressions supplied by user input. Versions 31.2, 30.4, and 29.6 contain a fix for this issue. As a workaround, GeoTools can operate with reduced functionality by removing the `gt-complex` jar from one's application. As an example of the impact, application schema `datastore` would not function without the ability to use XPath expressions to query complex content. Alternatively, one may utilize a drop-in replacement GeoTools jar from SourceForge for versions 31.1, 30.3, 30.2, 29.2, 28.2, 27.5, 27.4, 26.7, 26.4, 25.2, and 24.0. These jars are for download only and are not available from maven central, intended to quickly provide a fix to affected applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39143 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ResidenceCMS 2.10.1 that allows a low-privilege user to create malicious propert...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39143</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ResidenceCMS 2.10.1 that allows a low-privilege user to create malicious property content with HTML inside which acts as a stored XSS payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39119 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via admin/info_deal.php?mudi=rev&amp;nohrefStr=close.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39119</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via admin/info_deal.php?mudi=rev&amp;amp;nohrefStr=close.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6441 | ORIPA LoaderXML.java deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6441</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ORIPA up to 1.72. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file src/main/java/oripa/persistence/doc/loader/LoaderXML.java. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.80 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-270169 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4268 | Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.9 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Blocks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4268</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6088 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated User Registration Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6088</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user registration due to a missing capability check on the 'register' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass disabled user registration to create a new account with the default role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6099 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.1 - Unauthenticated Bypass to User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6099</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated bypass to user registration in versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8.1. This is due to missing checks in the 'check_validate_fields' function in the checkout. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as the default role on the site, even if registration is disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6264 | Post Meta Data Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6264</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘$meta_key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6439 | SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6439</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270167.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6440 | SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6440</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270168.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6438 | Hitout Carsale OrderController.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6438</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Hitout Carsale 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file OrderController.java. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270166 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 10:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6011 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6011</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘textarea.description’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6012 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Content Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6012</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'embed-create-page' and 'embed-insert-pages' functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary posts and append arbitrary content to existing posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20888 | Improper access control in OneUIHome prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities. User interactio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20888</link><description>Improper access control in OneUIHome prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20889 | Improper authentication in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to pair with devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20889</link><description>Improper authentication in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to pair with devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20890 | Improper input validation in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to trigger abnormal behavior.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20890</link><description>Improper input validation in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to trigger abnormal behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20891 | Improper access control in launchFullscreenIntent of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20891</link><description>Improper access control in launchFullscreenIntent of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20892 | Improper verification of signature in FilterProvider prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute privileged behaviors....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20892</link><description>Improper verification of signature in FilterProvider prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute privileged behaviors. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20893 | Improper input validation in libmediaextractorservice.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20893</link><description>Improper input validation in libmediaextractorservice.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20894 | Improper handling of exceptional conditions in Secure Folder prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20894</link><description>Improper handling of exceptional conditions in Secure Folder prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication under certain condition. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20895 | Improper access control in Dar service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restriction for calling SDP features...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20895</link><description>Improper access control in Dar service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restriction for calling SDP features.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20896 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Configuration message prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20896</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Configuration message prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20897 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in FCM function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20897</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in FCM function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20898 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in SoftphoneClient in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20898</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in SoftphoneClient in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20899 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in RCS function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20899</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in RCS function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20900 | Improper authentication in MTP application prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to enter MTP mode without proper authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20900</link><description>Improper authentication in MTP application prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to enter MTP mode without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20901 | Improper input validation in copying data to buffer cache in libsaped prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20901</link><description>Improper input validation in copying data to buffer cache in libsaped prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34583 | Improper access control in system property prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device identifier.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34583</link><description>Improper access control in system property prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device identifier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34584 | Improper privilege management in SumeNNService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34584</link><description>Improper privilege management in SumeNNService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34585 | Improper access control in launchApp of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34585</link><description>Improper access control in launchApp of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34586 | Improper access control in KnoxCustomManagerService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure Knox privacy policy.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34586</link><description>Improper access control in KnoxCustomManagerService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure Knox privacy policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34587 | Improper input validation in parsing application information from RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34587</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing application information from RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34588 | Improper input validation혻in parsing RTCP SR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34588</link><description>Improper input validation혻in parsing RTCP SR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34589 | Improper input validation in parsing RTCP RR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34589</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing RTCP RR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34590 | Improper input validation혻in parsing an item type from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34590</link><description>Improper input validation혻in parsing an item type from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34591 | Improper input validation in parsing an item data from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34591</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing an item data from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34592 | Improper input validation in parsing RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger tempor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34592</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34593 | Improper input validation in parsing and distributing RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34593</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing and distributing RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34594 | Exposure of sensitive information in proc file system prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to read kernel memory address.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34594</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in proc file system prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to read kernel memory address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34595 | Improper access control in clickAdapterItem of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34595</link><description>Improper access control in clickAdapterItem of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34596 | Improper authentication in SmartThings prior to version 1.8.17 allows remote attackers to bypass the expiration date for members set by the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34596</link><description>Improper authentication in SmartThings prior to version 1.8.17 allows remote attackers to bypass the expiration date for members set by the owner.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34597 | Improper input validation in Samsung Health prior to version 6.27.0.113 allows local attackers to write arbitrary document files to the sand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34597</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Health prior to version 6.27.0.113 allows local attackers to write arbitrary document files to the sandbox of Samsung Health. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34599 | Improper input validation in Tips prior to version 6.2.9.4 in Android 14 allows local attacker to send broadcast with Tips' privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34599</link><description>Improper input validation in Tips prior to version 6.2.9.4 in Android 14 allows local attacker to send broadcast with Tips' privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34600 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.13.0 allows local attackers to copy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34600</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.13.0 allows local attackers to copy image files to external storage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34601 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in GalaxyStore prior to version 4.5.81.0 allows local attackers to launc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34601</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in GalaxyStore prior to version 4.5.81.0 allows local attackers to launch unexported activities of GalaxyStore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4836 | LFI in sites managed by Edito CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4836</link><description>Web services managed by Edito CMS (Content Management System) in versions from 3.5 through 3.25 leak sensitive data as they allow downloading configuration files by an unauthenticated user.
The issue in versions 3.5 - 3.25 was removed in releases which dates from 10th of January 2014. Higher versions were never affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5260 | Sina Extension for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via read_more_text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5260</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘read_more_text’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31071 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31071</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36243 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36243</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds read and write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36260 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36260</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36278 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36278</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37030 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37030</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37077 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37077</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37185 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37185</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38857 | Reflected links in visuals facilitate phishing attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38857</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p8, 2.2.0p28, 2.1.0p45, and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows attackers to craft malicious links that can facilitate phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41917 | Improper input validation in Kiloview P1/P2 devices allows for remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41917</link><description>Inadequate input validation exposes the system to potential remote code execution (RCE) risks. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by appending shell commands to the Speed-Measurement feature, enabling unauthorized code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41918 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41918</link><description>A vulnerability allows unauthorized access to functionality inadequately constrained by ACLs. Attackers may exploit this to unauthenticated execute commands potentially leading to unauthorized data manipulation, access to privileged functions, or even the execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41919 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41919</link><description>Hardcoded credentials are discovered within the application's source code, creating a potential security risk for unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41920 | Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41920</link><description>The vulnerability allows attackers access to the root account without having to authenticate. Specifically, if the device is configured with the IP address of 10.10.10.10, the root user is automatically logged in.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41921 | Download of Code Without Integrity Check in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41921</link><description>A vulnerability allows attackers to download source code or an executable from a remote location and execute the code without sufficiently verifying the origin and integrity of the code. This vulnerability can allow attackers to modify the firmware before uploading it to the system, thus achieving the modification of the target’s integrity to achieve an insecure state.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41922 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41922</link><description>A 'Cross-site Scripting' (XSS) vulnerability, characterized by improper input neutralization during web page generation, has been discovered. This vulnerability allows for Stored XSS attacks to occur. Multiple areas within the administration interface of the webserver lack adequate input validation, resulting in multiple instances of Stored XSS vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41923 | Weak Password Requirements in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41923</link><description>The user management section of the web application permits the creation of user accounts with excessively weak passwords, including single-character passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41926 | Insufficiently protected credentials in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41926</link><description>The webserver utilizes basic authentication for its user login to the configuration interface. As encryption is disabled on port 80, it enables potential eavesdropping on user traffic, making it possible to intercept their credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41927 | Weak TLS Cipher Suites Supported in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41927</link><description>The server supports at least one cipher suite which is on the NCSC-NL list of cipher suites to be phased out, increasing the risk of cryptographic weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41928 | Remote server offers deprecated TLS protocol in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41928</link><description>The device is observed to accept deprecated TLS protocols, increasing the risk of cryptographic weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37479 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.1 - Contributor+ Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37479</link><description>Local File Inclusion vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor via "LaStudioKit Progress Bar" widget in New Post, specifically in the "progress_type" attribute.This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3513 | Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title tag attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3513</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the title tag parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5504 | Rife Elementor Extensions &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Writing Effect Headline Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5504</link><description>The Rife Elementor Extensions &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tag' attribute within the plugin's Writing Effect Headline widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5544 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.17 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5544</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the order parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5545 | Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp;amp; Listing &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5545</link><description>The Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp; Listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the stm_edit_delete_user_car function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to unpublish arbitrary posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37126 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37126</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized gain of root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37134 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37134</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37132 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A high privileged attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37132</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37133 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37133</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized gain of root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32853 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.2 contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability. A local low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32853</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.2 contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32854 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privilege attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32854</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privilege attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32852 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.0 contain use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unprivileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32852</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.0 contain use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unprivileged network malicious attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to data leaks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5219 | Easy Google Maps &amp;lt;= 1.11.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5219</link><description>The Easy Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6172 | Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.7.25 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via unsubscribe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6172</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the db parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.25 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0158 | Dell BIOS contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges may potentially ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0158</link><description>Dell BIOS contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify a UEFI variable, leading to denial of service and escalation of privileges</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3999 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3999</link><description>The EazyDocs  WordPress plugin before 2.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4627 | Rank Math SEO &amp;lt; 1.0.219 - Authenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4627</link><description>The Rank Math SEO  WordPress plugin before 1.0.219 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow users with access to the General Settings (by default admin, however such access can be given to lower roles via the Role Manager feature of the Rank Math SEO  WordPress plugin before 1.0.219) to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5606 | Quiz And Survey Master &amp;lt; 9.0.2 - Contributor+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5606</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.0.2 is vulnerable does not validate and escape the question_id parameter in the qsm_bulk_delete_question_from_database AJAX action, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by Contributors and above role</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5767 | Sitetweet &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5767</link><description>The sitetweet WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1427 | The Post Grid &amp;lt;= 7.7.1 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via section title tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1427</link><description>The The Post Grid – Shortcode, Gutenberg Blocks and Elementor Addon for Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the section title tag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5349 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5349</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8.1 via the 'map_style' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5419 | Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cf7_redirect_page Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5419</link><description>The Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cf7_redirect_page' attribute within the plugin's Void Contact From 7 widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2819 | File Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2819</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions, Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Common Services: before 11.0.2-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5938 | Boot Store &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5938</link><description>The Boot Store theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4679 | Folder Permission Vulnerability in JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4679</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent for Windows, Hitachi JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent on Windows, Hitachi Job Management Partner1/Extensible SNMP Agent on Windows allows File Manipulation.This issue affects JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent for Windows: from 12-00 before 12-00-01, from 11-00 through 11-00-*; JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent: from 10-10 through 10-10-01, from 10-00 through 10-00-02, from 09-00 through 09-00-04; Job Management Partner1/Extensible SNMP Agent: from 10-10 through 10-10-01, from 10-00 through 10-00-02, from 09-00 through 09-00-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37764 | MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated stored cross-site scripting.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37764</link><description>MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated stored cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37762 | MachForm up to version 21 is affected by an authenticated unrestricted file upload which leads to a remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37762</link><description>MachForm up to version 21 is affected by an authenticated unrestricted file upload which leads to a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37763 | MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an unauthenticated stored cross-site scripting which affects users with valid sessions whom can vie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37763</link><description>MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an unauthenticated stored cross-site scripting which affects users with valid sessions whom can view compiled forms results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39314 | toy-blog administrative token leaked through the command line parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39314</link><description>toy-blog is a headless content management system implementation. Starting in version 0.4.3 and prior to version 0.5.0, the administrative password was leaked through the command line parameter. The problem was patched in version 0.5.0. As a workaround, pass `--read-bearer-token-from-stdin` to the launch arguments and feed the token from the standard input in version 0.4.14 or later. Earlier versions do not have this workaround.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23737 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Jira allows attackers to allows attackers to manipula...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23737</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Jira allows attackers to allows attackers to manipulate a user's S/MIME certificate of PGP key via malicious link or email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37765 | Machform up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated Blind SQL injection in the user account settings page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37765</link><description>Machform up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated Blind SQL injection in the user account settings page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39313 | toy-blog Improper Input Validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39313</link><description>toy-blog is a headless content management system implementation. Starting in version 0.5.4 and prior to version 0.6.1, articles with private visibility can be read if the reader does not set credentials for the request. Users should upgrade to 0.6.1 or later to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23736 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Confluence allows attackers to manipulate a user's S/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23736</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Confluence allows attackers to manipulate a user's S/MIME certificate of PGP key via malicious link or email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39309 | ZDI-CAN-23894: Parse Server literalizeRegexPart SQL Injection Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39309</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. A vulnerability in versions prior to 6.5.7 and 7.1.0 allows SQL injection when Parse Server is configured to use the PostgreSQL database. The algorithm to detect SQL injection has been improved in versions 6.5.7 and 7.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39310 | WordPress Basil Theme Authenticated (Contributor+) Persistent Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39310</link><description>The Basil recipe theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the `post_title` parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers with contributor-level access and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses a compromised page. Because the of the default WordPress validation, it is not possible to insert the payload directly but if the Cooked plugin is installed, it is possible to create a recipe post type (cp_recipe) and inject the payload in the title field. Version 2.0.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38368 | Trunk&amp;#x27;s &amp;#x27;Claim your pod&amp;#x27; could be used to obtain un-used pods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38368</link><description>trunk.cocoapods.org is the authentication server for the CoacoaPods dependency manager. A vulnerability affected older pods which migrated from the pre-2014 pull request workflow to trunk. If the pods had never been claimed then it was still possible to do so. It was also possible to have all owners removed from a pod, and that made the pod available for the same claiming system. This was patched server-side in commit 71be5440906b6bdfbc0bcc7f8a9fec33367ea0f4 in September 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39305 | Envoy Proxy use after free when route hash policy is configured with cookie attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39305</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Prior to versions 1.30.4, 1.29.7, 1.28.5, and 1.27.7. Envoy references already freed memory when route hash policy is configured with cookie attributes. Note that this vulnerability has been fixed in the open as the effect would be immediately apparent if it was configured. Memory allocated for holding attribute values is freed after configuration was parsed. During request processing Envoy will attempt to copy content of de-allocated memory into request cookie header. This can lead to arbitrary content of Envoy's memory to be sent to the upstream service or abnormal process termination. This vulnerability is fixed in Envoy versions v1.30.4, v1.29.7, v1.28.5, and v1.27.7. As a workaround, do not use cookie attributes in route action hash policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28200 | N-central Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28200</link><description>The N-central server is vulnerable to an authentication bypass of the user interface. This vulnerability is present in all deployments of N-central prior to 2024.2.

This vulnerability was discovered through internal N-central source code review and N-able has not observed any exploitation in the wild.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38367 | CoacoaPods trunk sessions verification step could be manipulated for owner session hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38367</link><description>trunk.cocoapods.org is the authentication server for the CoacoaPods dependency manager. Prior to commit d4fa66f49cedab449af9a56a21ab40697b9f7b97, the trunk sessions verification step could be manipulated for owner session hijacking Compromising a victim’s session will result in a full takeover of the CocoaPods trunk account. The threat actor could manipulate their pod specifications, disrupt the distribution of legitimate libraries, or cause widespread disruption within the CocoaPods ecosystem. This was patched server-side with commit d4fa66f49cedab449af9a56a21ab40697b9f7b97 in October 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5322 | N-central Authentication Bypass via Session Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5322</link><description>The N-central server is vulnerable to session rebinding of already authenticated users when using Entra SSO, which can lead to authentication bypass.
 
This vulnerability is present in all Entra-supported deployments of N-central prior to 2024.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38366 | CoacoaPods trunk RCE in email verification system rfc-822</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38366</link><description>trunk.cocoapods.org is the authentication server for the CoacoaPods dependency manager. The part of trunk which verifies whether a user has a real email address on signup used a rfc-822 library which executes a shell command to validate the email domain MX records validity. It works via an DNS MX. This lookup could be manipulated to also execute a command on the trunk server, effectively giving root access to the server and the infrastructure. This issue was patched server-side with commit 001cc3a430e75a16307f5fd6cdff1363ad2f40f3 in September 2023. This RCE triggered a full user-session reset, as an attacker could have used this method to write to any Podspec in trunk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32228 | FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a SEGV at libavcodec/hevcdec.c:2947:22 in hevc_frame_end.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32228</link><description>FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a SEGV at libavcodec/hevcdec.c:2947:22 in hevc_frame_end.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32229 | FFmpeg 7.0 contains a heap-buffer-overflow at libavfilter/vf_tiltandshift.c:189:5 in copy_column.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32229</link><description>FFmpeg 7.0 contains a heap-buffer-overflow at libavfilter/vf_tiltandshift.c:189:5 in copy_column.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32230 | FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a negative-size-param bug at libavcodec/mpegvideo_enc.c:1216:21 in load_input_picture ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32230</link><description>FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a negative-size-param bug at libavcodec/mpegvideo_enc.c:1216:21 in load_input_picture in FFmpeg7.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39249 | Async &lt;= 2.6.4 and &lt;= 3.2.5 are vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) while parsing function in autoinject function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39249</link><description>Async &lt;= 2.6.4 and &lt;= 3.2.5 are vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) while parsing function in autoinject function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39236 | Gradio v4.36.1 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the component /gradio/component_meta.py. This vulnerability is t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39236</link><description>Gradio v4.36.1 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the component /gradio/component_meta.py. This vulnerability is triggered via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39303 | Weblate vulnerabler to improper sanitization of project backups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39303</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. Prior to version 5.6.2, Weblate didn't correctly validate filenames when restoring project backup. It may be possible to gain unauthorized access to files on the server using a crafted ZIP file. This issue has been addressed in Weblate 5.6.2. As a workaround, do not allow untrusted users to create projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38513 | Fiber Session Middleware Token Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38513</link><description>Fiber is an Express-inspired web framework written in Go A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.52.5 is a session middleware issue in GoFiber versions 2 and above. This vulnerability allows users to supply their own session_id value, resulting in the creation of a session with that key. If a website relies on the mere presence of a session for security purposes, this can lead to significant security risks, including unauthorized access and session fixation attacks. All users utilizing GoFiber's session middleware in the affected versions are impacted. The issue has been addressed in version 2.52.5. Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade to version 2.52.5 or higher to mitigate this vulnerability. Users who are unable to upgrade immediately can apply the following workarounds to reduce the risk: Either implement additional validation to ensure session IDs are not supplied by the user and are securely generated by the server, or regularly rotate session IDs and enforce strict session expiration policies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37145 | GHSL-2023-247: Flowise xss in /api/v1/chatflows-streaming/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37145</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `/api/v1/chatflows-streaming/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37146 | GHSL-2023-248: Flowise xss in /api/v1/credentials/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37146</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `/api/v1/credentials/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37298 | Potential memory exhaustion attack due to sparse slice deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37298</link><description>gorilla/schema converts structs to and from form values. Prior to version 1.4.1 Running `schema.Decoder.Decode()` on a struct that has a field of type `[]struct{...}` opens it up to malicious attacks regarding memory allocations, taking advantage of the sparse slice functionality. Any use of `schema.Decoder.Decode()` on a struct with arrays of other structs could be vulnerable to this memory exhaustion vulnerability. Version 1.4.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39251 | An issue in the component ControlCenter.sys/ControlCenter64.sys of ThundeRobot Control Center v2.0.0.10 allows attackers to access sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39251</link><description>An issue in the component ControlCenter.sys/ControlCenter64.sys of ThundeRobot Control Center v2.0.0.10 allows attackers to access sensitive information, execute arbitrary code, or escalate privileges via sending crafted IOCTL requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36387 | Apache HTTP Server: DoS by Null pointer in websocket over HTTP/2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36387</link><description>Serving WebSocket protocol upgrades over a HTTP/2 connection could result in a Null Pointer dereference, leading to a crash of the server process, degrading performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36423 | GHSL-2023-246: Flowise xss in /api/v1/public-chatflows/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36423</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `/api/v1/public-chatflows/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38472 | Apache HTTP Server on WIndows UNC SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38472</link><description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests or content 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60 which fixes this issue.  Note: Existing configurations that access UNC paths will have to configure new directive "UNCList" to allow access during request processing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38473 | Apache HTTP Server proxy encoding problem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38473</link><description>Encoding problem in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows request URLs with incorrect encoding to be sent to backend services, potentially bypassing authentication via crafted requests.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38474 | Apache HTTP Server weakness with encoded question marks in backreferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38474</link><description>Substitution encoding issue in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows attacker to execute scripts in
directories permitted by the configuration but not directly reachable by any URL or source disclosure of scripts meant to only to be executed as CGI.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.

Some RewriteRules that capture and substitute unsafely will now fail unless rewrite flag "UnsafeAllow3F" is specified.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38475 | Apache HTTP Server weakness in mod_rewrite when first segment of substitution matches filesystem path.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38475</link><description>Improper escaping of output in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to map URLs to filesystem locations that are permitted to be served by the server but are not intentionally/directly reachable by any URL, resulting in code execution or source code disclosure. 

Substitutions in server context that use a backreferences or variables as the first segment of the substitution are affected.  Some unsafe RewiteRules will be broken by this change and the rewrite flag "UnsafePrefixStat" can be used to opt back in once ensuring the substitution is appropriately constrained.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38476 | Apache HTTP Server may use exploitable/malicious backend application output to run local handlers via internal redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38476</link><description>Vulnerability in core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier are vulnerably to information disclosure, SSRF or local script execution via backend applications whose response headers are malicious or exploitable.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38477 | Apache HTTP Server: Crash resulting in Denial of Service in mod_proxy via a malicious request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38477</link><description>null pointer dereference in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to crash the server via a malicious request.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39573 | Apache HTTP Server: mod_rewrite proxy handler substitution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39573</link><description>Potential SSRF in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to cause unsafe RewriteRules to unexpectedly setup URL's to be handled by mod_proxy.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39878 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 private key could be exposed via testing GitHub App Connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39878</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 private key could be exposed via testing GitHub App Connection</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39879 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 application token could be exposed in EC2 Cloud Profile settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39879</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 application token could be exposed in EC2 Cloud Profile settings</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36997 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in conf-web/settings REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36997</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312, an admin user could store and execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the browser context of another Splunk user through the conf-web/settings REST endpoint. This could potentially cause a persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) exploit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36993 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Web Bulletin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36993</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the admin or power Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through a Splunk Web Bulletin Messages that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36995 | Low-privileged user could create experimental items</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36995</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the admin or power Splunk roles could create experimental items.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21586 | Junos OS: SRX Series: Specific valid traffic leads to a PFE crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21586</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

If an SRX Series device receives specific valid traffic destined to the device, it will cause the PFE to crash and restart.  Continued receipt and processing of this traffic will create a sustained DoS condition.

This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series:

  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S7.9,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S5.3,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S4.11,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3.




Junos OS versions prior to 21.4R1 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36982 | Denial of Service through null pointer reference in “cluster/config” REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36982</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.109 and 9.1.2308.207, an attacker could trigger a null pointer reference on the “cluster/config” REST endpoint, which could result in a crash of the Splunk daemon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36983 | Command Injection using External Lookups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36983</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.109 and 9.1.2308.207, an authenticated user could create an external lookup that calls a legacy internal function. The authenticated user could use this internal function to insert code into the Splunk platform installation directory. From there, the user could execute arbitrary code on the Splunk platform Instance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36984 | Remote Code Execution through Serialized Session Payload in Splunk Enterprise on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36984</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 on Windows, an authenticated user could execute a specially crafted query that they could then use to serialize untrusted data. The attacker could use the query to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36985 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) through an external lookup due to “copybuckets.py“ script in the “splunk_archiver“ application in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36985</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin“ or “power“ Splunk roles could cause a Remote Code Execution through an external lookup that references the “splunk_archiver“ application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36986 | Risky command safeguards bypass through Search ID query in Analytics Workspace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36986</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, an authenticated user could run risky commands using the permissions of a higher-privileged user to bypass [SPL safeguards for risky commands](https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/SplunkCloud/latest/Security/SPLsafeguards) in the Analytics Workspace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The vulnerability requires the authenticated user to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser. The authenticated user should not be able to exploit the vulnerability at will.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36987 | Insecure File Upload in the indexing/preview REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36987</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200, an authenticated, low-privileged user who does not hold the admin or power Splunk roles could upload a file with an arbitrary extension using the indexing/preview REST endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36989 | Low-privileged user could create notifications in Splunk Web Bulletin Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36989</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could create notifications in Splunk Web Bulletin Messages that all users on the instance receive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36990 | Denial of Service (DoS) on the datamodel/web REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36990</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.100, an authenticated, low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could send a specially crafted HTTP POST request to the datamodel/web REST endpoint in Splunk Enterprise, potentially causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36991 | Path Traversal on the “/modules/messaging/“ endpoint in Splunk Enterprise on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36991</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise on Windows versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10, an attacker could perform a path traversal on the “/modules/messaging/“ endpoint in Splunk Enterprise on Windows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This vulnerability should only affect Splunk Enterprise on Windows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36992 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Dashboard Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36992</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through a View that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.&lt;br /&gt;The “url” parameter of the Dashboard element does not have proper input validation to reject invalid URLs, which could lead to a Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) exploit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36994 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Dashboard Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36994</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through a View and Splunk Web Bulletin Messages that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36996 | Information Disclosure of user names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36996</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.109, an attacker could determine whether or not another user exists on the instance by deciphering the error response that they would likely receive from the instance when they attempt to log in. This disclosure could then lead to additional brute-force password-guessing attacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This vulnerability would require that the Splunk platform instance uses the Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication scheme.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20399 | A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36421 | GHSL-2023-234: Flowise Cors Misconfiguration in packages/server/src/index.ts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36421</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, A CORS misconfiguration sets the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header to all, allowing arbitrary origins to connect to the website. In the default configuration (unauthenticated), arbitrary origins may be able to make requests to Flowise, stealing information from the user. This CORS misconfiguration may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker attackers without access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36422 | GHSL-2023-245: Flowise xss in api/v1/chatflows/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36422</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `api/v1/chatflows/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36420 | GHSL-2023-232: Flowise Path Injection at /api/v1/openai-assistants-file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36420</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, the `/api/v1/openai-assistants-file` endpoint in `index.ts` is vulnerable to arbitrary file read due to lack of sanitization of the `fileName` body parameter. No known patches for this issue are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36401 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in evaluating property name expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36401</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Prior to versions 2.23.6, 2.24.4, and 2.25.2, multiple OGC request parameters allow Remote Code Execution (RCE) by unauthenticated users through specially crafted input against a default GeoServer installation due to unsafely evaluating property names as XPath expressions.

The GeoTools library API that GeoServer calls evaluates property/attribute names for feature types in a way that unsafely passes them to the commons-jxpath library which can execute arbitrary code when evaluating XPath expressions. This XPath evaluation is intended to be used only by complex feature types (i.e., Application Schema data stores) but is incorrectly being applied to simple feature types as well which makes this vulnerability apply to **ALL** GeoServer instances. No public PoC is provided but this vulnerability has been confirmed to be exploitable through WFS GetFeature, WFS GetPropertyValue, WMS GetMap, WMS GetFeatureInfo, WMS GetLegendGraphic and WPS Execute requests. This vulnerability can lead to executing arbitrary code.

Versions 2.23.6, 2.24.4, and 2.25.2 contain a patch for the issue. A workaround exists by removing the `gt-complex-x.y.jar` file from the GeoServer where `x.y` is the GeoTools version (e.g., `gt-complex-31.1.jar` if running GeoServer 2.25.1). This will remove the vulnerable code from GeoServer but may break some GeoServer functionality or prevent GeoServer from deploying if the gt-complex module is needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6376 | ejson shell parser in MongoDB Compass maybe bypassed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6376</link><description>MongoDB Compass may be susceptible to code injection due to insufficient sandbox protection settings with the usage of ejson shell parser in Compass' connection handling. This issue affects MongoDB Compass versions prior to version 1.42.2</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6375 | Missing authorization check may lead to shard key refinement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6375</link><description>A command for refining a collection shard key is missing an authorization check. This may cause the command to run directly on a shard, leading to either degradation of query performance, or to revealing chunk boundaries through timing side channels. This affects MongoDB Server v5.0 versions, prior to 5.0.22, MongoDB Server v6.0 versions, prior to 6.0.11 and MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34696 |  GeoServer&amp;#x27;s Server Status shows sensitive environmental variables and Java properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34696</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Starting in version 2.10.0 and prior to versions 2.24.4 and 2.25.1, GeoServer's Server Status page and REST API lists all environment variables and Java properties to any GeoServer user with administrative rights as part of those modules' status message. These variables/properties can also contain sensitive information, such as database passwords or API keys/tokens. Additionally, many community-developed GeoServer container images `export` other credentials from their start-up scripts as environment variables to the GeoServer (`java`) process. The precise scope of the issue depends on which container image is used and how it is configured.

The `about status` API endpoint which powers the Server Status page is only available to administrators.Depending on the operating environment, administrators might have legitimate access to credentials in other ways, but this issue defeats more sophisticated controls (like break-glass access to secrets or role accounts).By default, GeoServer only allows same-origin authenticated API access. This limits the scope for a third-party attacker to use an administrator’s credentials to gain access to credentials. The researchers who found the vulnerability were unable to determine any other conditions under which the GeoServer REST API may be available more broadly.

Users should update container images to use GeoServer 2.24.4 or 2.25.1 to get the bug fix. As a workaround, leave environment variables and Java system properties hidden by default. Those who provide the option to re-enable it should communicate the impact and risks so that users can make an informed choice.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43554 | Improper Restriction of Operations withing the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43554</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL handler in FastRPC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21456 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21456</link><description>Information Disclosure while parsing beacon frame in STA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21457 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21457</link><description>INformation disclosure while handling Multi-link IE in beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21458 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21458</link><description>Information disclosure while handling SA query action frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21460 | Use of Insufficiently Random Values in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21460</link><description>Information disclosure when ASLR relocates the IMEM and Secure DDR portions as one chunk in virtual address space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21461 | Double Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21461</link><description>Memory corruption while performing finish HMAC operation when context is freed by keymaster.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21462 | Buffer Over-read in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21462</link><description>Transient DOS while loading the TA ELF file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21465 | Buffer Over-read in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21465</link><description>Memory corruption while processing key blob passed by the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21466 | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21466</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing sub-IE length during new IE generation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21469 | Permissions, Privileges, and Access Control issues in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21469</link><description>Memory corruption when an invoke call and a TEE call are bound for the same trusted application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21482 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Linux Boot Loader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21482</link><description>Memory corruption during the secure boot process, when the `bootm` command is used, it bypasses the authentication of the kernel/rootfs image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23368 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Qualcomm IPC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23368</link><description>Memory corruption when allocating and accessing an entry in an SMEM partition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23372 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23372</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL call for GPU memory allocation and size param is greater than expected size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23373 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23373</link><description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap operation fails, the DMA and anon buffers are getting released.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23380 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23380</link><description>Memory corruption while handling user packets during VBO bind operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24749 | Classpath resource disclosure in GWC Web Resource API on Windows / Tomcat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24749</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Prior to versions 2.23.5 and 2.24.3, if GeoServer is deployed in the Windows operating system using an Apache Tomcat web application server, it is possible to bypass existing input validation in the GeoWebCache ByteStreamController class and read arbitrary classpath resources with specific file name extensions. If GeoServer is also deployed as a web archive using the data directory embedded in the `geoserver.war` file (rather than an external data directory), it will likely be possible to read specific resources to gain administrator privileges. However, it is very unlikely that production environments will be using the embedded data directory since, depending on how GeoServer is deployed, it will be erased and re-installed (which would also reset to the default password) either every time the server restarts or every time a new GeoServer WAR is installed and is therefore difficult to maintain. An external data directory will always be used if GeoServer is running in standalone mode (via an installer or a binary). Versions 2.23.5 and 2.24.3 contain a patch for the issue. Some workarounds are available. One may change from a Windows environment to a Linux environment; or change from Apache Tomcat to Jetty application server. One may also disable anonymous access to the embeded GeoWebCache administration and status pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6050 | Reflected XSS in SOWA OPAC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6050</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability in SOKRATES-software SOWA OPAC allows a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker might trick somebody into using a crafted URL, which will cause a script to be run in user's browser. This issue affects SOWA OPAC software in versions from 4.0 before 4.9.10, from 5.0 before 6.2.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38953 | phpok 6.4.003 contains a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ok_f() method under the framework/api/upload_control.php file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38953</link><description>phpok 6.4.003 contains a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ok_f() method under the framework/api/upload_control.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38987 | aofl cli-lib v3.14.0 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component defaultsDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38987</link><description>aofl cli-lib v3.14.0 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component defaultsDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38990 | Tada5hi sp-common v0.5.4 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38990</link><description>Tada5hi sp-common v0.5.4 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38991 | akbr patch-into v1.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function patchInto. This vulnerability allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38991</link><description>akbr patch-into v1.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function patchInto. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38992 | airvertco frappejs v0.0.11 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function registerView. This vulnerability allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38992</link><description>airvertco frappejs v0.0.11 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function registerView. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38993 | rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function empty. This vulnerability allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38993</link><description>rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function empty. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38994 | amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38994</link><description>amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38996 | ag-grid-community v31.3.2 and ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 were discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the _.mergeDeep function. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38996</link><description>ag-grid-community v31.3.2 and ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 were discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the _.mergeDeep function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38997 | adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extendDefaults. This vulnerability allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38997</link><description>adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extendDefaults. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38998 | jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function config. This vulnerability allows attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38998</link><description>jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function config. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38999 | jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function s.contexts._.configure. This vulnerability allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38999</link><description>jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function s.contexts._.configure. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39000 | adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39000</link><description>adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39001 | ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component _ModuleSupport.jsonApply. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39001</link><description>ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component _ModuleSupport.jsonApply. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39002 | rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function util.clone. This vulnerability allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39002</link><description>rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function util.clone. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39003 | amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function setValue. This vulnerability allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39003</link><description>amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function setValue. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39008 | robinweser fast-loops v1.1.3 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function objectMergeDeep. This vulnerability allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39008</link><description>robinweser fast-loops v1.1.3 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function objectMergeDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39013 | 2o3t-utility v0.1.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39013</link><description>2o3t-utility v0.1.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39014 | ahilfoley cahil/utils v2.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function set. This vulnerability allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39014</link><description>ahilfoley cahil/utils v2.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function set. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39015 | cafebazaar hod v0.4.14 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function request. This vulnerability allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39015</link><description>cafebazaar hod v0.4.14 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function request. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39016 | che3vinci c3/utils-1 1.0.131 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function assign. This vulnerability allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39016</link><description>che3vinci c3/utils-1 1.0.131 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function assign. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39017 | agreejs shared v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeInternalComponents. This vulnerability allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39017</link><description>agreejs shared v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeInternalComponents. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39018 | harvey-woo cat5th/key-serializer v0.2.5 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function "query". This vulnerability allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39018</link><description>harvey-woo cat5th/key-serializer v0.2.5 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function "query". This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39853 | adolph_dudu ratio-swiper 0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39853</link><description>adolph_dudu ratio-swiper 0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6424 | Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6424</link><description>External server-side request vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version, which could allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to exploit the endpoint "/api/Proxy/Post?userName=&amp;amp;password=&amp;amp;uri=&lt;ARCHIVO|URL INTERNA|IP/HOST" to read the source code of web files, read internal files or access network resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6425 | Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6425</link><description>Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version. An unauthenticated remote attacker can register user accounts without being authenticated from the route "/account/Register/" and in the parameters "UserName=&amp;amp;Password=&amp;amp;ConfirmPassword=".</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6387 | Openssh: possible remote code execution due to a race condition in signal handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6387</link><description>A signal handler race condition was found in OpenSSH's server (sshd), where a client does not authenticate within LoginGraceTime seconds (120 by default, 600 in old OpenSSH versions), then sshd's SIGALRM handler is called asynchronously. However, this signal handler calls various functions that are not async-signal-safe, for example, syslog().</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4007 | Hard coded default credential contained in install package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4007</link><description>Default credential in install package in ABB ASPECT; NEXUS Series; MATRIX Series version 3.07 allows attacker to login to product instances wrongly configured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0153 | Mali GPU Firmware allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0153</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Firmware, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Firmware allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU processing operations to access a limited amount outside of buffer bounds. If the operations are carefully prepared, then this in turn could give them access to all system memory. This issue affects Valhall GPU Firmware: from r29p0 through r46p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Firmware: from r41p0 through r46p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39427 | In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39427</link><description>In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39428 | In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39428</link><description>In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39429 | In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39429</link><description>In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39430 | In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39430</link><description>In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4934 | Quiz And Survey Master &amp;lt; 9.0.2 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4934</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.0.2 does not validate and escape some of its Quiz fields before outputting them back in a page/post where the Quiz is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6130 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.26 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6130</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.26 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20076 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20076</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01297806; Issue ID: MSV-1481.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20077 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20077</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01297807; Issue ID: MSV-1482.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20078 | In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20078</link><description>In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08737250; Issue ID: MSV-1452.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20079 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20079</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08044040; Issue ID: MSV-1491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20080 | In gnss service, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to improper certificate validation. This could lead to remote escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20080</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to improper certificate validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08720039; Issue ID: MSV-1424.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20081 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20081</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08719602; Issue ID: MSV-1412.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3123 | CHANGING Mobile One Time Password - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3123</link><description>CHANGING Mobile One Time Password's uploading function in a hidden page does not filter file type properly. Remote attackers with  administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload and run malicious file to execute system commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3122 | CHANGING Mobile One Time Password - Arbitrary File Reading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3122</link><description>CHANGING Mobile One Time Password does not properly filter parameters for the file download functionality, allowing remote attackers with administrator privilege to read arbitrary file on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38480 | "Piccoma" App for Android and iOS versions prior to 6.20.0 uses a hard-coded API key for an external service, which may allow a local attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38480</link><description>"Piccoma" App for Android and iOS versions prior to 6.20.0 uses a hard-coded API key for an external service, which may allow a local attacker to obtain the API key. Note that the users of the app are not directly affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>