<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:19:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-2150 | SourceCodester Insurance Management System file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2150</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Insurance Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255503.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2149 | CodeAstro Membership Management System settings.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2149</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file settings.php. The manipulation of the argument currency leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255502 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 17:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2148 | SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store Users.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2148</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Users.php. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 17:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2147 | SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255500.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 16:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28512 | IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28512</link><description>IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2 could allow an attacker with specific knowledge about the system to manipulate data due to improper input validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  250396.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27291 | IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27291</link><description>IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores 4.6.0, 4.6.1, 4.6.2, and 4.6.3 does not encrypt sensitive or critical information before storage or transmission which could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  248740.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43880 | IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43880</link><description>IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent 10.0 through 10.1.2 could allow a privileged user to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  240151.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2146 | SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store ?p=products cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2146</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /?p=products. The manipulation of the argument search leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255499.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0765 | Default user role exporting save state of instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0765</link><description>As a default user on a multi-user instance of AnythingLLM, you could execute a call to the `/export-data` endpoint of the system and then unzip and read that export that would enable you do exfiltrate data of the system at that save state.

This would require the attacked to be granted explicit access to the system, but they can do this at any role. Additionally, post-download, the data is deleted so no evidence would exist that the exfiltration occured.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2145 | SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store update-tracker.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2145</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/update-tracker.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255498 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22355 | IBM QRadar Suite information dislosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22355</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Products 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.18.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  280781.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43054 | IBM Engineering Test Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43054</link><description>IBM Engineering Test Management 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  267459.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47742 | IBM QRadar Suite information dislosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47742</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Products 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.18.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 could disclose sensitive information using man in the middle techniques due to not correctly enforcing all aspects of certificate validation in some circumstances.  IBM X-Force ID:  272533.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47745 | IBM MQ Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47745</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 2.0.0 LTS, 2.0.18 LTS, 3.0.0 CD, 3.0.1 CD, 2.4.0 through 2.4.7, 2.3.0 through 2.3.3, 2.2.0 through 2.2.2, and 2.3.0 through 2.3.3 stores or transmits user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user using a trace command.  IBM X-Force ID:  272638.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27255 | IBM MQ Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27255</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 2.0.0 LTS, 2.0.18 LTS, 3.0.0 CD, 3.0.1 CD, 2.4.0 through 2.4.7, 2.3.0 through 2.3.3, 2.2.0 through 2.2.2, and 2.3.0 through 2.3.3 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  283905.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 11:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26469 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Tunis Soft "Product Designer" (productdesigner) module for PrestaShop before version 1.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26469</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Tunis Soft "Product Designer" (productdesigner) module for PrestaShop before version 1.178.36, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) and escalate privileges via the url parameter in the postProcess() method.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 09:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24302 | An issue was discovered in Tunis Soft "Product Designer" (productdesigner) module for PrestaShop before version 1.178.36, allows remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24302</link><description>An issue was discovered in Tunis Soft "Product Designer" (productdesigner) module for PrestaShop before version 1.178.36, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via the postProcess() method.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 09:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25847 | SQL Injection vulnerability in MyPrestaModules "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel) Import" (simpleimportproduct) modules for PrestaShop versions 6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25847</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in MyPrestaModules "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel) Import" (simpleimportproduct) modules for PrestaShop versions 6.5.0 and before, allows attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via Send::__construct() and importProducts::_addDataToDb methods.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 08:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25839 | An issue was discovered in Webbax "Super Newsletter" (supernewsletter) module for PrestaShop versions 1.4.21 and before, allows local attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25839</link><description>An issue was discovered in Webbax "Super Newsletter" (supernewsletter) module for PrestaShop versions 1.4.21 and before, allows local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 08:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25842 | An issue was discovered in Presta World "Account Manager - Sales Representative &amp; Dealers - CRM" (prestasalesmanager) module for PrestaShop ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25842</link><description>An issue was discovered in Presta World "Account Manager - Sales Representative &amp; Dealers - CRM" (prestasalesmanager) module for PrestaShop before version 9.0, allows remote attackers to escalate privilege and obtain sensitive information via the uploadLogo() and postProcess methods.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 08:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24307 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Tunis Soft "Product Designer" (productdesigner) module for PrestaShop before version 1.178.36, allows a remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24307</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Tunis Soft "Product Designer" (productdesigner) module for PrestaShop before version 1.178.36, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the ajaxProcessCropImage() method.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 08:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25844 | An issue was discovered in Common-Services "So Flexibilite" (soflexibilite) module for PrestaShop before version 4.1.26, allows remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25844</link><description>An issue was discovered in Common-Services "So Flexibilite" (soflexibilite) module for PrestaShop before version 4.1.26, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via debug file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 07:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25551 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in sourcecodester Simple Student Attendance System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25551</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in sourcecodester Simple Student Attendance System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted GET request to web application URL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 07:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25016 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25016</link><description>IBM MQ and IBM MQ Appliance 9.0, 9.1, 9.2, 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service due to incorrect buffering logic.  IBM X-Force ID:  281279.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 03:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2135 | Bdtask Hospita AutoManager Hospital Activities Page form cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2135</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Hospita AutoManager up to 20240223 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /hospital_activities/birth/form of the component Hospital Activities Page. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input &lt;img src=a onerror=alert(1)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255497 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 03:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2134 | Bdtask Hospita AutoManager Investigation Report cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2134</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask Hospita AutoManager up to 20240223 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /investigation/delete/ of the component Investigation Report Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255496. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2133 | Bdtask Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution Manage Sale Page manage_invoice cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2133</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Bdtask Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution 4.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /dashboard/Cinvoice/manage_invoice of the component Manage Sale Page. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255495.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 23:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52559 | iommu/vt-d: Avoid memory allocation in iommu_suspend()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52559</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommu/vt-d: Avoid memory allocation in iommu_suspend()

The iommu_suspend() syscore suspend callback is invoked with IRQ disabled.
Allocating memory with the GFP_KERNEL flag may re-enable IRQs during
the suspend callback, which can cause intermittent suspend/hibernation
problems with the following kernel traces:

Calling iommu_suspend+0x0/0x1d0
------------[ cut here ]------------
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 15 at kernel/time/timekeeping.c:868 ktime_get+0x9b/0xb0
...
CPU: 0 PID: 15 Comm: rcu_preempt Tainted: G     U      E      6.3-intel #r1
RIP: 0010:ktime_get+0x9b/0xb0
...
Call Trace:
 &lt;IRQ&gt;
 tick_sched_timer+0x22/0x90
 ? __pfx_tick_sched_timer+0x10/0x10
 __hrtimer_run_queues+0x111/0x2b0
 hrtimer_interrupt+0xfa/0x230
 __sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x63/0x140
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x7b/0xa0
 &lt;/IRQ&gt;
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 asm_sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x1f/0x30
...
------------[ cut here ]------------
Interrupts enabled after iommu_suspend+0x0/0x1d0
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 27420 at drivers/base/syscore.c:68 syscore_suspend+0x147/0x270
CPU: 0 PID: 27420 Comm: rtcwake Tainted: G     U  W   E      6.3-intel #r1
RIP: 0010:syscore_suspend+0x147/0x270
...
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 hibernation_snapshot+0x25b/0x670
 hibernate+0xcd/0x390
 state_store+0xcf/0xe0
 kobj_attr_store+0x13/0x30
 sysfs_kf_write+0x3f/0x50
 kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x128/0x200
 vfs_write+0x1fd/0x3c0
 ksys_write+0x6f/0xf0
 __x64_sys_write+0x1d/0x30
 do_syscall_64+0x3b/0x90
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x72/0xdc

Given that only 4 words memory is needed, avoid the memory allocation in
iommu_suspend().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52560 | mm/damon/vaddr-test: fix memory leak in damon_do_test_apply_three_regions()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52560</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/damon/vaddr-test: fix memory leak in damon_do_test_apply_three_regions()

When CONFIG_DAMON_VADDR_KUNIT_TEST=y and making CONFIG_DEBUG_KMEMLEAK=y
and CONFIG_DEBUG_KMEMLEAK_AUTO_SCAN=y, the below memory leak is detected.

Since commit 9f86d624292c ("mm/damon/vaddr-test: remove unnecessary
variables"), the damon_destroy_ctx() is removed, but still call
damon_new_target() and damon_new_region(), the damon_region which is
allocated by kmem_cache_alloc() in damon_new_region() and the damon_target
which is allocated by kmalloc in damon_new_target() are not freed.  And
the damon_region which is allocated in damon_new_region() in
damon_set_regions() is also not freed.

So use damon_destroy_target to free all the damon_regions and damon_target.

    unreferenced object 0xffff888107c9a940 (size 64):
      comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1069, jiffies 4294670592 (age 732.761s)
      hex dump (first 32 bytes):
        00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 06 00 00 00 6b 6b 6b 6b  ............kkkk
        60 c7 9c 07 81 88 ff ff f8 cb 9c 07 81 88 ff ff  `...............
      backtrace:
        [&lt;ffffffff817e0167&gt;] kmalloc_trace+0x27/0xa0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c11cf&gt;] damon_new_target+0x3f/0x1b0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c7d55&gt;] damon_do_test_apply_three_regions.constprop.0+0x95/0x3e0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c82be&gt;] damon_test_apply_three_regions1+0x21e/0x260
        [&lt;ffffffff829fce6a&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x4a/0x90
        [&lt;ffffffff81237cf6&gt;] kthread+0x2b6/0x380
        [&lt;ffffffff81097add&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70
        [&lt;ffffffff81003791&gt;] ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20
    unreferenced object 0xffff8881079cc740 (size 56):
      comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1069, jiffies 4294670592 (age 732.761s)
      hex dump (first 32 bytes):
        05 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 14 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
        6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 00 00 00 00 6b 6b 6b 6b  kkkkkkkk....kkkk
      backtrace:
        [&lt;ffffffff819bc492&gt;] damon_new_region+0x22/0x1c0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c7d91&gt;] damon_do_test_apply_three_regions.constprop.0+0xd1/0x3e0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c82be&gt;] damon_test_apply_three_regions1+0x21e/0x260
        [&lt;ffffffff829fce6a&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x4a/0x90
        [&lt;ffffffff81237cf6&gt;] kthread+0x2b6/0x380
        [&lt;ffffffff81097add&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70
        [&lt;ffffffff81003791&gt;] ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20
    unreferenced object 0xffff888107c9ac40 (size 64):
      comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1071, jiffies 4294670595 (age 732.843s)
      hex dump (first 32 bytes):
        00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 06 00 00 00 6b 6b 6b 6b  ............kkkk
        a0 cc 9c 07 81 88 ff ff 78 a1 76 07 81 88 ff ff  ........x.v.....
      backtrace:
        [&lt;ffffffff817e0167&gt;] kmalloc_trace+0x27/0xa0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c11cf&gt;] damon_new_target+0x3f/0x1b0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c7d55&gt;] damon_do_test_apply_three_regions.constprop.0+0x95/0x3e0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c851e&gt;] damon_test_apply_three_regions2+0x21e/0x260
        [&lt;ffffffff829fce6a&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x4a/0x90
        [&lt;ffffffff81237cf6&gt;] kthread+0x2b6/0x380
        [&lt;ffffffff81097add&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70
        [&lt;ffffffff81003791&gt;] ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20
    unreferenced object 0xffff8881079ccc80 (size 56):
      comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1071, jiffies 4294670595 (age 732.843s)
      hex dump (first 32 bytes):
        05 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 14 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
        6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 6b 00 00 00 00 6b 6b 6b 6b  kkkkkkkk....kkkk
      backtrace:
        [&lt;ffffffff819bc492&gt;] damon_new_region+0x22/0x1c0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c7d91&gt;] damon_do_test_apply_three_regions.constprop.0+0xd1/0x3e0
        [&lt;ffffffff819c851e&gt;] damon_test_apply_three_regions2+0x21e/0x260
        [&lt;ffffffff829fce6a&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x4a/0x90
        [&lt;ffffffff81237cf6&gt;] kthread+0x2b6/0x380
        [&lt;ffffffff81097add&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70
        [&lt;ffff
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52561 | arm64: dts: qcom: sdm845-db845c: Mark cont splash memory region as reserved</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52561</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

arm64: dts: qcom: sdm845-db845c: Mark cont splash memory region as reserved

Adding a reserved memory region for the framebuffer memory
(the splash memory region set up by the bootloader).

It fixes a kernel panic (arm-smmu: Unhandled context fault
at this particular memory region) reported on DB845c running
v5.10.y.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52562 | mm/slab_common: fix slab_caches list corruption after kmem_cache_destroy()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52562</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/slab_common: fix slab_caches list corruption after kmem_cache_destroy()

After the commit in Fixes:, if a module that created a slab cache does not
release all of its allocated objects before destroying the cache (at rmmod
time), we might end up releasing the kmem_cache object without removing it
from the slab_caches list thus corrupting the list as kmem_cache_destroy()
ignores the return value from shutdown_cache(), which in turn never removes
the kmem_cache object from slabs_list in case __kmem_cache_shutdown() fails
to release all of the cache's slabs.

This is easily observable on a kernel built with CONFIG_DEBUG_LIST=y
as after that ill release the system will immediately trip on list_add,
or list_del, assertions similar to the one shown below as soon as another
kmem_cache gets created, or destroyed:

  [ 1041.213632] list_del corruption. next-&gt;prev should be ffff89f596fb5768, but was 52f1e5016aeee75d. (next=ffff89f595a1b268)
  [ 1041.219165] ------------[ cut here ]------------
  [ 1041.221517] kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:62!
  [ 1041.223452] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  [ 1041.225408] CPU: 2 PID: 1852 Comm: rmmod Kdump: loaded Tainted: G    B   W  OE      6.5.0 #15
  [ 1041.228244] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS edk2-20230524-3.fc37 05/24/2023
  [ 1041.231212] RIP: 0010:__list_del_entry_valid+0xae/0xb0

Another quick way to trigger this issue, in a kernel with CONFIG_SLUB=y,
is to set slub_debug to poison the released objects and then just run
cat /proc/slabinfo after removing the module that leaks slab objects,
in which case the kernel will panic:

  [   50.954843] general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xa56b6b6b6b6b6b8b: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  [   50.961545] CPU: 2 PID: 1495 Comm: cat Kdump: loaded Tainted: G    B   W  OE      6.5.0 #15
  [   50.966808] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS edk2-20230524-3.fc37 05/24/2023
  [   50.972663] RIP: 0010:get_slabinfo+0x42/0xf0

This patch fixes this issue by properly checking shutdown_cache()'s
return value before taking the kmem_cache_release() branch.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52563 | drm/meson: fix memory leak on -&amp;gt;hpd_notify callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52563</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/meson: fix memory leak on -&gt;hpd_notify callback

The EDID returned by drm_bridge_get_edid() needs to be freed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52564 | Revert &amp;quot;tty: n_gsm: fix UAF in gsm_cleanup_mux&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52564</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "tty: n_gsm: fix UAF in gsm_cleanup_mux"

This reverts commit 9b9c8195f3f0d74a826077fc1c01b9ee74907239.

The commit above is reverted as it did not solve the original issue.

gsm_cleanup_mux() tries to free up the virtual ttys by calling
gsm_dlci_release() for each available DLCI. There, dlci_put() is called to
decrease the reference counter for the DLCI via tty_port_put() which
finally calls gsm_dlci_free(). This already clears the pointer which is
being checked in gsm_cleanup_mux() before calling gsm_dlci_release().
Therefore, it is not necessary to clear this pointer in gsm_cleanup_mux()
as done in the reverted commit. The commit introduces a null pointer
dereference:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 ? __die+0x1f/0x70
 ? page_fault_oops+0x156/0x420
 ? search_exception_tables+0x37/0x50
 ? fixup_exception+0x21/0x310
 ? exc_page_fault+0x69/0x150
 ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x26/0x30
 ? tty_port_put+0x19/0xa0
 gsmtty_cleanup+0x29/0x80 [n_gsm]
 release_one_tty+0x37/0xe0
 process_one_work+0x1e6/0x3e0
 worker_thread+0x4c/0x3d0
 ? __pfx_worker_thread+0x10/0x10
 kthread+0xe1/0x110
 ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
 ret_from_fork+0x2f/0x50
 ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30
 &lt;/TASK&gt;

The actual issue is that nothing guards dlci_put() from being called
multiple times while the tty driver was triggered but did not yet finished
calling gsm_dlci_free().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52565 | media: uvcvideo: Fix OOB read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52565</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: uvcvideo: Fix OOB read

If the index provided by the user is bigger than the mask size, we might do
an out of bound read.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52566 | nilfs2: fix potential use after free in nilfs_gccache_submit_read_data()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52566</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix potential use after free in nilfs_gccache_submit_read_data()

In nilfs_gccache_submit_read_data(), brelse(bh) is called to drop the
reference count of bh when the call to nilfs_dat_translate() fails.  If
the reference count hits 0 and its owner page gets unlocked, bh may be
freed.  However, bh-&gt;b_page is dereferenced to put the page after that,
which may result in a use-after-free bug.  This patch moves the release
operation after unlocking and putting the page.

NOTE: The function in question is only called in GC, and in combination
with current userland tools, address translation using DAT does not occur
in that function, so the code path that causes this issue will not be
executed.  However, it is possible to run that code path by intentionally
modifying the userland GC library or by calling the GC ioctl directly.

[konishi.ryusuke@gmail.com: NOTE added to the commit log]</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52567 | serial: 8250_port: Check IRQ data before use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52567</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

serial: 8250_port: Check IRQ data before use

In case the leaf driver wants to use IRQ polling (irq = 0) and
IIR register shows that an interrupt happened in the 8250 hardware
the IRQ data can be NULL. In such a case we need to skip the wake
event as we came to this path from the timer interrupt and quite
likely system is already awake.

Without this fix we have got an Oops:

    serial8250: ttyS0 at I/O 0x3f8 (irq = 0, base_baud = 115200) is a 16550A
    ...
    BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000010
    RIP: 0010:serial8250_handle_irq+0x7c/0x240
    Call Trace:
     ? serial8250_handle_irq+0x7c/0x240
     ? __pfx_serial8250_timeout+0x10/0x10</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52568 | x86/sgx: Resolves SECS reclaim vs. page fault for EAUG race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52568</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/sgx: Resolves SECS reclaim vs. page fault for EAUG race

The SGX EPC reclaimer (ksgxd) may reclaim the SECS EPC page for an
enclave and set secs.epc_page to NULL. The SECS page is used for EAUG
and ELDU in the SGX page fault handler. However, the NULL check for
secs.epc_page is only done for ELDU, not EAUG before being used.

Fix this by doing the same NULL check and reloading of the SECS page as
needed for both EAUG and ELDU.

The SECS page holds global enclave metadata. It can only be reclaimed
when there are no other enclave pages remaining. At that point,
virtually nothing can be done with the enclave until the SECS page is
paged back in.

An enclave can not run nor generate page faults without a resident SECS
page. But it is still possible for a #PF for a non-SECS page to race
with paging out the SECS page: when the last resident non-SECS page A
triggers a #PF in a non-resident page B, and then page A and the SECS
both are paged out before the #PF on B is handled.

Hitting this bug requires that race triggered with a #PF for EAUG.
Following is a trace when it happens.

BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
RIP: 0010:sgx_encl_eaug_page+0xc7/0x210
Call Trace:
 ? __kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x16a/0x440
 ? xa_load+0x6e/0xa0
 sgx_vma_fault+0x119/0x230
 __do_fault+0x36/0x140
 do_fault+0x12f/0x400
 __handle_mm_fault+0x728/0x1110
 handle_mm_fault+0x105/0x310
 do_user_addr_fault+0x1ee/0x750
 ? __this_cpu_preempt_check+0x13/0x20
 exc_page_fault+0x76/0x180
 asm_exc_page_fault+0x27/0x30</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52569 | btrfs: remove BUG() after failure to insert delayed dir index item</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52569</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: remove BUG() after failure to insert delayed dir index item

Instead of calling BUG() when we fail to insert a delayed dir index item
into the delayed node's tree, we can just release all the resources we
have allocated/acquired before and return the error to the caller. This is
fine because all existing call chains undo anything they have done before
calling btrfs_insert_delayed_dir_index() or BUG_ON (when creating pending
snapshots in the transaction commit path).

So remove the BUG() call and do proper error handling.

This relates to a syzbot report linked below, but does not fix it because
it only prevents hitting a BUG(), it does not fix the issue where somehow
we attempt to use twice the same index number for different index items.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52570 | vfio/mdev: Fix a null-ptr-deref bug for mdev_unregister_parent()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52570</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/mdev: Fix a null-ptr-deref bug for mdev_unregister_parent()

Inject fault while probing mdpy.ko, if kstrdup() of create_dir() fails in
kobject_add_internal() in kobject_init_and_add() in mdev_type_add()
in parent_create_sysfs_files(), it will return 0 and probe successfully.
And when rmmod mdpy.ko, the mdpy_dev_exit() will call
mdev_unregister_parent(), the mdev_type_remove() may traverse uninitialized
parent-&gt;types[i] in parent_remove_sysfs_files(), and it will cause
below null-ptr-deref.

If mdev_type_add() fails, return the error code and kset_unregister()
to fix the issue.

 general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000002: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN
 KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000010-0x0000000000000017]
 CPU: 2 PID: 10215 Comm: rmmod Tainted: G        W        N 6.6.0-rc2+ #20
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
 RIP: 0010:__kobject_del+0x62/0x1c0
 Code: 48 89 fa 48 c1 ea 03 80 3c 02 00 0f 85 51 01 00 00 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 48 8b 6b 28 48 8d 7d 10 48 89 fa 48 c1 ea 03 &lt;80&gt; 3c 02 00 0f 85 24 01 00 00 48 8b 75 10 48 89 df 48 8d 6b 3c e8
 RSP: 0018:ffff88810695fd30 EFLAGS: 00010202
 RAX: dffffc0000000000 RBX: ffffffffa0270268 RCX: 0000000000000000
 RDX: 0000000000000002 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: 0000000000000010
 RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffffed10233a4ef1
 R10: ffff888119d2778b R11: 0000000063666572 R12: 0000000000000000
 R13: fffffbfff404e2d4 R14: dffffc0000000000 R15: ffffffffa0271660
 FS:  00007fbc81981540(0000) GS:ffff888119d00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
 CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
 CR2: 00007fc14a142dc0 CR3: 0000000110a62003 CR4: 0000000000770ee0
 DR0: ffffffff8fb0bce8 DR1: ffffffff8fb0bce9 DR2: ffffffff8fb0bcea
 DR3: ffffffff8fb0bceb DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000600
 PKRU: 55555554
 Call Trace:
  &lt;TASK&gt;
  ? die_addr+0x3d/0xa0
  ? exc_general_protection+0x144/0x220
  ? asm_exc_general_protection+0x22/0x30
  ? __kobject_del+0x62/0x1c0
  kobject_del+0x32/0x50
  parent_remove_sysfs_files+0xd6/0x170 [mdev]
  mdev_unregister_parent+0xfb/0x190 [mdev]
  ? mdev_register_parent+0x270/0x270 [mdev]
  ? find_module_all+0x9d/0xe0
  mdpy_dev_exit+0x17/0x63 [mdpy]
  __do_sys_delete_module.constprop.0+0x2fa/0x4b0
  ? module_flags+0x300/0x300
  ? __fput+0x4e7/0xa00
  do_syscall_64+0x35/0x80
  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x46/0xb0
 RIP: 0033:0x7fbc813221b7
 Code: 73 01 c3 48 8b 0d d1 8c 2c 00 f7 d8 64 89 01 48 83 c8 ff c3 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 44 00 00 b8 b0 00 00 00 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 8b 0d a1 8c 2c 00 f7 d8 64 89 01 48
 RSP: 002b:00007ffe780e0648 EFLAGS: 00000206 ORIG_RAX: 00000000000000b0
 RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007ffe780e06a8 RCX: 00007fbc813221b7
 RDX: 000000000000000a RSI: 0000000000000800 RDI: 000055e214df9b58
 RBP: 000055e214df9af0 R08: 00007ffe780df5c1 R09: 0000000000000000
 R10: 00007fbc8139ecc0 R11: 0000000000000206 R12: 00007ffe780e0870
 R13: 00007ffe780e0ed0 R14: 000055e214df9260 R15: 000055e214df9af0
  &lt;/TASK&gt;
 Modules linked in: mdpy(-) mdev vfio_iommu_type1 vfio [last unloaded: mdpy]
 Dumping ftrace buffer:
    (ftrace buffer empty)
 ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
 RIP: 0010:__kobject_del+0x62/0x1c0
 Code: 48 89 fa 48 c1 ea 03 80 3c 02 00 0f 85 51 01 00 00 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 48 8b 6b 28 48 8d 7d 10 48 89 fa 48 c1 ea 03 &lt;80&gt; 3c 02 00 0f 85 24 01 00 00 48 8b 75 10 48 89 df 48 8d 6b 3c e8
 RSP: 0018:ffff88810695fd30 EFLAGS: 00010202
 RAX: dffffc0000000000 RBX: ffffffffa0270268 RCX: 0000000000000000
 RDX: 0000000000000002 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: 0000000000000010
 RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffffed10233a4ef1
 R10: ffff888119d2778b R11: 0000000063666572 R12: 0000000000000000
 R13: fffffbfff404e2d4 R14: dffffc0000000000 R15: ffffffffa0271660
 FS:  00007fbc81981540(0000) GS:ffff888119d00000(000
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52571 | power: supply: rk817: Fix node refcount leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52571</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

power: supply: rk817: Fix node refcount leak

Dan Carpenter reports that the Smatch static checker warning has found
that there is another refcount leak in the probe function. While
of_node_put() was added in one of the return paths, it should in
fact be added for ALL return paths that return an error and at driver
removal time.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52572 | cifs: Fix UAF in cifs_demultiplex_thread()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52572</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cifs: Fix UAF in cifs_demultiplex_thread()

There is a UAF when xfstests on cifs:

  BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in smb2_is_network_name_deleted+0x27/0x160
  Read of size 4 at addr ffff88810103fc08 by task cifsd/923

  CPU: 1 PID: 923 Comm: cifsd Not tainted 6.1.0-rc4+ #45
  ...
  Call Trace:
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   dump_stack_lvl+0x34/0x44
   print_report+0x171/0x472
   kasan_report+0xad/0x130
   kasan_check_range+0x145/0x1a0
   smb2_is_network_name_deleted+0x27/0x160
   cifs_demultiplex_thread.cold+0x172/0x5a4
   kthread+0x165/0x1a0
   ret_from_fork+0x1f/0x30
   &lt;/TASK&gt;

  Allocated by task 923:
   kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
   kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
   __kasan_slab_alloc+0x54/0x60
   kmem_cache_alloc+0x147/0x320
   mempool_alloc+0xe1/0x260
   cifs_small_buf_get+0x24/0x60
   allocate_buffers+0xa1/0x1c0
   cifs_demultiplex_thread+0x199/0x10d0
   kthread+0x165/0x1a0
   ret_from_fork+0x1f/0x30

  Freed by task 921:
   kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
   kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
   kasan_save_free_info+0x2a/0x40
   ____kasan_slab_free+0x143/0x1b0
   kmem_cache_free+0xe3/0x4d0
   cifs_small_buf_release+0x29/0x90
   SMB2_negotiate+0x8b7/0x1c60
   smb2_negotiate+0x51/0x70
   cifs_negotiate_protocol+0xf0/0x160
   cifs_get_smb_ses+0x5fa/0x13c0
   mount_get_conns+0x7a/0x750
   cifs_mount+0x103/0xd00
   cifs_smb3_do_mount+0x1dd/0xcb0
   smb3_get_tree+0x1d5/0x300
   vfs_get_tree+0x41/0xf0
   path_mount+0x9b3/0xdd0
   __x64_sys_mount+0x190/0x1d0
   do_syscall_64+0x35/0x80
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x46/0xb0

The UAF is because:

 mount(pid: 921)               | cifsd(pid: 923)
-------------------------------|-------------------------------
                               | cifs_demultiplex_thread
SMB2_negotiate                 |
 cifs_send_recv                |
  compound_send_recv           |
   smb_send_rqst               |
    wait_for_response          |
     wait_event_state      [1] |
                               |  standard_receive3
                               |   cifs_handle_standard
                               |    handle_mid
                               |     mid-&gt;resp_buf = buf;  [2]
                               |     dequeue_mid           [3]
     KILL the process      [4] |
    resp_iov[i].iov_base = buf |
 free_rsp_buf              [5] |
                               |   is_network_name_deleted [6]
                               |   callback

1. After send request to server, wait the response until
    mid-&gt;mid_state != SUBMITTED;
2. Receive response from server, and set it to mid;
3. Set the mid state to RECEIVED;
4. Kill the process, the mid state already RECEIVED, get 0;
5. Handle and release the negotiate response;
6. UAF.

It can be easily reproduce with add some delay in [3] - [6].

Only sync call has the problem since async call's callback is
executed in cifsd process.

Add an extra state to mark the mid state to READY before wakeup the
waitter, then it can get the resp safely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52573 | net: rds: Fix possible NULL-pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52573</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: rds: Fix possible NULL-pointer dereference

In rds_rdma_cm_event_handler_cmn() check, if conn pointer exists
before dereferencing it as rdma_set_service_type() argument

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52574 | team: fix null-ptr-deref when team device type is changed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52574</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

team: fix null-ptr-deref when team device type is changed

Get a null-ptr-deref bug as follows with reproducer [1].

BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000228
...
RIP: 0010:vlan_dev_hard_header+0x35/0x140 [8021q]
...
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 ? __die+0x24/0x70
 ? page_fault_oops+0x82/0x150
 ? exc_page_fault+0x69/0x150
 ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x26/0x30
 ? vlan_dev_hard_header+0x35/0x140 [8021q]
 ? vlan_dev_hard_header+0x8e/0x140 [8021q]
 neigh_connected_output+0xb2/0x100
 ip6_finish_output2+0x1cb/0x520
 ? nf_hook_slow+0x43/0xc0
 ? ip6_mtu+0x46/0x80
 ip6_finish_output+0x2a/0xb0
 mld_sendpack+0x18f/0x250
 mld_ifc_work+0x39/0x160
 process_one_work+0x1e6/0x3f0
 worker_thread+0x4d/0x2f0
 ? __pfx_worker_thread+0x10/0x10
 kthread+0xe5/0x120
 ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
 ret_from_fork+0x34/0x50
 ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30

[1]
$ teamd -t team0 -d -c '{"runner": {"name": "loadbalance"}}'
$ ip link add name t-dummy type dummy
$ ip link add link t-dummy name t-dummy.100 type vlan id 100
$ ip link add name t-nlmon type nlmon
$ ip link set t-nlmon master team0
$ ip link set t-nlmon nomaster
$ ip link set t-dummy up
$ ip link set team0 up
$ ip link set t-dummy.100 down
$ ip link set t-dummy.100 master team0

When enslave a vlan device to team device and team device type is changed
from non-ether to ether, header_ops of team device is changed to
vlan_header_ops. That is incorrect and will trigger null-ptr-deref
for vlan-&gt;real_dev in vlan_dev_hard_header() because team device is not
a vlan device.

Cache eth_header_ops in team_setup(), then assign cached header_ops to
header_ops of team net device when its type is changed from non-ether
to ether to fix the bug.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52575 | x86/srso: Fix SBPB enablement for spec_rstack_overflow=off</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52575</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/srso: Fix SBPB enablement for spec_rstack_overflow=off

If the user has requested no SRSO mitigation, other mitigations can use
the lighter-weight SBPB instead of IBPB.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52576 | x86/mm, kexec, ima: Use memblock_free_late() from ima_free_kexec_buffer()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52576</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/mm, kexec, ima: Use memblock_free_late() from ima_free_kexec_buffer()

The code calling ima_free_kexec_buffer() runs long after the memblock
allocator has already been torn down, potentially resulting in a use
after free in memblock_isolate_range().

With KASAN or KFENCE, this use after free will result in a BUG
from the idle task, and a subsequent kernel panic.

Switch ima_free_kexec_buffer() over to memblock_free_late() to avoid
that bug.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52577 | dccp: fix dccp_v4_err()/dccp_v6_err() again</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52577</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dccp: fix dccp_v4_err()/dccp_v6_err() again

dh-&gt;dccph_x is the 9th byte (offset 8) in "struct dccp_hdr",
not in the "byte 7" as Jann claimed.

We need to make sure the ICMP messages are big enough,
using more standard ways (no more assumptions).

syzbot reported:
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in pskb_may_pull_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:2667 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in pskb_may_pull include/linux/skbuff.h:2681 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in dccp_v6_err+0x426/0x1aa0 net/dccp/ipv6.c:94
pskb_may_pull_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:2667 [inline]
pskb_may_pull include/linux/skbuff.h:2681 [inline]
dccp_v6_err+0x426/0x1aa0 net/dccp/ipv6.c:94
icmpv6_notify+0x4c7/0x880 net/ipv6/icmp.c:867
icmpv6_rcv+0x19d5/0x30d0
ip6_protocol_deliver_rcu+0xda6/0x2a60 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:438
ip6_input_finish net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:483 [inline]
NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:304 [inline]
ip6_input+0x15d/0x430 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:492
ip6_mc_input+0xa7e/0xc80 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:586
dst_input include/net/dst.h:468 [inline]
ip6_rcv_finish+0x5db/0x870 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:79
NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:304 [inline]
ipv6_rcv+0xda/0x390 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:310
__netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5523 [inline]
__netif_receive_skb+0x1a6/0x5a0 net/core/dev.c:5637
netif_receive_skb_internal net/core/dev.c:5723 [inline]
netif_receive_skb+0x58/0x660 net/core/dev.c:5782
tun_rx_batched+0x83b/0x920
tun_get_user+0x564c/0x6940 drivers/net/tun.c:2002
tun_chr_write_iter+0x3af/0x5d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2048
call_write_iter include/linux/fs.h:1985 [inline]
new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:491 [inline]
vfs_write+0x8ef/0x15c0 fs/read_write.c:584
ksys_write+0x20f/0x4c0 fs/read_write.c:637
__do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:649 [inline]
__se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:646 [inline]
__x64_sys_write+0x93/0xd0 fs/read_write.c:646
do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:50 [inline]
do_syscall_64+0x41/0xc0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:80
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

Uninit was created at:
slab_post_alloc_hook+0x12f/0xb70 mm/slab.h:767
slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3478 [inline]
kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x577/0xa80 mm/slub.c:3523
kmalloc_reserve+0x13d/0x4a0 net/core/skbuff.c:559
__alloc_skb+0x318/0x740 net/core/skbuff.c:650
alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:1286 [inline]
alloc_skb_with_frags+0xc8/0xbd0 net/core/skbuff.c:6313
sock_alloc_send_pskb+0xa80/0xbf0 net/core/sock.c:2795
tun_alloc_skb drivers/net/tun.c:1531 [inline]
tun_get_user+0x23cf/0x6940 drivers/net/tun.c:1846
tun_chr_write_iter+0x3af/0x5d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2048
call_write_iter include/linux/fs.h:1985 [inline]
new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:491 [inline]
vfs_write+0x8ef/0x15c0 fs/read_write.c:584
ksys_write+0x20f/0x4c0 fs/read_write.c:637
__do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:649 [inline]
__se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:646 [inline]
__x64_sys_write+0x93/0xd0 fs/read_write.c:646
do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:50 [inline]
do_syscall_64+0x41/0xc0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:80
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

CPU: 0 PID: 4995 Comm: syz-executor153 Not tainted 6.6.0-rc1-syzkaller-00014-ga747acc0b752 #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 08/04/2023</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52578 | net: bridge: use DEV_STATS_INC()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52578</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: bridge: use DEV_STATS_INC()

syzbot/KCSAN reported data-races in br_handle_frame_finish() [1]
This function can run from multiple cpus without mutual exclusion.

Adopt SMP safe DEV_STATS_INC() to update dev-&gt;stats fields.

Handles updates to dev-&gt;stats.tx_dropped while we are at it.

[1]
BUG: KCSAN: data-race in br_handle_frame_finish / br_handle_frame_finish

read-write to 0xffff8881374b2178 of 8 bytes by interrupt on cpu 1:
br_handle_frame_finish+0xd4f/0xef0 net/bridge/br_input.c:189
br_nf_hook_thresh+0x1ed/0x220
br_nf_pre_routing_finish_ipv6+0x50f/0x540
NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:304 [inline]
br_nf_pre_routing_ipv6+0x1e3/0x2a0 net/bridge/br_netfilter_ipv6.c:178
br_nf_pre_routing+0x526/0xba0 net/bridge/br_netfilter_hooks.c:508
nf_hook_entry_hookfn include/linux/netfilter.h:144 [inline]
nf_hook_bridge_pre net/bridge/br_input.c:272 [inline]
br_handle_frame+0x4c9/0x940 net/bridge/br_input.c:417
__netif_receive_skb_core+0xa8a/0x21e0 net/core/dev.c:5417
__netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5521 [inline]
__netif_receive_skb+0x57/0x1b0 net/core/dev.c:5637
process_backlog+0x21f/0x380 net/core/dev.c:5965
__napi_poll+0x60/0x3b0 net/core/dev.c:6527
napi_poll net/core/dev.c:6594 [inline]
net_rx_action+0x32b/0x750 net/core/dev.c:6727
__do_softirq+0xc1/0x265 kernel/softirq.c:553
run_ksoftirqd+0x17/0x20 kernel/softirq.c:921
smpboot_thread_fn+0x30a/0x4a0 kernel/smpboot.c:164
kthread+0x1d7/0x210 kernel/kthread.c:388
ret_from_fork+0x48/0x60 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:304

read-write to 0xffff8881374b2178 of 8 bytes by interrupt on cpu 0:
br_handle_frame_finish+0xd4f/0xef0 net/bridge/br_input.c:189
br_nf_hook_thresh+0x1ed/0x220
br_nf_pre_routing_finish_ipv6+0x50f/0x540
NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:304 [inline]
br_nf_pre_routing_ipv6+0x1e3/0x2a0 net/bridge/br_netfilter_ipv6.c:178
br_nf_pre_routing+0x526/0xba0 net/bridge/br_netfilter_hooks.c:508
nf_hook_entry_hookfn include/linux/netfilter.h:144 [inline]
nf_hook_bridge_pre net/bridge/br_input.c:272 [inline]
br_handle_frame+0x4c9/0x940 net/bridge/br_input.c:417
__netif_receive_skb_core+0xa8a/0x21e0 net/core/dev.c:5417
__netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5521 [inline]
__netif_receive_skb+0x57/0x1b0 net/core/dev.c:5637
process_backlog+0x21f/0x380 net/core/dev.c:5965
__napi_poll+0x60/0x3b0 net/core/dev.c:6527
napi_poll net/core/dev.c:6594 [inline]
net_rx_action+0x32b/0x750 net/core/dev.c:6727
__do_softirq+0xc1/0x265 kernel/softirq.c:553
do_softirq+0x5e/0x90 kernel/softirq.c:454
__local_bh_enable_ip+0x64/0x70 kernel/softirq.c:381
__raw_spin_unlock_bh include/linux/spinlock_api_smp.h:167 [inline]
_raw_spin_unlock_bh+0x36/0x40 kernel/locking/spinlock.c:210
spin_unlock_bh include/linux/spinlock.h:396 [inline]
batadv_tt_local_purge+0x1a8/0x1f0 net/batman-adv/translation-table.c:1356
batadv_tt_purge+0x2b/0x630 net/batman-adv/translation-table.c:3560
process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:2630 [inline]
process_scheduled_works+0x5b8/0xa30 kernel/workqueue.c:2703
worker_thread+0x525/0x730 kernel/workqueue.c:2784
kthread+0x1d7/0x210 kernel/kthread.c:388
ret_from_fork+0x48/0x60 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:304

value changed: 0x00000000000d7190 -&gt; 0x00000000000d7191

Reported by Kernel Concurrency Sanitizer on:
CPU: 0 PID: 14848 Comm: kworker/u4:11 Not tainted 6.6.0-rc1-syzkaller-00236-gad8a69f361b9 #0</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52579 | ipv4: fix null-deref in ipv4_link_failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52579</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv4: fix null-deref in ipv4_link_failure

Currently, we assume the skb is associated with a device before calling
__ip_options_compile, which is not always the case if it is re-routed by
ipvs.
When skb-&gt;dev is NULL, dev_net(skb-&gt;dev) will become null-dereference.
This patch adds a check for the edge case and switch to use the net_device
from the rtable when skb-&gt;dev is NULL.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52580 | net/core: Fix ETH_P_1588 flow dissector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52580</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/core: Fix ETH_P_1588 flow dissector

When a PTP ethernet raw frame with a size of more than 256 bytes followed
by a 0xff pattern is sent to __skb_flow_dissect, nhoff value calculation
is wrong. For example: hdr-&gt;message_length takes the wrong value (0xffff)
and it does not replicate real header length. In this case, 'nhoff' value
was overridden and the PTP header was badly dissected. This leads to a
kernel crash.

net/core: flow_dissector
net/core flow dissector nhoff = 0x0000000e
net/core flow dissector hdr-&gt;message_length = 0x0000ffff
net/core flow dissector nhoff = 0x0001000d (u16 overflow)
...
skb linear:   00000000: 00 a0 c9 00 00 00 00 a0 c9 00 00 00 88
skb frag:     00000000: f7 ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff

Using the size of the ptp_header struct will allow the corrected
calculation of the nhoff value.

net/core flow dissector nhoff = 0x0000000e
net/core flow dissector nhoff = 0x00000030 (sizeof ptp_header)
...
skb linear:   00000000: 00 a0 c9 00 00 00 00 a0 c9 00 00 00 88 f7 ff ff
skb linear:   00000010: ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff
skb linear:   00000020: ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff
skb frag:     00000000: ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff ff

Kernel trace:
[   74.984279] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[   74.989471] kernel BUG at include/linux/skbuff.h:2440!
[   74.995237] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
[   75.001098] CPU: 4 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/4 Tainted: G     U            5.15.85-intel-ese-standard-lts #1
[   75.011629] Hardware name: Intel Corporation A-Island (CPU:AlderLake)/A-Island (ID:06), BIOS SB_ADLP.01.01.00.01.03.008.D-6A9D9E73-dirty Mar 30 2023
[   75.026507] RIP: 0010:eth_type_trans+0xd0/0x130
[   75.031594] Code: 03 88 47 78 eb c7 8b 47 68 2b 47 6c 48 8b 97 c0 00 00 00 83 f8 01 7e 1b 48 85 d2 74 06 66 83 3a ff 74 09 b8 00 04 00 00 eb ab &lt;0f&gt; 0b b8 00 01 00 00 eb a2 48 85 ff 74 eb 48 8d 54 24 06 31 f6 b9
[   75.052612] RSP: 0018:ffff9948c0228de0 EFLAGS: 00010297
[   75.058473] RAX: 00000000000003f2 RBX: ffff8e47047dc300 RCX: 0000000000001003
[   75.066462] RDX: ffff8e4e8c9ea040 RSI: ffff8e4704e0a000 RDI: ffff8e47047dc300
[   75.074458] RBP: ffff8e4704e2acc0 R08: 00000000000003f3 R09: 0000000000000800
[   75.082466] R10: 000000000000000d R11: ffff9948c0228dec R12: ffff8e4715e4e010
[   75.090461] R13: ffff9948c0545018 R14: 0000000000000001 R15: 0000000000000800
[   75.098464] FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8e4e8fb00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[   75.107530] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[   75.113982] CR2: 00007f5eb35934a0 CR3: 0000000150e0a002 CR4: 0000000000770ee0
[   75.121980] PKRU: 55555554
[   75.125035] Call Trace:
[   75.127792]  &lt;IRQ&gt;
[   75.130063]  ? eth_get_headlen+0xa4/0xc0
[   75.134472]  igc_process_skb_fields+0xcd/0x150
[   75.139461]  igc_poll+0xc80/0x17b0
[   75.143272]  __napi_poll+0x27/0x170
[   75.147192]  net_rx_action+0x234/0x280
[   75.151409]  __do_softirq+0xef/0x2f4
[   75.155424]  irq_exit_rcu+0xc7/0x110
[   75.159432]  common_interrupt+0xb8/0xd0
[   75.163748]  &lt;/IRQ&gt;
[   75.166112]  &lt;TASK&gt;
[   75.168473]  asm_common_interrupt+0x22/0x40
[   75.173175] RIP: 0010:cpuidle_enter_state+0xe2/0x350
[   75.178749] Code: 85 c0 0f 8f 04 02 00 00 31 ff e8 39 6c 67 ff 45 84 ff 74 12 9c 58 f6 c4 02 0f 85 50 02 00 00 31 ff e8 52 b0 6d ff fb 45 85 f6 &lt;0f&gt; 88 b1 00 00 00 49 63 ce 4c 2b 2c 24 48 89 c8 48 6b d1 68 48 c1
[   75.199757] RSP: 0018:ffff9948c013bea8 EFLAGS: 00000202
[   75.205614] RAX: ffff8e4e8fb00000 RBX: ffffb948bfd23900 RCX: 000000000000001f
[   75.213619] RDX: 0000000000000004 RSI: ffffffff94206161 RDI: ffffffff94212e20
[   75.221620] RBP: 0000000000000004 R08: 000000117568973a R09: 0000000000000001
[   75.229622] R10: 000000000000afc8 R11: ffff8e4e8fb29ce4 R12: ffffffff945ae980
[   75.237628] R13: 000000117568973a R14: 0000000000000004 R15: 0000000000000000
[   75.245635]  ? 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52581 | netfilter: nf_tables: fix memleak when more than 255 elements expired</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52581</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: fix memleak when more than 255 elements expired

When more than 255 elements expired we're supposed to switch to a new gc
container structure.

This never happens: u8 type will wrap before reaching the boundary
and nft_trans_gc_space() always returns true.

This means we recycle the initial gc container structure and
lose track of the elements that came before.

While at it, don't deref 'gc' after we've passed it to call_rcu.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52582 | netfs: Only call folio_start_fscache() one time for each folio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52582</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfs: Only call folio_start_fscache() one time for each folio

If a network filesystem using netfs implements a clamp_length()
function, it can set subrequest lengths smaller than a page size.

When we loop through the folios in netfs_rreq_unlock_folios() to
set any folios to be written back, we need to make sure we only
call folio_start_fscache() once for each folio.

Otherwise, this simple testcase:

  mount -o fsc,rsize=1024,wsize=1024 127.0.0.1:/export /mnt/nfs
  dd if=/dev/zero of=/mnt/nfs/file.bin bs=4096 count=1
  1+0 records in
  1+0 records out
  4096 bytes (4.1 kB, 4.0 KiB) copied, 0.0126359 s, 324 kB/s
  echo 3 &gt; /proc/sys/vm/drop_caches
  cat /mnt/nfs/file.bin &gt; /dev/null

will trigger an oops similar to the following:

  page dumped because: VM_BUG_ON_FOLIO(folio_test_private_2(folio))
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  kernel BUG at include/linux/netfs.h:44!
  ...
  CPU: 5 PID: 134 Comm: kworker/u16:5 Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.4.0-rc5
  ...
  RIP: 0010:netfs_rreq_unlock_folios+0x68e/0x730 [netfs]
  ...
  Call Trace:
    netfs_rreq_assess+0x497/0x660 [netfs]
    netfs_subreq_terminated+0x32b/0x610 [netfs]
    nfs_netfs_read_completion+0x14e/0x1a0 [nfs]
    nfs_read_completion+0x2f9/0x330 [nfs]
    rpc_free_task+0x72/0xa0 [sunrpc]
    rpc_async_release+0x46/0x70 [sunrpc]
    process_one_work+0x3bd/0x710
    worker_thread+0x89/0x610
    kthread+0x181/0x1c0
    ret_from_fork+0x29/0x50</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48628 | ceph: drop messages from MDS when unmounting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48628</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ceph: drop messages from MDS when unmounting

When unmounting all the dirty buffers will be flushed and after
the last osd request is finished the last reference of the i_count
will be released. Then it will flush the dirty cap/snap to MDSs,
and the unmounting won't wait the possible acks, which will ihold
the inodes when updating the metadata locally but makes no sense
any more, of this. This will make the evict_inodes() to skip these
inodes.

If encrypt is enabled the kernel generate a warning when removing
the encrypt keys when the skipped inodes still hold the keyring:

WARNING: CPU: 4 PID: 168846 at fs/crypto/keyring.c:242 fscrypt_destroy_keyring+0x7e/0xd0
CPU: 4 PID: 168846 Comm: umount Tainted: G S  6.1.0-rc5-ceph-g72ead199864c #1
Hardware name: Supermicro SYS-5018R-WR/X10SRW-F, BIOS 2.0 12/17/2015
RIP: 0010:fscrypt_destroy_keyring+0x7e/0xd0
RSP: 0018:ffffc9000b277e28 EFLAGS: 00010202
RAX: 0000000000000002 RBX: ffff88810d52ac00 RCX: ffff88810b56aa00
RDX: 0000000080000000 RSI: ffffffff822f3a09 RDI: ffff888108f59000
RBP: ffff8881d394fb88 R08: 0000000000000028 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000001 R11: 11ff4fe6834fcd91 R12: ffff8881d394fc40
R13: ffff888108f59000 R14: ffff8881d394f800 R15: 0000000000000000
FS:  00007fd83f6f1080(0000) GS:ffff88885fd00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f918d417000 CR3: 000000017f89a005 CR4: 00000000003706e0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
&lt;TASK&gt;
generic_shutdown_super+0x47/0x120
kill_anon_super+0x14/0x30
ceph_kill_sb+0x36/0x90 [ceph]
deactivate_locked_super+0x29/0x60
cleanup_mnt+0xb8/0x140
task_work_run+0x67/0xb0
exit_to_user_mode_prepare+0x23d/0x240
syscall_exit_to_user_mode+0x25/0x60
do_syscall_64+0x40/0x80
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd
RIP: 0033:0x7fd83dc39e9b

Later the kernel will crash when iput() the inodes and dereferencing
the "sb-&gt;s_master_keys", which has been released by the
generic_shutdown_super().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52499 | powerpc/47x: Fix 47x syscall return crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52499</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

powerpc/47x: Fix 47x syscall return crash

Eddie reported that newer kernels were crashing during boot on his 476
FSP2 system:

  kernel tried to execute user page (b7ee2000) - exploit attempt? (uid: 0)
  BUG: Unable to handle kernel instruction fetch
  Faulting instruction address: 0xb7ee2000
  Oops: Kernel access of bad area, sig: 11 [#1]
  BE PAGE_SIZE=4K FSP-2
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 0 PID: 61 Comm: mount Not tainted 6.1.55-d23900f.ppcnf-fsp2 #1
  Hardware name: ibm,fsp2 476fpe 0x7ff520c0 FSP-2
  NIP: b7ee2000 LR: 8c008000 CTR: 00000000
  REGS: bffebd83 TRAP: 0400 Not tainted (6.1.55-d23900f.ppcnf-fs p2)
  MSR: 00000030 &lt;IR,DR&gt; CR: 00001000 XER: 20000000
  GPR00: c00110ac bffebe63 bffebe7e bffebe88 8c008000 00001000 00000d12 b7ee2000
  GPR08: 00000033 00000000 00000000 c139df10 48224824 1016c314 10160000 00000000
  GPR16: 10160000 10160000 00000008 00000000 10160000 00000000 10160000 1017f5b0
  GPR24: 1017fa50 1017f4f0 1017fa50 1017f740 1017f630 00000000 00000000 1017f4f0
  NIP [b7ee2000] 0xb7ee2000
  LR [8c008000] 0x8c008000
  Call Trace:
  Instruction dump:
  XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX
  XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX XXXXXXXX
  ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

The problem is in ret_from_syscall where the check for
icache_44x_need_flush is done. When the flush is needed the code jumps
out-of-line to do the flush, and then intends to jump back to continue
the syscall return.

However the branch back to label 1b doesn't return to the correct
location, instead branching back just prior to the return to userspace,
causing bogus register values to be used by the rfi.

The breakage was introduced by commit 6f76a01173cc
("powerpc/syscall: implement system call entry/exit logic in C for PPC32") which
inadvertently removed the "1" label and reused it elsewhere.

Fix it by adding named local labels in the correct locations. Note that
the return label needs to be outside the ifdef so that CONFIG_PPC_47x=n
compiles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52500 | scsi: pm80xx: Avoid leaking tags when processing OPC_INB_SET_CONTROLLER_CONFIG command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52500</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: pm80xx: Avoid leaking tags when processing OPC_INB_SET_CONTROLLER_CONFIG command

Tags allocated for OPC_INB_SET_CONTROLLER_CONFIG command need to be freed
when we receive the response.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52501 | ring-buffer: Do not attempt to read past &amp;quot;commit&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52501</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ring-buffer: Do not attempt to read past "commit"

When iterating over the ring buffer while the ring buffer is active, the
writer can corrupt the reader. There's barriers to help detect this and
handle it, but that code missed the case where the last event was at the
very end of the page and has only 4 bytes left.

The checks to detect the corruption by the writer to reads needs to see the
length of the event. If the length in the first 4 bytes is zero then the
length is stored in the second 4 bytes. But if the writer is in the process
of updating that code, there's a small window where the length in the first
4 bytes could be zero even though the length is only 4 bytes. That will
cause rb_event_length() to read the next 4 bytes which could happen to be off the
allocated page.

To protect against this, fail immediately if the next event pointer is
less than 8 bytes from the end of the commit (last byte of data), as all
events must be a minimum of 8 bytes anyway.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52502 | net: nfc: fix races in nfc_llcp_sock_get() and nfc_llcp_sock_get_sn()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52502</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: nfc: fix races in nfc_llcp_sock_get() and nfc_llcp_sock_get_sn()

Sili Luo reported a race in nfc_llcp_sock_get(), leading to UAF.

Getting a reference on the socket found in a lookup while
holding a lock should happen before releasing the lock.

nfc_llcp_sock_get_sn() has a similar problem.

Finally nfc_llcp_recv_snl() needs to make sure the socket
found by nfc_llcp_sock_from_sn() does not disappear.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52503 | tee: amdtee: fix use-after-free vulnerability in amdtee_close_session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52503</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tee: amdtee: fix use-after-free vulnerability in amdtee_close_session

There is a potential race condition in amdtee_close_session that may
cause use-after-free in amdtee_open_session. For instance, if a session
has refcount == 1, and one thread tries to free this session via:

    kref_put(&amp;sess-&gt;refcount, destroy_session);

the reference count will get decremented, and the next step would be to
call destroy_session(). However, if in another thread,
amdtee_open_session() is called before destroy_session() has completed
execution, alloc_session() may return 'sess' that will be freed up
later in destroy_session() leading to use-after-free in
amdtee_open_session.

To fix this issue, treat decrement of sess-&gt;refcount and removal of
'sess' from session list in destroy_session() as a critical section, so
that it is executed atomically.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52504 | x86/alternatives: Disable KASAN in apply_alternatives()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52504</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/alternatives: Disable KASAN in apply_alternatives()

Fei has reported that KASAN triggers during apply_alternatives() on
a 5-level paging machine:

	BUG: KASAN: out-of-bounds in rcu_is_watching()
	Read of size 4 at addr ff110003ee6419a0 by task swapper/0/0
	...
	__asan_load4()
	rcu_is_watching()
	trace_hardirqs_on()
	text_poke_early()
	apply_alternatives()
	...

On machines with 5-level paging, cpu_feature_enabled(X86_FEATURE_LA57)
gets patched. It includes KASAN code, where KASAN_SHADOW_START depends on
__VIRTUAL_MASK_SHIFT, which is defined with cpu_feature_enabled().

KASAN gets confused when apply_alternatives() patches the
KASAN_SHADOW_START users. A test patch that makes KASAN_SHADOW_START
static, by replacing __VIRTUAL_MASK_SHIFT with 56, works around the issue.

Fix it for real by disabling KASAN while the kernel is patching alternatives.

[ mingo: updated the changelog ]</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52505 | phy: lynx-28g: serialize concurrent phy_set_mode_ext() calls to shared registers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52505</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

phy: lynx-28g: serialize concurrent phy_set_mode_ext() calls to shared registers

The protocol converter configuration registers PCC8, PCCC, PCCD
(implemented by the driver), as well as others, control protocol
converters from multiple lanes (each represented as a different
struct phy). So, if there are simultaneous calls to phy_set_mode_ext()
to lanes sharing the same PCC register (either for the "old" or for the
"new" protocol), corruption of the values programmed to hardware is
possible, because lynx_28g_rmw() has no locking.

Add a spinlock in the struct lynx_28g_priv shared by all lanes, and take
the global spinlock from the phy_ops :: set_mode() implementation. There
are no other callers which modify PCC registers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52506 | LoongArch: Set all reserved memblocks on Node#0 at initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52506</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

LoongArch: Set all reserved memblocks on Node#0 at initialization

After commit 61167ad5fecdea ("mm: pass nid to reserve_bootmem_region()")
we get a panic if DEFERRED_STRUCT_PAGE_INIT is enabled:

[    0.000000] CPU 0 Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address 0000000000002b82, era == 90000000040e3f28, ra == 90000000040e3f18
[    0.000000] Oops[#1]:
[    0.000000] CPU: 0 PID: 0 Comm: swapper Not tainted 6.5.0+ #733
[    0.000000] pc 90000000040e3f28 ra 90000000040e3f18 tp 90000000046f4000 sp 90000000046f7c90
[    0.000000] a0 0000000000000001 a1 0000000000200000 a2 0000000000000040 a3 90000000046f7ca0
[    0.000000] a4 90000000046f7ca4 a5 0000000000000000 a6 90000000046f7c38 a7 0000000000000000
[    0.000000] t0 0000000000000002 t1 9000000004b00ac8 t2 90000000040e3f18 t3 90000000040f0800
[    0.000000] t4 00000000000f0000 t5 80000000ffffe07e t6 0000000000000003 t7 900000047fff5e20
[    0.000000] t8 aaaaaaaaaaaaaaab u0 0000000000000018 s9 0000000000000000 s0 fffffefffe000000
[    0.000000] s1 0000000000000000 s2 0000000000000080 s3 0000000000000040 s4 0000000000000000
[    0.000000] s5 0000000000000000 s6 fffffefffe000000 s7 900000000470b740 s8 9000000004ad4000
[    0.000000]    ra: 90000000040e3f18 reserve_bootmem_region+0xec/0x21c
[    0.000000]   ERA: 90000000040e3f28 reserve_bootmem_region+0xfc/0x21c
[    0.000000]  CRMD: 000000b0 (PLV0 -IE -DA +PG DACF=CC DACM=CC -WE)
[    0.000000]  PRMD: 00000000 (PPLV0 -PIE -PWE)
[    0.000000]  EUEN: 00000000 (-FPE -SXE -ASXE -BTE)
[    0.000000]  ECFG: 00070800 (LIE=11 VS=7)
[    0.000000] ESTAT: 00010800 [PIL] (IS=11 ECode=1 EsubCode=0)
[    0.000000]  BADV: 0000000000002b82
[    0.000000]  PRID: 0014d000 (Loongson-64bit, Loongson-3A6000)
[    0.000000] Modules linked in:
[    0.000000] Process swapper (pid: 0, threadinfo=(____ptrval____), task=(____ptrval____))
[    0.000000] Stack : 0000000000000000 9000000002eb5430 0000003a00000020 90000000045ccd00
[    0.000000]         900000000470e000 90000000002c1918 0000000000000000 9000000004110780
[    0.000000]         00000000fe6c0000 0000000480000000 9000000004b4e368 9000000004110748
[    0.000000]         0000000000000000 900000000421ca84 9000000004620000 9000000004564970
[    0.000000]         90000000046f7d78 9000000002cc9f70 90000000002c1918 900000000470e000
[    0.000000]         9000000004564970 90000000040bc0e0 90000000046f7d78 0000000000000000
[    0.000000]         0000000000004000 90000000045ccd00 0000000000000000 90000000002c1918
[    0.000000]         90000000002c1900 900000000470b700 9000000004b4df78 9000000004620000
[    0.000000]         90000000046200a8 90000000046200a8 0000000000000000 9000000004218b2c
[    0.000000]         9000000004270008 0000000000000001 0000000000000000 90000000045ccd00
[    0.000000]         ...
[    0.000000] Call Trace:
[    0.000000] [&lt;90000000040e3f28&gt;] reserve_bootmem_region+0xfc/0x21c
[    0.000000] [&lt;900000000421ca84&gt;] memblock_free_all+0x114/0x350
[    0.000000] [&lt;9000000004218b2c&gt;] mm_core_init+0x138/0x3cc
[    0.000000] [&lt;9000000004200e38&gt;] start_kernel+0x488/0x7a4
[    0.000000] [&lt;90000000040df0d8&gt;] kernel_entry+0xd8/0xdc
[    0.000000]
[    0.000000] Code: 02eb21ad  00410f4c  380c31ac &lt;262b818d&gt; 6800b70d  02c1c196  0015001c  57fe4bb1  260002cd

The reason is early memblock_reserve() in memblock_init() set node id to
MAX_NUMNODES, making NODE_DATA(nid) a NULL dereference in the call chain
reserve_bootmem_region() -&gt; init_reserved_page(). After memblock_init(),
those late calls of memblock_reserve() operate on subregions of memblock
.memory regions. As a result, these reserved regions will be set to the
correct node at the first iteration of memmap_init_reserved_pages().

So set all reserved memblocks on Node#0 at initialization can avoid this
panic.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52507 | nfc: nci: assert requested protocol is valid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52507</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfc: nci: assert requested protocol is valid

The protocol is used in a bit mask to determine if the protocol is
supported. Assert the provided protocol is less than the maximum
defined so it doesn't potentially perform a shift-out-of-bounds and
provide a clearer error for undefined protocols vs unsupported ones.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52508 | nvme-fc: Prevent null pointer dereference in nvme_fc_io_getuuid()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52508</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme-fc: Prevent null pointer dereference in nvme_fc_io_getuuid()

The nvme_fc_fcp_op structure describing an AEN operation is initialized with a
null request structure pointer. An FC LLDD may make a call to
nvme_fc_io_getuuid passing a pointer to an nvmefc_fcp_req for an AEN operation.

Add validation of the request structure pointer before dereference.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52509 | ravb: Fix use-after-free issue in ravb_tx_timeout_work()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52509</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ravb: Fix use-after-free issue in ravb_tx_timeout_work()

The ravb_stop() should call cancel_work_sync(). Otherwise,
ravb_tx_timeout_work() is possible to use the freed priv after
ravb_remove() was called like below:

CPU0			CPU1
			ravb_tx_timeout()
ravb_remove()
unregister_netdev()
free_netdev(ndev)
// free priv
			ravb_tx_timeout_work()
			// use priv

unregister_netdev() will call .ndo_stop() so that ravb_stop() is
called. And, after phy_stop() is called, netif_carrier_off()
is also called. So that .ndo_tx_timeout() will not be called
after phy_stop().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52510 | ieee802154: ca8210: Fix a potential UAF in ca8210_probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52510</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ieee802154: ca8210: Fix a potential UAF in ca8210_probe

If of_clk_add_provider() fails in ca8210_register_ext_clock(),
it calls clk_unregister() to release priv-&gt;clk and returns an
error. However, the caller ca8210_probe() then calls ca8210_remove(),
where priv-&gt;clk is freed again in ca8210_unregister_ext_clock(). In
this case, a use-after-free may happen in the second time we call
clk_unregister().

Fix this by removing the first clk_unregister(). Also, priv-&gt;clk could
be an error code on failure of clk_register_fixed_rate(). Use
IS_ERR_OR_NULL to catch this case in ca8210_unregister_ext_clock().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52511 | spi: sun6i: reduce DMA RX transfer width to single byte</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52511</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: sun6i: reduce DMA RX transfer width to single byte

Through empirical testing it has been determined that sometimes RX SPI
transfers with DMA enabled return corrupted data. This is down to single
or even multiple bytes lost during DMA transfer from SPI peripheral to
memory. It seems the RX FIFO within the SPI peripheral can become
confused when performing bus read accesses wider than a single byte to it
during an active SPI transfer.

This patch reduces the width of individual DMA read accesses to the
RX FIFO to a single byte to mitigate that issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52512 | pinctrl: nuvoton: wpcm450: fix out of bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52512</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: nuvoton: wpcm450: fix out of bounds write

Write into 'pctrl-&gt;gpio_bank' happens before the check for GPIO index
validity, so out of bounds write may happen.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52513 | RDMA/siw: Fix connection failure handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52513</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/siw: Fix connection failure handling

In case immediate MPA request processing fails, the newly
created endpoint unlinks the listening endpoint and is
ready to be dropped. This special case was not handled
correctly by the code handling the later TCP socket close,
causing a NULL dereference crash in siw_cm_work_handler()
when dereferencing a NULL listener. We now also cancel
the useless MPA timeout, if immediate MPA request
processing fails.

This patch furthermore simplifies MPA processing in general:
Scheduling a useless TCP socket read in sk_data_ready() upcall
is now surpressed, if the socket is already moved out of
TCP_ESTABLISHED state.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52514 | x86/reboot: VMCLEAR active VMCSes before emergency reboot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52514</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/reboot: VMCLEAR active VMCSes before emergency reboot

VMCLEAR active VMCSes before any emergency reboot, not just if the kernel
may kexec into a new kernel after a crash.  Per Intel's SDM, the VMX
architecture doesn't require the CPU to flush the VMCS cache on INIT.  If
an emergency reboot doesn't RESET CPUs, cached VMCSes could theoretically
be kept and only be written back to memory after the new kernel is booted,
i.e. could effectively corrupt memory after reboot.

Opportunistically remove the setting of the global pointer to NULL to make
checkpatch happy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52515 | RDMA/srp: Do not call scsi_done() from srp_abort()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52515</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/srp: Do not call scsi_done() from srp_abort()

After scmd_eh_abort_handler() has called the SCSI LLD eh_abort_handler
callback, it performs one of the following actions:
* Call scsi_queue_insert().
* Call scsi_finish_command().
* Call scsi_eh_scmd_add().
Hence, SCSI abort handlers must not call scsi_done(). Otherwise all
the above actions would trigger a use-after-free. Hence remove the
scsi_done() call from srp_abort(). Keep the srp_free_req() call
before returning SUCCESS because we may not see the command again if
SUCCESS is returned.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52516 | dma-debug: don&amp;#x27;t call __dma_entry_alloc_check_leak() under free_entries_lock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52516</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dma-debug: don't call __dma_entry_alloc_check_leak() under free_entries_lock

__dma_entry_alloc_check_leak() calls into printk -&gt; serial console
output (qcom geni) and grabs port-&gt;lock under free_entries_lock
spin lock, which is a reverse locking dependency chain as qcom_geni
IRQ handler can call into dma-debug code and grab free_entries_lock
under port-&gt;lock.

Move __dma_entry_alloc_check_leak() call out of free_entries_lock
scope so that we don't acquire serial console's port-&gt;lock under it.

Trimmed-down lockdep splat:

 The existing dependency chain (in reverse order) is:

               -&gt; #2 (free_entries_lock){-.-.}-{2:2}:
        _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x60/0x80
        dma_entry_alloc+0x38/0x110
        debug_dma_map_page+0x60/0xf8
        dma_map_page_attrs+0x1e0/0x230
        dma_map_single_attrs.constprop.0+0x6c/0xc8
        geni_se_rx_dma_prep+0x40/0xcc
        qcom_geni_serial_isr+0x310/0x510
        __handle_irq_event_percpu+0x110/0x244
        handle_irq_event_percpu+0x20/0x54
        handle_irq_event+0x50/0x88
        handle_fasteoi_irq+0xa4/0xcc
        handle_irq_desc+0x28/0x40
        generic_handle_domain_irq+0x24/0x30
        gic_handle_irq+0xc4/0x148
        do_interrupt_handler+0xa4/0xb0
        el1_interrupt+0x34/0x64
        el1h_64_irq_handler+0x18/0x24
        el1h_64_irq+0x64/0x68
        arch_local_irq_enable+0x4/0x8
        ____do_softirq+0x18/0x24
        ...

               -&gt; #1 (&amp;port_lock_key){-.-.}-{2:2}:
        _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x60/0x80
        qcom_geni_serial_console_write+0x184/0x1dc
        console_flush_all+0x344/0x454
        console_unlock+0x94/0xf0
        vprintk_emit+0x238/0x24c
        vprintk_default+0x3c/0x48
        vprintk+0xb4/0xbc
        _printk+0x68/0x90
        register_console+0x230/0x38c
        uart_add_one_port+0x338/0x494
        qcom_geni_serial_probe+0x390/0x424
        platform_probe+0x70/0xc0
        really_probe+0x148/0x280
        __driver_probe_device+0xfc/0x114
        driver_probe_device+0x44/0x100
        __device_attach_driver+0x64/0xdc
        bus_for_each_drv+0xb0/0xd8
        __device_attach+0xe4/0x140
        device_initial_probe+0x1c/0x28
        bus_probe_device+0x44/0xb0
        device_add+0x538/0x668
        of_device_add+0x44/0x50
        of_platform_device_create_pdata+0x94/0xc8
        of_platform_bus_create+0x270/0x304
        of_platform_populate+0xac/0xc4
        devm_of_platform_populate+0x60/0xac
        geni_se_probe+0x154/0x160
        platform_probe+0x70/0xc0
        ...

               -&gt; #0 (console_owner){-...}-{0:0}:
        __lock_acquire+0xdf8/0x109c
        lock_acquire+0x234/0x284
        console_flush_all+0x330/0x454
        console_unlock+0x94/0xf0
        vprintk_emit+0x238/0x24c
        vprintk_default+0x3c/0x48
        vprintk+0xb4/0xbc
        _printk+0x68/0x90
        dma_entry_alloc+0xb4/0x110
        debug_dma_map_sg+0xdc/0x2f8
        __dma_map_sg_attrs+0xac/0xe4
        dma_map_sgtable+0x30/0x4c
        get_pages+0x1d4/0x1e4 [msm]
        msm_gem_pin_pages_locked+0x38/0xac [msm]
        msm_gem_pin_vma_locked+0x58/0x88 [msm]
        msm_ioctl_gem_submit+0xde4/0x13ac [msm]
        drm_ioctl_kernel+0xe0/0x15c
        drm_ioctl+0x2e8/0x3f4
        vfs_ioctl+0x30/0x50
        ...

 Chain exists of:
   console_owner --&gt; &amp;port_lock_key --&gt; free_entries_lock

  Possible unsafe locking scenario:

        CPU0                    CPU1
        ----                    ----
   lock(free_entries_lock);
                                lock(&amp;port_lock_key);
                                lock(free_entries_lock);
   lock(console_owner);

                *** DEADLOCK ***

 Call trace:
  dump_backtrace+0xb4/0xf0
  show_stack+0x20/0x30
  dump_stack_lvl+0x60/0x84
  dump_stack+0x18/0x24
  print_circular_bug+0x1cc/0x234
  check_noncircular+0x78/0xac
  __lock_acquire+0xdf8/0x109c
  lock_acquire+0x234/0x284
  console_flush_all+0x330/0x454
  consol
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52517 | spi: sun6i: fix race between DMA RX transfer completion and RX FIFO drain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52517</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: sun6i: fix race between DMA RX transfer completion and RX FIFO drain

Previously the transfer complete IRQ immediately drained to RX FIFO to
read any data remaining in FIFO to the RX buffer. This behaviour is
correct when dealing with SPI in interrupt mode. However in DMA mode the
transfer complete interrupt still fires as soon as all bytes to be
transferred have been stored in the FIFO. At that point data in the FIFO
still needs to be picked up by the DMA engine. Thus the drain procedure
and DMA engine end up racing to read from RX FIFO, corrupting any data
read. Additionally the RX buffer pointer is never adjusted according to
DMA progress in DMA mode, thus calling the RX FIFO drain procedure in DMA
mode is a bug.
Fix corruptions in DMA RX mode by draining RX FIFO only in interrupt mode.
Also wait for completion of RX DMA when in DMA mode before returning to
ensure all data has been copied to the supplied memory buffer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52518 | Bluetooth: hci_codec: Fix leaking content of local_codecs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52518</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: hci_codec: Fix leaking content of local_codecs

The following memory leak can be observed when the controller supports
codecs which are stored in local_codecs list but the elements are never
freed:

unreferenced object 0xffff88800221d840 (size 32):
  comm "kworker/u3:0", pid 36, jiffies 4294898739 (age 127.060s)
  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
    f8 d3 02 03 80 88 ff ff 80 d8 21 02 80 88 ff ff  ..........!.....
    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
  backtrace:
    [&lt;ffffffffb324f557&gt;] __kmalloc+0x47/0x120
    [&lt;ffffffffb39ef37d&gt;] hci_codec_list_add.isra.0+0x2d/0x160
    [&lt;ffffffffb39ef643&gt;] hci_read_codec_capabilities+0x183/0x270
    [&lt;ffffffffb39ef9ab&gt;] hci_read_supported_codecs+0x1bb/0x2d0
    [&lt;ffffffffb39f162e&gt;] hci_read_local_codecs_sync+0x3e/0x60
    [&lt;ffffffffb39ff1b3&gt;] hci_dev_open_sync+0x943/0x11e0
    [&lt;ffffffffb396d55d&gt;] hci_power_on+0x10d/0x3f0
    [&lt;ffffffffb30c99b4&gt;] process_one_work+0x404/0x800
    [&lt;ffffffffb30ca134&gt;] worker_thread+0x374/0x670
    [&lt;ffffffffb30d9108&gt;] kthread+0x188/0x1c0
    [&lt;ffffffffb304db6b&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x2b/0x50
    [&lt;ffffffffb300206a&gt;] ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52519 | HID: intel-ish-hid: ipc: Disable and reenable ACPI GPE bit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52519</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

HID: intel-ish-hid: ipc: Disable and reenable ACPI GPE bit

The EHL (Elkhart Lake) based platforms provide a OOB (Out of band)
service, which allows to wakup device when the system is in S5 (Soft-Off
state). This OOB service can be enabled/disabled from BIOS settings. When
enabled, the ISH device gets PME wake capability. To enable PME wakeup,
driver also needs to enable ACPI GPE bit.

On resume, BIOS will clear the wakeup bit. So driver need to re-enable it
in resume function to keep the next wakeup capability. But this BIOS
clearing of wakeup bit doesn't decrement internal OS GPE reference count,
so this reenabling on every resume will cause reference count to overflow.

So first disable and reenable ACPI GPE bit using acpi_disable_gpe().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52520 | platform/x86: think-lmi: Fix reference leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52520</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86: think-lmi: Fix reference leak

If a duplicate attribute is found using kset_find_obj(), a reference
to that attribute is returned which needs to be disposed accordingly
using kobject_put(). Move the setting name validation into a separate
function to allow for this change without having to duplicate the
cleanup code for this setting.
As a side note, a very similar bug was fixed in
commit 7295a996fdab ("platform/x86: dell-sysman: Fix reference leak"),
so it seems that the bug was copied from that driver.

Compile-tested only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52521 | bpf: Annotate bpf_long_memcpy with data_race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52521</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Annotate bpf_long_memcpy with data_race

syzbot reported a data race splat between two processes trying to
update the same BPF map value via syscall on different CPUs:

  BUG: KCSAN: data-race in bpf_percpu_array_update / bpf_percpu_array_update

  write to 0xffffe8fffe7425d8 of 8 bytes by task 8257 on cpu 1:
   bpf_long_memcpy include/linux/bpf.h:428 [inline]
   bpf_obj_memcpy include/linux/bpf.h:441 [inline]
   copy_map_value_long include/linux/bpf.h:464 [inline]
   bpf_percpu_array_update+0x3bb/0x500 kernel/bpf/arraymap.c:380
   bpf_map_update_value+0x190/0x370 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:175
   generic_map_update_batch+0x3ae/0x4f0 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:1749
   bpf_map_do_batch+0x2df/0x3d0 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:4648
   __sys_bpf+0x28a/0x780
   __do_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5241 [inline]
   __se_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5239 [inline]
   __x64_sys_bpf+0x43/0x50 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5239
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:50 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0x41/0xc0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:80
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

  write to 0xffffe8fffe7425d8 of 8 bytes by task 8268 on cpu 0:
   bpf_long_memcpy include/linux/bpf.h:428 [inline]
   bpf_obj_memcpy include/linux/bpf.h:441 [inline]
   copy_map_value_long include/linux/bpf.h:464 [inline]
   bpf_percpu_array_update+0x3bb/0x500 kernel/bpf/arraymap.c:380
   bpf_map_update_value+0x190/0x370 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:175
   generic_map_update_batch+0x3ae/0x4f0 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:1749
   bpf_map_do_batch+0x2df/0x3d0 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:4648
   __sys_bpf+0x28a/0x780
   __do_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5241 [inline]
   __se_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5239 [inline]
   __x64_sys_bpf+0x43/0x50 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5239
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:50 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0x41/0xc0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:80
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

  value changed: 0x0000000000000000 -&gt; 0xfffffff000002788

The bpf_long_memcpy is used with 8-byte aligned pointers, power-of-8 size
and forced to use long read/writes to try to atomically copy long counters.
It is best-effort only and no barriers are here since it _will_ race with
concurrent updates from BPF programs. The bpf_long_memcpy() is called from
bpf(2) syscall. Marco suggested that the best way to make this known to
KCSAN would be to use data_race() annotation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52522 | net: fix possible store tearing in neigh_periodic_work()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52522</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: fix possible store tearing in neigh_periodic_work()

While looking at a related syzbot report involving neigh_periodic_work(),
I found that I forgot to add an annotation when deleting an
RCU protected item from a list.

Readers use rcu_deference(*np), we need to use either
rcu_assign_pointer() or WRITE_ONCE() on writer side
to prevent store tearing.

I use rcu_assign_pointer() to have lockdep support,
this was the choice made in neigh_flush_dev().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52523 | bpf, sockmap: Reject sk_msg egress redirects to non-TCP sockets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52523</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf, sockmap: Reject sk_msg egress redirects to non-TCP sockets

With a SOCKMAP/SOCKHASH map and an sk_msg program user can steer messages
sent from one TCP socket (s1) to actually egress from another TCP
socket (s2):

tcp_bpf_sendmsg(s1)		// = sk_prot-&gt;sendmsg
  tcp_bpf_send_verdict(s1)	// __SK_REDIRECT case
    tcp_bpf_sendmsg_redir(s2)
      tcp_bpf_push_locked(s2)
	tcp_bpf_push(s2)
	  tcp_rate_check_app_limited(s2) // expects tcp_sock
	  tcp_sendmsg_locked(s2)	 // ditto

There is a hard-coded assumption in the call-chain, that the egress
socket (s2) is a TCP socket.

However in commit 122e6c79efe1 ("sock_map: Update sock type checks for
UDP") we have enabled redirects to non-TCP sockets. This was done for the
sake of BPF sk_skb programs. There was no indention to support sk_msg
send-to-egress use case.

As a result, attempts to send-to-egress through a non-TCP socket lead to a
crash due to invalid downcast from sock to tcp_sock:

 BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 000000000000002f
 ...
 Call Trace:
  &lt;TASK&gt;
  ? show_regs+0x60/0x70
  ? __die+0x1f/0x70
  ? page_fault_oops+0x80/0x160
  ? do_user_addr_fault+0x2d7/0x800
  ? rcu_is_watching+0x11/0x50
  ? exc_page_fault+0x70/0x1c0
  ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x27/0x30
  ? tcp_tso_segs+0x14/0xa0
  tcp_write_xmit+0x67/0xce0
  __tcp_push_pending_frames+0x32/0xf0
  tcp_push+0x107/0x140
  tcp_sendmsg_locked+0x99f/0xbb0
  tcp_bpf_push+0x19d/0x3a0
  tcp_bpf_sendmsg_redir+0x55/0xd0
  tcp_bpf_send_verdict+0x407/0x550
  tcp_bpf_sendmsg+0x1a1/0x390
  inet_sendmsg+0x6a/0x70
  sock_sendmsg+0x9d/0xc0
  ? sockfd_lookup_light+0x12/0x80
  __sys_sendto+0x10e/0x160
  ? syscall_enter_from_user_mode+0x20/0x60
  ? __this_cpu_preempt_check+0x13/0x20
  ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x82/0x110
  __x64_sys_sendto+0x1f/0x30
  do_syscall_64+0x38/0x90
  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

Reject selecting a non-TCP sockets as redirect target from a BPF sk_msg
program to prevent the crash. When attempted, user will receive an EACCES
error from send/sendto/sendmsg() syscall.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52524 | net: nfc: llcp: Add lock when modifying device list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52524</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: nfc: llcp: Add lock when modifying device list

The device list needs its associated lock held when modifying it, or the
list could become corrupted, as syzbot discovered.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52525 | wifi: mwifiex: Fix oob check condition in mwifiex_process_rx_packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52525</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mwifiex: Fix oob check condition in mwifiex_process_rx_packet

Only skip the code path trying to access the rfc1042 headers when the
buffer is too small, so the driver can still process packets without
rfc1042 headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52526 | erofs: fix memory leak of LZMA global compressed deduplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52526</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

erofs: fix memory leak of LZMA global compressed deduplication

When stressing microLZMA EROFS images with the new global compressed
deduplication feature enabled (`-Ededupe`), I found some short-lived
temporary pages weren't properly released, which could slowly cause
unexpected OOMs hours later.

Let's fix it now (LZ4 and DEFLATE don't have this issue.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52527 | ipv4, ipv6: Fix handling of transhdrlen in __ip{,6}_append_data()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52527</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv4, ipv6: Fix handling of transhdrlen in __ip{,6}_append_data()

Including the transhdrlen in length is a problem when the packet is
partially filled (e.g. something like send(MSG_MORE) happened previously)
when appending to an IPv4 or IPv6 packet as we don't want to repeat the
transport header or account for it twice.  This can happen under some
circumstances, such as splicing into an L2TP socket.

The symptom observed is a warning in __ip6_append_data():

    WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 5042 at net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1800 __ip6_append_data.isra.0+0x1be8/0x47f0 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1800

that occurs when MSG_SPLICE_PAGES is used to append more data to an already
partially occupied skbuff.  The warning occurs when 'copy' is larger than
the amount of data in the message iterator.  This is because the requested
length includes the transport header length when it shouldn't.  This can be
triggered by, for example:

        sfd = socket(AF_INET6, SOCK_DGRAM, IPPROTO_L2TP);
        bind(sfd, ...); // ::1
        connect(sfd, ...); // ::1 port 7
        send(sfd, buffer, 4100, MSG_MORE);
        sendfile(sfd, dfd, NULL, 1024);

Fix this by only adding transhdrlen into the length if the write queue is
empty in l2tp_ip6_sendmsg(), analogously to how UDP does things.

l2tp_ip_sendmsg() looks like it won't suffer from this problem as it builds
the UDP packet itself.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52528 | net: usb: smsc75xx: Fix uninit-value access in __smsc75xx_read_reg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52528</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: usb: smsc75xx: Fix uninit-value access in __smsc75xx_read_reg

syzbot reported the following uninit-value access issue:

=====================================================
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in smsc75xx_wait_ready drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:975 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in smsc75xx_bind+0x5c9/0x11e0 drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:1482
CPU: 0 PID: 8696 Comm: kworker/0:3 Not tainted 5.8.0-rc5-syzkaller #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/01/2011
Workqueue: usb_hub_wq hub_event
Call Trace:
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:77 [inline]
 dump_stack+0x21c/0x280 lib/dump_stack.c:118
 kmsan_report+0xf7/0x1e0 mm/kmsan/kmsan_report.c:121
 __msan_warning+0x58/0xa0 mm/kmsan/kmsan_instr.c:215
 smsc75xx_wait_ready drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:975 [inline]
 smsc75xx_bind+0x5c9/0x11e0 drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:1482
 usbnet_probe+0x1152/0x3f90 drivers/net/usb/usbnet.c:1737
 usb_probe_interface+0xece/0x1550 drivers/usb/core/driver.c:374
 really_probe+0xf20/0x20b0 drivers/base/dd.c:529
 driver_probe_device+0x293/0x390 drivers/base/dd.c:701
 __device_attach_driver+0x63f/0x830 drivers/base/dd.c:807
 bus_for_each_drv+0x2ca/0x3f0 drivers/base/bus.c:431
 __device_attach+0x4e2/0x7f0 drivers/base/dd.c:873
 device_initial_probe+0x4a/0x60 drivers/base/dd.c:920
 bus_probe_device+0x177/0x3d0 drivers/base/bus.c:491
 device_add+0x3b0e/0x40d0 drivers/base/core.c:2680
 usb_set_configuration+0x380f/0x3f10 drivers/usb/core/message.c:2032
 usb_generic_driver_probe+0x138/0x300 drivers/usb/core/generic.c:241
 usb_probe_device+0x311/0x490 drivers/usb/core/driver.c:272
 really_probe+0xf20/0x20b0 drivers/base/dd.c:529
 driver_probe_device+0x293/0x390 drivers/base/dd.c:701
 __device_attach_driver+0x63f/0x830 drivers/base/dd.c:807
 bus_for_each_drv+0x2ca/0x3f0 drivers/base/bus.c:431
 __device_attach+0x4e2/0x7f0 drivers/base/dd.c:873
 device_initial_probe+0x4a/0x60 drivers/base/dd.c:920
 bus_probe_device+0x177/0x3d0 drivers/base/bus.c:491
 device_add+0x3b0e/0x40d0 drivers/base/core.c:2680
 usb_new_device+0x1bd4/0x2a30 drivers/usb/core/hub.c:2554
 hub_port_connect drivers/usb/core/hub.c:5208 [inline]
 hub_port_connect_change drivers/usb/core/hub.c:5348 [inline]
 port_event drivers/usb/core/hub.c:5494 [inline]
 hub_event+0x5e7b/0x8a70 drivers/usb/core/hub.c:5576
 process_one_work+0x1688/0x2140 kernel/workqueue.c:2269
 worker_thread+0x10bc/0x2730 kernel/workqueue.c:2415
 kthread+0x551/0x590 kernel/kthread.c:292
 ret_from_fork+0x1f/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:293

Local variable ----buf.i87@smsc75xx_bind created at:
 __smsc75xx_read_reg drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:83 [inline]
 smsc75xx_wait_ready drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:968 [inline]
 smsc75xx_bind+0x485/0x11e0 drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:1482
 __smsc75xx_read_reg drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:83 [inline]
 smsc75xx_wait_ready drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:968 [inline]
 smsc75xx_bind+0x485/0x11e0 drivers/net/usb/smsc75xx.c:1482

This issue is caused because usbnet_read_cmd() reads less bytes than requested
(zero byte in the reproducer). In this case, 'buf' is not properly filled.

This patch fixes the issue by returning -ENODATA if usbnet_read_cmd() reads
less bytes than requested.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52529 | HID: sony: Fix a potential memory leak in sony_probe()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52529</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

HID: sony: Fix a potential memory leak in sony_probe()

If an error occurs after a successful usb_alloc_urb() call, usb_free_urb()
should be called.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52530 | wifi: mac80211: fix potential key use-after-free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52530</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mac80211: fix potential key use-after-free

When ieee80211_key_link() is called by ieee80211_gtk_rekey_add()
but returns 0 due to KRACK protection (identical key reinstall),
ieee80211_gtk_rekey_add() will still return a pointer into the
key, in a potential use-after-free. This normally doesn't happen
since it's only called by iwlwifi in case of WoWLAN rekey offload
which has its own KRACK protection, but still better to fix, do
that by returning an error code and converting that to success on
the cfg80211 boundary only, leaving the error for bad callers of
ieee80211_gtk_rekey_add().</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52531 | wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: Fix a memory corruption issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52531</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: Fix a memory corruption issue

A few lines above, space is kzalloc()'ed for:
	sizeof(struct iwl_nvm_data) +
	sizeof(struct ieee80211_channel) +
	sizeof(struct ieee80211_rate)

'mvm-&gt;nvm_data' is a 'struct iwl_nvm_data', so it is fine.

At the end of this structure, there is the 'channels' flex array.
Each element is of type 'struct ieee80211_channel'.
So only 1 element is allocated in this array.

When doing:
  mvm-&gt;nvm_data-&gt;bands[0].channels = mvm-&gt;nvm_data-&gt;channels;
We point at the first element of the 'channels' flex array.
So this is fine.

However, when doing:
  mvm-&gt;nvm_data-&gt;bands[0].bitrates =
			(void *)((u8 *)mvm-&gt;nvm_data-&gt;channels + 1);
because of the "(u8 *)" cast, we add only 1 to the address of the beginning
of the flex array.

It is likely that we want point at the 'struct ieee80211_rate' allocated
just after.

Remove the spurious casting so that the pointer arithmetic works as
expected.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52532 | net: mana: Fix TX CQE error handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52532</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: mana: Fix TX CQE error handling

For an unknown TX CQE error type (probably from a newer hardware),
still free the SKB, update the queue tail, etc., otherwise the
accounting will be wrong.

Also, TX errors can be triggered by injecting corrupted packets, so
replace the WARN_ONCE to ratelimited error logging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25865 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in hexo-theme-anzhiyu v1.6.12, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the algolia se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25865</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in hexo-theme-anzhiyu v1.6.12, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the algolia search function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0968 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - DOM in langchain-ai/chat-langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0968</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - DOM in GitHub repository langchain-ai/chat-langchain prior to 0.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48627 | vt: fix memory overlapping when deleting chars in the buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48627</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vt: fix memory overlapping when deleting chars in the buffer

A memory overlapping copy occurs when deleting a long line. This memory
overlapping copy can cause data corruption when scr_memcpyw is optimized
to memcpy because memcpy does not ensure its behavior if the destination
buffer overlaps with the source buffer. The line buffer is not always
broken, because the memcpy utilizes the hardware acceleration, whose
result is not deterministic.

Fix this problem by using replacing the scr_memcpyw with scr_memmovew.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26621 | mm: huge_memory: don&amp;#x27;t force huge page alignment on 32 bit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26621</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: huge_memory: don't force huge page alignment on 32 bit

commit efa7df3e3bb5 ("mm: align larger anonymous mappings on THP
boundaries") caused two issues [1] [2] reported on 32 bit system or compat
userspace.

It doesn't make too much sense to force huge page alignment on 32 bit
system due to the constrained virtual address space.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/linux-mm/d0a136a0-4a31-46bc-adf4-2db109a61672@kernel.org/
[2] https://lore.kernel.org/linux-mm/CAJuCfpHXLdQy1a2B6xN2d7quTYwg2OoZseYPZTRpU0eHHKD-sQ@mail.gmail.com/</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0795 | Create user API role not enforced </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0795</link><description>If an attacked was given access to an instance with the admin or manager role there is no backend authentication that would prevent the attacked from creating a new user with an `admin` role and then be able to use this new account to have elevated privileges on the instance</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1398 | The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the heading_title_tag ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1398</link><description>The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the heading_title_tag and heading_sub_title_tag parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6326 | The Master Slider  Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6326</link><description>The Master Slider  Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'process_bulk_action' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to duplicate or delete arbitrary sliders via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0611 | The Master Slider  Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the slides callback functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0611</link><description>The Master Slider  Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the slides callback functionality in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1449 | The Master Slider  Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ms_slide shor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1449</link><description>The Master Slider  Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ms_slide shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0378 | The AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0378</link><description>The AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the AI chat data when discussion tracking is enabled in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 09:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1775 | The Nextend Social Login and Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to a self-based Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the error_descr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1775</link><description>The Nextend Social Login and Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to a self-based Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the error_description parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers, with access to a subscriber-level account, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. NOTE: This vulnerability can be successfully exploited on a vulnerable WordPress instance against an OAuth pre-authenticated higher-level user (e.g., administrator) by leveraging a cross-site request forgery in conjunction with a certain social engineering technique to achieve a critical impact scenario (cross-site scripting to administrator-level account creation). However, successful exploitation requires "Debug mode" to be enabled in the plugin's "Global Settings".</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 07:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1592 | The Complianz  GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1592</link><description>The Complianz  GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_delete function in class-DNSMPD.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete GDPR data requests via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25063 | Due to insufficient server-side validation, a successful exploit of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain access to certain URL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25063</link><description>Due to insufficient server-side validation, a successful exploit of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain access to certain URLs that the attacker should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 03:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25064 | Due to insufficient server-side validation, an attacker with login privileges could access certain resources that the attacker should not ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25064</link><description>Due to insufficient server-side validation, an attacker with login privileges could access certain resources that the attacker should not have access to by changing parameter values.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 03:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24511 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Pkp OJS v.3.4 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Input Title component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24511</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Pkp OJS v.3.4 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Input Title component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24512 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Pkp OJS v.3.4 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the input subtitle component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24512</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Pkp OJS v.3.4 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the input subtitle component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25434 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Pkp Ojs v3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25434</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Pkp Ojs v3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Publicname parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25436 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Production module of Pkp Ojs v3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25436</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Production module of Pkp Ojs v3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Input subject field under the Add Discussion function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25438 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Submission module of Pkp Ojs v3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25438</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Submission module of Pkp Ojs v3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Input subject field under the Add Discussion function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27354 | An issue was discovered in phpseclib 1.x before 1.0.23, 2.x before 2.0.47, and 3.x before 3.0.36. An attacker can construct a malformed cert...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27354</link><description>An issue was discovered in phpseclib 1.x before 1.0.23, 2.x before 2.0.47, and 3.x before 3.0.36. An attacker can construct a malformed certificate containing an extremely large prime to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption for an isPrime primality check). NOTE: this issue was introduced when attempting to fix CVE-2023-27560.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27355 | An issue was discovered in phpseclib 1.x before 1.0.23, 2.x before 2.0.47, and 3.x before 3.0.36. When processing the ASN.1 object identifie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27355</link><description>An issue was discovered in phpseclib 1.x before 1.0.23, 2.x before 2.0.47, and 3.x before 3.0.36. When processing the ASN.1 object identifier of a certificate, a sub identifier may be provided that leads to a denial of service (CPU consumption for decodeOID).</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49539 | Book Store Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /bsms_ci/index.php/category. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49539</link><description>Book Store Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /bsms_ci/index.php/category. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the category parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49540 | Book Store Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /bsms_ci/index.php/history. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49540</link><description>Book Store Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /bsms_ci/index.php/history. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the history parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49543 | Incorrect access control in Book Store Management System v1 allows attackers to access unauthorized pages and execute administrative functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49543</link><description>Incorrect access control in Book Store Management System v1 allows attackers to access unauthorized pages and execute administrative functions without authenticating.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27744 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27744</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the image parameter in the profile.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49544 | A local file inclusion (LFI) in Customer Support System v1 allows attackers to include internal PHP files and gain unauthorized acces via ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49544</link><description>A local file inclusion (LFI) in Customer Support System v1 allows attackers to include internal PHP files and gain unauthorized acces via manipulation of the page= parameter at /customer_support/index.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49545 | A directory listing vulnerability in Customer Support System v1 allows attackers to list directories and sensitive files within the applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49545</link><description>A directory listing vulnerability in Customer Support System v1 allows attackers to list directories and sensitive files within the application without requiring authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27746 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27746</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the email address parameter in the index.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27743 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27743</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Address parameter in the add_invoices.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27747 | File Upload vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27747</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Petrol Pump Mangement Software v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the email Image parameter in the profile.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1869 | Certain HP DesignJet print products are potentially vulnerable to information disclosure related to accessing memory out-of-bounds when usin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1869</link><description>Certain HP DesignJet print products are potentially vulnerable to information disclosure related to accessing memory out-of-bounds when using the general-purpose gateway (GGW) over port 9220.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47069 | ipc/mqueue, msg, sem: avoid relying on a stack reference past its expiry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47069</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipc/mqueue, msg, sem: avoid relying on a stack reference past its expiry

do_mq_timedreceive calls wq_sleep with a stack local address.  The
sender (do_mq_timedsend) uses this address to later call pipelined_send.

This leads to a very hard to trigger race where a do_mq_timedreceive
call might return and leave do_mq_timedsend to rely on an invalid
address, causing the following crash:

  RIP: 0010:wake_q_add_safe+0x13/0x60
  Call Trace:
   __x64_sys_mq_timedsend+0x2a9/0x490
   do_syscall_64+0x80/0x680
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x44/0xa9
  RIP: 0033:0x7f5928e40343

The race occurs as:

1. do_mq_timedreceive calls wq_sleep with the address of `struct
   ext_wait_queue` on function stack (aliased as `ewq_addr` here) - it
   holds a valid `struct ext_wait_queue *` as long as the stack has not
   been overwritten.

2. `ewq_addr` gets added to info-&gt;e_wait_q[RECV].list in wq_add, and
   do_mq_timedsend receives it via wq_get_first_waiter(info, RECV) to call
   __pipelined_op.

3. Sender calls __pipelined_op::smp_store_release(&amp;this-&gt;state,
   STATE_READY).  Here is where the race window begins.  (`this` is
   `ewq_addr`.)

4. If the receiver wakes up now in do_mq_timedreceive::wq_sleep, it
   will see `state == STATE_READY` and break.

5. do_mq_timedreceive returns, and `ewq_addr` is no longer guaranteed
   to be a `struct ext_wait_queue *` since it was on do_mq_timedreceive's
   stack.  (Although the address may not get overwritten until another
   function happens to touch it, which means it can persist around for an
   indefinite time.)

6. do_mq_timedsend::__pipelined_op() still believes `ewq_addr` is a
   `struct ext_wait_queue *`, and uses it to find a task_struct to pass to
   the wake_q_add_safe call.  In the lucky case where nothing has
   overwritten `ewq_addr` yet, `ewq_addr-&gt;task` is the right task_struct.
   In the unlucky case, __pipelined_op::wake_q_add_safe gets handed a
   bogus address as the receiver's task_struct causing the crash.

do_mq_timedsend::__pipelined_op() should not dereference `this` after
setting STATE_READY, as the receiver counterpart is now free to return.
Change __pipelined_op to call wake_q_add_safe on the receiver's
task_struct returned by get_task_struct, instead of dereferencing `this`
which sits on the receiver's stack.

As Manfred pointed out, the race potentially also exists in
ipc/msg.c::expunge_all and ipc/sem.c::wake_up_sem_queue_prepare.  Fix
those in the same way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47070 | uio_hv_generic: Fix another memory leak in error handling paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47070</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

uio_hv_generic: Fix another memory leak in error handling paths

Memory allocated by 'vmbus_alloc_ring()' at the beginning of the probe
function is never freed in the error handling path.

Add the missing 'vmbus_free_ring()' call.

Note that it is already freed in the .remove function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47071 | uio_hv_generic: Fix a memory leak in error handling paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47071</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

uio_hv_generic: Fix a memory leak in error handling paths

If 'vmbus_establish_gpadl()' fails, the (recv|send)_gpadl will not be
updated and 'hv_uio_cleanup()' in the error handling path will not be
able to free the corresponding buffer.

In such a case, we need to free the buffer explicitly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47072 | btrfs: fix removed dentries still existing after log is synced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47072</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix removed dentries still existing after log is synced

When we move one inode from one directory to another and both the inode
and its previous parent directory were logged before, we are not supposed
to have the dentry for the old parent if we have a power failure after the
log is synced. Only the new dentry is supposed to exist.

Generally this works correctly, however there is a scenario where this is
not currently working, because the old parent of the file/directory that
was moved is not authoritative for a range that includes the dir index and
dir item keys of the old dentry. This case is better explained with the
following example and reproducer:

  # The test requires a very specific layout of keys and items in the
  # fs/subvolume btree to trigger the bug. So we want to make sure that
  # on whatever platform we are, we have the same leaf/node size.
  #
  # Currently in btrfs the node/leaf size can not be smaller than the page
  # size (but it can be greater than the page size). So use the largest
  # supported node/leaf size (64K).

  $ mkfs.btrfs -f -n 65536 /dev/sdc
  $ mount /dev/sdc /mnt

  # "testdir" is inode 257.
  $ mkdir /mnt/testdir
  $ chmod 755 /mnt/testdir

  # Create several empty files to have the directory "testdir" with its
  # items spread over several leaves (7 in this case).
  $ for ((i = 1; i &lt;= 1200; i++)); do
       echo -n &gt; /mnt/testdir/file$i
    done

  # Create our test directory "dira", inode number 1458, which gets all
  # its items in leaf 7.
  #
  # The BTRFS_DIR_ITEM_KEY item for inode 257 ("testdir") that points to
  # the entry named "dira" is in leaf 2, while the BTRFS_DIR_INDEX_KEY
  # item that points to that entry is in leaf 3.
  #
  # For this particular filesystem node size (64K), file count and file
  # names, we endup with the directory entry items from inode 257 in
  # leaves 2 and 3, as previously mentioned - what matters for triggering
  # the bug exercised by this test case is that those items are not placed
  # in leaf 1, they must be placed in a leaf different from the one
  # containing the inode item for inode 257.
  #
  # The corresponding BTRFS_DIR_ITEM_KEY and BTRFS_DIR_INDEX_KEY items for
  # the parent inode (257) are the following:
  #
  #    item 460 key (257 DIR_ITEM 3724298081) itemoff 48344 itemsize 34
  #         location key (1458 INODE_ITEM 0) type DIR
  #         transid 6 data_len 0 name_len 4
  #         name: dira
  #
  # and:
  #
  #    item 771 key (257 DIR_INDEX 1202) itemoff 36673 itemsize 34
  #         location key (1458 INODE_ITEM 0) type DIR
  #         transid 6 data_len 0 name_len 4
  #         name: dira

  $ mkdir /mnt/testdir/dira

  # Make sure everything done so far is durably persisted.
  $ sync

  # Now do a change to inode 257 ("testdir") that does not result in
  # COWing leaves 2 and 3 - the leaves that contain the directory items
  # pointing to inode 1458 (directory "dira").
  #
  # Changing permissions, the owner/group, updating or adding a xattr,
  # etc, will not change (COW) leaves 2 and 3. So for the sake of
  # simplicity change the permissions of inode 257, which results in
  # updating its inode item and therefore change (COW) only leaf 1.

  $ chmod 700 /mnt/testdir

  # Now fsync directory inode 257.
  #
  # Since only the first leaf was changed/COWed, we log the inode item of
  # inode 257 and only the dentries found in the first leaf, all have a
  # key type of BTRFS_DIR_ITEM_KEY, and no keys of type
  # BTRFS_DIR_INDEX_KEY, because they sort after the former type and none
  # exist in the first leaf.
  #
  # We also log 3 items that represent ranges for dir items and dir
  # indexes for which the log is authoritative:
  #
  # 1) a key of type BTRFS_DIR_LOG_ITEM_KEY, which indicates the log is
  #    authoritative for all BTRFS_DIR_ITEM_KEY keys that have an offset
  #    in the range [0, 2285968570] (the offset here is th
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47073 | platform/x86: dell-smbios-wmi: Fix oops on rmmod dell_smbios</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47073</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86: dell-smbios-wmi: Fix oops on rmmod dell_smbios

init_dell_smbios_wmi() only registers the dell_smbios_wmi_driver on systems
where the Dell WMI interface is supported. While exit_dell_smbios_wmi()
unregisters it unconditionally, this leads to the following oops:

[  175.722921] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  175.722925] Unexpected driver unregister!
[  175.722939] WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 3630 at drivers/base/driver.c:194 driver_unregister+0x38/0x40
...
[  175.723089] Call Trace:
[  175.723094]  cleanup_module+0x5/0xedd [dell_smbios]
...
[  175.723148] ---[ end trace 064c34e1ad49509d ]---

Make the unregister happen on the same condition the register happens
to fix this.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47074 | nvme-loop: fix memory leak in nvme_loop_create_ctrl()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47074</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme-loop: fix memory leak in nvme_loop_create_ctrl()

When creating loop ctrl in nvme_loop_create_ctrl(), if nvme_init_ctrl()
fails, the loop ctrl should be freed before jumping to the "out" label.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47075 | nvmet: fix memory leak in nvmet_alloc_ctrl()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47075</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvmet: fix memory leak in nvmet_alloc_ctrl()

When creating ctrl in nvmet_alloc_ctrl(), if the cntlid_min is larger
than cntlid_max of the subsystem, and jumps to the
"out_free_changed_ns_list" label, but the ctrl-&gt;sqs lack of be freed.
Fix this by jumping to the "out_free_sqs" label.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47076 | RDMA/rxe: Return CQE error if invalid lkey was supplied</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47076</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/rxe: Return CQE error if invalid lkey was supplied

RXE is missing update of WQE status in LOCAL_WRITE failures.  This caused
the following kernel panic if someone sent an atomic operation with an
explicitly wrong lkey.

[leonro@vm ~]$ mkt test
test_atomic_invalid_lkey (tests.test_atomic.AtomicTest) ...
 WARNING: CPU: 5 PID: 263 at drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe_comp.c:740 rxe_completer+0x1a6d/0x2e30 [rdma_rxe]
 Modules linked in: crc32_generic rdma_rxe ip6_udp_tunnel udp_tunnel rdma_ucm rdma_cm ib_umad ib_ipoib iw_cm ib_cm mlx5_ib ib_uverbs ib_core mlx5_core ptp pps_core
 CPU: 5 PID: 263 Comm: python3 Not tainted 5.13.0-rc1+ #2936
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS rel-1.13.0-0-gf21b5a4aeb02-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
 RIP: 0010:rxe_completer+0x1a6d/0x2e30 [rdma_rxe]
 Code: 03 0f 8e 65 0e 00 00 3b 93 10 06 00 00 0f 84 82 0a 00 00 4c 89 ff 4c 89 44 24 38 e8 2d 74 a9 e1 4c 8b 44 24 38 e9 1c f5 ff ff &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 0c e8 ff ff b8 05 00 00 00 41 bf 05 00 00 00 e9 ab e7 ff
 RSP: 0018:ffff8880158af090 EFLAGS: 00010246
 RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff888016a78000 RCX: ffffffffa0cf1652
 RDX: 1ffff9200004b442 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffffc9000025a210
 RBP: dffffc0000000000 R08: 00000000ffffffea R09: ffff88801617740b
 R10: ffffed1002c2ee81 R11: 0000000000000007 R12: ffff88800f3b63e8
 R13: ffff888016a78008 R14: ffffc9000025a180 R15: 000000000000000c
 FS:  00007f88b622a740(0000) GS:ffff88806d540000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
 CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
 CR2: 00007f88b5a1fa10 CR3: 000000000d848004 CR4: 0000000000370ea0
 DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
 DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
 Call Trace:
  rxe_do_task+0x130/0x230 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_rcv+0xb11/0x1df0 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_loopback+0x157/0x1e0 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_responder+0x5532/0x7620 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_do_task+0x130/0x230 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_rcv+0x9c8/0x1df0 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_loopback+0x157/0x1e0 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_requester+0x1efd/0x58c0 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_do_task+0x130/0x230 [rdma_rxe]
  rxe_post_send+0x998/0x1860 [rdma_rxe]
  ib_uverbs_post_send+0xd5f/0x1220 [ib_uverbs]
  ib_uverbs_write+0x847/0xc80 [ib_uverbs]
  vfs_write+0x1c5/0x840
  ksys_write+0x176/0x1d0
  do_syscall_64+0x3f/0x80
  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x44/0xae</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47077 | scsi: qedf: Add pointer checks in qedf_update_link_speed()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47077</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: qedf: Add pointer checks in qedf_update_link_speed()

The following trace was observed:

 [   14.042059] Call Trace:
 [   14.042061]  &lt;IRQ&gt;
 [   14.042068]  qedf_link_update+0x144/0x1f0 [qedf]
 [   14.042117]  qed_link_update+0x5c/0x80 [qed]
 [   14.042135]  qed_mcp_handle_link_change+0x2d2/0x410 [qed]
 [   14.042155]  ? qed_set_ptt+0x70/0x80 [qed]
 [   14.042170]  ? qed_set_ptt+0x70/0x80 [qed]
 [   14.042186]  ? qed_rd+0x13/0x40 [qed]
 [   14.042205]  qed_mcp_handle_events+0x437/0x690 [qed]
 [   14.042221]  ? qed_set_ptt+0x70/0x80 [qed]
 [   14.042239]  qed_int_sp_dpc+0x3a6/0x3e0 [qed]
 [   14.042245]  tasklet_action_common.isra.14+0x5a/0x100
 [   14.042250]  __do_softirq+0xe4/0x2f8
 [   14.042253]  irq_exit+0xf7/0x100
 [   14.042255]  do_IRQ+0x7f/0xd0
 [   14.042257]  common_interrupt+0xf/0xf
 [   14.042259]  &lt;/IRQ&gt;

API qedf_link_update() is getting called from QED but by that time
shost_data is not initialised. This results in a NULL pointer dereference
when we try to dereference shost_data while updating supported_speeds.

Add a NULL pointer check before dereferencing shost_data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47078 | RDMA/rxe: Clear all QP fields if creation failed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47078</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/rxe: Clear all QP fields if creation failed

rxe_qp_do_cleanup() relies on valid pointer values in QP for the properly
created ones, but in case rxe_qp_from_init() failed it was filled with
garbage and caused tot the following error.

  refcount_t: underflow; use-after-free.
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 12560 at lib/refcount.c:28 refcount_warn_saturate+0x1d1/0x1e0 lib/refcount.c:28
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 1 PID: 12560 Comm: syz-executor.4 Not tainted 5.12.0-syzkaller #0
  Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/01/2011
  RIP: 0010:refcount_warn_saturate+0x1d1/0x1e0 lib/refcount.c:28
  Code: e9 db fe ff ff 48 89 df e8 2c c2 ea fd e9 8a fe ff ff e8 72 6a a7 fd 48 c7 c7 e0 b2 c1 89 c6 05 dc 3a e6 09 01 e8 ee 74 fb 04 &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 af fe ff ff 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 41 56 41 55 41 54 55
  RSP: 0018:ffffc900097ceba8 EFLAGS: 00010286
  RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: 0000000000000000
  RDX: 0000000000040000 RSI: ffffffff815bb075 RDI: fffff520012f9d67
  RBP: 0000000000000003 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: ffffffff815b4eae R11: 0000000000000000 R12: ffff8880322a4800
  R13: ffff8880322a4940 R14: ffff888033044e00 R15: 0000000000000000
  FS:  00007f6eb2be3700(0000) GS:ffff8880b9d00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: 00007fdbe5d41000 CR3: 000000001d181000 CR4: 00000000001506e0
  DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
  DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
  Call Trace:
   __refcount_sub_and_test include/linux/refcount.h:283 [inline]
   __refcount_dec_and_test include/linux/refcount.h:315 [inline]
   refcount_dec_and_test include/linux/refcount.h:333 [inline]
   kref_put include/linux/kref.h:64 [inline]
   rxe_qp_do_cleanup+0x96f/0xaf0 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe_qp.c:805
   execute_in_process_context+0x37/0x150 kernel/workqueue.c:3327
   rxe_elem_release+0x9f/0x180 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe_pool.c:391
   kref_put include/linux/kref.h:65 [inline]
   rxe_create_qp+0x2cd/0x310 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe_verbs.c:425
   _ib_create_qp drivers/infiniband/core/core_priv.h:331 [inline]
   ib_create_named_qp+0x2ad/0x1370 drivers/infiniband/core/verbs.c:1231
   ib_create_qp include/rdma/ib_verbs.h:3644 [inline]
   create_mad_qp+0x177/0x2d0 drivers/infiniband/core/mad.c:2920
   ib_mad_port_open drivers/infiniband/core/mad.c:3001 [inline]
   ib_mad_init_device+0xd6f/0x1400 drivers/infiniband/core/mad.c:3092
   add_client_context+0x405/0x5e0 drivers/infiniband/core/device.c:717
   enable_device_and_get+0x1cd/0x3b0 drivers/infiniband/core/device.c:1331
   ib_register_device drivers/infiniband/core/device.c:1413 [inline]
   ib_register_device+0x7c7/0xa50 drivers/infiniband/core/device.c:1365
   rxe_register_device+0x3d5/0x4a0 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe_verbs.c:1147
   rxe_add+0x12fe/0x16d0 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe.c:247
   rxe_net_add+0x8c/0xe0 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe_net.c:503
   rxe_newlink drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe.c:269 [inline]
   rxe_newlink+0xb7/0xe0 drivers/infiniband/sw/rxe/rxe.c:250
   nldev_newlink+0x30e/0x550 drivers/infiniband/core/nldev.c:1555
   rdma_nl_rcv_msg+0x36d/0x690 drivers/infiniband/core/netlink.c:195
   rdma_nl_rcv_skb drivers/infiniband/core/netlink.c:239 [inline]
   rdma_nl_rcv+0x2ee/0x430 drivers/infiniband/core/netlink.c:259
   netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1312 [inline]
   netlink_unicast+0x533/0x7d0 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1338
   netlink_sendmsg+0x856/0xd90 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1927
   sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:654 [inline]
   sock_sendmsg+0xcf/0x120 net/socket.c:674
   ____sys_sendmsg+0x6e8/0x810 net/socket.c:2350
   ___sys_sendmsg+0xf3/0x170 net/socket.c:2404
   __sys_sendmsg+0xe5/0x1b0 net/socket.c:2433
   do_syscall_64+0x3a/0xb0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:47
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47079 | platform/x86: ideapad-laptop: fix a NULL pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47079</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86: ideapad-laptop: fix a NULL pointer dereference

The third parameter of dytc_cql_command should not be NULL since it will
be dereferenced immediately.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47080 | RDMA/core: Prevent divide-by-zero error triggered by the user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47080</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

RDMA/core: Prevent divide-by-zero error triggered by the user

The user_entry_size is supplied by the user and later used as a
denominator to calculate number of entries. The zero supplied by the user
will trigger the following divide-by-zero error:

 divide error: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN PTI
 CPU: 4 PID: 497 Comm: c_repro Not tainted 5.13.0-rc1+ #281
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.13.0-0-gf21b5a4aeb02-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
 RIP: 0010:ib_uverbs_handler_UVERBS_METHOD_QUERY_GID_TABLE+0x1b1/0x510
 Code: 87 59 03 00 00 e8 9f ab 1e ff 48 8d bd a8 00 00 00 e8 d3 70 41 ff 44 0f b7 b5 a8 00 00 00 e8 86 ab 1e ff 31 d2 4c 89 f0 31 ff &lt;49&gt; f7 f5 48 89 d6 48 89 54 24 10 48 89 04 24 e8 1b ad 1e ff 48 8b
 RSP: 0018:ffff88810416f828 EFLAGS: 00010246
 RAX: 0000000000000008 RBX: 1ffff1102082df09 RCX: ffffffff82183f3d
 RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: ffff888105f2da00 RDI: 0000000000000000
 RBP: ffff88810416fa98 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffffed102082df5f
 R10: ffff88810416faf7 R11: ffffed102082df5e R12: 0000000000000000
 R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000008 R15: ffff88810416faf0
 FS:  00007f5715efa740(0000) GS:ffff88811a700000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
 CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
 CR2: 0000000020000840 CR3: 000000010c2e0001 CR4: 0000000000370ea0
 DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
 DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
 Call Trace:
  ? ib_uverbs_handler_UVERBS_METHOD_INFO_HANDLES+0x4b0/0x4b0
  ib_uverbs_cmd_verbs+0x1546/0x1940
  ib_uverbs_ioctl+0x186/0x240
  __x64_sys_ioctl+0x38a/0x1220
  do_syscall_64+0x3f/0x80
  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x44/0xae</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47081 | habanalabs/gaudi: Fix a potential use after free in gaudi_memset_device_memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47081</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

habanalabs/gaudi: Fix a potential use after free in gaudi_memset_device_memory

Our code analyzer reported a uaf.

In gaudi_memset_device_memory, cb is get via hl_cb_kernel_create()
with 2 refcount.
If hl_cs_allocate_job() failed, the execution runs into release_cb
branch. One ref of cb is dropped by hl_cb_put(cb) and could be freed
if other thread also drops one ref. Then cb is used by cb-&gt;id later,
which is a potential uaf.

My patch add a variable 'id' to accept the value of cb-&gt;id before the
hl_cb_put(cb) is called, to avoid the potential uaf.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27101 | Integer overflow in chunking helper causes dispatching to miss elements or panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27101</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source, Google Zanzibar-inspired database for creating and managing security-critical application permissions. Integer overflow in chunking helper causes dispatching to miss elements or panic.  Any SpiceDB cluster with any schema where a resource being checked has more than 65535 relationships for the same resource and subject type is affected by this problem.  The CheckPermission, BulkCheckPermission, and LookupSubjects API methods are affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.29.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23492 | Commend WS203VICM Weak Encoding for Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23492</link><description>A weak encoding is used to transmit credentials for WS203VICM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21767 | Commend WS203VICM Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21767</link><description>A remote attacker may be able to bypass access control of Commend WS203VICM by creating a malicious request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22182 | Commend WS203VICM Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22182</link><description>A remote, unauthenticated attacker may be able to send crafted messages 
to the web server of the Commend WS203VICM causing the system to 
restart, interrupting service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20328 | ClamAV VirusEvent File Processing Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20328</link><description>A vulnerability in the VirusEvent feature of ClamAV could allow a local attacker to inject arbitrary commands with the privileges of the application service account.The vulnerability is due to unsafe handling of file names. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a file name containing command-line sequences. When processed on a system using configuration options for the VirusEvent feature, the attacker could cause the application to execute arbitrary commands.
ClamAV has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7242 | Ethercat Zeek Plugin Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7242</link><description>Industrial Control Systems Network Protocol Parsers (ICSNPP) - Ethercat 
Zeek Plugin versions d78dda6 and prior are vulnerable to out-of-bounds 
read during the process of analyzing a specific Ethercat packet. This 
could allow an attacker to crash the Zeek process and leak some 
information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7243 | Ethercat Zeek Plugin Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7243</link><description>Industrial Control Systems Network Protocol Parsers (ICSNPP) - Ethercat 
Zeek Plugin versions d78dda6 and prior are vulnerable to out-of-bounds 
write while analyzing specific Ethercat datagrams. This could allow an 
attacker to cause arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7244 | Ethercat Zeek Plugin Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7244</link><description>Industrial Control Systems Network Protocol Parsers (ICSNPP) - Ethercat 
Zeek Plugin versions d78dda6 and prior are vulnerable to out-of-bounds 
write in their primary analyses function for Ethercat communication 
packets. This could allow an attacker to cause arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1174 | Previous versions of HP ThinPro (prior to HP ThinPro 8.0 SP 8) could potentially contain security vulnerabilities. HP has released HP ThinPr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1174</link><description>Previous versions of HP ThinPro (prior to HP ThinPro 8.0 SP 8) could potentially contain security vulnerabilities. HP has released HP ThinPro 8.0 SP 8, which includes updates to mitigate potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1453 | Santesoft Sante DICOM Viewer Pro Out-of-Bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1453</link><description>In Sante DICOM Viewer Pro versions 14.0.3 and prior, a user must open a malicious DICOM file, which could allow a local attacker to disclose information or execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2076 | CodeAstro House Rental Management System tenant.php missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file booking.php/owner.php/tenant.php. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255392.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2077 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2077</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument category_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255393 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2075 | SourceCodester Daily Habit Tracker update-tracker.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2075</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Daily Habit Tracker 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/update-tracker.php. The manipulation of the argument day leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255391.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27298 | Parse Server literalizeRegexPart SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27298</link><description>parse-server is a Parse Server for Node.js / Express. This vulnerability allows SQL injection when Parse Server is configured to use the PostgreSQL database. The vulnerability has been fixed in 6.5.0 and 7.0.0-alpha.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2074 | Mini-Tmall 1 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2074</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mini-Tmall up to 20231017 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ?r=tmall/admin/user/1/1. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255389 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2072 | SourceCodester Flashcard Quiz App update-flashcard.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2072</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Flashcard Quiz App 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/update-flashcard.php. The manipulation of the argument question/answer leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255387.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2073 | SourceCodester Block Inserter for Dynamic Content view_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2073</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Block Inserter for Dynamic Content 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file view_post.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255388.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27734 | A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CSZ CMS v.1.3.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the Site Name f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27734</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CSZ CMS v.1.3.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the Site Name fields of the Site Settings component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52558 | OpenBSD 7.4 and 7.3 m_split() network buffer kernel crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52558</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.4 before errata 002 and OpenBSD 7.3 before errata 019, anetwork buffer that had to be split at certain length that could crash the kernel after receiving specially crafted escape sequences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27689 | Stupid Simple CMS v1.2.4 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /update-article.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27689</link><description>Stupid Simple CMS v1.2.4 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /update-article.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2071 | SourceCodester FAQ Management System Update FAQ cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2071</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Update FAQ. The manipulation of the argument Frequently Asked Question leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-255386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27558 | Stupid Simple CMS 1.2.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) within the blog title of the settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27558</link><description>Stupid Simple CMS 1.2.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) within the blog title of the settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27559 | Stupid Simple CMS v1.2.4 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /save_settings.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27559</link><description>Stupid Simple CMS v1.2.4 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /save_settings.php</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52556 | OpenBSD 7.4 pf state race condition kernel crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52556</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.4 before errata 009, a race condition between pf(4)'s processing of packets and expiration of packet states may cause a kernel panic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52557 | OpenBSD 7.3 invalid l2tp message npppd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52557</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.3 before errata 016, npppd(8) could crash by a l2tp message which has an AVP (Attribute-Value Pair) with wrong length.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2070 | SourceCodester FAQ Management System add-faq.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2070</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-faq.php. The manipulation of the argument question/answer leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255385 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1624 | OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting documentation server on certain Releases of 3DEXPERIENCE, SIMULIA Abaqus, SIMULIA Isight and CATIA Composer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1624</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting documentation server on 3DEXPERIENCE from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x, SIMULIA Abaqus from Release 2022 through Release 2024, SIMULIA Isight from Release 2022 through Release 2024 and CATIA Composer from Release R2023 through Release R2024. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27296 | Directus version number disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27296</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Prior to version 10.8.3, the exact Directus version number was being shipped in compiled JS bundles which are accessible without authentication. With this information a malicious attacker can trivially look for known vulnerabilities in Directus core or any of its shipped dependencies in that specific running version. The problem has been resolved in versions 10.8.3 and newer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27138 | Apache Archiva: disabling user registration is not effective</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27138</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Archiva.

Apache Archiva has a setting to disable user registration, however this restriction can be bypassed. As Apache Archiva has been retired, we do not expect to release a version of Apache Archiva that fixes this issue. You are recommended to look into migrating to a different solution, or isolate your instance from any untrusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27139 | Apache Archiva: incorrect authentication potentially leading to account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27139</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **

Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Archiva: a vulnerability in Apache Archiva allows an unauthenticated attacker to modify account data, potentially leading to account takeover.

This issue affects Apache Archiva: from 2.0.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27140 | Apache Archiva: reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27140</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **

Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Archiva.

This issue affects Apache Archiva: from 2.0.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users. Alternatively, you could configure a HTTP proxy in front of your Archiva instance to only forward requests that do not have malicious characters in the URL.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27295 | Directus MySQL accent insensitive email matching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27295</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. The password reset mechanism of the Directus backend allows attackers to receive a password reset email of a victim user, specifically having it arrive at a similar email address as the victim with a one or more characters changed to use accents. This is due to the fact that by default MySQL/MariaDB are configured for accent-insensitive and case-insensitive comparisons. This vulnerability is fixed in version 10.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2068 | SourceCodester Computer Inventory System update-computer.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2068</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Inventory System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/update-computer.php. The manipulation of the argument model leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255383.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2069 | SourceCodester FAQ Management System delete-faq.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2069</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/delete-faq.php. The manipulation of the argument faq leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255384.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27499 | Bagisto v1.5.1 is vulnerable for Cross site scripting(XSS) via png file upload vulnerability in product review option.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27499</link><description>Bagisto v1.5.1 is vulnerable for Cross site scripting(XSS) via png file upload vulnerability in product review option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27497 | Linksys E2000 Ver.1.0.06 build 1 is vulnerable to authentication bypass via the position.js file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27497</link><description>Linksys E2000 Ver.1.0.06 build 1 is vulnerable to authentication bypass via the position.js file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2067 | SourceCodester Computer Inventory System delete-computer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2067</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Inventory System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/delete-computer.php. The manipulation of the argument computer leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50378 | Apache Ambari: Various XSS problems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50378</link><description>Lack of proper input validation and constraint enforcement in Apache Ambari prior to 2.7.8

Impact : As it will be stored XSS,Could be exploited to perform unauthorized actions, varying from data access to session hijacking and delivering malicious payloads. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to version  2.7.8 which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0967 | OpenText / Micro Focus ArcSight Enterprise Security Manager Remote Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0967</link><description>A potential vulnerability has been identified in OpenText / Micro Focus ArcSight Enterprise Security Manager (ESM). The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2065 | SourceCodester Barangay Population Monitoring System update-resident.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2065</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Barangay Population Monitoring System up to 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/update-resident.php. The manipulation of the argument full_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255380.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2066 | SourceCodester Computer Inventory System add-computer.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2066</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Inventory System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/add-computer.php. The manipulation of the argument model leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255381 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27567 | LBT T300- T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the vpn_client_ip parameter in the config_vpn_pptp function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27567</link><description>LBT T300- T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the vpn_client_ip parameter in the config_vpn_pptp function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27568 | LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the apn_name_3g parameter in the setupEC20Apn function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27568</link><description>LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the apn_name_3g parameter in the setupEC20Apn function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27569 | LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the init_nvram function. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27569</link><description>LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the init_nvram function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27570 | LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the generate_conf_router function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27570</link><description>LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the generate_conf_router function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27571 | LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the makeCurRemoteApList function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27571</link><description>LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the makeCurRemoteApList function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27572 | LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the updateCurAPlist function. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27572</link><description>LBT T300-T390 v2.2.1.8 were discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ApCliSsid parameter in the updateCurAPlist function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2064 | rahman SelectCours Template CacheController.java getCacheNames injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2064</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in rahman SelectCours 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getCacheNames of the file CacheController.java of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument fragment leads to injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255379.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46950 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Contribsys Sidekiq v.6.5.8 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted URL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46950</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Contribsys Sidekiq v.6.5.8 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted URL to the filter functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46951 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Contribsys Sidekiq v.6.5.8 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46951</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Contribsys Sidekiq v.6.5.8 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the uniquejobs function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24903 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, version 5.10+, contain a weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten passwords. An adja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24903</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, version 5.10+, contain a weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten passwords. An adjacent network low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access to the application with privileges of the compromised account. The attacker could retrieve the reset password token without authorization and then perform the password change.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24904 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. An adjacent network ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24904</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. An adjacent network high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the storage of malicious HTML or JavaScript codes in a trusted application data store. When a victim user accesses the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24905 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. An adjacent network ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24905</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. An adjacent network high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the storage of malicious HTML or JavaScript codes in a trusted application data store. When a victim user accesses the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24907 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in the Filters page. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24907</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in the Filters page. An adjacent network high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the storage of malicious HTML or JavaScript codes in a trusted application data store. When a victim user accesses the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24906 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Policy page. An ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24906</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain(s) a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Policy page. An adjacent network high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the storage of malicious HTML or JavaScript codes in a trusted application data store. When a victim user accesses the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24900 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain an improper authorization vulnerability. An adjacent network low pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24900</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Policy Manager, all versions, contain an improper authorization vulnerability. An adjacent network low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized devices added to policies. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure and unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2062 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software edit_categories.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2062</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit_categories.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255377 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2063 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software profile_crud.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2063</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/app/profile_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255378 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39254 | Dell Update Package (DUP), Versions prior to 4.9.10 contain an Uncontrolled Search Path vulnerability. A malicious user with local access to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39254</link><description>Dell Update Package (DUP), Versions prior to 4.9.10 contain an Uncontrolled Search Path vulnerability. A malicious user with local access to the system could potentially exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary code as admin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48674 | Dell Platform BIOS contains an Improper Null Termination vulnerability. A high privilege user with network access to the system could potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48674</link><description>Dell Platform BIOS contains an Improper Null Termination vulnerability. A high privilege user with network access to the system could potentially send malicious data to the device in order to cause some services to cease to function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2060 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software login_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2060</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/app/login_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255375.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2061 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software edit_supplier.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2061</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_supplier.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255376.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2057 | Harrison Chase LangChain tfidf.py load_local server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2057</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Harrison Chase LangChain 0.1.9. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function load_local in the library libs/community/langchain_community/retrievers/tfidf.py. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255372.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2059 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software service_crud.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2059</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/service_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255374 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2078 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in HelpDeskZ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2078</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been found in HelpDeskZ affecting version 2.0.2 and earlier. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload within the email field and partially take control of an authenticated user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22457 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway 5.20 contains an improper authentication vulnerability during the SRS to SCG update path. A remote low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22457</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway 5.20 contains an improper authentication vulnerability during the SRS to SCG update path. A remote low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to impersonation of the server through presenting a fake self-signed certificate and communicating with the remote server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26280 | Apache Airflow: Overly broad default permissions for Viewer/Ops (audit logs)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26280</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.2, has a vulnerability that allows authenticated Ops and Viewers users to view all information on audit logs, including dag names and usernames they were not permitted to view.With 2.8.2 and newer, Ops and Viewer users do not have audit log permission by default, they need to be explicitly granted permissions to see the logs. Only admin users have audit log permission by default.

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.2 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22458 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway, 5.18, contains an Inadequate Encryption Strength Vulnerability. An unauthenticated network attacker could poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22458</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway, 5.18, contains an Inadequate Encryption Strength Vulnerability. An unauthenticated network attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to recover plaintext from a block of ciphertext.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2058 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2058</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/product.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255373 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 10:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1120 | The NextMove Lite  Thank You Page for WooCommerce and Finale Lite  Sales Countdown Timer &amp; Discount for WooCommerce plugins for WordPress ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1120</link><description>The NextMove Lite  Thank You Page for WooCommerce and Finale Lite  Sales Countdown Timer &amp; Discount for WooCommerce plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the download_tools_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export system information that can aid attackers in an attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25972 | Initialization of a resource with an insecure default vulnerability in OET-213H-BTS1 sold in Japan by Atsumi Electric Co., Ltd. allows a net...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25972</link><description>Initialization of a resource with an insecure default vulnerability in OET-213H-BTS1 sold in Japan by Atsumi Electric Co., Ltd. allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to configure and control the affected product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0692 | SolarWinds Security Event Manager Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0692</link><description>The SolarWinds Security Event Manager was susceptible to Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated user to abuse SolarWinds service, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25091 | Protection mechanism failure issue exists in RevoWorks SCVX prior to scvimage4.10.21_1013 (when using 'VirusChecker' or 'ThreatChecker' feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25091</link><description>Protection mechanism failure issue exists in RevoWorks SCVX prior to scvimage4.10.21_1013 (when using 'VirusChecker' or 'ThreatChecker' feature) and RevoWorks Browser prior to 2.2.95 (when using 'VirusChecker' or 'ThreatChecker' feature).  If data containing malware is saved in a specific file format (eml, dmg, vhd, iso, msi), malware may be taken outside the sandboxed environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52555 | In mongo-express 1.0.2, /admin allows CSRF, as demonstrated by deletion of a Collection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52555</link><description>In mongo-express 1.0.2, /admin allows CSRF, as demonstrated by deletion of a Collection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25552 | Wiesemann &amp;amp; Theis: Multiple products prone to unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25552</link><description>A local attacker can gain administrative privileges by inserting an executable file in the path of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27950 | WordPress Sirv Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.0 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27950</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sirv.Com Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN  Sirv.This issue affects Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN  Sirv: from n/a through 7.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 07:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27949 | WordPress Sirv Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.0 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27949</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in sirv.Com Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN  Sirv.This issue affects Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN  Sirv: from n/a through 7.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 07:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1859 | The Slider Responsive Slideshow  Image slider, Gallery slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1859</link><description>The Slider Responsive Slideshow  Image slider, Gallery slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8 via deserialization of untrusted input to the awl_slider_responsive_shortcode function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 06:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25386 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in DICOM Connectivity Framework by laurelbridge before v.2.7.6b allows a remote attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25386</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in DICOM Connectivity Framework by laurelbridge before v.2.7.6b allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the format_logfile.pl file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 06:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22891 | Nteract v.0.28.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Markdown link.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22891</link><description>Nteract v.0.28.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Markdown link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 05:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25293 | mjml-app versions 3.0.4 and 3.1.0-beta were discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) via the href attribute.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25293</link><description>mjml-app versions 3.0.4 and 3.1.0-beta were discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) via the href attribute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 05:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50312 | IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50312</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 24.0.0.2 could provide weaker than expected security for outbound TLS connections caused by a failure to honor user configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  274711.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38366 | IBM FileNet Content Manager directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38366</link><description>IBM Filenet Content Manager Component 5.5.8.0, 5.5.10.0, and 5.5.11.0 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  261115.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47716 | IBM FileNet Content Manager privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47716</link><description>IBM CP4BA - Filenet Content Manager Component 5.5.8.0, 5.5.10.0, and 5.5.11.0 could allow a user to gain the privileges of another user under unusual circumstances.  IBM X-Force ID:  271656.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28525 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28525</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management 9.7.2.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  251052.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28949 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28949</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management DOORS 9.7.2.7 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  251216.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50305 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50305</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management DOORS 9.7.2.7 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  273336.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50324 | IBM Cognos Command Center information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50324</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 exposes details the X-AspNet-Version Response Header that could allow an attacker to obtain information of the application environment to conduct further attacks.  IBM X-Force ID:  275038.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22100 | MicroDicom DICOM Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22100</link><description>MicroDicom DICOM Viewer versions 2023.3 (Build 9342) and prior are affected by a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of DICOM Viewer. A user must open a malicious DCM file in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25578 | MicroDicom DICOM Viewer Out-of-Bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25578</link><description>MicroDicom DICOM Viewer versions 2023.3 (Build 9342) and prior contain a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which could result in memory corruption within the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1941 | Delta Electronics CNCSoft-B Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1941</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-B versions 1.0.0.4 and prior are vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, which may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2022 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway list_ipAddressPolicy.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2022</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/list_ipAddressPolicy.php. The manipulation of the argument GroupId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255301 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>