<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 07:41:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-0841 | UTT 进取 520W formPictureUrl strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0841</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPictureUrl. The manipulation of the argument importpictureurl results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 07:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0840 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigNoticeConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0840</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigNoticeConfig. The manipulation of the argument timestart leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0839 | UTT 进取 520W APSecurity strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0839</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected is the function strcpy of the file /goform/APSecurity. Executing a manipulation of the argument wepkey1 can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0838 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigWirelessBase strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0838</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This impacts the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigWirelessBase. Performing a manipulation of the argument ssid results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0837 | UTT 进取 520W formFireWall strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0837</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formFireWall. Such manipulation of the argument GroupName leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0836 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigFastDirectionW strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0836</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigFastDirectionW. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15505 | Luxul XWR-600 Web Administration cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Luxul XWR-600 up to 4.0.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Web Administration Interface. The manipulation of the argument Guest Network/Wireless Profile SSID results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond with a technical statement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0824 | questdb ui Web Console cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0824</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in questdb ui up to 1.11.9. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Web Console. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. Upgrading to version 1.1.10 is recommended to address this issue. The patch is identified as b42fd9f18476d844ae181a10a249e003dafb823d. You should upgrade the affected component. The vendor confirmed early that the fix "is going to be released as a part of QuestDB 9.3.0" as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12379 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.17.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Modern Heading Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12379</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a combination of the 'tag' and ‘title_tag’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13393 | Featured Image from URL (FIFU) &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;fifu_input_url&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13393</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.1. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs before passing them to the getimagesize() function in the Elementor widget integration. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services via the fifu_input_url parameter in the FIFU Elementor widget granted they have permissions to use Elementor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0822 | quickjs-ng quickjs quickjs.c js_typed_array_sort heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0822</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in quickjs-ng quickjs up to 0.11.0. This issue affects the function js_typed_array_sort of the file quickjs.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is 53eefbcd695165a3bd8c584813b472cb4a69fbf5. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0821 | quickjs-ng quickjs quickjs.c js_typed_array_constructor heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0821</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in quickjs-ng quickjs up to 0.11.0. This vulnerability affects the function js_typed_array_constructor of the file quickjs.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called c5d80831e51e48a83eab16ea867be87f091783c5. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14555 | Countdown Timer - Widget Countdown &amp;lt;= 2.7.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14555</link><description>The Countdown Timer – Widget Countdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpdevart_countdown' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15504 | lief-project LIEF ELF Binary Parser.tcc parse_binary null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15504</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in lief-project LIEF up to 0.17.1. Affected by this issue is the function Parser::parse_binary of the file src/ELF/Parser.tcc of the component ELF Binary Parser. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. Upgrading to version 0.17.2 can resolve this issue. The patch is identified as 81bd5d7ea0c390563f1c4c017c9019d154802978. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14506 | ConvertForce Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 0.0.7 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting via entrance_animation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14506</link><description>The ConvertForce Popup Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Gutenberg block's `entrance_animation` attribute in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.7. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52435 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: Invalid error handling in pause encryption procedure in NimBLE controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52435</link><description>J2EE Misconfiguration: Data Transmission Without Encryption vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Improper handling of Pause Encryption procedure on Link Layer results in a previously encrypted connection being left in un-encrypted state allowing an eavesdropper to observe the remainder of the exchange.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through &lt;= 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53470 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in NimBLE HCI H4 driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53470</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Apache  NimBLE HCI H4 driver. Specially crafted HCI event could lead to invalid memory read in H4 driver.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.8. 

This issue requires a broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53477 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: NULL Pointer Dereference in NimBLE host HCI layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53477</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Apache Nimble.

Missing validation of HCI connection complete or HCI command TX buffer could lead to NULL pointer dereference.
This issue requires disabled asserts and broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62235 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: Incorrect handling of SMP Security Request could lead to undesirable pairing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62235</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Receiving specially crafted Security Request could lead to removal of original bond and re-bond with impostor.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0831 | Templately &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary JSON File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0831</link><description>The Templately plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8. This is due to inadequate input validation in the `save_template_to_file()` function where user-controlled parameters like `session_id`, `content_id`, and `ai_page_ids` are used to construct file paths without proper sanitization. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to write arbitrary `.ai.json` files to locations within the uploads directory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15503 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System common.jsp unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15503</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /fort/trust/version/common/common.jsp. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14976 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 4.4.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14976</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form Builder, Custom Login Form, User Profile, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'process_row_actions' function with the 'delete' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary post via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15502 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System session SessionController os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15502</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. The affected element is the function SessionController of the file /isomp-protocol/protocol/session. Such manipulation of the argument Hostname leads to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14948 | miniOrange OTP Verification and SMS Notification for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.3.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Notification Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14948</link><description>The miniOrange OTP Verification and SMS Notification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the `enable_wc_sms_notification` AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable or disable SMS notification settings for WooCommerce orders.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 07:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14943 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 8.7.2 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14943</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.2. This is due to a misconfigured authorization check on the 'getShipItemFullText' function which only verifies that a user has the 'read' capability (Subscriber-level) and a valid nonce, but fails to verify whether the user has permission to access the specific post being requested. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract data from password-protected, private, or draft posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22773 | vLLM is vulnerable to DoS in Idefics3 vision models via image payload with ambiguous dimensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22773</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). In versions from 0.6.4 to before 0.12.0, users can crash the vLLM engine serving multimodal models that use the Idefics3 vision model implementation by sending a specially crafted 1x1 pixel image. This causes a tensor dimension mismatch that results in an unhandled runtime error, leading to complete server termination. This issue has been patched in version 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22777 | ComfyUI-Manager is Vulnerable to CRLF Injection in Configuration Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22777</link><description>ComfyUI-Manager is an extension designed to enhance the usability of ComfyUI. Prior to versions 3.39.2 and 4.0.5, an attacker can inject special characters into HTTP query parameters to add arbitrary configuration values to the config.ini file. This can lead to security setting tampering or modification of application behavior. This issue has been patched in versions 3.39.2 and 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22704 | haxcms-php 11.0.6 Stored XSS Leading to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22704</link><description>HAX CMS helps manage microsite universe with PHP or NodeJs backends. In versions 11.0.6 to before 25.0.0, HAX CMS is vulnerable to stored XSS, which could lead to account takeover. This issue has been patched in version 25.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22702 | virtualenv Has TOCTOU Vulnerabilities in Directory Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22702</link><description>virtualenv is a tool for creating isolated virtual python environments. Prior to version 20.36.1, TOCTOU (Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use) vulnerabilities in virtualenv allow local attackers to perform symlink-based attacks on directory creation operations. An attacker with local access can exploit a race condition between directory existence checks and creation to redirect virtualenv's app_data and lock file operations to attacker-controlled locations. This issue has been patched in version 20.36.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22703 | Cosign verification accepts any valid Rekor entry under certain conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22703</link><description>Cosign provides code signing and transparency for containers and binaries. Prior to versions 2.6.2 and 3.0.4, Cosign bundle can be crafted to successfully verify an artifact even if the embedded Rekor entry does not reference the artifact's digest, signature or public key. When verifying a Rekor entry, Cosign verifies the Rekor entry signature, and also compares the artifact's digest, the user's public key from either a Fulcio certificate or provided by the user, and the artifact signature to the Rekor entry contents. Without these comparisons, Cosign would accept any response from Rekor as valid. A malicious actor that has compromised a user's identity or signing key could construct a valid Cosign bundle by including any arbitrary Rekor entry, thus preventing the user from being able to audit the signing event. This issue has been patched in versions 2.6.2 and 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22705 | RustCrypto: Signatures has timing side-channel in ML-DSA decomposition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22705</link><description>RustCrypto: Signatures offers support for digital signatures, which provide authentication of data using public-key cryptography. Prior to version 0.1.0-rc.2, a timing side-channel was discovered in the Decompose algorithm which is used during ML-DSA signing to generate hints for the signature. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.0-rc.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22701 | filelock Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) Symlink Vulnerability in SoftFileLock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22701</link><description>filelock is a platform-independent file lock for Python. Prior to version 3.20.3, a TOCTOU race condition vulnerability exists in the SoftFileLock implementation of the filelock package. An attacker with local filesystem access and permission to create symlinks can exploit a race condition between the permission validation and file creation to cause lock operations to fail or behave unexpectedly. The vulnerability occurs in the _acquire() method between raise_on_not_writable_file() (permission check) and os.open() (file creation). During this race window, an attacker can create a symlink at the lock file path, potentially causing the lock to operate on an unintended target file or leading to denial of service. This issue has been patched in version 3.20.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22693 | Null Pointer Dereference in SubtableUnicodesCache::create leading to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22693</link><description>HarfBuzz is a text shaping engine. Prior to version 12.3.0, a null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the SubtableUnicodesCache::create function located in src/hb-ot-cmap-table.hh. The function fails to check if hb_malloc returns NULL before using placement new to construct an object at the returned pointer address. When hb_malloc fails to allocate memory (which can occur in low-memory conditions or when using custom allocators that simulate allocation failures), it returns NULL. The code then attempts to call the constructor on this null pointer using placement new syntax, resulting in undefined behavior and a Segmentation Fault. This issue has been patched in version 12.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22685 | DevToys Path Traversal (“Zip Slip”) Vulnerability in DevToys Extension Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22685</link><description>DevToys is a desktop app for developers. In versions from 2.0.0.0 to before 2.0.9.0, a path traversal vulnerability exists in the DevToys extension installation mechanism. When processing extension packages (NUPKG archives), DevToys does not sufficiently validate file paths contained within the archive. A malicious extension package could include crafted file entries such as ../../…/target-file, causing the extraction process to write files outside the intended extensions directory. This flaw enables an attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the user’s system with the privileges of the DevToys process. Depending on the environment, this may lead to code execution, configuration tampering, or corruption of application or system files. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22689 | Mailpit is vulnerable to Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking (CSWSH) allowing unauthenticated access to emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22689</link><description>Mailpit is an email testing tool and API for developers. Prior to version 1.28.2, the Mailpit WebSocket server is configured to accept connections from any origin. This lack of Origin header validation introduces a Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking (CSWSH) vulnerability. An attacker can host a malicious website that, when visited by a developer running Mailpit locally, establishes a WebSocket connection to the victim's Mailpit instance (default ws://localhost:8025). This allows the attacker to intercept sensitive data such as email contents, headers, and server statistics in real-time. This issue has been patched in version 1.28.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22611 | AWS SDK for .NET V4 adopted defense in depth enhancement for region parameter value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22611</link><description>AWS SDK for .NET works with Amazon Web Services to help build scalable solutions with Amazon S3, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon Glacier, and more. From versions 4.0.0 to before 4.0.3.3, Customer applications could be configured to improperly route AWS API calls to non-existent or non-AWS hosts. This notification is related to the use of specific values for the region input field when calling AWS services. An actor with access to the environment in which the SDK is used could set the region input field to an invalid value. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22698 | RustCrypto SM2-PKE has 32-bit Biased Nonce Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22698</link><description>RustCrypto: Elliptic Curves is general purpose Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) support, including types and traits for representing various elliptic curve forms, scalars, points, and public/secret keys composed thereof. In versions 0.14.0-pre.0 and 0.14.0-rc.0, a  critical vulnerability exists in the SM2 Public Key Encryption (PKE) implementation where the ephemeral nonce k is generated with severely reduced entropy. A unit mismatch error causes the nonce generation function to request only 32 bits of randomness instead of the expected 256 bits. This reduces the security of the encryption from a 128-bit level to a trivial 16-bit level, allowing a practical attack to recover the nonce k and decrypt any ciphertext given only the public key and ciphertext. This issue has been patched via commit e4f7778.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22699 | RustCrypto SM2-PKE has Unchecked AffinePoint Decoding (unwrap) in decrypt()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22699</link><description>RustCrypto: Elliptic Curves is general purpose Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) support, including types and traits for representing various elliptic curve forms, scalars, points, and public/secret keys composed thereof. In versions 0.14.0-pre.0 and 0.14.0-rc.0, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the SM2 PKE decryption path where an invalid elliptic-curve point (C1) is decoded and the resulting value is unwrapped without checking. Specifically, AffinePoint::from_encoded_point(&amp;amp;encoded_c1) may return a None/CtOption::None when the supplied coordinates are syntactically valid but do not lie on the SM2 curve. The calling code previously used .unwrap(), causing a panic when presented with such input. This issue has been patched via commit 085b7be.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22700 | RustCrypto Has Insufficient Length Validation in decrypt() in SM2-PKE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22700</link><description>RustCrypto: Elliptic Curves is general purpose Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) support, including types and traits for representing various elliptic curve forms, scalars, points, and public/secret keys composed thereof. In versions 0.14.0-pre.0 and 0.14.0-rc.0, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the SM2 public-key encryption (PKE) implementation: the decrypt() path performs unchecked slice::split_at operations on input buffers derived from untrusted ciphertext. An attacker can submit short/undersized ciphertext or carefully-crafted DER-encoded structures to trigger bounds-check panics (Rust unwinding) which crash the calling thread or process. This issue has been patched via commit e60e991.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22690 | pypdf has possible long runtimes for missing /Root object with large /Size values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22690</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to version 6.6.0, pypdf has possible long runtimes for missing /Root object with large /Size values. An attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to possibly long runtimes for actually invalid files. This can be achieved by omitting the /Root entry in the trailer, while using a rather large /Size value. Only the non-strict reading mode is affected. This issue has been patched in version 6.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22691 | pypdf has possible long runtimes for malformed startxref</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22691</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to version 6.6.0, pypdf has possible long runtimes for malformed startxref. An attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to possibly long runtimes for invalid startxref entries. When rebuilding the cross-reference table, PDF files with lots of whitespace characters become problematic. Only the non-strict reading mode is affected. Only the non-strict reading mode is affected. This issue has been patched in version 6.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22687 | WeKnora vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22687</link><description>WeKnora is an LLM-powered framework designed for deep document understanding and semantic retrieval. Prior to version 0.2.5, after WeKnora enables the Agent service, it allows users to call the database query tool. Due to insufficient backend validation, an attacker can use prompt‑based bypass techniques to evade query restrictions and obtain sensitive information from the target server and database. This issue has been patched in version 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22688 | WeKnora has Command Injection in MCP stdio test</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22688</link><description>WeKnora is an LLM-powered framework designed for deep document understanding and semantic retrieval. Prior to version 0.2.5, there is a command injection vulnerability that allows authenticated users to inject stdio_config.command/args into MCP stdio settings, causing the server to execute subprocesses using these injected values. This issue has been patched in version 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13457 | WooCommerce Square &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure in get_token_by_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13457</link><description>The WooCommerce Square plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.1 via the get_token_by_id  function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to expose arbitrary Square "ccof" (credit card on file) values and leverage this value to potentially make fraudulent charges on the target site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61674 | October CMS Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Editor and Branding Styles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61674</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform. Prior to versions 3.7.13 and 4.0.12, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in October CMS backend configuration forms. A user with the Global Editor Settings permission could inject malicious HTML/JS into the stylesheet input at Markup Styles. A specially crafted input could break out of the intended</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61676 | October CMS Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Branding Styles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61676</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform. Prior to versions 3.7.13 and 4.0.12, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities was identified in October CMS backend configuration forms. A user with the Customize Backend Styles permission could inject malicious HTML/JS into the stylesheet input at Styles from Branding &amp; Appearance settings. A specially crafted input could break out of the intended</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65090 | XWiki Full Calendar Macro vulnerable to data leak through Calendar.JSONService</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65090</link><description>XWiki Full Calendar Macro displays objects from the wiki on the calendar. Prior to version 2.4.6, users with the rights to view the Calendar.JSONService page (including guest users) can exploit the data leak vulnerability by accessing database info, with the exception of passwords. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65091 | XWiki Full Calendar Macro vulnerable to SQL injection through Calendar.JSONService</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65091</link><description>XWiki Full Calendar Macro displays objects from the wiki on the calendar. Prior to version 2.4.5, users with the right to view the Calendar.JSONService page (including guest users) can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability by accessing database info or starting a DoS attack. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22589 | Spree API has Unauthenticated IDOR - Guest Address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22589</link><description>Spree is an open source e-commerce solution built with Ruby on Rails. Prior to versions 4.10.2, 5.0.7, 5.1.9, and 5.2.5, an Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability was identified that allows an unauthenticated attacker to access guest address information without supplying valid credentials or session cookies. This issue has been patched in versions 4.10.2, 5.0.7, 5.1.9, and 5.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22610 | Angular has XSS Vulnerability via Unsanitized SVG Script Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22610</link><description>Angular is a development platform for building mobile and desktop web applications using TypeScript/JavaScript and other languages. Prior to versions 19.2.18, 20.3.16, 21.0.7, and 21.1.0-rc.0, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Angular Template Compiler. The vulnerability exists because Angular’s internal sanitization schema fails to recognize the href and xlink:href attributes of SVG</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59057 | React Router has XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59057</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/react versions 1.15.0 through 2.17.0. and react-router versions 7.0.0 through 7.8.2, a XSS vulnerability exists in in React Router's meta()/ APIs in Framework Mode when generating script:ld+json tags which could allow arbitrary JavaScript execution during SSR if untrusted content is used to generate the tag. There is no impact if the application is being used in Declarative Mode () or Data Mode (createBrowserRouter/). This issue has been patched in @remix-run/react version 2.17.1 and react-router version 7.9.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61686 | React Router has Path Traversal in File Session Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61686</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @react-router/node versions 7.0.0 through 7.9.3, @remix-run/deno prior to version 2.17.2, and @remix-run/node prior to version 2.17.2, if createFileSessionStorage() is being used from @react-router/node (or @remix-run/node/@remix-run/deno in Remix v2) with an unsigned cookie, it is possible for an attacker to cause the session to try to read/write from a location outside the specified session file directory. The success of the attack would depend on the permissions of the web server process to access those files. Read files cannot be returned directly to the attacker. Session file reads would only succeed if the file matched the expected session file format. If the file matched the session file format, the data would be populated into the server side session but not directly returned to the attacker unless the application logic returned specific session information. This issue has been patched in @react-router/node version 7.9.4, @remix-run/deno version 2.17.2, and @remix-run/node version 2.17.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68470 | React Router has unexpected external redirect via untrusted paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68470</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In versions 6.0.0 through 6.30.1 and 7.0.0 through 7.9.5, an attacker-supplied path can be crafted so that when a React Router application navigates to it via navigate(), , or redirect(), the app performs a navigation/redirect to an external URL. This is only an issue if you are passing untrusted content into navigation paths in your application code. This issue has been patched in versions 6.30.2 and 7.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21884 | React Router SSR XSS in ScrollRestoration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21884</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/react version prior to 2.17.3. and react-router 7.0.0 through 7.11.0, a XSS vulnerability exists in in React Router's  API in Framework Mode when using the getKey/storageKey props during Server-Side Rendering which could allow arbitrary JavaScript execution during SSR if untrusted content is used to generate the keys. There is no impact if server-side rendering in Framework Mode is disabled, or if Declarative Mode () or Data Mode (createBrowserRouter/) is being used. This issue has been patched in @remix-run/react version 2.17.3 and react-router version 7.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22029 | React Router vulnerable to XSS via Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22029</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/router version prior to 1.23.2. and react-router 7.0.0 through 7.11.0, React Router (and Remix v1/v2) SPA open navigation redirects originating from loaders or actions in Framework Mode, Data Mode, or the unstable RSC modes can result in unsafe URLs causing unintended javascript execution on the client. This is only an issue if you are creating redirect paths from untrusted content or via an open redirect. There is no impact if Declarative Mode () is being used. This issue has been patched in @remix-run/router version 1.23.2 and react-router version 7.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22030 | React Router has CSRF issue in Action/Server Action Request Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22030</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/server-runtime version prior to 2.17.3. and react-router 7.0.0 through 7.11.0, React Router (or Remix v2) is vulnerable to CSRF attacks on document POST requests to UI routes when using server-side route action handlers in Framework Mode, or when using React Server Actions in the new unstable RSC modes. There is no impact if Declarative Mode () or Data Mode (createBrowserRouter/) is being used. This issue has been patched in @remix-run/server-runtime version 2.17.3 and react-router version 7.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22594 | Ghost has Staff 2FA bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22594</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.105.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost's 2FA mechanism allows staff users to skip email 2FA. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22595 | Ghost has Staff Token permission bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22595</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.121.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost's handling of Staff Token authentication allowed certain endpoints to be accessed that were only intended to be accessible via Staff Session authentication. External systems that have been authenticated via Staff Tokens for Admin/Owner-role users would have had access to these endpoints. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22596 | Ghost has SQL Injection in Members Activity Feed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22596</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.90.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost's /ghost/api/admin/members/events endpoint allows users with authentication credentials for the Admin API to execute arbitrary SQL. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22597 | Ghost has SSRF via External Media Inliner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22597</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.38.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost’s media inliner mechanism allows staff users in possession of a valid authentication token for the Ghost Admin API to exfiltrate data from internal systems via SSRF. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22600 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read via ImageMagick SVG Coder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22600</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. A Local File Read (LFR) vulnerability exists in the work package PDF export functionality of OpenProject prior to version 16.6.4. By uploading a specially crafted SVG file (disguised as a PNG) as a work package attachment, an attacker can exploit the backend image processing engine (ImageMagick). When the work package is exported to PDF, the backend attempts to resize the image, triggering the ImageMagick text: coder. This allows an attacker to read arbitrary local files that the application user has permissions to access (e.g., /etc/passwd, all project configuration files, private project data, etc.). The attack requires permissions to upload attachments to a container that can be exported to PDF, such as a work package. The issue has been patched in version 16.6.4. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22601 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to Code Execution in E-Mail function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22601</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. For OpenProject version 16.6.1 and below, a registered administrator can execute arbitrary command by configuring sendmail binary path and sending a test email. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22602 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to User Enumeration via User ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22602</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to version 16.6.2, a low‑privileged logged-in user can view the full names of other users. Since user IDs are assigned sequentially and predictably (e.g., 1 to 1000), an attacker can extract a complete list of all users’ full names by iterating through these URLs. The same behavior can also be reproduced via the OpenProject API, allowing automated retrieval of full names through the API as well. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22603 | OpenProject has no protection against brute-force attacks in the Change Password function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22603</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to version 16.6.2, OpenProject’s unauthenticated password-change endpoint (/account/change_password) was not protected by the same brute-force safeguards that apply to the normal login form. In affected versions, an attacker who can guess or enumerate user IDs can send unlimited password-change requests for a given account without triggering lockout or other rate-limiting controls. This allows automated password-guessing (e.g., with wordlists of common passwords) against valid accounts. Successful guessing results in full account compromise for the targeted user and, depending on that user’s role, can lead to further privilege escalation inside the application. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22604 | OpenProject is vulnerable to user enumeration via the change password function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22604</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. For OpenProject versions from 11.2.1 to before 16.6.2, when sending a POST request to the /account/change_password endpoint with an arbitrary User ID as the password_change_user_id parameter, the resulting error page would show the username for the requested user. Since this endpoint is intended to be called without being authenticated, this allows to enumerate the user names of all accounts registered in an OpenProject instance. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22605 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in Meetings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22605</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. OpenProject versions prior to version 16.6.3, allowed users with the View Meetings permission on any project, to access meeting details of meetings that belonged to projects, the user does not have access to. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22606 | Fickling has a bypass via runpy.run_path() and runpy.run_module()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22606</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Fickling versions up to and including 0.1.6 do not treat Python’s runpy module as unsafe. Because of this, a malicious pickle that uses runpy.run_path() or runpy.run_module() is classified as SUSPICIOUS instead of OVERTLY_MALICIOUS. If a user relies on Fickling’s output to decide whether a pickle is safe to deserialize, this misclassification can lead them to execute attacker-controlled code on their system. This affects any workflow or product that uses Fickling as a security gate for pickle deserialization. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22607 | Fickling Blocklist Bypass: cProfile.run()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22607</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Fickling versions up to and including 0.1.6 do not treat Python's cProfile module as unsafe. Because of this, a malicious pickle that uses cProfile.run() is classified as SUSPICIOUS instead of OVERTLY_MALICIOUS. If a user relies on Fickling's output to decide whether a pickle is safe to deserialize, this misclassification can lead them to execute attacker-controlled code on their system. This affects any workflow or product that uses Fickling as a security gate for pickle deserialization. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22608 | Fickling vulnerable to use of ctypes and pydoc gadget chain to bypass detection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22608</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Prior to version 0.1.7, both ctypes and pydoc modules aren't explicitly blocked. Even other existing pickle scanning tools (like picklescan) do not block pydoc.locate. Chaining these two together can achieve RCE while the scanner still reports the file as LIKELY_SAFE. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22609 | Fickling has Static Analysis Bypass via Incomplete Dangerous Module Blocklist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22609</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Prior to version 0.1.7, the unsafe_imports() method in Fickling's static analyzer fails to flag several high-risk Python modules that can be used for arbitrary code execution. Malicious pickles importing these modules will not be detected as unsafe, allowing attackers to bypass Fickling's primary static safety checks. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22612 | Fickling vulnerable to detection bypass due to &amp;quot;builtins&amp;quot; blindness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22612</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Prior to version 0.1.7, Fickling is vulnerable to detection bypass due to "builtins" blindness. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21897 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-Bounds Write in Crypto_Config_Add_Gvcid_Managed_Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21897</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the Crypto_Config_Add_Gvcid_Managed_Parameters function only checks whether gvcid_counter &gt; GVCID_MAN_PARAM_SIZE. As a result, it allows up to the 251st entry, which causes a write past the end of the array, overwriting gvcid_counter located immediately after gvcid_managed_parameters_array[250]. This leads to an out-of-bounds write, and the overwritten gvcid_counter may become an arbitrary value, potentially affecting the parameter lookup/registration logic that relies on it. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21898 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-bounds Read in Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21898</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity function reads memory without valid bounds checking when parsing AOS frame hashes. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21899 | CryptoLib has an out-of-bounds read and crash vulnerability when decoding an empty Base64url string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21899</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, in base64urlDecode, padding-stripping dereferences input[inputLen - 1] before checking that inputLen &gt; 0 or that input != NULL. For inputLen == 0, this becomes an OOB read at input[-1], potentially crashing the process. If input == NULL and inputLen == 0, it dereferences NULL - 1. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21900 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-Bounds Read in KMC Encrypt Metadata Parsing via Flawed strtok Pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21900</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, an out-of-bounds heap read vulnerability in cryptography_encrypt() occurs when parsing JSON metadata from KMC server responses. The flawed strtok iteration pattern uses ptr + strlen(ptr) + 1 which reads one byte past allocated buffer boundaries when processing short or malformed metadata strings. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22023 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-Bounds Read in KMC AEAD Encrypt Metadata Parsing via Flawed strtok Pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22023</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, there is an out-of-bounds heap read vulnerability in cryptography_aead_encrypt(). This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22024 | CryptoLib Memory Leak in KMC Encrypt Function Leads to Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22024</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the cryptography_encrypt() function allocates multiple buffers for HTTP requests and JSON parsing that are never freed on any code path. Each call leaks approximately 400 bytes of memory. Sustained traffic can gradually exhaust available memory. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22025 | CryptoLib Memory Leak on HTTP Error Response in KMC Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22025</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, when the KMC server returns a non-200 HTTP status code, cryptography_encrypt() and cryptography_decrypt() return immediately without freeing previously allocated buffers. Each failed request leaks approximately 467 bytes. Repeated failures (from a malicious server or network issues) can gradually exhaust memory. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22026 | CryptoLib Unbounded Memory Allocation in KMC HTTP Response Handler Allows Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22026</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the libcurl write_callback function in the KMC crypto service client allows unbounded memory growth by reallocating response buffers without any size limit or overflow check. A malicious KMC server can return arbitrarily large HTTP responses, forcing the client to allocate excessive memory until the process is terminated by the OS. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22027 | CryptoLib Vulnerable to Heap Buffer Overflow in MariaDB SA Hexstring Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22027</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the convert_hexstring_to_byte_array() function in the MariaDB SA interface writes decoded bytes into a caller-provided buffer without any capacity check. When importing SA fields from the database (e.g., IV, ARSN, ABM), a malformed or oversized hex string in the database can overflow the destination buffer, corrupting adjacent heap memory. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22697 | CryptoLib Has Heap Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in KMC Base64 Decode Handling (KMC JSON base64ciphertext/base64cleartext)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22697</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, CryptoLib’s KMC crypto service integration is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow when decoding Base64-encoded ciphertext/cleartext fields returned by the KMC service. The decode destination buffer is sized using an expected output length (len_data_out), but the Base64 decoder writes output based on the actual Base64 input length and does not enforce any destination size limit. An oversized Base64 string in the KMC JSON response can cause out-of-bounds writes on the heap, resulting in process crash and potentially code execution under certain conditions. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15501 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System getCmd WriterHandle.getCmd os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15501</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. Impacted is the function WriterHandle.getCmd of the file /isomp-protocol/protocol/getCmd. This manipulation of the argument sessionPath causes os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22584 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Salesforce Uni2TS on MacOS, Windows, Linux allows Leverage Execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22584</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Salesforce Uni2TS on MacOS, Windows, Linux allows Leverage Executable Code in Non-Executable Files.This issue affects Uni2TS: through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15499 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System VersionController.java uploadCN os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15499</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. This vulnerability affects the function uploadCN of the file VersionController.java. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15500 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System HTTP POST Request getHis os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15500</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /isomp-protocol/protocol/getHis of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument sessionPath results in os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46286 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2. Restoring from a backup may prevent p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46286</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2. Restoring from a backup may prevent passcode from being required immediately after Face ID enrollment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46297 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.2. An app may be able to access protec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46297</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.2. An app may be able to access protected files within an App Sandbox container.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46298 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26.2, Safari 26.2, watchOS 26.2, visionOS 26.2, iOS 26.2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46298</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26.2, Safari 26.2, watchOS 26.2, visionOS 26.2, iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2, macOS Tahoe 26.2. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46299 | A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26.2, Safari 26.2, watchOS 26.2, visi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46299</link><description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26.2, Safari 26.2, watchOS 26.2, visionOS 26.2, iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2, macOS Tahoe 26.2. Processing maliciously crafted web content may disclose internal states of the app.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62487 | Under certain configurations, file artifacts uploaded to the Dossier and Slides apps did not inherit security markings of their parent artifact. This lack of security markings could lead to unintended access to the uploaded files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62487</link><description>### Details
On October 1, 2025, Palantir discovered that images uploaded through the Dossier front-end app were not being marked correctly with the proper security levels. The regression was traced back to a change in May 2025, which was meant to allow file uploads to be shared among different artifacts (e.g. other dossiers and presentations).

On deployments configured with CBAC, the front-end would present a security picker dialog to set the security level on the uploads, thereby mitigating the issue.

On deployments without a CBAC configuration, no security picker dialog appears, leading to a security level of CUSTOM with no markings or datasets selected. The resulting markings and groups for the file uploads thus will be only those added by the “Default authorization rules” defined in the Auth Chooser configuration. On most environments, it is expected that the “Default authorization rules" only add the Everyone group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0830 | Command Injection in Kiro GitLab Merge Request Helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0830</link><description>Processing specially crafted workspace folder names could allow for arbitrary command injection in the Kiro GitLab Merge-Request helper in Kiro IDE before version 0.6.18 when opening maliciously crafted workspaces.

To mitigate, users should update to version 0.6.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51626 | SQL injection vulnerability in pss.sale.com 1.0 via the id parameter to the userfiles/php/cancel_order.php endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51626</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in pss.sale.com 1.0 via the id parameter to the userfiles/php/cancel_order.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60538 | A lack of rate limiting in the login page of shiori v1.7.4 and below allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60538</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the login page of shiori v1.7.4 and below allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66715 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in Axtion ODISSAAS ODIS v1.8.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted DLL file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66715</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in Axtion ODISSAAS ODIS v1.8.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted DLL file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67810 | In Area9 Rhapsode 1.47.3, an authenticated attacker can exploit the operation, url, and filename parameters via POST request to read arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67810</link><description>In Area9 Rhapsode 1.47.3, an authenticated attacker can exploit the operation, url, and filename parameters via POST request to read arbitrary files from the server filesystem. Fixed in 1.47.4 (#7254) and further versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67811 | Area9 Rhapsode 1.47.3 allows SQL Injection via multiple API endpoints accessible to authenticated users. Insufficient input validation allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67811</link><description>Area9 Rhapsode 1.47.3 allows SQL Injection via multiple API endpoints accessible to authenticated users. Insufficient input validation allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands, resulting in unauthorized database access and potential compromise of sensitive data. Fixed in v.1.47.4 and beyond.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67070 | A vulnerability exists in Intelbras CFTV IP NVD 9032 R Ftd V2.800.00IB00C.0.T, which allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass the multi-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67070</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Intelbras CFTV IP NVD 9032 R Ftd V2.800.00IB00C.0.T, which allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass the multi-factor authentication (MFA) mechanism during the password recovery process. This results in the ability to change the admin password and gain full access to the administrative panel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15035 | Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability in TP-Link Archer AXE75</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15035</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in TP-Link Archer AXE75 v1.6 (vpn modules) allows an authenticated adjacent attacker to delete arbitrary server file, leading to possible loss of critical system files and service interruption or degraded functionality.This issue affects Archer AXE75 v1.6: ≤ build 20250107.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66744 | In Yonyou YonBIP v3 and before, the LoginWithV8 interface in the series data application service system is vulnerable to path traversal, all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66744</link><description>In Yonyou YonBIP v3 and before, the LoginWithV8 interface in the series data application service system is vulnerable to path traversal, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive information within the system</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15495 | BiggiDroid Simple PHP CMS editsite.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15495</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BiggiDroid Simple PHP CMS 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/editsite.php. The manipulation of the argument image results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15496 | guchengwuyue yshopmall jobs getPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15496</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in guchengwuyue yshopmall up to 1.9.1. Affected is the function getPage of the file /api/jobs. This manipulation of the argument sort causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36875 | AccessAlly &amp;lt; 3.3.2 Unauthenticated Arbitrary PHP Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36875</link><description>AccessAlly WordPress plugin versions prior to 3.3.2 contain an unauthenticated arbitrary PHP code execution vulnerability in the Login Widget. The plugin processes the login_error parameter as PHP code, allowing an attacker to supply and execute arbitrary PHP in the context of the WordPress web server process, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67004 | An Information Disclosure vulnerability in CouchCMS 2.4 allow an Admin user to read arbitrary files via traversing directories back after ba...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67004</link><description>An Information Disclosure vulnerability in CouchCMS 2.4 allow an Admin user to read arbitrary files via traversing directories back after back. It can Disclosure the source code or any other confidential information if weaponize accordingly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15493 | RainyGao DocSys ReposAuthMapper.xml sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15493</link><description>A flaw has been found in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file src/com/DocSystem/mapping/ReposAuthMapper.xml. Executing a manipulation of the argument searchWord can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15494 | RainyGao DocSys UserMapper.xml sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15494</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.37. This affects an unknown function of the file com/DocSystem/mapping/UserMapper.xml. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69542 | A Command Injection Vulnerability has been discovered in the DHCP daemon service of D-Link DIR895LA1 v102b07. The vulnerability exists in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69542</link><description>A Command Injection Vulnerability has been discovered in the DHCP daemon service of D-Link DIR895LA1 v102b07. The vulnerability exists in the lease renewal processing logic where the DHCP hostname parameter is directly concatenated into a system command without proper sanitization. When a DHCP client renews an existing lease with a malicious hostname, arbitrary commands can be executed with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46645 | Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46645</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release version 8.3.1.10, LTS2024 release versions 7.13.1.0 through 7.13.1.40, LTS 2023 release versions 7.10.1.0 through 7.10.1.70, contain an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69425 | Ruckus vRIoT IoT Controller &amp;lt; 3.0.0.0 Hardcoded Tokens RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69425</link><description>The Ruckus vRIoT IoT Controller firmware versions prior to 3.0.0.0 (GA) expose a command execution service on TCP port 2004 running with root privileges. Authentication to this service relies on a hardcoded Time-based One-Time Password (TOTP) secret and an embedded static token. An attacker who extracts these credentials from the appliance or a compromised device can generate valid authentication tokens and execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges, resulting in complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69426 | Ruckus vRIoT IoT Controller &amp;lt; 3.0.0.0 Hardcoded SSH Credentials RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69426</link><description>The Ruckus vRIoT IoT Controller firmware versions prior to 3.0.0.0 (GA) contain hardcoded credentials for an operating system user account within an initialization script. The SSH service is network-accessible without IP-based restrictions. Although the configuration disables SCP and pseudo-TTY allocation, an attacker can authenticate using the hardcoded credentials and establish SSH local port forwarding to access the Docker socket. By mounting the host filesystem via Docker, an attacker can escape the container and execute arbitrary OS commands as root on the underlying vRIoT controller, resulting in complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70161 | EDIMAX BR-6208AC V2_1.02 is vulnerable to Command Injection. This arises because the pppUserName field is directly passed to a shell command...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70161</link><description>EDIMAX BR-6208AC V2_1.02 is vulnerable to Command Injection. This arises because the pppUserName field is directly passed to a shell command via the system() function without proper sanitization. An attacker can exploit this by injecting malicious commands into the pppUserName field, allowing arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22194 | GestSup &amp;lt;= 3.2.56 CSRF Allows Privileged Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22194</link><description>GestSup versions up to and including 3.2.56 contain a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability where the application does not verify the authenticity of client requests. An attacker can induce a logged-in user to submit crafted requests that perform actions with the victim's privileges. This can be exploited to create privileged accounts by targeting the administrative user creation endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22195 | GestSup &amp;lt;= 3.2.56 SQL Injection in Search Bar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22195</link><description>GestSup versions up to and including 3.2.56 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in the search bar functionality. User-controlled search input is incorporated into SQL queries without sufficient neutralization, allowing an authenticated attacker to manipulate database queries. Successful exploitation can result in unauthorized access to or modification of database contents depending on database privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22196 | GestSup &amp;lt;= 3.2.56 SQL Injection in Ticket Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22196</link><description>GestSup versions up to and including 3.2.56 contain a SQL injection vulnerability in ticket creation functionality. User-controlled input provided during ticket creation is incorporated into SQL queries without sufficient neutralization, allowing an authenticated attacker to manipulate database queries. Successful exploitation can result in unauthorized access to or modification of database contents depending on database privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22197 | GestSup &amp;lt;= 3.2.56 Multiple SQL Injections in Asset List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22197</link><description>GestSup versions up to and including 3.2.56 contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in the asset list functionality. Multiple request parameters used to filter, search, or sort assets are incorporated into SQL queries without sufficient neutralization, allowing an authenticated attacker to manipulate database queries. Successful exploitation can result in unauthorized access to or modification of database contents depending on database privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22198 | GestSup &amp;lt;= 3.2.56 Stored XSS in API Error Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22198</link><description>GestSup versions up to and including 3.2.56 contain a pre-authentication stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the API error logging functionality. By sending an API request with a crafted X-API-KEY header value (for example, to /api/v1/ticket.php), an unauthenticated attacker can cause attacker-controlled HTML/JavaScript to be written to log entries. When an administrator later views the affected logs in the web interface, the injected content is rendered without proper output encoding, resulting in arbitrary script execution in the administrator’s browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15492 | RainyGao DocSys GroupMemberMapper.xml sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15492</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. The affected element is an unknown function of the file src/com/DocSystem/mapping/GroupMemberMapper.xml. Performing a manipulation of the argument searchWord results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46643 | Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46643</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release version 8.3.1.10, LTS2024 release versions 7.13.1.0 through 7.13.1.40, LTS 2023 release versions 7.10.1.0 through 7.10.1.70, contain a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56225 | fluidsynth-2.4.6 and earlier versions is vulnerable to Null pointer dereference in fluid_synth_monopoly.c, that can be triggered when loadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56225</link><description>fluidsynth-2.4.6 and earlier versions is vulnerable to Null pointer dereference in fluid_synth_monopoly.c, that can be triggered when loading an invalid midi file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46676 | Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46676</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release version 8.3.1.10, LTS2024 release versions 7.13.1.0 through 7.13.1.40, LTS 2023 release versions 7.10.1.0 through 7.10.1.70, contain an Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0817 | CampaignEvents API missing authorization exposes meeting and chat URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0817</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki - CampaignEvents extension allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects MediaWiki - CampaignEvents extension: 1.45, 1.44, 1.43, 1.39.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67278 | An issue in TIM Solution GmbH TIM BPM Suite &amp; TIM FLOW before v.9.1.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted HTTP req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67278</link><description>An issue in TIM Solution GmbH TIM BPM Suite &amp; TIM FLOW before v.9.1.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted HTTP request</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67279 | An issue in TIM Solution GmbH TIM BPM Suite &amp; TIM FLOW before v.9.1.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the application st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67279</link><description>An issue in TIM Solution GmbH TIM BPM Suite &amp; TIM FLOW before v.9.1.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the application stores password hashes in MD5 format</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67280 | In TIM BPM Suite/ TIM FLOW through 9.1.2 multiple Hibernate Query Language injection vulnerabilities exist which allow a low privileged user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67280</link><description>In TIM BPM Suite/ TIM FLOW through 9.1.2 multiple Hibernate Query Language injection vulnerabilities exist which allow a low privileged user to extract passwords of other users and access sensitive data of another user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67281 | In TIM BPM Suite/ TIM FLOW through 9.1.2 multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities exists which allow a low privileged and administrative user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67281</link><description>In TIM BPM Suite/ TIM FLOW through 9.1.2 multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities exists which allow a low privileged and administrative user to access the database and its content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67282 | In TIM BPM Suite/ TIM FLOW through 9.1.2 multiple Authorization Bypass vulnerabilities exists which allow a low privileged user to download ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67282</link><description>In TIM BPM Suite/ TIM FLOW through 9.1.2 multiple Authorization Bypass vulnerabilities exists which allow a low privileged user to download password hashes of other user, access work items of other user, modify restricted content in workflows, modify the applications logo and manipulate the profile of other user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46644 | Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46644</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) of Feature Release versions 7.7.1.0 through 8.4.0.0, LTS2025 release version 8.3.1.10, LTS2024 release versions 7.13.1.0 through 7.13.1.40, LTS2023 release versions 7.10.1.0 through 7.10.1.70, contain an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67133 | An issue in Hero Motocorp Vida V1 Pro 2.0.7 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the BLE component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67133</link><description>An issue in Hero Motocorp Vida V1 Pro 2.0.7 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the BLE component</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0803 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System enroll.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0803</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System up to 3.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /enroll.php. The manipulation of the argument studentregno/Pincode/session/department/level/course/sem results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14598 | CVE-2025-14598</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14598</link><description>BeeS Software Solutions BET Portal contains an SQL injection vulnerability in the login functionality of affected sites. The vulnerability enables arbitrary SQL commands to be executed on the backend database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66052 | Command injection in Vivotek IP7137 cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66052</link><description>Vivotek IP7137 camera with firmware version 0200a is vulnerable to command injection. Parameter "system_ntpIt" used by "/cgi-bin/admin/setparam.cgi" endpoint is not sanitized properly, allowing a user with administrative privileges to perform an attack. Due to CVE-2025-66050, administrative access is not protected by default, 
The vendor has not replied to the CNA Possibly all firmware versions are affected. Since the product has met End-Of-Life phase, a fix is not expected to be released.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66049 | Unprotected RTSP stream in Vivotek IP7137 cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66049</link><description>Vivotek IP7137 camera with firmware version 0200a is vulnerable to an information disclosure issue where live camera footage can be accessed through the RTSP protocol on port 8554 without requiring authentication. This allows unauthorized users with network access to view the camera's feed, potentially compromising user privacy and security. 
The vendor has not replied to the CNA. Possibly all firmware versions are affected. Since the product has met End-Of-Life phase, a fix is not expected to be released.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66050 | No password set for administrative account in Vivotek IP7137 cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66050</link><description>Vivotek IP7137 camera with firmware version 0200a by default dos not require to provide any password when logging in as an administrator. While it is possible to set up such a password, a user is not informed about such a need.
The vendor has not replied to the CNA. Possibly all firmware versions are affected. Since the product has met End-Of-Life phase, a fix is not expected to be released.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66051 | Path traversal in Vivotek IP7137 cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66051</link><description>Vivotek IP7137 camera with firmware version 0200a is vulnerable to path traversal. It is possible for an authenticated attacker to access resources beyond webroot directory using a direct HTTP request. Due to CVE-2025-66050, a password for administration panel is not set by default.
The vendor has not replied to the CNA. Possibly all firmware versions are affected. Since the product has met End-Of-Life phase, a fix is not expected to be released.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7072 | Hardcoded credentials in KAON CG3000T/CG3000CT routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7072</link><description>The firmware in KAON CG3000TC and CG3000T routers contains hard-coded credentials in clear text (shared across all routers of this model) that an unauthenticated remote attacker could use to execute commands with root privileges.
This vulnerability has been fixed in firmware version: 1.00.67 for CG3000TC and 1.00.27 for CG3000T.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22082 | Insecure Session ID Management Vulnerability in Tenda Wireless Routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22082</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Tenda wireless routers (300Mbps Wireless Router F3 and N300 Easy Setup Router) due to the use of login credentials as the session ID through its web-based administrative interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting network traffic and capturing the session ID during insecure transmission.
  
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to hijack an authenticated session and compromise sensitive configuration information on the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11453 | Header and Footer Scripts &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11453</link><description>The Header and Footer Scripts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the _inpost_head_script parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13701 | Shabat Keeper &amp;lt;= 0.4.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13701</link><description>The Shabat Keeper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the $_SERVER['PHP_SELF'] parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13704 | Autogen Headers Menu &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;head_class&amp;#x27; Shortcode Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13704</link><description>The Autogen Headers Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'head_class' parameter of the 'autogen_menu' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13717 | Contact Form vCard Generator &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;wp-gvc-cf-download-id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13717</link><description>The Contact Form vCard Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_gvccf_check_download_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export sensitive Contact Form 7 submission data via the 'wp-gvc-cf-download-id' parameter, including names, phone numbers, email addresses, and messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13852 | Debt.com Business in a Box &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13852</link><description>The Debt.com Business in a Box plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'configuration' parameter of the lead_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13854 | Curved Text &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13854</link><description>The Curved Text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'radius' parameter of the arctext shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13862 | Menu Card &amp;lt;= 0.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13862</link><description>The Menu Card plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `category` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13892 | MG AdvancedOptions &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13892</link><description>The MG AdvancedOptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13893 | Lesson Plan Book &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13893</link><description>The Lesson Plan Book plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13897 | Client Testimonial Slider &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;aft_testimonial_meta_name&amp;#x27; Metabox Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13897</link><description>The Client Testimonial Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'aft_testimonial_meta_name' custom field in the Client Information metabox in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected administrative page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13903 | PullQuote &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13903</link><description>The PullQuote plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'pullquote' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13908 | The Tooltip &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13908</link><description>The The Tooltip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'the_tooltip' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13967 | Woodpecker for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;form_name&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13967</link><description>The Woodpecker for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'form_name' parameter of the [woodpecker-connector] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14172 | WP Page Permalink Extension &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Rewrite Rules Flush</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14172</link><description>The WP Page Permalink Extension plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4. This is due to missing authorization checks on the `cwpp_trigger_flush_rewrite_rules` function hooked to `wp_ajax_cwpp_trigger_flush_rewrite_rules`. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to flush the site's rewrite rules via the `action` parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22081 | Cookie without HTTPOnly Flag Vulnerability in Tenda Wireless Routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22081</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Tenda wireless routers (300Mbps Wireless Router F3 and N300 Easy Setup Router) due to the missing HTTPOnly flag for session cookies associated with the web-based administrative interface. A remote at-tacker could exploit this vulnerability by capturing session cookies transmitted over an insecure HTTP connection.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information and gain unau-thorized access to the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22080 | Insecure Transmission Vulnerability in Tenda wireless routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22080</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Tenda wireless routers (300Mbps Wireless Router F3 and N300 Easy Setup Router) due to the transmission of credentials encoded using reversible Base64 encoding through the web-based administrative interface. An attacker on the same network could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting network traffic and capturing the Base64-encoded credentials.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information and gain unauthorized access to the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22079 | Cleartext Transmission Vulnerability in Tenda wireless routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22079</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Tenda wireless routers (300Mbps Wireless Router F3 and N300 Easy Setup Router) due to the plaintext transmission of login credentials during the initial login or post-factory reset setup through the web-based administrative interface. An attacker on the same network could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting network traffic and capturing the credentials transmitted in plaintext.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information and gain unauthorized access to the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10569 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10569</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 8.3 before 18.5.5, 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to create a denial of service condition by providing crafted responses to external API calls.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11246 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11246</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.4 before 18.5.5, 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user with specific permissions to remove all project runners from unrelated projects by manipulating GraphQL runner associations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13761 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13761</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary code in the context of an  authenticated user's browser by convincing the legitimate user to visit a specially crafted webpage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13772 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13772</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.4 before 18.5.5, 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to access and utilize AI model settings from unauthorized namespaces by manipulating namespace identifiers in API requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13781 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13781</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.5 before 18.5.5, 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to modify instance-wide AI feature provider settings by exploiting missing authorization checks in GraphQL mutations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3950 | Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3950</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 10.3 before 18.5.5, 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed a user to leak certain information by referencing specially crafted images that bypass asset proxy protection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64092 | Unauthenticated SQL injection via GET request parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64092</link><description>This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to inject an SQL request into GET request parameters and directly query the underlying database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64093 | Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via the device hostname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64093</link><description>Remote Code Execution vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary commands into the hostname of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9222 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9222</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 18.2.2 before 18.5.5, 18.6 before 18.6.3, and 18.7 before 18.7.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to achieve stored cross-site scripting by exploiting GitLab Flavored Markdown.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64090 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in device hostname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64090</link><description>This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to execute commands via the hostname of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64091 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in the NTP-configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64091</link><description>This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to execute commands via the NTP-configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13729 | Entry Views &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13729</link><description>The Entry Views plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'entry-views' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13853 | Nearby Now Reviews &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13853</link><description>The Nearby Now Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'data_tech' parameter of the nn-tech shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13895 | Top Position Google Finance &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13895</link><description>The Top Position Google Finance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13900 | WP Popup Magic &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;name&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13900</link><description>The WP Popup Magic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'name' parameter of the [wppum_end] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0627 | AMP for WP &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0627</link><description>The AMP for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.10. This is due to insufficient sanitization of SVG file content that only removes `</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69195 | Wget2: gnu wget2: memory corruption and crash via filename sanitization logic with attacker-controlled urls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69195</link><description>A flaw was found in GNU Wget2. This vulnerability, a stack-based buffer overflow, occurs in the filename sanitization logic when processing attacker-controlled URL paths, particularly when filename restriction options are active. A remote attacker can exploit this by providing a specially crafted URL, which, upon user interaction with wget2, can lead to memory corruption. This can cause the application to crash and potentially allow for further malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69194 | Wget2: arbitrary file write via metalink path traversal in gnu wget2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69194</link><description>A security issue was discovered in GNU Wget2 when handling Metalink documents. The application fails to properly validate file paths provided in Metalink  elements. An attacker can abuse this behavior to write files to unintended locations on the system. This can lead to data loss or potentially allow further compromise of the user’s environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13628 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Coupon Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13628</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and deletion of data due to a missing capability check on the 'bulk_action_handler' and 'coupon_permanent_delete' functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to delete, activate, deactivate, or trash arbitrary coupons.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13753 | WP Table Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.19 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Table Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13753</link><description>The WP Table Builder – Drag &amp; Drop Table Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an incorrect authorization check on the save_table() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new wptb-table posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13934 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Course Enrollment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13934</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized course enrollment in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.3. This is due to a missing capability check and purchasability validation in the `course_enrollment()` AJAX handler. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to enroll themselves in any course without going through the proper purchase flow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13935 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Course Completion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13935</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized course completion in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.2. This is due to missing enrollment verification in the 'mark_course_complete' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to mark any course as completed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14146 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.14.10 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14146</link><description>The Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 10.14.10 via the `WPBC_FLEXTIMELINE_NAV` AJAX action. This is due to the nonce verification being conditionally disabled by default (`booking_is_nonce_at_front_end` option is `'Off'` by default). When the `booking_is_show_popover_in_timeline_front_end` option is enabled (which is the default in demo installations and can be enabled by administrators), it is possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive booking data including customer names, email addresses, phone numbers, and booking details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14657 | Eventin – Event Manager, Event Booking, Calendar, Tickets and Registration Plugin (AI Powered) &amp;lt;= 4.0.51 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;post_settings&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14657</link><description>The Eventin – Event Manager, Events Calendar, Event Tickets and Registrations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'post_settings' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.51. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings. Furthermore, due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'etn_primary_color' setting, this enables unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that will execute whenever a user accesses a page where Eventin styles are loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14741 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.28.25 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Data Deletion via &amp;#x27;delete post&amp;#x27; Form Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14741</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to missing authorization to unauthorized data modification and deletion due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_object' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.28.25. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts, pages, products, taxonomy terms, and user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14937 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.28.23 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;update_field&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14937</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'acff' parameter in the 'frontend_admin/forms/update_field' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.28.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21409 | Improper authorization vulnerability exists in RICOH Streamline NX 3.5.1 to 24R3. If a man-in-the-middle attack is conducted on the communic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21409</link><description>Improper authorization vulnerability exists in RICOH Streamline NX 3.5.1 to 24R3. If a man-in-the-middle attack is conducted on the communication between the affected product and its user, and some crafted request is processed by the product, the user's registration information and/or OIDC (OpenID Connect) tokens may be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70974 | Fastjson before 1.2.48 mishandles autoType because, when an @type key is in a JSON document, and the value of that key is the name of a Java...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70974</link><description>Fastjson before 1.2.48 mishandles autoType because, when an @type key is in a JSON document, and the value of that key is the name of a Java class, there may be calls to certain public methods of that class. Depending on the behavior of those methods, there may be JNDI injection with an attacker-supplied payload located elsewhere in that JSON document. This was exploited in the wild in 2023 through 2025. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2017-18349. Also, a later bypass is covered by CVE-2022-25845.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14574 | weDocs: AI Powered Knowledge Base, Docs, Documentation, Wiki &amp;amp; AI Chatbot &amp;lt;= 2.1.15 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14574</link><description>The weDocs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.15 via the `/wp-json/wp/v2/docs/settings` REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including third party services API keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14718 | Schedule Post Changes With PublishPress Future: Unpublish, Delete, Change Status, Trash, Change Categories &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Workflow Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14718</link><description>The Schedule Post Changes With PublishPress Future plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to create, update, delete, and publish malicious workflows that may automatically delete any post upon publication or update, including posts created by administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14720 | Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia &amp;lt;= 1.2.38 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Multiple AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14720</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on multiple AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.38. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to mark payments as refunded, trigger sending of queued notifications (emails/SMS/WhatsApp), and access debug information among other things.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14736 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.28.25 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation to Administrator via Role Form Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14736</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.28.25. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied role values in the 'validate_value', 'pre_update_value', and 'get_fields_display' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as administrators and gain complete control of the site, granted they can access a user registration form containing a Role field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14782 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.49.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Forminator User+) CSV Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14782</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.49.1 via the 'listen_for_csv_export' function. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with access to the Forminator dashboard, to export sensitive form submission data including personally identifiable information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14893 | IndieWeb &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Telephone&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14893</link><description>The IndieWeb plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Telephone' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14980 | BetterDocs &amp;lt;= 4.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14980</link><description>The BetterDocs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.3 via the scripts() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the OpenAI API key stored in plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15019 | BIALTY - Bulk Image Alt Text (Alt tag, Alt Attribute) with Yoast SEO + WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15019</link><description>The BIALTY - Bulk Image Alt Text (Alt tag, Alt Attribute) with Yoast SEO + WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'bialty_cs_alt' post meta in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever an administrator accesses the post editor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15055 | SlimStat Analytics &amp;lt;= 5.3.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;notes/resource&amp;#x27; Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15055</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'notes' and 'resource' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever an administrator accesses the Recent Custom Events report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15057 | SlimStat Analytics &amp;lt;= 5.3.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;fh&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15057</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `fh` (fingerprint) parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the fingerprint value stored in the database. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever an administrator views the Real-time Access Log report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0563 | WP Google Street View (with 360° virtual tour) &amp;amp; Google maps + Local SEO &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;wpgsv_map&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0563</link><description>The WP Google Street View (with 360° virtual tour) &amp; Google maps + Local SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpgsv_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20968 | Use after free in DualDAR prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20968</link><description>Use after free in DualDAR prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20969 | Improper input validation in SecSettings prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attacker to access file with system privilege. User in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20969</link><description>Improper input validation in SecSettings prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attacker to access file with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20970 | Improper access control in SLocation prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute the privileged APIs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20970</link><description>Improper access control in SLocation prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute the privileged APIs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20971 | Use After Free in PROCA driver prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20971</link><description>Use After Free in PROCA driver prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20972 | Improper Export of Android Application Components in UwbTest prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable UWB.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20972</link><description>Improper Export of Android Application Components in UwbTest prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable UWB.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20973 | Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows remote attacker to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20973</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows remote attacker to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20974 | Improper input validation in data related to network restrictions prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass Carrie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20974</link><description>Improper input validation in data related to network restrictions prior to SMR Jan-2026 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass Carrier Relock.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20975 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in Samsung Cloud prior to version 5.6.11 allows local attackers to access specific files in arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20975</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in Samsung Cloud prior to version 5.6.11 allows local attackers to access specific files in arbitrary path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20976 | Improper input validation in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.6.02 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20976</link><description>Improper input validation in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.6.02 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14803 | Nex-Forms Express WP Form Builder &amp;lt; 9.1.8 - Authenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14803</link><description>The NEX-Forms  WordPress plugin before 9.1.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings. The NEX-Forms  WordPress plugin before 9.1.8 can be configured in such a way that could allow subscribers to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13749 | Clearfy &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Update Notification Tampering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13749</link><description>The Clearfy Cache – WordPress optimization plugin, Minify HTML, CSS &amp; JS, Defer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the "wbcr_upm_change_flag" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable plugin/theme update notifications via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 05:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14886 | Japanized for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.7.17 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Order Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14886</link><description>The Japanized for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the `order` REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.17. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to mark any WooCommerce order as processed/completed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66315 | ZTE MF258K Pro Version Server has a Configuration Defect Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66315</link><description>There is a configuration defect vulnerability in the version server of ZTE MF258K Pro products. Due to improper directory permission settings, an attacker can execute write permissions in a specific directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 03:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22712 | ApprovedRevs allows bypassing the inline CSS sanitizer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22712</link><description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output due to magic word replacement in ParserAfterTidy vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - ApprovedRevs Extension allows Input Data Manipulation.This issue affects Mediawiki - ApprovedRevs Extension: 1.45, 1.44, 1.43, 1.39.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22713 | Stored XSS through edit summaries in GrowthExperiments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22713</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: 1.45, 1.44, 1.43, 1.39.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>