<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-32853 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.2 contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability. A local low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32853</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.2 contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32854 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privilege attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32854</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privilege attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32852 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.0 contain use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unprivileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32852</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.0 contain use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unprivileged network malicious attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to data leaks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5219 | Easy Google Maps &amp;lt;= 1.11.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5219</link><description>The Easy Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6172 | Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.7.25 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via unsubscribe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6172</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the db parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.25 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0158 | Dell BIOS contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges may potentially ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0158</link><description>Dell BIOS contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify a UEFI variable, leading to denial of service and escalation of privileges</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3999 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3999</link><description>The EazyDocs  WordPress plugin before 2.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4627 | Rank Math SEO &amp;lt; 1.0.219 - Authenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4627</link><description>The Rank Math SEO  WordPress plugin before 1.0.219 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow users with access to the General Settings (by default admin, however such access can be given to lower roles via the Role Manager feature of the Rank Math SEO  WordPress plugin before 1.0.219) to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5606 | Quiz And Survey Master &amp;lt; 9.0.2 - Contributor+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5606</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.0.2 is vulnerable does not validate and escape the question_id parameter in the qsm_bulk_delete_question_from_database AJAX action, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by Contributors and above role</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5767 | Sitetweet &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5767</link><description>The sitetweet WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1427 | The Post Grid &amp;lt;= 7.7.1 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via section title tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1427</link><description>The The Post Grid – Shortcode, Gutenberg Blocks and Elementor Addon for Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the section title tag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5349 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5349</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8.1 via the 'map_style' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5419 | Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cf7_redirect_page Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5419</link><description>The Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cf7_redirect_page' attribute within the plugin's Void Contact From 7 widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2819 | File Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2819</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions, Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Common Services: before 11.0.2-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5938 | Boot Store &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5938</link><description>The Boot Store theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4679 | Folder Permission Vulnerability in JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4679</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent for Windows, Hitachi JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent on Windows, Hitachi Job Management Partner1/Extensible SNMP Agent on Windows allows File Manipulation.This issue affects JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent for Windows: from 12-00 before 12-00-01, from 11-00 through 11-00-*; JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent: from 10-10 through 10-10-01, from 10-00 through 10-00-02, from 09-00 through 09-00-04; Job Management Partner1/Extensible SNMP Agent: from 10-10 through 10-10-01, from 10-00 through 10-00-02, from 09-00 through 09-00-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37764 | MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated stored cross-site scripting.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37764</link><description>MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated stored cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37762 | MachForm up to version 21 is affected by an authenticated unrestricted file upload which leads to a remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37762</link><description>MachForm up to version 21 is affected by an authenticated unrestricted file upload which leads to a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37763 | MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an unauthenticated stored cross-site scripting which affects users with valid sessions whom can vie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37763</link><description>MachForm up to version 19 is affected by an unauthenticated stored cross-site scripting which affects users with valid sessions whom can view compiled forms results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39314 | toy-blog administrative token leaked through the command line parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39314</link><description>toy-blog is a headless content management system implementation. Starting in version 0.4.3 and prior to version 0.5.0, the administrative password was leaked through the command line parameter. The problem was patched in version 0.5.0. As a workaround, pass `--read-bearer-token-from-stdin` to the launch arguments and feed the token from the standard input in version 0.4.14 or later. Earlier versions do not have this workaround.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23737 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Jira allows attackers to allows attackers to manipula...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23737</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Jira allows attackers to allows attackers to manipulate a user's S/MIME certificate of PGP key via malicious link or email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37765 | Machform up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated Blind SQL injection in the user account settings page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37765</link><description>Machform up to version 19 is affected by an authenticated Blind SQL injection in the user account settings page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39313 | toy-blog Improper Input Validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39313</link><description>toy-blog is a headless content management system implementation. Starting in version 0.5.4 and prior to version 0.6.1, articles with private visibility can be read if the reader does not set credentials for the request. Users should upgrade to 0.6.1 or later to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23736 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Confluence allows attackers to manipulate a user's S/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23736</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in savignano S/Notify before 4.0.2 for Confluence allows attackers to manipulate a user's S/MIME certificate of PGP key via malicious link or email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39309 | ZDI-CAN-23894: Parse Server literalizeRegexPart SQL Injection Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39309</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. A vulnerability in versions prior to 6.5.7 and 7.1.0 allows SQL injection when Parse Server is configured to use the PostgreSQL database. The algorithm to detect SQL injection has been improved in versions 6.5.7 and 7.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39310 | WordPress Basil Theme Authenticated (Contributor+) Persistent Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39310</link><description>The Basil recipe theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the `post_title` parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers with contributor-level access and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses a compromised page. Because the of the default WordPress validation, it is not possible to insert the payload directly but if the Cooked plugin is installed, it is possible to create a recipe post type (cp_recipe) and inject the payload in the title field. Version 2.0.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38368 | Trunk&amp;#x27;s &amp;#x27;Claim your pod&amp;#x27; could be used to obtain un-used pods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38368</link><description>trunk.cocoapods.org is the authentication server for the CoacoaPods dependency manager. A vulnerability affected older pods which migrated from the pre-2014 pull request workflow to trunk. If the pods had never been claimed then it was still possible to do so. It was also possible to have all owners removed from a pod, and that made the pod available for the same claiming system. This was patched server-side in commit 71be5440906b6bdfbc0bcc7f8a9fec33367ea0f4 in September 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39305 | Envoy Proxy use after free when route hash policy is configured with cookie attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39305</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Prior to versions 1.30.4, 1.29.7, 1.28.5, and 1.27.7. Envoy references already freed memory when route hash policy is configured with cookie attributes. Note that this vulnerability has been fixed in the open as the effect would be immediately apparent if it was configured. Memory allocated for holding attribute values is freed after configuration was parsed. During request processing Envoy will attempt to copy content of de-allocated memory into request cookie header. This can lead to arbitrary content of Envoy's memory to be sent to the upstream service or abnormal process termination. This vulnerability is fixed in Envoy versions v1.30.4, v1.29.7, v1.28.5, and v1.27.7. As a workaround, do not use cookie attributes in route action hash policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28200 | N-central Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28200</link><description>The N-central server is vulnerable to an authentication bypass of the user interface. This vulnerability is present in all deployments of N-central prior to 2024.2.

This vulnerability was discovered through internal N-central source code review and N-able has not observed any exploitation in the wild.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38367 | CoacoaPods trunk sessions verification step could be manipulated for owner session hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38367</link><description>trunk.cocoapods.org is the authentication server for the CoacoaPods dependency manager. Prior to commit d4fa66f49cedab449af9a56a21ab40697b9f7b97, the trunk sessions verification step could be manipulated for owner session hijacking Compromising a victim’s session will result in a full takeover of the CocoaPods trunk account. The threat actor could manipulate their pod specifications, disrupt the distribution of legitimate libraries, or cause widespread disruption within the CocoaPods ecosystem. This was patched server-side with commit d4fa66f49cedab449af9a56a21ab40697b9f7b97 in October 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5322 | N-central Authentication Bypass via Session Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5322</link><description>The N-central server is vulnerable to session rebinding of already authenticated users when using Entra SSO, which can lead to authentication bypass.
 
This vulnerability is present in all Entra-supported deployments of N-central prior to 2024.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38366 | CoacoaPods trunk RCE in email verification system rfc-822</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38366</link><description>trunk.cocoapods.org is the authentication server for the CoacoaPods dependency manager. The part of trunk which verifies whether a user has a real email address on signup used a rfc-822 library which executes a shell command to validate the email domain MX records validity. It works via an DNS MX. This lookup could be manipulated to also execute a command on the trunk server, effectively giving root access to the server and the infrastructure. This issue was patched server-side with commit 001cc3a430e75a16307f5fd6cdff1363ad2f40f3 in September 2023. This RCE triggered a full user-session reset, as an attacker could have used this method to write to any Podspec in trunk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32228 | FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a SEGV at libavcodec/hevcdec.c:2947:22 in hevc_frame_end.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32228</link><description>FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a SEGV at libavcodec/hevcdec.c:2947:22 in hevc_frame_end.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32229 | FFmpeg 7.0 contains a heap-buffer-overflow at libavfilter/vf_tiltandshift.c:189:5 in copy_column.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32229</link><description>FFmpeg 7.0 contains a heap-buffer-overflow at libavfilter/vf_tiltandshift.c:189:5 in copy_column.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32230 | FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a negative-size-param bug at libavcodec/mpegvideo_enc.c:1216:21 in load_input_picture ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32230</link><description>FFmpeg 7.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is a negative-size-param bug at libavcodec/mpegvideo_enc.c:1216:21 in load_input_picture in FFmpeg7.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39249 | Async &lt;= 2.6.4 and &lt;= 3.2.5 are vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) while parsing function in autoinject function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39249</link><description>Async &lt;= 2.6.4 and &lt;= 3.2.5 are vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) while parsing function in autoinject function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39236 | Gradio v4.36.1 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the component /gradio/component_meta.py. This vulnerability is t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39236</link><description>Gradio v4.36.1 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the component /gradio/component_meta.py. This vulnerability is triggered via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39303 | Weblate vulnerabler to improper sanitization of project backups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39303</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. Prior to version 5.6.2, Weblate didn't correctly validate filenames when restoring project backup. It may be possible to gain unauthorized access to files on the server using a crafted ZIP file. This issue has been addressed in Weblate 5.6.2. As a workaround, do not allow untrusted users to create projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38513 | Fiber Session Middleware Token Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38513</link><description>Fiber is an Express-inspired web framework written in Go A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.52.5 is a session middleware issue in GoFiber versions 2 and above. This vulnerability allows users to supply their own session_id value, resulting in the creation of a session with that key. If a website relies on the mere presence of a session for security purposes, this can lead to significant security risks, including unauthorized access and session fixation attacks. All users utilizing GoFiber's session middleware in the affected versions are impacted. The issue has been addressed in version 2.52.5. Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade to version 2.52.5 or higher to mitigate this vulnerability. Users who are unable to upgrade immediately can apply the following workarounds to reduce the risk: Either implement additional validation to ensure session IDs are not supplied by the user and are securely generated by the server, or regularly rotate session IDs and enforce strict session expiration policies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37145 | GHSL-2023-247: Flowise xss in /api/v1/chatflows-streaming/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37145</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `/api/v1/chatflows-streaming/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37146 | GHSL-2023-248: Flowise xss in /api/v1/credentials/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37146</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `/api/v1/credentials/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37298 | Potential memory exhaustion attack due to sparse slice deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37298</link><description>gorilla/schema converts structs to and from form values. Prior to version 1.4.1 Running `schema.Decoder.Decode()` on a struct that has a field of type `[]struct{...}` opens it up to malicious attacks regarding memory allocations, taking advantage of the sparse slice functionality. Any use of `schema.Decoder.Decode()` on a struct with arrays of other structs could be vulnerable to this memory exhaustion vulnerability. Version 1.4.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39251 | An issue in the component ControlCenter.sys/ControlCenter64.sys of ThundeRobot Control Center v2.0.0.10 allows attackers to access sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39251</link><description>An issue in the component ControlCenter.sys/ControlCenter64.sys of ThundeRobot Control Center v2.0.0.10 allows attackers to access sensitive information, execute arbitrary code, or escalate privileges via sending crafted IOCTL requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36387 | Apache HTTP Server: DoS by Null pointer in websocket over HTTP/2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36387</link><description>Serving WebSocket protocol upgrades over a HTTP/2 connection could result in a Null Pointer dereference, leading to a crash of the server process, degrading performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36423 | GHSL-2023-246: Flowise xss in /api/v1/public-chatflows/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36423</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `/api/v1/public-chatflows/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38472 | Apache HTTP Server on WIndows UNC SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38472</link><description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests or content 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60 which fixes this issue.  Note: Existing configurations that access UNC paths will have to configure new directive "UNCList" to allow access during request processing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38473 | Apache HTTP Server proxy encoding problem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38473</link><description>Encoding problem in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows request URLs with incorrect encoding to be sent to backend services, potentially bypassing authentication via crafted requests.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38474 | Apache HTTP Server weakness with encoded question marks in backreferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38474</link><description>Substitution encoding issue in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows attacker to execute scripts in
directories permitted by the configuration but not directly reachable by any URL or source disclosure of scripts meant to only to be executed as CGI.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.

Some RewriteRules that capture and substitute unsafely will now fail unless rewrite flag "UnsafeAllow3F" is specified.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38475 | Apache HTTP Server weakness in mod_rewrite when first segment of substitution matches filesystem path.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38475</link><description>Improper escaping of output in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to map URLs to filesystem locations that are permitted to be served by the server but are not intentionally/directly reachable by any URL, resulting in code execution or source code disclosure. 

Substitutions in server context that use a backreferences or variables as the first segment of the substitution are affected.  Some unsafe RewiteRules will be broken by this change and the rewrite flag "UnsafePrefixStat" can be used to opt back in once ensuring the substitution is appropriately constrained.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38476 | Apache HTTP Server may use exploitable/malicious backend application output to run local handlers via internal redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38476</link><description>Vulnerability in core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier are vulnerably to information disclosure, SSRF or local script execution via backend applications whose response headers are malicious or exploitable.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38477 | Apache HTTP Server: Crash resulting in Denial of Service in mod_proxy via a malicious request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38477</link><description>null pointer dereference in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to crash the server via a malicious request.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39573 | Apache HTTP Server: mod_rewrite proxy handler substitution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39573</link><description>Potential SSRF in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to cause unsafe RewriteRules to unexpectedly setup URL's to be handled by mod_proxy.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39878 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 private key could be exposed via testing GitHub App Connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39878</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 private key could be exposed via testing GitHub App Connection</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39879 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 application token could be exposed in EC2 Cloud Profile settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39879</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.3 application token could be exposed in EC2 Cloud Profile settings</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36997 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in conf-web/settings REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36997</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312, an admin user could store and execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the browser context of another Splunk user through the conf-web/settings REST endpoint. This could potentially cause a persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) exploit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36993 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Web Bulletin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36993</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the admin or power Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through a Splunk Web Bulletin Messages that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36995 | Low-privileged user could create experimental items</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36995</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the admin or power Splunk roles could create experimental items.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 17:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21586 | Junos OS: SRX Series: Specific valid traffic leads to a PFE crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21586</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

If an SRX Series device receives specific valid traffic destined to the device, it will cause the PFE to crash and restart.  Continued receipt and processing of this traffic will create a sustained DoS condition.

This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series:

  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S7.9,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S5.3,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S4.11,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3.




Junos OS versions prior to 21.4R1 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36982 | Denial of Service through null pointer reference in “cluster/config” REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36982</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.109 and 9.1.2308.207, an attacker could trigger a null pointer reference on the “cluster/config” REST endpoint, which could result in a crash of the Splunk daemon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36983 | Command Injection using External Lookups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36983</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.109 and 9.1.2308.207, an authenticated user could create an external lookup that calls a legacy internal function. The authenticated user could use this internal function to insert code into the Splunk platform installation directory. From there, the user could execute arbitrary code on the Splunk platform Instance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36984 | Remote Code Execution through Serialized Session Payload in Splunk Enterprise on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36984</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 on Windows, an authenticated user could execute a specially crafted query that they could then use to serialize untrusted data. The attacker could use the query to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36985 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) through an external lookup due to “copybuckets.py“ script in the “splunk_archiver“ application in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36985</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin“ or “power“ Splunk roles could cause a Remote Code Execution through an external lookup that references the “splunk_archiver“ application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36986 | Risky command safeguards bypass through Search ID query in Analytics Workspace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36986</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, an authenticated user could run risky commands using the permissions of a higher-privileged user to bypass [SPL safeguards for risky commands](https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/SplunkCloud/latest/Security/SPLsafeguards) in the Analytics Workspace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The vulnerability requires the authenticated user to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser. The authenticated user should not be able to exploit the vulnerability at will.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36987 | Insecure File Upload in the indexing/preview REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36987</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200, an authenticated, low-privileged user who does not hold the admin or power Splunk roles could upload a file with an arbitrary extension using the indexing/preview REST endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36989 | Low-privileged user could create notifications in Splunk Web Bulletin Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36989</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could create notifications in Splunk Web Bulletin Messages that all users on the instance receive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36990 | Denial of Service (DoS) on the datamodel/web REST endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36990</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.100, an authenticated, low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could send a specially crafted HTTP POST request to the datamodel/web REST endpoint in Splunk Enterprise, potentially causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36991 | Path Traversal on the “/modules/messaging/“ endpoint in Splunk Enterprise on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36991</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise on Windows versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10, an attacker could perform a path traversal on the “/modules/messaging/“ endpoint in Splunk Enterprise on Windows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This vulnerability should only affect Splunk Enterprise on Windows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36992 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Dashboard Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36992</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through a View that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.&lt;br /&gt;The “url” parameter of the Dashboard element does not have proper input validation to reject invalid URLs, which could lead to a Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) exploit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36994 | Persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Dashboard Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36994</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.200 and 9.1.2308.207, a low-privileged user that does not hold the “admin” or “power” Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through a View and Splunk Web Bulletin Messages that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36996 | Information Disclosure of user names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36996</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.2, 9.1.5, and 9.0.10 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.1.2312.109, an attacker could determine whether or not another user exists on the instance by deciphering the error response that they would likely receive from the instance when they attempt to log in. This disclosure could then lead to additional brute-force password-guessing attacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This vulnerability would require that the Splunk platform instance uses the Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication scheme.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20399 | A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36421 | GHSL-2023-234: Flowise Cors Misconfiguration in packages/server/src/index.ts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36421</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, A CORS misconfiguration sets the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header to all, allowing arbitrary origins to connect to the website. In the default configuration (unauthenticated), arbitrary origins may be able to make requests to Flowise, stealing information from the user. This CORS misconfiguration may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker attackers without access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36422 | GHSL-2023-245: Flowise xss in api/v1/chatflows/id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36422</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs in the `api/v1/chatflows/id` endpoint. If the default configuration is used (unauthenticated), an attacker may be able to craft a specially crafted URL that injects Javascript into the user sessions, allowing the attacker to steal information, create false popups, or even redirect the user to other websites without interaction. If the chatflow ID is not found, its value is reflected in the 404 page, which has type text/html. This allows an attacker to attach arbitrary scripts to the page, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information. This XSS may be chained with the path injection to allow an attacker without direct access to Flowise to read arbitrary files from the Flowise server. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36420 | GHSL-2023-232: Flowise Path Injection at /api/v1/openai-assistants-file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36420</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 1.4.3 of Flowise, the `/api/v1/openai-assistants-file` endpoint in `index.ts` is vulnerable to arbitrary file read due to lack of sanitization of the `fileName` body parameter. No known patches for this issue are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36401 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in evaluating property name expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36401</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Prior to versions 2.23.6, 2.24.4, and 2.25.2, multiple OGC request parameters allow Remote Code Execution (RCE) by unauthenticated users through specially crafted input against a default GeoServer installation due to unsafely evaluating property names as XPath expressions.

The GeoTools library API that GeoServer calls evaluates property/attribute names for feature types in a way that unsafely passes them to the commons-jxpath library which can execute arbitrary code when evaluating XPath expressions. This XPath evaluation is intended to be used only by complex feature types (i.e., Application Schema data stores) but is incorrectly being applied to simple feature types as well which makes this vulnerability apply to **ALL** GeoServer instances. No public PoC is provided but this vulnerability has been confirmed to be exploitable through WFS GetFeature, WFS GetPropertyValue, WMS GetMap, WMS GetFeatureInfo, WMS GetLegendGraphic and WPS Execute requests. This vulnerability can lead to executing arbitrary code.

Versions 2.23.6, 2.24.4, and 2.25.2 contain a patch for the issue. A workaround exists by removing the `gt-complex-x.y.jar` file from the GeoServer where `x.y` is the GeoTools version (e.g., `gt-complex-31.1.jar` if running GeoServer 2.25.1). This will remove the vulnerable code from GeoServer but may break some GeoServer functionality or prevent GeoServer from deploying if the gt-complex module is needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6376 | ejson shell parser in MongoDB Compass maybe bypassed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6376</link><description>MongoDB Compass may be susceptible to code injection due to insufficient sandbox protection settings with the usage of ejson shell parser in Compass' connection handling. This issue affects MongoDB Compass versions prior to version 1.42.2</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6375 | Missing authorization check may lead to shard key refinement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6375</link><description>A command for refining a collection shard key is missing an authorization check. This may cause the command to run directly on a shard, leading to either degradation of query performance, or to revealing chunk boundaries through timing side channels. This affects MongoDB Server v5.0 versions, prior to 5.0.22, MongoDB Server v6.0 versions, prior to 6.0.11 and MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34696 |  GeoServer&amp;#x27;s Server Status shows sensitive environmental variables and Java properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34696</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Starting in version 2.10.0 and prior to versions 2.24.4 and 2.25.1, GeoServer's Server Status page and REST API lists all environment variables and Java properties to any GeoServer user with administrative rights as part of those modules' status message. These variables/properties can also contain sensitive information, such as database passwords or API keys/tokens. Additionally, many community-developed GeoServer container images `export` other credentials from their start-up scripts as environment variables to the GeoServer (`java`) process. The precise scope of the issue depends on which container image is used and how it is configured.

The `about status` API endpoint which powers the Server Status page is only available to administrators.Depending on the operating environment, administrators might have legitimate access to credentials in other ways, but this issue defeats more sophisticated controls (like break-glass access to secrets or role accounts).By default, GeoServer only allows same-origin authenticated API access. This limits the scope for a third-party attacker to use an administrator’s credentials to gain access to credentials. The researchers who found the vulnerability were unable to determine any other conditions under which the GeoServer REST API may be available more broadly.

Users should update container images to use GeoServer 2.24.4 or 2.25.1 to get the bug fix. As a workaround, leave environment variables and Java system properties hidden by default. Those who provide the option to re-enable it should communicate the impact and risks so that users can make an informed choice.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43554 | Improper Restriction of Operations withing the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43554</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL handler in FastRPC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21456 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21456</link><description>Information Disclosure while parsing beacon frame in STA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21457 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21457</link><description>INformation disclosure while handling Multi-link IE in beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21458 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21458</link><description>Information disclosure while handling SA query action frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21460 | Use of Insufficiently Random Values in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21460</link><description>Information disclosure when ASLR relocates the IMEM and Secure DDR portions as one chunk in virtual address space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21461 | Double Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21461</link><description>Memory corruption while performing finish HMAC operation when context is freed by keymaster.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21462 | Buffer Over-read in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21462</link><description>Transient DOS while loading the TA ELF file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21465 | Buffer Over-read in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21465</link><description>Memory corruption while processing key blob passed by the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21466 | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21466</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing sub-IE length during new IE generation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21469 | Permissions, Privileges, and Access Control issues in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21469</link><description>Memory corruption when an invoke call and a TEE call are bound for the same trusted application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21482 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Linux Boot Loader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21482</link><description>Memory corruption during the secure boot process, when the `bootm` command is used, it bypasses the authentication of the kernel/rootfs image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23368 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Qualcomm IPC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23368</link><description>Memory corruption when allocating and accessing an entry in an SMEM partition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23372 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23372</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL call for GPU memory allocation and size param is greater than expected size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23373 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23373</link><description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap operation fails, the DMA and anon buffers are getting released.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23380 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23380</link><description>Memory corruption while handling user packets during VBO bind operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24749 | Classpath resource disclosure in GWC Web Resource API on Windows / Tomcat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24749</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Prior to versions 2.23.5 and 2.24.3, if GeoServer is deployed in the Windows operating system using an Apache Tomcat web application server, it is possible to bypass existing input validation in the GeoWebCache ByteStreamController class and read arbitrary classpath resources with specific file name extensions. If GeoServer is also deployed as a web archive using the data directory embedded in the `geoserver.war` file (rather than an external data directory), it will likely be possible to read specific resources to gain administrator privileges. However, it is very unlikely that production environments will be using the embedded data directory since, depending on how GeoServer is deployed, it will be erased and re-installed (which would also reset to the default password) either every time the server restarts or every time a new GeoServer WAR is installed and is therefore difficult to maintain. An external data directory will always be used if GeoServer is running in standalone mode (via an installer or a binary). Versions 2.23.5 and 2.24.3 contain a patch for the issue. Some workarounds are available. One may change from a Windows environment to a Linux environment; or change from Apache Tomcat to Jetty application server. One may also disable anonymous access to the embeded GeoWebCache administration and status pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6050 | Reflected XSS in SOWA OPAC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6050</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability in SOKRATES-software SOWA OPAC allows a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker might trick somebody into using a crafted URL, which will cause a script to be run in user's browser. This issue affects SOWA OPAC software in versions from 4.0 before 4.9.10, from 5.0 before 6.2.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38953 | phpok 6.4.003 contains a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ok_f() method under the framework/api/upload_control.php file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38953</link><description>phpok 6.4.003 contains a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ok_f() method under the framework/api/upload_control.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38987 | aofl cli-lib v3.14.0 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component defaultsDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38987</link><description>aofl cli-lib v3.14.0 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component defaultsDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38990 | Tada5hi sp-common v0.5.4 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38990</link><description>Tada5hi sp-common v0.5.4 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38991 | akbr patch-into v1.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function patchInto. This vulnerability allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38991</link><description>akbr patch-into v1.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function patchInto. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38992 | airvertco frappejs v0.0.11 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function registerView. This vulnerability allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38992</link><description>airvertco frappejs v0.0.11 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function registerView. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38993 | rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function empty. This vulnerability allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38993</link><description>rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function empty. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38994 | amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38994</link><description>amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38996 | ag-grid-community v31.3.2 and ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 were discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the _.mergeDeep function. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38996</link><description>ag-grid-community v31.3.2 and ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 were discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the _.mergeDeep function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38997 | adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extendDefaults. This vulnerability allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38997</link><description>adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extendDefaults. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38998 | jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function config. This vulnerability allows attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38998</link><description>jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function config. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38999 | jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function s.contexts._.configure. This vulnerability allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38999</link><description>jrburke requirejs v2.3.6 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function s.contexts._.configure. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39000 | adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39000</link><description>adolph_dudu ratio-swiper v0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39001 | ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component _ModuleSupport.jsonApply. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39001</link><description>ag-grid-enterprise v31.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component _ModuleSupport.jsonApply. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39002 | rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function util.clone. This vulnerability allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39002</link><description>rjrodger jsonic-next v2.12.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function util.clone. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39003 | amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function setValue. This vulnerability allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39003</link><description>amoyjs amoy common v1.0.10 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function setValue. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39008 | robinweser fast-loops v1.1.3 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function objectMergeDeep. This vulnerability allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39008</link><description>robinweser fast-loops v1.1.3 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function objectMergeDeep. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39013 | 2o3t-utility v0.1.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39013</link><description>2o3t-utility v0.1.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function extend. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39014 | ahilfoley cahil/utils v2.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function set. This vulnerability allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39014</link><description>ahilfoley cahil/utils v2.3.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function set. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39015 | cafebazaar hod v0.4.14 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function request. This vulnerability allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39015</link><description>cafebazaar hod v0.4.14 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function request. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39016 | che3vinci c3/utils-1 1.0.131 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function assign. This vulnerability allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39016</link><description>che3vinci c3/utils-1 1.0.131 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function assign. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39017 | agreejs shared v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeInternalComponents. This vulnerability allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39017</link><description>agreejs shared v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeInternalComponents. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39018 | harvey-woo cat5th/key-serializer v0.2.5 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function "query". This vulnerability allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39018</link><description>harvey-woo cat5th/key-serializer v0.2.5 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function "query". This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39853 | adolph_dudu ratio-swiper 0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39853</link><description>adolph_dudu ratio-swiper 0.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function parse. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6424 | Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6424</link><description>External server-side request vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version, which could allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to exploit the endpoint "/api/Proxy/Post?userName=&amp;amp;password=&amp;amp;uri=&lt;ARCHIVO|URL INTERNA|IP/HOST" to read the source code of web files, read internal files or access network resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6425 | Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6425</link><description>Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version. An unauthenticated remote attacker can register user accounts without being authenticated from the route "/account/Register/" and in the parameters "UserName=&amp;amp;Password=&amp;amp;ConfirmPassword=".</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6387 | Openssh: possible remote code execution due to a race condition in signal handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6387</link><description>A signal handler race condition was found in OpenSSH's server (sshd), where a client does not authenticate within LoginGraceTime seconds (120 by default, 600 in old OpenSSH versions), then sshd's SIGALRM handler is called asynchronously. However, this signal handler calls various functions that are not async-signal-safe, for example, syslog().</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4007 | Hard coded default credential contained in install package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4007</link><description>Default credential in install package in ABB ASPECT; NEXUS Series; MATRIX Series version 3.07 allows attacker to login to product instances wrongly configured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0153 | Mali GPU Firmware allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0153</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Firmware, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Firmware allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU processing operations to access a limited amount outside of buffer bounds. If the operations are carefully prepared, then this in turn could give them access to all system memory. This issue affects Valhall GPU Firmware: from r29p0 through r46p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Firmware: from r41p0 through r46p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39427 | In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39427</link><description>In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39428 | In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39428</link><description>In trusty service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39429 | In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39429</link><description>In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39430 | In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39430</link><description>In faceid servive, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4934 | Quiz And Survey Master &amp;lt; 9.0.2 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4934</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.0.2 does not validate and escape some of its Quiz fields before outputting them back in a page/post where the Quiz is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6130 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.26 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6130</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.26 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20076 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20076</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01297806; Issue ID: MSV-1481.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20077 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20077</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01297807; Issue ID: MSV-1482.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20078 | In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20078</link><description>In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08737250; Issue ID: MSV-1452.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20079 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20079</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08044040; Issue ID: MSV-1491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20080 | In gnss service, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to improper certificate validation. This could lead to remote escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20080</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to improper certificate validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08720039; Issue ID: MSV-1424.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20081 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20081</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08719602; Issue ID: MSV-1412.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3123 | CHANGING Mobile One Time Password - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3123</link><description>CHANGING Mobile One Time Password's uploading function in a hidden page does not filter file type properly. Remote attackers with  administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload and run malicious file to execute system commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3122 | CHANGING Mobile One Time Password - Arbitrary File Reading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3122</link><description>CHANGING Mobile One Time Password does not properly filter parameters for the file download functionality, allowing remote attackers with administrator privilege to read arbitrary file on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38480 | "Piccoma" App for Android and iOS versions prior to 6.20.0 uses a hard-coded API key for an external service, which may allow a local attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38480</link><description>"Piccoma" App for Android and iOS versions prior to 6.20.0 uses a hard-coded API key for an external service, which may allow a local attacker to obtain the API key. Note that the users of the app are not directly affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6419 | SourceCodester Medicine Tracker System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6419</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Medicine Tracker System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_medicine. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270010 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6418 | SourceCodester Medicine Tracker System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6418</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Medicine Tracker System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Users.php?f=register_user. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270009 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 23:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6417 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6417</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_user. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270008.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6416 | SeaCMS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6416</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SeaCMS 12.9. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /js/player/dmplayer/dmku/?ac=edit. The manipulation of the argument cid with the input (select(0)from(select(sleep(10)))v) leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270007.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 22:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34703 | Botan Vulnerable to Denial of Service Due to Overly Large Elliptic Curve Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34703</link><description>Botan is a C++ cryptography library. X.509 certificates can identify elliptic curves using either an object identifier or using explicit encoding of the parameters. Prior to versions 3.3.0 and 2.19.4, an attacker could present an ECDSA X.509 certificate using explicit encoding where the parameters are very large. The proof of concept used a 16Kbit prime for this purpose. When parsing, the parameter is checked to be prime, causing excessive computation. This was patched in 2.19.4 and 3.3.0 to allow the prime parameter of the elliptic curve to be at most 521 bits. No known workarounds are available. Note that support for explicit encoding of elliptic curve parameters is deprecated in Botan.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 20:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50964 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50964</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  276102.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28794 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28794</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  286831.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50952 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50952</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.  IBM X-Force ID:  275774.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50953 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50953</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275775.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28797 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28797</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable stored to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  287136.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31898 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server data modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31898</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow an authenticated user to read or modify sensitive information by bypassing authentication using insecure direct object references.   IBM X-Force ID:  288182.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50954 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50954</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 returns sensitive information in URL information that could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275776.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31902 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31902</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.   IBM X-Force ID:  289234.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35119 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35119</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in a stack trace.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  290342.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28798 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28798</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  287172.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35022 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35022</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a local user to update projects that they do not have the authorization to access.  IBM X-Force ID:  258254.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28795 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28795</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  286832.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5062 | Reflected XSS through survey redirect parameter in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5062</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in zenml-io/zenml version 0.57.1. The vulnerability exists due to improper neutralization of input during web page generation, specifically within the survey redirect parameter. This flaw allows an attacker to redirect users to a specified URL after completing a survey, without proper validation of the 'redirect' parameter. Consequently, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the user's browser session. This vulnerability could be exploited to steal cookies, potentially leading to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6415 | Ingenico Estate Manager New Widget cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6415</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /emgui/rest/preferences/PREF_HOME_PAGE/sponsor/3/ of the component New Widget Handler. The manipulation of the argument URL leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270001 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 04:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6414 | Parsec Automation TrakSYS Export Page contentpage direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6414</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Parsec Automation TrakSYS 11.x.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file TS/export/contentpage of the component Export Page. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270000. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5926 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;\..\filename&amp;#x27; in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5926</link><description>Path Traversal: '\..\filename' in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 01:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>