<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6823 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.18 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via mla-inline-edit-upload-scripts AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6823</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation involving the mla-inline-edit-upload-scripts AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.18. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7247 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Gallery and Countdown Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7247</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Custom Gallery and Countdown widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39591 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Document Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39591</link><description>SAP Document Builder does not perform necessary authorization checks for one of the function modules resulting in escalation of privileges causing low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42373 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42373</link><description>SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM) fails to conduct proper authorization checks for authenticated users, leading to the potential escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation it could allow an attacker to delete non-sensitive report variants that are typically restricted, causing minimal impact on the integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7092 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 5.9.27 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via no_more_items_text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7092</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘no_more_items_text’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41734 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41734</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform, an authenticated attacker could call an underlying transaction, which leads to disclosure of user related information. There is no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28166 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28166</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
  Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
  network, that could be executed by the application. On successful
  exploitation, the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the
  application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41731 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41731</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
network, that could be executed by the application. On successful exploitation,
the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41736 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Permit to Work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41736</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP Permit to Work
allows an authenticated attacker to access information which would otherwise be
restricted causing low impact on the confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42375 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42375</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
  Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
  network, that could be executed by the application. On successful exploitation,
  the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41732 | Improper Access Control in SAP Netweaver Application Server ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41732</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP allows
  an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link that could bypass allowlist
  controls. Depending on the web applications provided by this server, the
  attacker might inject CSS code or links into the web application that could
  allow the attacker to read or modify information. There is no impact on
  availability of application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41737 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in SAP CRM ABAP (Insights Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41737</link><description>SAP CRM ABAP (Insights
Management) allows an authenticated attacker to enumerate HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33005 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP and Java),SAP Web Dispatcher and SAP Content Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33005</link><description>Due to the missing authorization checks in the
local systems, the admin users of SAP Web Dispatcher, SAP NetWeaver Application
Server (ABAP and Java), and SAP Content Server can impersonate other users and
may perform some unintended actions. This could lead to a low impact on
confidentiality and a high impact on the integrity and availability of the
applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41733 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41733</link><description>In SAP Commerce, valid user accounts can be
identified during the customer registration and login processes. This allows a
potential attacker to learn if a given e-mail is used for an account, but does
not grant access to any customer data beyond this knowledge. The attacker must
already know the e-mail that they wish to test for. The impact on
confidentiality therefore is low and no impact to integrity or availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41735 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Commerce Backoffice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41735</link><description>SAP Commerce Backoffice does not sufficiently
encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)
vulnerability causing low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42377 | Multiple Missing Authorization Check vulnerabilities in SAP Shared Service Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42377</link><description>SAP shared service framework allows an
authenticated non-administrative user to call a remote-enabled function, which
will allow them to insert value entries into a non-sensitive table, causing low
impact on integrity of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33003 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Commerce Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33003</link><description>Some OCC API endpoints in SAP Commerce Cloud
allows Personally Identifiable Information (PII) data, such as passwords, email
addresses, mobile numbers, coupon codes, and voucher codes, to be included in
the request URL as query or path parameters. On successful exploitation, this
could lead to a High impact on confidentiality and integrity of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41730 | Missing Authentication check in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41730</link><description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
Platform, if Single Signed On is enabled on Enterprise authentication, an
unauthorized user can get a logon token using a REST endpoint. The attacker can
fully compromise the system resulting in High impact on confidentiality,
integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42374 | XML injection in SAP BEx Web Java Runtime Export Web Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42374</link><description>BEx Web Java Runtime Export Web Service does not
sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source. An
attacker can retrieve information from the SAP ADS system and exhaust the
number of XMLForm service which makes the SAP ADS rendering (PDF creation)
unavailable. This affects the confidentiality and availability of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42376 | Multiple Missing Authorization Check vulnerabilities in SAP Shared Service Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42376</link><description>SAP Shared Service Framework does not perform necessary
authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges. On successful exploitation, an attacker can cause a high impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7094 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Code Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7094</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection leading to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.6 via the 'storeTheme' function. This is due to a lack of sanitization on user-supplied values, which replace values in the style.php file, along with missing capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. This issue was partially patched in 2.8.6 when the code injection issue was resolved, and fully patched in 2.8.7 when the missing authorization and cross-site request forgery protection was added.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7388 | WP Bannerize Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7388</link><description>The WP Bannerize Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via banner alt data in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38382 | IBM Cloud Pak for Security session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38382</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security (CP4S) 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow another user to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  233672.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7709 | OcoMon URL require_access_recovery.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7709</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in OcoMon 4.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /includes/common/require_access_recovery.php of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.0.1 and 5.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7707 | Tenda FH1206 HTTP POST Request SafeEmailFilter formSafeEmailFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 02.03.01.35 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSafeEmailFilter of the file /goform/SafeEmailFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37924 | WordPress WP2Speed Faster – Optimize PageSpeed Insights Score 90-100 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37924</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Wp2speed WP2Speed Faster allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP2Speed Faster: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37930 | WordPress SmartMag theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37930</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeSphere SmartMag allows Excavation, Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects SmartMag: from n/a through 9.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35775 | WordPress Slider by Soliloquy plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35775</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting'), Improper Authentication vulnerability in Soliloquy Team Slider by Soliloquy allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Slider by Soliloquy: from n/a through 2.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43123 | WordPress Card Elements for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43123</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Techeshta Card Elements for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Card Elements for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43124 | WordPress Graphina plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Iqonic Design Graphina allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Graphina: from n/a through 1.8.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43125 | WordPress WP Table Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Table Builder WP Table Builder – WordPress Table Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Table Builder – WordPress Table Plugin: from n/a through 1.4.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43126 | WordPress Sender – Newsletter, SMS and Email Marketing Automation for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43126</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sender Sender – Newsletter, SMS and Email Marketing Automation for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Sender – Newsletter, SMS and Email Marketing Automation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.6.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43127 | WordPress  Products, Order &amp;amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43130 | WordPress Football Pool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43130</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Antoine Hurkmans Football Pool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Football Pool: from n/a through 2.11.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43133 | WordPress Themify Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themify Themify Shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themify Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43137 | WordPress WappPress Basic plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WappPress Team WappPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WappPress: from n/a through 6.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7705 | Fujian mwcms Image Upload uploadeditor.html uploadeditor unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function uploadeditor of the file /uploadeditor.html?action=uploadimage of the component Image Upload. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7706 | Fujian mwcms uploadfile.html uploadimage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function uploadimage of the file /uploadfile.html. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43139 | WordPress Football Pool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43139</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Antoine Hurkmans Football Pool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Football Pool: from n/a through 2.11.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43147 | WordPress Selection Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43147</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Merkulove Selection Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Selection Lite: from n/a through 1.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43148 | WordPress StreamCast  &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43148</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins StreamCast allows Stored XSS.This issue affects StreamCast: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43149 | WordPress CM Tooltip Glossary Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43149</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Tooltip Glossary allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CM Tooltip Glossary: from n/a through 4.3.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43150 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43150</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43151 | WordPress Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43151</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite: from n/a through 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43152 | WordPress 3D FlipBook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43152</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in iberezansky 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook Viewer, Flipbook Image Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook Viewer, Flipbook Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.15.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43155 | WordPress ComboBlocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.86 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43155</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins ComboBlocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ComboBlocks: from n/a through 2.2.86.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43156 | WordPress Post Grid Master plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43156</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AddonMaster Post Grid Master allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Post Grid Master: from n/a through 3.4.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43161 | WordPress Slider &amp;amp; Popup Builder by Depicter plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43161</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Averta Depicter Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43163 | WordPress ParcelPanel plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43163</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Parcel Panel ParcelPanel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ParcelPanel: from n/a through 4.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43164 | WordPress Blockspare plugin  &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43164</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blockspare allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blockspare: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7066 | Siemens Teamcenter Visualization and JT2Go Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7066</link><description>The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of 
an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted PDF files. This 
could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current 
process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43210 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43210</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7590 | WordPress Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin&amp;lt;= 2.14.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Spectra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Spectra: from n/a through 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43213 | WordPress MultiVendorX Marketplace plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.17 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43213</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MultiVendorX WC Marketplace allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WC Marketplace: from n/a through 4.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43216 | WordPress Filr – Secure document library plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43216</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Patrick Posner Filr – Secure document library allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Filr – Secure document library: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43217 | WordPress Kodex Posts likes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43217</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pierre Lebedel Kodex Posts likes allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kodex Posts likes: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43218 | WordPress Mediavine Control Panel plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43218</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mediavine Mediavine Control Panel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediavine Control Panel: from n/a through 2.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43220 | WordPress Form Maker by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.26 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43220</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 10Web Form Builder Team Form Maker by 10Web allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Form Maker by 10Web: from n/a through 1.15.26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43224 | WordPress YaMaps for WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.27 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yuri Baranov YaMaps for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects YaMaps for WordPress: from n/a through 0.6.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43225 | WordPress Enter Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeLooks Enter Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Enter Addons: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43226 | WordPress WP Dashboard Notes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43226</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeroen Sormani WP Dashboard Notes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Dashboard Notes: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43227 | WordPress BetterDocs – Best Documentation, FAQ &amp;amp; Knowledge Base Plugin with AI Support &amp;amp; Instant Answer for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43227</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper BetterDocs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BetterDocs: from n/a through 3.5.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43231 | WordPress Tutor LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeum Tutor LMS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tutor LMS: from n/a through 2.7.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43233 | WordPress BSK Forms Blacklist plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BannerSky BSK Forms Blacklist allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BSK Forms Blacklist: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43360 | ZoneMinder Time-based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43360</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. ZoneMinder is affected by a time-based SQL Injection vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34 and 1.37.61.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43358 | XSS vulnerability in filter view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43358</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. ZoneMinder has a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the filter view via the filter[Id]. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34 and 1.37.61.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43359 | XSS vulnerabilities in montagereview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43359</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. ZoneMinder has a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the montagereview via the displayinterval, speed, and scale parameters. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34 and 1.37.61.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7704 | Weaver e-cology Source Code ecology_dev.zip information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology 8. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cloudstore/ecode/setup/ecology_dev.zip of the component Source Code Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41884 | ZoneMinder Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (&amp;#x27;SQL Injection&amp;#x27;) in watch.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41884</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source Closed-circuit television software application. In WWW/AJAX/watch.php, Line: 51 takes a few parameter in sql query without sanitizing it which makes it vulnerable to sql injection. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42741 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setL2tpServerCfg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42741</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setL2tpServerCfg. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42742 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUrlFilterRule...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42742</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUrlFilterRules. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42743 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setSyslogCfg . A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42743</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setSyslogCfg . Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42744 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setModifyVpnUser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42744</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setModifyVpnUser. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42745 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUPnPCfg. Auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42745</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUPnPCfg. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42747 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWanIeCfg. Aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42747</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWanIeCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42748 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWiFiWpsCfg. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42748</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWiFiWpsCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48171 | An issue in OWASP DefectDojo before v.1.5.3.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the user permissions component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48171</link><description>An issue in OWASP DefectDojo before v.1.5.3.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the user permissions component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42546 | TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the password parameter in the loginauth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42546</link><description>TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the password parameter in the loginauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42547 | TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42547</link><description>TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41710 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41710</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (R6.4.0.136) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrative privilege to conduct an argument injection attack, due to insufficient parameter sanitization during the boot process. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40893 | Firewalla BTLE Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40893</link><description>Multiple authenticated operating system (OS) command injection vulnerabilities exist in Firewalla Box Software 
versions before 1.979. A physically close 
attacker that is authenticated to the Bluetooth Low-Energy (BTLE) interface can use the network configuration service to inject commands in various configuration parameters including networkConfig.Interface.Phy.Eth0.Extra.PingTestIP, networkConfig.Interface.Phy.Eth0.Extra.DNSTestDomain, and networkConfig.Interface.Phy.Eth0.Gateway6. Additionally, because the configuration can be synced to the Firewalla cloud, the attacker may be able to persist access even after hardware resets and firmware re-flashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40892 | Firewalla BTLE Weak Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40892</link><description>A weak credential vulnerability exists in Firewalla Box Software versions before 1.979. This vulnerability allows a physically close attacker to use the license UUID for authentication and provision SSH credentials over the Bluetooth Low-Energy (BTLE) interface. Once an attacker gains access to the LAN, they could log into the SSH interface using the provisioned credentials. The license UUID can be acquired through plain-text Bluetooth sniffing, reading the QR code on the bottom of the device, or brute-forcing the UUID (though this is less likely).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6768 | Denial of Service in CLFS.sys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6768</link><description>A Denial of Service in CLFS.sys in Microsoft Windows 10, Windows 11, Windows Server 2016, Windows Server 2019, and Windows Server 2022 allows a malicious authenticated low-privilege user to cause a Blue Screen of Death via a forced call to the KeBugCheckEx function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42543 | TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42543</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42545 | TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the ssid parameter in setWizardCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42545</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the ssid parameter in setWizardCfg function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41651 | An issue in Prestashop v.8.1.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the module upgrade functionality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41651</link><description>An issue in Prestashop v.8.1.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the module upgrade functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42474 | Streamlit Path Traversal Security Vulnerability on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42474</link><description>Streamlit is a data oriented application development framework for python. Snowflake Streamlit open source addressed a security vulnerability via the static file sharing feature. Users of hosted Streamlit app(s) on Windows were vulnerable to a path traversal vulnerability when the static file sharing feature is enabled. An attacker could utilize the vulnerability to leak the password hash of the Windows user running Streamlit. The vulnerability was patched on Jul 25, 2024, as part of Streamlit open source version 1.37.0. The vulnerability only affects Windows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7700 | Foreman: command injection in &amp;quot;host init config&amp;quot; template via &amp;quot;install packages&amp;quot; field on foreman</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7700</link><description>A command injection flaw was found in the "Host Init Config" template in the Foreman application, via the "Install Packages" field on the "Register Host" page. This issue may allow an attacker with the necessary privileges to inject arbitrary commands into the configuration, potentially allowing unauthorized command execution during host registration. Although this issue requires user interaction to execute injected commands, it poses a significant risk if an unsuspecting user runs the generated registration script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40500 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Martin Kucej i-librarian v.5.11.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40500</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Martin Kucej i-librarian v.5.11.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the search function in the import component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41475 | Gnuboard g6 6.0.7 is vulnerable to Session hijacking due to a CORS misconfiguration.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41475</link><description>Gnuboard g6 6.0.7 is vulnerable to Session hijacking due to a CORS misconfiguration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42623 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/delete/1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42623</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/delete/1</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42624 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/delete/10.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42624</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/delete/10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42625 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/add</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42625</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/add</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42626 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42626</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/add.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42627 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/delete/3.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42627</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/delete/3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7249 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Directory Services allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7249</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Directory Services allows Path Traversal.This issue affects OpenText Directory Services: from 16.4.2 before 24.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41909 | Apache MINA SSHD: integrity check bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41909</link><description>Like many other SSH implementations, Apache MINA SSHD suffered from the issue that is more widely known as CVE-2023-48795. An attacker that can intercept traffic between client and server could drop certain packets from the stream, potentially causing client and server to consequently end up with a connection for which 
some security features have been downgraded or disabled, aka a Terrapin 
attack

The mitigations to prevent this type of attack were implemented in Apache MINA SSHD 2.12.0, both client and server side. Users are recommended to upgrade to at least this version. Note that both the client and the server implementation must have mitigations applied against this issue, otherwise the connection may still be affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42489 | Pro Macros Remote Code Execution via Viewpdf and similar macros</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42489</link><description>Pro Macros provides XWiki rendering macros. Missing escaping in the Viewpdf macro allows any user with view right on the `CKEditor.HTMLConverter` page or edit or comment right on any page to perform remote code execution. Other macros like Viewppt are vulnerable to the same kind of attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42628 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/edit/3.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42628</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/edit/3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42629 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/edit/10.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42629</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/edit/10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42630 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/create_file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42630</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/create_file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42631 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/edit/1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42631</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/edit/1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42482 | fish-shop/syntax-check Improper Neutralization of Delimiters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42482</link><description>fish-shop/syntax-check is a GitHub action for syntax checking fish shell files. Improper neutralization of delimiters in the `pattern` input (specifically the command separator `;` and command substitution characters `(` and `)`) mean that arbitrary command injection is possible by modification of the input value used in a workflow. This has the potential for exposure or exfiltration of sensitive information from the workflow runner, such as might be achieved by sending environment variables to an external entity. It is recommended that users update to the patched version `v1.6.12` or the latest release version `v2.0.0`, however remediation may be possible through careful control of workflows and the `pattern` input value used by this action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42485 | Filament Excel Vulnerable to Path Traversal Attack on Export Download Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42485</link><description>Filament Excel enables excel export for Filament admin resources. The export download route `/filament-excel/{path}` allowed downloading any file without login when the webserver allows `../` in the URL.  Patched with Version v2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42632 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42632</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/add.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39091 | An OS command injection vulnerability in the ccm_debug component of MIPC Camera firmware prior to v5.4.1.240424171021 allows attackers withi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39091</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the ccm_debug component of MIPC Camera firmware prior to v5.4.1.240424171021 allows attackers within the same network to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42481 | Complete crash of host system due to calculateDirectorySize in skyportd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42481</link><description>Skyport Daemon (skyportd) is the daemon for the Skyport Panel. By making thousands of folders &amp; files (easy due to skyport's lack of rate limiting on createFolder. createFile), skyportd in a lot of cases will cause 100% CPU usage and an OOM, probably crashing the system. This is fixed in 0.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36877 | Micro-Star International Z-series motherboards (Z590, Z490, and Z790) and B-series motherboards (B760, B560, B660, and B460) with firmware 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36877</link><description>Micro-Star International Z-series motherboards (Z590, Z490, and Z790) and B-series motherboards (B760, B560, B660, and B460) with firmware 7D25v14, 7D25v17 to 7D25v19, and 7D25v1A to 7D25v1H was discovered to contain a write-what-where condition in the in the SW handler for SMI 0xE3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42480 | Kamaji&amp;#x27;s RBAC Roles for `etcd` are not disjunct</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42480</link><description>Kamaji is the Hosted Control Plane Manager for Kubernetes. In versions 1.0.0 and earlier, Kamaji uses an "open at the top" range definition in RBAC for etcd roles leading to some TCPs API servers being able to read, write, and delete the data of other control planes. This vulnerability is fixed in edge-24.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27443 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the CalendarInvite ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27443</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the CalendarInvite feature of the Zimbra webmail classic user interface, because of improper input validation in the handling of the calendar header. An attacker can exploit this via an email message containing a crafted calendar header with an embedded XSS payload. When a victim views this message in the Zimbra webmail classic interface, the payload is executed in the context of the victim's session, potentially leading to execution of arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42478 | llama.cpp allows Arbitrary Address Read in rpc_server::get_tensor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42478</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. The unsafe `data` pointer member in the `rpc_tensor` structure can cause arbitrary address reading. This vulnerability is fixed in b3561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42479 | llama.cpp allows write-what-where in rpc_server::set_tensor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42479</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. The unsafe `data` pointer member in the `rpc_tensor` structure can cause arbitrary address writing. This vulnerability is fixed in b3561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21550 | SteVe is an open platform that implements different version of the OCPP protocol for Electric Vehicle charge points, acting as a central ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21550</link><description>SteVe is an open platform that implements different version of the OCPP protocol for Electric Vehicle charge points, acting as a central server for management of registered charge points. Attackers can inject arbitrary HTML and Javascript code via WebSockets leading to persistent Cross-Site Scripting in the SteVe management interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27442 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The zmmailboxdmgr binary, a component of ZCS, is intended to be executed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27442</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The zmmailboxdmgr binary, a component of ZCS, is intended to be executed by the zimbra user with root privileges for specific mailbox operations. However, an attacker can escalate privileges from the zimbra user to root, because of improper handling of input arguments. An attacker can execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges, leading to local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33533 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0, issue 1 of 2. A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33533</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0, issue 1 of 2. A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Zimbra webmail admin interface. This vulnerability occurs due to inadequate input validation of the packages parameter, allowing an authenticated attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of another user's browser session. By uploading a malicious JavaScript file and crafting a URL containing its location in the packages parameter, the attacker can exploit this vulnerability. Subsequently, when another user visits the crafted URL, the malicious JavaScript code is executed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33535 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability involves unauthenticated local file inclusion (LFI) in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33535</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability involves unauthenticated local file inclusion (LFI) in a web application, specifically impacting the handling of the packages parameter. Attackers can exploit this flaw to include arbitrary local files without authentication, potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is limited to files within a specific directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33536 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability occurs due to inadequate input validation of the res p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33536</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability occurs due to inadequate input validation of the res parameter, allowing an authenticated attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of another user's browser session. By uploading a malicious JavaScript file, accessible externally, and crafting a URL containing its location in the res parameter, the attacker can exploit this vulnerability. Subsequently, when another user visits the crafted URL, the malicious JavaScript code is executed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42477 | llama.cpp global-buffer-overflow in ggml_type_size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42477</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. The unsafe `type` member in the `rpc_tensor` structure can cause `global-buffer-overflow`. This vulnerability may lead to memory data leakage. The vulnerability is fixed in b3561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38530 | Open eClass Platform allows Arbitrary File Upload in &amp;quot;modules/h5p/save.php&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38530</link><description>The Open eClass platform (formerly known as GUnet eClass) is a complete Course Management System. An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the "save" functionality of the H5P module enables unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files on the server's filesystem. This may lead in unrestricted RCE on the backend server, since the upload location is accessible from the internet. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42520 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in /bin/boa via formParentControl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42520</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in /bin/boa via formParentControl.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6917 | RCE in Veribilim Software&amp;#x27;s Veribase Order Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6917</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Veribilim Software Veribase Order Management allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Veribase Order Management: before v4.010.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42258 | mm: huge_memory: use !CONFIG_64BIT to relax huge page alignment on 32 bit machines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42258</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: huge_memory: use !CONFIG_64BIT to relax huge page alignment on 32 bit machines

Yves-Alexis Perez reported commit 4ef9ad19e176 ("mm: huge_memory: don't
force huge page alignment on 32 bit") didn't work for x86_32 [1].  It is
because x86_32 uses CONFIG_X86_32 instead of CONFIG_32BIT.

!CONFIG_64BIT should cover all 32 bit machines.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/linux-mm/CAHbLzkr1LwH3pcTgM+aGQ31ip2bKqiqEQ8=FQB+t2c3dhNKNHA@mail.gmail.com/</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6639 | MDx &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mdx_list_item Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6639</link><description>The MDx theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mdx_list_item' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6684 | Authentication Bypass in GST Electronics&amp;#x27; inohom Nova Panel N7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6684</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in GST Electronics inohom Nova Panel N7 allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects inohom Nova Panel N7: through 1.9.9.6. NOTE: The vendor was contacted and it was learned that the product is not supported.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42167 | Command Injection in Organisationname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42167</link><description>The function "generate_app_certificates" in controllers/saml2/saml2.js of FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 does not neutralize special elements used in an OS Command properly. This allows an authenticated user with permissions to create applications to execute commands by creating an application with a malicious organisationname.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42165 | Arbitrary User Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42165</link><description>Insufficiently random values for generating activation token in FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 allow attackers to activate accounts of any user by predicting the token for the activation link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42166 | Command Injection in Applicationname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42166</link><description>The function "generate_app_certificates" in lib/app_certificates.js of FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 does not neutralize special elements used in an OS Command properly. This allows an authenticated user with permissions to create applications to execute commands by creating an application with a malicious name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42164 | Disabling MFA without Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42164</link><description>Insufficiently random values for generating password reset token in FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 allow attackers to disable two factor authorization of any user by predicting the token for the disable_2fa link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42163 | Password Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42163</link><description>Insufficiently random values for generating password reset token in FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 allow attackers to take over the account of any user by predicting the token for the password reset link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6758 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Sprecher Automation SPRECON-E</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6758</link><description>Improper Privilege Management in Sprecher Automation SPRECON-E below version 8.71j allows a remote attacker with low privileges to save unauthorized protection assignments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7697 | Logical vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to user information leakage risks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7697</link><description>Logical vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to user information leakage risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 08:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36034 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36034</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8003 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in aggregate reports' search option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36035 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36035</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8003 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in user session recording.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36518 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36518</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8110 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in attack surface analyzer's dashboard.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5487 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5487</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8110 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in attack surface analyzer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5651 | Fence-agent: fence agent command line options leads to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5651</link><description>A flaw was found in fence agents that rely on SSH/Telnet. This vulnerability can allow a Remote Code Execution (RCE) primitive by supplying an arbitrary command to execute in the --ssh-path/--telnet-path arguments. A low-privilege user, for example, a user with developer access, can create a specially crafted FenceAgentsRemediation for a fence agent supporting  --ssh-path/--telnet-path arguments to execute arbitrary commands on the operator's pod. This RCE leads to a privilege escalation, first as the service account running the operator, then to another service account with cluster-admin privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 05:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5527 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5527</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8110 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in file auditing configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7694 | TeamT5 ThreatSonar Anti-Ransomware - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7694</link><description>ThreatSonar Anti-Ransomware from TeamT5 does not properly validate the content of uploaded files. Remote attackers with  administrator privileges on the product platform can upload malicious files, which can be used to execute arbitrary system command on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 03:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7693 | Team Johnlong software Raiden MAILD Remote Management System -  Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7693</link><description>Raiden MAILD Remote Management System from Team Johnlong Software has a Relative Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary file on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7685 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System adds.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7685</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file adds.php. The manipulation of the argument name/dob/email/mobile/address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7686 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System register_case.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7686</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file register_case.php. The manipulation of the argument title/description/opposite_lawyer leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7683 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System addcase_stage.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7683</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file addcase_stage.php. The manipulation of the argument cname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7684 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System add_act.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7684</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file add_act.php. The manipulation of the argument aname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7682 | code-projects Job Portal rw_i_nat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7682</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Portal 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file rw_i_nat.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7681 | code-projects College Management System Login Page login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7681</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects College Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 23:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7680 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System incedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7680</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /incedit.php?id=4. The manipulation of the argument id/inccat/desc/date/amount leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:10:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7678 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_package. The manipulation of the argument name/description/training_duration leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 12:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7677 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System SystemSettings.php update_settings_info cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7677</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function update_settings_info of the file /classes/SystemSettings.php?f=update_settings. The manipulation of the argument contact/address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7676 | Sourcecodester Car Driving School Management System Master.php save_package sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sourcecodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function save_package of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_package. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 09:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7669 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System Master.php delete_enrollment sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7669</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function delete_enrollment of the file Master.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 09:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7668 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System Master.php delete_package sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7668</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function delete_package of the file Master.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 08:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7667 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System User.php delete_users sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7667</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. This affects the function delete_users of the file User.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 08:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7666 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System view_package.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7666</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file view_package.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 07:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7665 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System manage_package.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7665</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_package.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7664 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System view_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7664</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 06:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7663 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7663</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 05:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7662 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System manag_package.php save_package cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7662</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function save_package of the file admin/packages/manag_package.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 04:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7661 | SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System index.php save_users cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Car Driving School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function save_users of the file admin/user/index.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 03:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7589 | OpenSSH pre-authentication async signal safety issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7589</link><description>A signal handler in sshd(8) may call a logging function that is not async-signal-safe.  The signal handler is invoked when a client does not authenticate within the LoginGraceTime seconds (120 by default).  This signal handler executes in the context of the sshd(8)'s privileged code, which is not sandboxed and runs with full root privileges.

This issue is another instance of the problem in CVE-2024-6387 addressed by FreeBSD-SA-24:04.openssh.  The faulty code in this case is from the integration of blacklistd in OpenSSH in FreeBSD.

As a result of calling functions that are not async-signal-safe in the privileged sshd(8) context, a race condition exists that a determined attacker may be able to exploit to allow an unauthenticated remote code execution as root.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 03:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7660 | SourceCodester File Manager App Add File cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7660</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester File Manager App 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Add File Handler. The manipulation of the argument File Title/Uploaded By leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 03:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6640 | pf incorrectly matches different ICMPv6 states in the state table</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6640</link><description>In ICMPv6 Neighbor Discovery (ND), the ID is always 0.  When pf is configured to allow ND and block incoming Echo Requests, a crafted Echo Request packet after a Neighbor Solicitation (NS) can trigger an Echo Reply.  The packet has to come from the same host as the NS and have a zero as identifier to match the state created by the Neighbor Discovery and allow replies to be generated.

ICMPv6 packets with identifier value of zero bypass firewall rules written on the assumption that the incoming packets are going to create a state in the state table.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6759 | NFS client accepts file names containing path separators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6759</link><description>When mounting a remote filesystem using NFS, the kernel did not sanitize remotely provided filenames for the path separator character, "/".  This allows readdir(3) and related functions to return filesystem entries with names containing additional path components.

The lack of validation described above gives rise to a confused deputy problem.  For example, a program copying files from an NFS mount could be tricked into copying from outside the intended source directory, and/or to a location outside the intended destination directory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6760 | ktrace(2) fails to detach when executing a setuid binary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6760</link><description>A logic bug in the code which disables kernel tracing for setuid programs meant that tracing was not disabled when it should have, allowing unprivileged users to trace and inspect the behavior of setuid programs.

The bug may be used by an unprivileged user to read the contents of files to which they would not otherwise have access, such as the local password database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7659 | projectsend Password Reset Token functions.php generate_random_string random values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7659</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in projectsend up to r1605. Affected is the function generate_random_string of the file includes/functions.php of the component Password Reset Token Handler. The manipulation leads to insufficiently random values. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. Upgrading to version r1720 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is aa27eb97edc2ff2b203f97e6675d7b5ba0a22a17. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7658 | projectsend process.php get_preview resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7658</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in projectsend up to r1605. This issue affects the function get_preview of the file process.php. The manipulation leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version r1720 is able to address this issue. The patch is named eb5a04774927e5855b9d0e5870a2aae5a3dc5a08. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7657 | Gila CMS HTTP POST Request page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7657</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Gila CMS 1.10.9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cm/update_rows/page?id=2 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>