<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:48:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2018-25112 | PHOENIX CONTACT: ILC 1x1 ETH Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25112</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use an uncontrolled resource consumption in the IEC 61131 program of the affected products by creating large amounts of network traffic that needs to be handled by the ILC. This results in a Denial-of-Service of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5583 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /register.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5581 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument User leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5582 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument content leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5580 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13967 | ession-Management Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13967</link><description>This vulnerability allows the successful attacker to gain unauthorized access to a 
configuration web page delivered by the integrated web Server of EIBPORT.

This issue affects EIBPORT V3 KNX: through 3.9.8; EIBPORT V3 KNX GSM: through 3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47728 | File Parsing Memory Corruption in CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47728</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5578 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System sales-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5578</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sales-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5579 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System search-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search-product.php. The manipulation of the argument productname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5576 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System bwdate-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5576</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /bwdate-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5577 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5577</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27444 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A reflected XSS vulnerability RSform!Pro component 3.0.0 - 3.3.13 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27444</link><description>A reflected XSS vulnerability in RSform!Pro component 3.0.0 - 3.3.13 for Joomla was discovered. The issue arises from the improper handling of the filter[dateFrom] GET parameter, which is reflected unescaped in the administrative backend interface. This allows an authenticated attacker with admin or editor privileges to inject arbitrary JavaScript code by crafting a malicious URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47724 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47724</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47725 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47725</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47726 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47726</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47727 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47727</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5482 | Sunshine Photo Cart &amp;lt;= 3.4.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5482</link><description>The Sunshine Photo Cart: Free Client Photo Galleries for Photographers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.11. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user-supplied key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords through the password reset functionality, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5575 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System add-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5575</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add-product.php. The manipulation of the argument productname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5574 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System add-company.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5574</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /add-company.php. The manipulation of the argument companyname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4578 | File Provider &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4578</link><description>The File Provider WordPress plugin through 1.2.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4580 | File Provider &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Item Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4580</link><description>The File Provider WordPress plugin through 1.2.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5572 | D-Link DCS-932L setSystemEmail stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5572</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSystemEmail of the file /setSystemEmail. The manipulation of the argument EmailSMTPPortNumber leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5573 | D-Link DCS-932L setSystemWizard setSystemControl os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5573</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setSystemWizard/setSystemControl of the file /setSystemWizard. The manipulation of the argument AdminID leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48710 | kro (Kube Resource Orchestrator) 0.1.0 before 0.2.1 allows users (with permission to create or modify ResourceGraphDefinition resources) to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48710</link><description>kro (Kube Resource Orchestrator) 0.1.0 before 0.2.1 allows users (with permission to create or modify ResourceGraphDefinition resources) to supply arbitrary container images. This can lead to a confused-deputy scenario where kro's controllers deploy and run attacker-controlled images, resulting in unauthenticated remote code execution on cluster nodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5569 | IdeaCMS getList.html Goods sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5569</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IdeaCMS up to 1.7 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function Article/Goods of the file /api/v1.index.article/getList.html. The manipulation of the argument Field leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.8 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 935aceb4c21338633de6d41e13332f7b9db4fa6a. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5571 | D-Link DCS-932L setSystemAdmin os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5571</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setSystemAdmin of the file /setSystemAdmin. The manipulation of the argument AdminID leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5562 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System edit-category-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-category-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5566 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System search-notice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5566</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /search-notice.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20981 | Improper access control in AudioService prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20981</link><description>Improper access control in AudioService prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20984 | Incorrect default permission in Samsung Cloud for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access data in Sams...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20984</link><description>Incorrect default permission in Samsung Cloud for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Cloud for Galaxy Watch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20985 | Improper privilege management in ThemeManager prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to reuse trial items.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20985</link><description>Improper privilege management in ThemeManager prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to reuse trial items.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20986 | Improper access control in ScreenCapture for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to take screenshots.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20986</link><description>Improper access control in ScreenCapture for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to take screenshots.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20987 | Improper access control in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a auth_token.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20987</link><description>Improper access control in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a auth_token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20988 | Out-of-bounds read in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20988</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20989 | Improper logging in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a hmac_key.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20989</link><description>Improper logging in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a hmac_key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20991 | Improper export of Android application components in Bluetooth prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to make devices discov...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20991</link><description>Improper export of Android application components in Bluetooth prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to make devices discoverable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20992 | Out-of-bound read in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20992</link><description>Out-of-bound read in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20993 | Out-of-bounds write in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20993</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20994 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in SyncClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20994</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in SyncClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0.0.59 allows local attackers to access read and write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20995 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in ClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0.0.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20995</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in ClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0.0.59 allows local attackers to read and write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20996 | Improper authorization in Smart Switch installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 3.7.64.10 allows local attackers to read data with t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20996</link><description>Improper authorization in Smart Switch installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 3.7.64.10 allows local attackers to read data with the privilege of Smart Switch. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31127 | MacOS Zscaler Client Connector Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31127</link><description>An improper verification of a loaded library in Zscaler Client Connector on Mac &lt; 4.2.0.241 may allow a local attacker to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5561 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System view-pass-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5561</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-pass-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5539 | Simplify Contact Management: WP Easy Contact &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5539</link><description>The Simple Contact Form Plugin for WordPress – WP Easy Contact plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'emd_mb_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5558 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5558</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/changeimage.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5560 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5560</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5531 | Staff Directory – Employee Directory for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5531</link><description>The Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'emd_mb_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5532 | Faculty Staff and Student Directory Plugin – Campus Directory &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5532</link><description>The Campus Directory – Faculty, Staff &amp; Student Directory Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'emd_mb_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5557 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System edit-course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5557</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-course.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5556 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System edit-teacher-info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5556</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-teacher-info.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 03:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5554 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System pass-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5554</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/pass-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 03:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49223 | billboard.js before 3.15.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function generate, which could allow attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49223</link><description>billboard.js before 3.15.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function generate, which could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5552 | ChestnutCMS API Endpoint exec deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5552</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ChestnutCMS up to 15.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /dev-api/groovy/exec of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5553 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System download-pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5553</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /download-pass.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5551 | FreeFloat FTP Server SYSTEM Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5551</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component SYSTEM Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5549 | FreeFloat FTP Server PASV Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5549</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component PASV Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5550 | FreeFloat FTP Server PBSZ Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5550</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component PBSZ Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5548 | FreeFloat FTP Server NOOP Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5548</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component NOOP Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5547 | FreeFloat FTP Server CDUP Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5547</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component CDUP Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5545 | aaluoxiang oa_system ProcedureController.java image path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5545</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in aaluoxiang oa_system up to 5b445a6227b51cee287bd0c7c33ed94b801a82a5. This affects the function image of the file src/main/java/cn/gson/oasys/controller/process/ProcedureController.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 23:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5546 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System expense-reports-detailed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5546</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System 1.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /expense-reports-detailed.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 23:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5544 | aaluoxiang oa_system UserpanelController.java image path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5544</link><description>A vulnerability was found in aaluoxiang oa_system up to 5b445a6227b51cee287bd0c7c33ed94b801a82a5. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function image of the file src/main/java/cn/gson/oasys/controller/user/UserpanelController.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 23:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24015 | Deno&amp;#x27;s AES GCM authentication tags are not verified</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24015</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime with secure defaults. Versions 1.46.0 through 2.1.6 have an issue that affects AES-256-GCM and AES-128-GCM in Deno in which the authentication tag is not being validated. This means tampered ciphertexts or incorrect keys might not be detected, which breaks the guarantees expected from AES-GCM. Older versions of Deno correctly threw errors in such cases, as does Node.js. Without authentication tag verification, AES-GCM degrades to essentially CTR mode, removing integrity protection. Authenticated data set with set_aad is also affected, as it is incorporated into the GCM hash (ghash) but this too is not validated, rendering AAD checks ineffective. Version 2.1.7 includes a patch that addresses this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 23:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5543 | TOTOLINK X2000R Parent Controls Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5543</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X2000R 1.0.0-B20230726.1108. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Parent Controls Page. The manipulation of the argument Device Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5542 | TOTOLINK X2000R Virtual Server Page formPortFw cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5542</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X2000R 1.0.0-B20230726.1108. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component Virtual Server Page. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48951 | Auth0-PHP SDK Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48951</link><description>Auth0-PHP is a PHP SDK for Auth0 Authentication and Management APIs. Versions 8.0.0-BETA3 prior to 8.14.0 contain a vulnerability due to insecure deserialization of cookie data. If exploited, since SDKs process cookie content without prior authentication, a threat actor could send a specially crafted cookie containing malicious serialized data. Applications using the Auth0-PHP SDK are affected, as are applications using the Auth0/symfony, Auth0/laravel-auth0, or Auth0/wordpress SDKs, because those SDKsrely on the Auth0-PHP SDK versions from 8.0.0-BETA3 until 8.14.0. Version 8.14.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49000 | InvenTree has uncontrolled memory allocation via built-in label-sheet plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49000</link><description>InvenTree is an Open Source Inventory Management System. Prior to version 0.17.13, the skip field in the built-in `label-sheet` plugin lacks an upper bound, so a large value forces the server to allocate an enormous Python list. This lets any authenticated label-printing user trigger a denial-of-service via memory exhaustion. the issue is fixed in versions 0.17.13 and higher. No workaround is available aside from upgrading to the patched version.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49001 | Dataease Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49001</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.10, secret verification does not take effect successfully, so a user can use any secret to forge a JWT token. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.10. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49002 | Dataease H2 Database Remote Code Execution (RCE) Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49002</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Versions prior to version 2.10.10 have a flaw in the patch for CVE-2025-32966 that allow the patch to be bypassed through case insensitivity because INIT and RUNSCRIPT are prohibited. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.10. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48999 | Dataease Redshift Data Source JDBC Connection Parameters Not Verified Leads to RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48999</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. A bypass of CVE-2025-46566's patch exists in versions prior to 2.10.10. In a malicious payload, `getUrlType()` retrieves `hostName`. Since the judgment statement returns false, it will not enter the if statement and will not be filtered. The payload can be directly concatenated at the replace location to construct a malicious JDBC statement. Version 2.10.10 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5527 | Tenda RX3 SetStaticRouteCfg save_staticroute_data stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5527</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function save_staticroute_data of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5525 | Jrohy trojan linux.go LogChan os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5525</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jrohy trojan up to 2.15.3. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function LogChan of the file trojan/util/linux.go. The manipulation of the argument c leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 20:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23097 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1380. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23097</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1380. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23100 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400. The absence of a NULL check leads to a Denial of Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23100</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400. The absence of a NULL check leads to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5523 | enilu web-flash File Upload upload fileService.upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5523</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in enilu web-flash 1.0. This affects the function fileService.upload of the file src/main/java/cn/enilu/flash/api/controller/FileController/upload of the component File Upload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35036 | hibernate-validator insecure default Expression Language interpolation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35036</link><description>Hibernate Validator before 6.2.0 and 7.0.0, by default and depending how it is used, may interpolate user-supplied input in a constraint violation message with Expression Language. This could allow an attacker to access sensitive information or execute arbitrary Java code. Hibernate Validator as of 6.2.0 and 7.0.0 no longer interpolates custom constraint violation messages with Expression Language and strongly recommends not allowing user-supplied input in constraint violation messages. CVE-2020-5245 and CVE-2025-4428 are examples of related, downstream vulnerabilities involving Expression Language intepolation of user-supplied data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23098 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, and 1380. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23098</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, and 1380. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5522 | jack0240 魏 bskms 蓝天幼儿园管理系统 User Creation addUser improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5522</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jack0240 魏 bskms 蓝天幼儿园管理系统 up to dffe6640b5b54d8e29da6f060e0493fea74b3fad. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sa/addUser of the component User Creation Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23102 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, and 1380. A Double Free in the mobi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23102</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, and 1380. A Double Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48998 | Dataease MYSQL JDBC File Reading Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48998</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, a bypass of the patch for CVE-2025-27103 allows authenticated users to read and deserialize arbitrary files through the background JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.10. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5521 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM updataPassword cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5521</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM 9.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/user/updataPassword. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48950 | MaxKB Python Sandbox Bypass in Function Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48950</link><description>MaxKB is an open-source AI assistant for enterprise. Prior to version 1.10.8-lts, Sandbox only restricts the execution permissions of binary files in common directories, such as `/bin,/usr/bin`, etc. Therefore, attackers can exploit some files with execution permissions in non blacklisted directories to carry out attacks. Version 1.10.8-lts fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48953 | Umbraco Vulnerable to By-Pass of Configured Allowed Extensions for File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48953</link><description>Umbraco is an ASP.NET content management system (CMS). Starting in version 14.0.0 and prior to versions 15.4.2 and 16.0.0, it's possible to upload a file that doesn't adhere with the configured allowable file extensions via a manipulated API request. The issue is patched in versions 15.4.2 and 16.0.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48997 | Multer vulnerable to Denial of Service via unhandled exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48997</link><description>Multer is a node.js middleware for handling `multipart/form-data`. A vulnerability that is present starting in version 1.4.4-lts.1 and prior to version 2.0.1 allows an attacker to trigger a Denial of Service (DoS) by sending an upload file request with an empty string field name. This request causes an unhandled exception, leading to a crash of the process. Users should upgrade to `2.0.1` to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5516 | TOTOLINK X2000R URL Filtering Page formFilter cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5516</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TOTOLINK X2000R 1.0.0-B20230726.1108. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component URL Filtering Page. The manipulation of the argument URL Address leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5520 | Open5GS AMF/MME emm_state_authentication assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5520</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.3. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function gmm_state_authentication/emm_state_authentication of the component AMF/MME. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 9f5d133657850e6167231527514ee1364d37a884. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. This is a different issue than CVE-2025-1893.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 18:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30360 | webpack-dev-server users&amp;#x27; source code may be stolen when they access a malicious web site with non-Chromium based browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30360</link><description>webpack-dev-server allows users to use webpack with a development server that provides live reloading. Prior to version 5.2.1, webpack-dev-server users' source code may be stolen when you access a malicious web site with non-Chromium based browser. The `Origin` header is checked to prevent Cross-site WebSocket hijacking from happening, which was reported by CVE-2018-14732. But webpack-dev-server always allows IP address `Origin` headers. This allows websites that are served on IP addresses to connect WebSocket. An attacker can obtain source code via a method similar to that used to exploit CVE-2018-14732. Version 5.2.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30359 | webpack-dev-server users&amp;#x27; source code may be stolen when they access a malicious web site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30359</link><description>webpack-dev-server allows users to use webpack with a development server that provides live reloading. Prior to version 5.2.1, webpack-dev-server users' source code may be stolen when they access a malicious web site. Because the request for classic script by a script tag is not subject to same origin policy, an attacker can inject a malicious script in their site and run the script. Note that the attacker has to know the port and the output entrypoint script path. Combined with prototype pollution, the attacker can get a reference to the webpack runtime variables. By using `Function::toString` against the values in `__webpack_modules__`, the attacker can get the source code. Version 5.2.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5513 | quequnlong shiyi-blog add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5513</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in quequnlong shiyi-blog up to 1.2.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dev-api/api/comment/add. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5515 | TOTOLINK X2000R formMapDel command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5515</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK X2000R 1.0.0-B20230726.1108. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formMapDel. The manipulation of the argument devicemac1 leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5511 | quequnlong shiyi-blog photos improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5511</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in quequnlong shiyi-blog up to 1.2.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dev api/app/album/photos/. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5512 | quequnlong shiyi-blog Administrator Backend verifyPassword improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5512</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in quequnlong shiyi-blog up to 1.2.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/sys/user/verifyPassword/ of the component Administrator Backend. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23107 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23107</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30167 | Jupyter Core on Windows Has Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30167</link><description>Jupyter Core is a package for the core common functionality of Jupyter projects. When using Jupyter Core prior to version 5.8.0 on Windows, the shared `%PROGRAMDATA%` directory is searched for configuration files (`SYSTEM_CONFIG_PATH` and `SYSTEM_JUPYTER_PATH`), which may allow users to create configuration files affecting other users. Only shared Windows systems with multiple users and unprotected `%PROGRAMDATA%` are affected. Users should upgrade to Jupyter Core version 5.8.0 or later to receive a patch. Some other mitigations are available. As administrator, modify the permissions on the `%PROGRAMDATA%` directory so it is not writable by unauthorized users; or as administrator, create the `%PROGRAMDATA%\jupyter` directory with appropriately restrictive permissions; or as user or administrator, set the `%PROGRAMDATA%` environment variable to a directory with appropriately restrictive permissions (e.g. controlled by administrators _or_ the current user).</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5510 | quequnlong shiyi-blog optimize server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5510</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in quequnlong shiyi-blog up to 1.2.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /app/sys/article/optimize. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32105 | A buffer overflow in the the Sangoma IMG2020 HTTP server through 2.3.9.6 allows an unauthenticated user to achieve remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32105</link><description>A buffer overflow in the the Sangoma IMG2020 HTTP server through 2.3.9.6 allows an unauthenticated user to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32106 | In Audiocodes Mediapack MP-11x through 6.60A.369.002, a crafted POST request request may result in an unauthenticated remote user's ability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32106</link><description>In Audiocodes Mediapack MP-11x through 6.60A.369.002, a crafted POST request request may result in an unauthenticated remote user's ability to execute unauthorized code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5508 | TOTOLINK A3002RU IP Port Filtering Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5508</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002RU 2.1.1-B20230720.1011. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component IP Port Filtering Page. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5509 | quequnlong shiyi-blog upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5509</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in quequnlong shiyi-blog up to 1.2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/file/upload. The manipulation of the argument file/source leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23103 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23103</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25020 | IBM QRadar Suite Software and IBM Cloud Pak for Security improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25020</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.11.2.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to improperly validating API data input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44148 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MailEnable before v10 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the failure.aspx co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44148</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MailEnable before v10 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the failure.aspx component</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5507 | TOTOLINK A3002RU MAC Filtering Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5507</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002RU 2.1.1-B20230720.1011. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component MAC Filtering Page. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1334 | IBM QRadar Suite Software and IBM Cloud Pak for Security information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1334</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.11.2.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25019 | IBM QRadar Suite Software and IBM Cloud Pak for Security session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25019</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.11.2.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 does not invalidate session after a logout which could allow a user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25021 | IBM QRadar Suite Software and IBM Cloud Pak for Security code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25021</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.11.2.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 could allow a privileged execute code in case management script creation due to the improper generation of code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25022 | IBM QRadar Suite Software and IBM Cloud Pak for Security information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25022</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.11.2.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 could allow an unauthenticated user in the environment to obtain highly sensitive information in configuration files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45854 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /server/executeExec of JEHC-BPM v2.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45854</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /server/executeExec of JEHC-BPM v2.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5505 | TOTOLINK A3002RU Virtual Server Page formPortFw cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002RU 2.1.1-B20230720.1011 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component Virtual Server Page. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5506 | TOTOLINK A3002RU NAT Mapping Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5506</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002RU 2.1.1-B20230720.1011. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component NAT Mapping Page. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45655 | IBM Application Gateway incorrect permission assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45655</link><description>IBM Application Gateway 19.12 through 24.09 could allow a local privileged user to perform unauthorized actions due to incorrect permissions assignment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46548 | Apache Pekko Management, Apache Pekko Management, Apache Pekko Management: management API basic authentication is not effective</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46548</link><description>If you enable Basic Authentication in Pekko Management using the Java DSL, the authenticator may not be properly applied.


Users that rely on authentication instead of making sure the Management API ports are only available to trusted users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.1.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36564 | Dell Encryption Admin Utilities versions prior to 11.10.2 contain an Improper Link Resolution vulnerability. A local malicious user could po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36564</link><description>Dell Encryption Admin Utilities versions prior to 11.10.2 contain an Improper Link Resolution vulnerability. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43923 | An issue was discovered in ReportController in Unicom Focal Point 7.6.1. A user who has administrative privilege in Focal Point can perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43923</link><description>An issue was discovered in ReportController in Unicom Focal Point 7.6.1. A user who has administrative privilege in Focal Point can perform SQL injection via the image parameter during a delete report image operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43924 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability was discovered in Unicom Focal Point 7.6.1. The val parameter in SettingController (for /fp/admin/setting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43924</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability was discovered in Unicom Focal Point 7.6.1. The val parameter in SettingController (for /fp/admin/settings/loginpage) and the rootserviceurl parameter in FriendsController (for /fp/admin/settings/friends), entered by an admin, allow stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43925 | An issue was discovered in Unicom Focal Point 7.6.1. The database is encrypted with a hardcoded key, making it easier to recover the clearte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43925</link><description>An issue was discovered in Unicom Focal Point 7.6.1. The database is encrypted with a hardcoded key, making it easier to recover the cleartext data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5503 | TOTOLINK X15 formMapReboot stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5503</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. This affects the function formMapReboot of the file /boafrm/formMapReboot. The manipulation of the argument deviceMacAddr leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5504 | TOTOLINK X2000R formWsc command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5504</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK X2000R 1.0.0-B20230726.1108 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formWsc. The manipulation of the argument peerRptPin leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45855 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /upload/GoodsCategory/image of erupt v1.12.19 allows attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45855</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /upload/GoodsCategory/image of erupt v1.12.19 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5501 | Open5GS NGAP PathSwitchRequest Message ngap-handler.c ngap_handle_path_switch_request_transfer assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5501</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.3. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ngap_handle_path_switch_request_transfer of the file src/smf/ngap-handler.c of the component NGAP PathSwitchRequest Message Handler. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 2daa44adab762c47a8cef69cc984946973a845b3. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5502 | TOTOLINK X15 formMapReboot command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5502</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. Affected by this issue is the function formMapReboot of the file /boafrm/formMapReboot. The manipulation of the argument deviceMacAddr leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46154 | Foxcms v1.25 has a SQL time injection in the $_POST['dbname'] parameter of installdb.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46154</link><description>Foxcms v1.25 has a SQL time injection in the $_POST['dbname'] parameter of installdb.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5498 | slackero phpwcms Custom Source Tab cnt21.readform.inc.php is_file deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5498</link><description>A vulnerability was found in slackero phpwcms up to 1.9.45/1.10.8. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function file_get_contents/is_file of the file include/inc_lib/content/cnt21.readform.inc.php of the component Custom Source Tab. The manipulation of the argument cpage_custom leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.9.46 and 1.10.9 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5499 | slackero phpwcms image_resized.php getimagesize deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5499</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in slackero phpwcms up to 1.9.45/1.10.8. Affected is the function is_file/getimagesize of the file image_resized.php. The manipulation of the argument imgfile leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.9.46 and 1.10.9 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12718 | Bypass extraction filter to modify file metadata outside extraction directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12718</link><description>Allows modifying some file metadata (e.g. last modified) with filter="data" or file permissions (chmod) with filter="tar" of files outside the extraction directory.
You are affected by this vulnerability if using the tarfile module to extract untrusted tar archives using TarFile.extractall() or TarFile.extract() using the filter= parameter with a value of "data" or "tar". See the tarfile  extraction filters documentation https://docs.python.org/3/library/tarfile.html#tarfile-extraction-filter  for more information. Only Python versions 3.12 or later are affected by these vulnerabilities, earlier versions don't include the extraction filter feature.

Note that for Python 3.14 or later the default value of filter= changed from "no filtering" to `"data", so if you are relying on this new default behavior then your usage is also affected.

Note that none of these vulnerabilities significantly affect the installation of source distributions which are tar archives as source distributions already allow arbitrary code execution during the build process. However when evaluating source distributions it's important to avoid installing source distributions with suspicious links.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4138 | Bypassing extraction filter to create symlinks to arbitrary targets outside extraction directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4138</link><description>Allows the extraction filter to be ignored, allowing symlink targets to point outside the destination directory, and the modification of some file metadata.


You are affected by this vulnerability if using the tarfile module to extract untrusted tar archives using TarFile.extractall() or TarFile.extract() using the filter= parameter with a value of "data" or "tar". See the tarfile  extraction filters documentation https://docs.python.org/3/library/tarfile.html#tarfile-extraction-filter  for more information. Only Python versions 3.12 or later are affected by these vulnerabilities, earlier versions don't include the extraction filter feature.

Note that for Python 3.14 or later the default value of filter= changed from "no filtering" to `"data", so if you are relying on this new default behavior then your usage is also affected.

Note that none of these vulnerabilities significantly affect the installation of source distributions which are tar archives as source distributions already allow arbitrary code execution during the build process. However when evaluating source distributions it's important to avoid installing source distributions with suspicious links.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4330 | Extraction filter bypass for linking outside extraction directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4330</link><description>Allows the extraction filter to be ignored, allowing symlink targets to point outside the destination directory, and the modification of some file metadata.


You are affected by this vulnerability if using the tarfile module to extract untrusted tar archives using TarFile.extractall() or TarFile.extract() using the filter= parameter with a value of "data" or "tar". See the tarfile  extraction filters documentation https://docs.python.org/3/library/tarfile.html#tarfile-extraction-filter  for more information. Only Python versions 3.12 or later are affected by these vulnerabilities, earlier versions don't include the extraction filter feature.

Note that for Python 3.14 or later the default value of filter= changed from "no filtering" to `"data", so if you are relying on this new default behavior then your usage is also affected.

Note that none of these vulnerabilities significantly affect the installation of source distributions which are tar archives as source distributions already allow arbitrary code execution during the build process. However when evaluating source distributions it's important to avoid installing source distributions with suspicious links.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4435 | Tarfile extracts filtered members when errorlevel=0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4435</link><description>When using a TarFile.errorlevel = 0 and extracting with a filter the documented behavior is that any filtered members would be skipped and not extracted. However the actual behavior of TarFile.errorlevel = 0 in affected versions is that the member would still be extracted and not skipped.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4517 | Arbitrary writes via tarfile realpath overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4517</link><description>Allows arbitrary filesystem writes outside the extraction directory during extraction with filter="data".


You are affected by this vulnerability if using the tarfile module to extract untrusted tar archives using TarFile.extractall() or TarFile.extract() using the filter= parameter with a value of "data" or "tar". See the tarfile  extraction filters documentation https://docs.python.org/3/library/tarfile.html#tarfile-extraction-filter  for more information. Only Python versions 3.12 or later are affected by these vulnerabilities, earlier versions don't include the extraction filter feature.

Note that for Python 3.14 or later the default value of filter= changed from "no filtering" to `"data", so if you are relying on this new default behavior then your usage is also affected.

Note that none of these vulnerabilities significantly affect the installation of source distributions which are tar archives as source distributions already allow arbitrary code execution during the build process. However when evaluating source distributions it's important to avoid installing source distributions with suspicious links.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5497 | slackero phpwcms Feedimport Module processing.inc.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5497</link><description>A vulnerability was found in slackero phpwcms up to 1.9.45/1.10.8. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file include/inc_module/mod_feedimport/inc/processing.inc.php of the component Feedimport Module. The manipulation of the argument cnt_text leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.9.46 and 1.10.9 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5495 | Netgear WNR614 URL improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5495</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WNR614 1.1.0.28_1.0.1WW. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component URL Handler. The manipulation with the input %00currentsetting.htm leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This issue appears to have been circulating as an 0day since 2024.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4205 | Popup Maker &amp;lt;= 1.20.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via popupID Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4205</link><description>The Popup Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘popupID' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.20.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4671 | Profile Builder &amp;lt;= 3.13.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via user_meta and compare Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4671</link><description>The Profile Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's user_meta and compare shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5340 | Music Player for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via album_buy_url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5340</link><description>The Music Player for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘album_buy_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 11:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5492 | D-Link DI-500WF-WT /usr/sbin/jhttpd msp_info.htm sub_456DE8 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5492</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DI-500WF-WT up to 20250511 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_456DE8 of the file /msp_info.htm?flag=cmd of the component /usr/sbin/jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 10:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5493 | Baison Channel Middleware Product ToJsonByControlName sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5493</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baison Channel Middleware Product 2.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /e3api/api/main/ToJsonByControlName. The manipulation of the argument data leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 10:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36486 | A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the virtual machine archive restoration functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36486</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the virtual machine archive restoration functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.1.1 (55740). When an archived virtual machine is restored, the prl_vmarchiver tool decompresses the file and writes the content back to its original location using root privileges. An attacker can exploit this process by using a hard link to write to an arbitrary file, potentially resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52561 | A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Snapshot functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.1.1 (build 55740). When a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52561</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Snapshot functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.1.1 (build 55740). When a snapshot of a virtual machine is deleted, a root service verifies and modifies the ownership of the snapshot files. By using a symlink, an attacker can change the ownership of files owned by root to a lower-privilege user, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54189 | A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Snapshot functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.1.1 (build 55740). When a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54189</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Snapshot functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.1.1 (build 55740). When a snapshot of a virtual machine is taken, a root service writes to a file owned by a normal user. By using a hard link, an attacker can write to an arbitrary file, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31359 | A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the PVMP package unpacking functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.2.2 (55879). ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31359</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the PVMP package unpacking functionality of Parallels Desktop for Mac version 20.2.2 (55879). This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to write to arbitrary files, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4392 | Shared Files &amp;lt;= 1.7.48 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sanitize_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4392</link><description>The Shared Files – Frontend File Upload Form &amp; Secure File Sharing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via html File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.48 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the sanitize_file() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin’s MIME-only checks and inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the html file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1725 | Bit File Manager – 100% Free &amp;amp; Open Source File Manager and Code Editor for WordPress &amp;lt;= 6.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1725</link><description>The Bit File Manager – 100% Free &amp; Open Source File Manager and Code Editor for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4420 | Vayu Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via containerWidth Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4420</link><description>The Vayu Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘containerWidth’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to a missing capability check on the vayu_blocks_option_panel_callback() function and insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5103 | Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via wps_wgm_save_post Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5103</link><description>The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to boolean-based SQL Injection via the 'default_price' and 'product_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5116 | WP Plugin Info Card &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via containerid Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5116</link><description>The WP Plugin Info Card plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘containerid’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This issue is due to an incomplete patch for CVE-2025-31835.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41428 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in TimeWorks 10.0 to 10.3. If exploited, arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41428</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in TimeWorks 10.0 to 10.3. If exploited, arbitrary JSON files on the server may be viewed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46355 | Incorrect default permissions issue in PC Time Tracer prior to 5.2. If exploited, arbitrary code may be executed with SYSTEM privilege on Wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46355</link><description>Incorrect default permissions issue in PC Time Tracer prior to 5.2. If exploited, arbitrary code may be executed with SYSTEM privilege on Windows system where the product is running by a local authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21479 | Incorrect Authorization in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21479</link><description>Memory corruption due to unauthorized command execution in GPU micronode while executing specific sequence of commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3584 | Newsletter &amp;lt; 8.8.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Subscription</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3584</link><description>The Newsletter  WordPress plugin before 8.8.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its Subscription settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3662 | FancyBox for WordPress &amp;lt; 3.3.6 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3662</link><description>The FancyBox for WordPress plugin before 3.3.6 does not escape captions and titles attributes before using them to populate galleries' caption fields. The issue was received as a Contributor+ Stored XSS, however one of our researcher (Marc Montpas) escalated it to an Unauthenticated Stored XSS</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4567 | Post Slider and Carousel with Widget &amp;lt; 3.2.10 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4567</link><description>The Post Slider and Post Carousel with Post Vertical Scrolling Widget  WordPress plugin before 3.2.10 does not validate and escape some of its Widget options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53010 | Improper Access Control in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53010</link><description>Memory corruption may occur while attaching VM when the HLOS retains access to VM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53013 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53013</link><description>Memory corruption may occur while processing voice call registration with user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53015 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53015</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL command to handle buffers associated with a session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53016 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53016</link><description>Memory corruption while processing I2C settings in Camera driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53017 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53017</link><description>Memory corruption while handling test pattern generator IOCTL command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53018 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53018</link><description>Memory corruption may occur while processing the OIS packet parser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53019 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53019</link><description>Information disclosure may occur while decoding the RTP packet with improper header length for number of contributing sources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53020 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53020</link><description>Information disclosure may occur while decoding the RTP packet with invalid header extension from network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53021 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53021</link><description>Information disclosure may occur while processing goodbye RTCP packet from network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53026 | Buffer Over-read in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53026</link><description>Information disclosure when an invalid RTCP packet is received during a VoLTE/VoWiFi IMS call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21463 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21463</link><description>Transient DOS while processing the EHT operation IE in the received beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21480 | Incorrect Authorization in Graphics Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21480</link><description>Memory corruption due to unauthorized command execution in GPU micronode while executing specific sequence of commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21485 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21485</link><description>Memory corruption while processing INIT and multimode invoke IOCTL calls on FastRPC.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21486 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21486</link><description>Memory corruption during dynamic process creation call when client is only passing address and length of shell binary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27029 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HAL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27029</link><description>Transient DOS while processing the tone measurement response buffer when the response buffer is out of range.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27031 | Use After Free in Bluetooth HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27031</link><description>memory corruption while processing IOCTL commands, when the buffer in write loopback mode is accessed after being freed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27038 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27038</link><description>Memory corruption while rendering graphics using Adreno GPU drivers in Chrome.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31710 | In engineermode service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31710</link><description>In engineermode service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 05:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31711 | In cplog service, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to local denial of service with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31711</link><description>In cplog service, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 05:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31712 | In cplog service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31712</link><description>In cplog service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 05:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4797 | Golo &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4797</link><description>The Golo - City Travel Guide WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to setting an authorization cookie. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including administrators, provided they know the user's email address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 04:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2939 | Ninja Tables – Easy Data Table Builder &amp;lt;= 5.0.18 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection to Limited Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2939</link><description>The Ninja Tables – Easy Data Table Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.18 via deserialization of untrusted input from the args[callback] parameter . This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to execute arbitrary functions, though it does not allow user supplied parameters only single functions can be called so the impact is limited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 03:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4047 | Broken Link Checker &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Missing Autorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Status Dashboard View</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4047</link><description>The Broken Link Checker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data access due to a missing capability check on the ajax_full_status and ajax_dashboard_status functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view the plugin's status.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 03:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4224 | wpForo + wpForo Advanced Attachments &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4224</link><description>The wpForo + wpForo Advanced Attachments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via media upload names in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 03:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49162 | Arris VIP1113 devices through 2025-05-30 with KreaTV SDK allow file overwrite via TFTP because a remote filename with a space character allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49162</link><description>Arris VIP1113 devices through 2025-05-30 with KreaTV SDK allow file overwrite via TFTP because a remote filename with a space character allows an attacker to control the local filename.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 23:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49163 | Arris VIP1113 devices through 2025-05-30 with KreaTV SDK allow booting an arbitrary image via a crafted /usr/bin/gunzip file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49163</link><description>Arris VIP1113 devices through 2025-05-30 with KreaTV SDK allow booting an arbitrary image via a crafted /usr/bin/gunzip file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 23:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49164 | Arris VIP1113 devices through 2025-05-30 with KreaTV SDK have a firmware decryption key of cd1c2d78f2cba1f73ca7e697b4a485f49a8a7d0c8b0fdc9f5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49164</link><description>Arris VIP1113 devices through 2025-05-30 with KreaTV SDK have a firmware decryption key of cd1c2d78f2cba1f73ca7e697b4a485f49a8a7d0c8b0fdc9f51ced50f2530668a.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 23:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5068 | Use after free in Blink in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.68 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5068</link><description>Use after free in Blink in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.68 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 23:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5419 | Out of bounds read and write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.68 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5419</link><description>Out of bounds read and write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.68 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 23:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3919 | WordPress Comments Import &amp;amp; Export &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3919</link><description>The WordPress Comments Import &amp; Export plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_settings function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3. Additionally, the plugin fails to properly sanitize and escape FTP settings parameters. 
This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts on the plugin settings page that will execute whenever an administrative user accesses an injected page.
The vulnerability was partially fixed in version 2.4.3 and fully fixed in version 2.4.4</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47585 | WordPress Booking and Rental Manager &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47585</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mage people team Booking and Rental Manager allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Booking and Rental Manager: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 19:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48387 | tar-fs has issue where extract can write outside the specified dir with a specific tarball</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48387</link><description>tar-fs provides filesystem bindings for tar-stream. Versions prior to 3.0.9, 2.1.3, and 1.16.5 have an issue where an extract can write outside the specified dir with a specific tarball. This has been patched in versions 3.0.9, 2.1.3, and 1.16.5. As a workaround, use the ignore option to ignore non files/directories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 19:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48996 | Unauthenticated Disclosure of PSU HAX CMS Site Listings via haxPsuUsage API Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48996</link><description>HAX open-apis provides microservice apis for HAX webcomponents repo that are shared infrastructure calls. Prior to open-apis commit 06c2e1fbb7131a8fe66aa0600f38dcacae6b7ac7, an unauthenticated information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Penn State University deployment of the HAX content management system via the `haxPsuUsage` API endpoint. This allows any remote unauthenticated user to retrieve a full list of PSU websites hosted on HAX CMS. When chained with other authorization issues (e.g., HAX-3), this could assist in targeted attacks such as unauthorized content modification or deletion. Commit 06c2e1fbb7131a8fe66aa0600f38dcacae6b7ac7 patches the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 19:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1051 | Sonos Era 300 Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1051</link><description>Sonos Era 300 Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Sonos Era 300 speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of ALAC data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the anacapa user. Was ZDI-CAN-25865.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 19:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49069 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49069</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cimatti Consulting Contact Forms by Cimatti allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Contact Forms by Cimatti: from n/a through 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23099 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23099</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23105 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23105</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27953 | An issue in Clinical Collaboration Platform 12.2.1.5 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27953</link><description>An issue in Clinical Collaboration Platform 12.2.1.5 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the session management component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27954 | An issue in Clinical Collaboration Platform 12.2.1.5 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27954</link><description>An issue in Clinical Collaboration Platform 12.2.1.5 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via the usertoken function of default.aspx.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27955 | Clinical Collaboration Platform 12.2.1.5 has a weak logout system where the session token remains valid after logout and allows a remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27955</link><description>Clinical Collaboration Platform 12.2.1.5 has a weak logout system where the session token remains valid after logout and allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5086 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability affecting DELMIA Apriso from Release 2020 through Release 2025</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5086</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability affecting DELMIA Apriso from Release 2020 through Release 2025 could lead to a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27956 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in WebLaudos 24.2 (04) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the id parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27956</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in WebLaudos 24.2 (04) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23104 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23104</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20297 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) on Splunk Enterprise through dashboard PDF generation component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20297</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.4.2, 9.3.4 and 9.2.6, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.3.2411.102, 9.3.2408.111 and 9.2.2406.118, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through the pdfgen/render REST endpoint that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20298 | Incorrect permission assignment on Universal Forwarder for Windows during new installation or upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20298</link><description>In Universal Forwarder for Windows versions below 9.4.2, 9.3.4, 9.2.6, and 9.1.9, a new installation of or an upgrade to an affected version can result in incorrect permissions assignment in the Universal Forwarder for Windows Installation directory (by default, C:\Program Files\SplunkUniversalForwarder). This lets non-administrator users on the machine access the directory and all its contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45387 | osTicket prior to v1.17.6 and v1.18.2 are vulnerable to Broken Access Control Vulnerability in /scp/ajax.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45387</link><description>osTicket prior to v1.17.6 and v1.18.2 are vulnerable to Broken Access Control Vulnerability in /scp/ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1440 | Open Redirection in Multiple WSO2 Products via Multi-Option Authentication Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1440</link><description>An open redirection vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to improper validation of the multi-option URL in the authentication endpoint when multi-option authentication is enabled. A malicious actor can craft a valid link that redirects users to an attacker-controlled site.

By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker may trick users into visiting a malicious page, enabling phishing attacks to harvest sensitive information or perform other harmful actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5036 | RFA File Parsing Use-After-Free Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5036</link><description>A maliciously crafted RFA file, when linked or imported into Autodesk Revit, can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3509 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Management Console of Multiple WSO2 Products via Rich Text Editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3509</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Management Console of multiple WSO2 products due to insufficient input validation in the Rich Text Editor within the registry section.
To exploit this vulnerability, a malicious actor must have a valid user account with administrative access to the Management Console. If successful, the actor could inject persistent JavaScript payloads, enabling the theft of user data or execution of unauthorized actions on behalf of other users.

While this issue enables persistent client-side script execution, session-related cookies remain protected with the httpOnly flag, preventing session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7073 | Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Multiple WSO2 Products via SOAP Admin Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7073</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to improper input validation in SOAP admin services. This flaw allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate server-side requests, enabling access to internal and external resources available through the network or filesystem.

Exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to unauthorized access to sensitive data and systems, including resources within private networks, as long as they are reachable by the affected product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7074 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload in Multiple WSO2 Products via SOAP Admin Service Leading to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7074</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to improper validation of user input in SOAP admin services. A malicious actor with administrative privileges can upload an arbitrary file to a user-controlled location on the server.

By leveraging this vulnerability, an attacker could upload a specially crafted payload, potentially achieving remote code execution (RCE) on the server. Exploitation requires valid admin credentials, limiting its impact to authorized but potentially malicious users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8008 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Multiple WSO2 Products via JDBC User Store Connection Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8008</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in multiple [Vendor Name] products due to insufficient output encoding in error messages generated by the JDBC user store connection validation request. A malicious actor can inject a specially crafted payload into the request, causing the browser to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the vulnerable page.

This vulnerability may allow UI manipulation, redirection to malicious websites, or data exfiltration from the browser. However, since all session-related sensitive cookies are protected with the httpOnly flag, session hijacking is not possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48995 | SignXML&amp;#x27;s signature verification with HMAC is vulnerable to a timing attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48995</link><description>SignXML is an implementation of the W3C XML Signature standard in Python. When verifying signatures with X509 certificate validation turned off and HMAC shared secret set (`signxml.XMLVerifier.verify(require_x509=False, hmac_key=...`), versions of SignXML prior to 4.0.4 are vulnerable to a potential timing attack. The verifier may leak information about the correct HMAC when comparing it with the user supplied hash, allowing users to reconstruct the correct HMAC for any data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48994 | SignXML&amp;#x27;s signature verification with HMAC is vulnerable to an algorithm confusion attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48994</link><description>SignXML is an implementation of the W3C XML Signature standard in Python. When verifying signatures with X509 certificate validation turned off and HMAC shared secret set (`signxml.XMLVerifier.verify(require_x509=False, hmac_key=...`), versions of SignXML prior to 4.0.4 are vulnerable to a potential algorithm confusion attack. Unless the user explicitly limits the expected signature algorithms using the `signxml.XMLVerifier.verify(expect_config=...)` setting, an attacker may supply a signature unexpectedly signed with a key other than the provided HMAC key, using a different (asymmetric key) signature algorithm. Starting with SignXML 4.0.4, specifying `hmac_key` causes the set of accepted signature algorithms to be restricted to HMAC only, if not already restricted by the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57459 | A time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in mydetailsstudent.php in the CloudClassroom PHP Project 1.0. The myds parameter does not p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57459</link><description>A time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in mydetailsstudent.php in the CloudClassroom PHP Project 1.0. The myds parameter does not properly validate user input, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48941 | MyBB may disclosure unviewable threads&amp;#x27; titles in searches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48941</link><description>MyBB is free and open source forum software. Prior to version 1.8.39, the search component does not validate permissions correctly, which allows attackers to determine the existence of hidden (draft, unapproved, or soft-deleted) threads containing specified text in the title. The visibility state (`mybb_threads.visible` integer column) of threads is not validated in internal search queries, whose result is used to output a general success or failure of the search. While MyBB validates permissions when displaying the final search results, a search operation that internally produces at least one result outputs a redirect response (as a HTTP redirect, or a success message page with delayed redirect, depending on configuration). On the other hand, a search operation that internally produces no results outputs a corresponding message in the response without a redirect. This allows a user to determine whether threads matching title search parameters exist, including draft threads (`visible` with a value of `-2`), soft-deleted threads (`visible` with a value of `-1`), and unapproved threads (`visible` with a value of `0`); in addition to displaying generally visible threads (`visible` with a value of `1`). This vulnerability does not affect other layers of permissions. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the user must have access to the search functionality, and general access to forums containing the thread(s). The vulnerability does not expose the message content of posts. MyBB 1.8.39 resolves this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48940 | MyBB&amp;#x27;s upgrade component vulnerable to local file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48940</link><description>MyBB is free and open source forum software. Prior to version 1.8.39, the upgrade component does not validate user input properly, which allows attackers to perform local file inclusion (LFI) via a specially crafted parameter value. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the installer must be unlocked (no `install/lock` file present) and the upgrade script must be accessible (by re-installing the forum via access to `install/index.php`; when the forum has not yet been installed; or the attacker is authenticated as a forum administrator). MyBB 1.8.39 resolves this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48866 | ModSecurity has possible DoS vulnerability in sanitiseArg action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48866</link><description>ModSecurity is an open source, cross platform web application firewall (WAF) engine for Apache, IIS and Nginx. Versions prior to 2.9.10 contain a denial of service vulnerability similar to GHSA-859r-vvv8-rm8r/CVE-2025-47947. The `sanitiseArg` (and `sanitizeArg` - this is the same action but an alias) is vulnerable to adding an excessive number of arguments, thereby leading to denial of service. Version 2.9.10 fixes the issue. As a workaround, avoid using rules that contain the  `sanitiseArg` (or `sanitizeArg`) action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45542 | SQL injection vulnerability in the registrationform endpoint of CloudClassroom-PHP-Project v1.0. The pass parameter is vulnerable due to imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45542</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the registrationform endpoint of CloudClassroom-PHP-Project v1.0. The pass parameter is vulnerable due to improper input validation, allowing attackers to inject SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44115 | A vulnerability has been found in Cotonti Siena v0.9.25. Affected by this vulnerability is the file /admin.php?m=config&amp;n=edit&amp;o=core&amp;p=titl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44115</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Cotonti Siena v0.9.25. Affected by this vulnerability is the file /admin.php?m=config&amp;amp;n=edit&amp;amp;o=core&amp;amp;p=title. The manipulation of the value of title leads to cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40112 | A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in Sitecom WLX-2006 Wall Mount Range Extender N300 v1.5 and before, which allows an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40112</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in Sitecom WLX-2006 Wall Mount Range Extender N300 v1.5 and before, which allows an attacker to manipulate the "language" cookie to include arbitrary files from the server. This vulnerability can be exploited to disclose sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40113 | Sitecom WLX-2006 Wall Mount Range Extender N300 v.1.5 and before is vulnerable to Use of Default Credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40113</link><description>Sitecom WLX-2006 Wall Mount Range Extender N300 v.1.5 and before is vulnerable to Use of Default Credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40114 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sitecom WLX-2006 Wall Mount Range Extender N300 v1.5 and before allows an attacker to manipula...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40114</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sitecom WLX-2006 Wall Mount Range Extender N300 v1.5 and before allows an attacker to manipulate the language cookie to inject malicious JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44172 | Tenda AC6 V15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the setSmartPowerManagement function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44172</link><description>Tenda AC6 V15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the setSmartPowerManagement function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48877 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the Shared String Table Record Parser implementation in xls2csv utility version 0.95. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48877</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the Shared String Table Record Parser implementation in xls2csv utility version 0.95. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to a heap buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52035 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the OLE Document File Allocation Table Parser functionality of catdoc 0.95. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52035</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the OLE Document File Allocation Table Parser functionality of catdoc 0.95. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54028 | An integer underflow vulnerability exists in the OLE Document DIFAT Parser functionality of catdoc 0.95. A specially crafted malformed file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54028</link><description>An integer underflow vulnerability exists in the OLE Document DIFAT Parser functionality of catdoc 0.95. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20001 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in High-Logic FontCreator 15.0.0.3015. A specially crafted font file can trigger this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20001</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in High-Logic FontCreator 15.0.0.3015. A specially crafted font file can trigger this vulnerability which can lead to disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37096 | A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37096</link><description>A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37095 | A directory traversal information disclosure vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37095</link><description>A directory traversal information disclosure vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37094 | A directory traversal arbitrary file deletion vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37094</link><description>A directory traversal arbitrary file deletion vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37092 | A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37092</link><description>A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37093 | An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37093</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37091 | A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37091</link><description>A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5447 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 ssid1MACFilter os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5447</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function ssid1MACFilter of the file /goform/ssid1MACFilter. The manipulation of the argument apselect_%d/newap_text_%d leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57783 | The desktop application in Dot through 0.9.3 allows XSS and resultant command execution because user input and LLM output are appended to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57783</link><description>The desktop application in Dot through 0.9.3 allows XSS and resultant command execution because user input and LLM output are appended to the DOM with innerHTML (in render.js), and because the Electron window can access Node.js APIs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37089 | A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37089</link><description>A command injection remote code execution vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37090 | A server-side request forgery vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37090</link><description>A server-side request forgery vulnerability exists in HPE StoreOnce Software.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26396 | SolarWinds Dameware Mini Remote Control Service Incorrect Permissions Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26396</link><description>The SolarWinds Dameware Mini Remote Control was determined to be affected by Incorrect Permissions Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability requires local access and a valid low privilege account to be susceptible to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5446 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 RP_checkCredentialsByBBS os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5446</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function RP_checkCredentialsByBBS of the file /goform/RP_checkCredentialsByBBS. The manipulation of the argument pwd leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12168 | DLL Hijacking in Yandex Telemost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12168</link><description>Yandex Telemost for Desktop before 2.7.0 has a DLL Hijacking Vulnerability because an untrusted search path is used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5445 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 RP_checkFWByBBS os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5445</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function RP_checkFWByBBS of the file /goform/RP_checkFWByBBS. The manipulation of the argument type/ch/ssidhex/security/extch/pwd/mode/ip/nm/gw leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 12:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46806 | Misaligned Memory Accesses in `is_openvpn_protocol()`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46806</link><description>A Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset vulnerability in sslh leads to denial of service on some architectures.This issue affects sslh before 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 12:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5444 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 RP_UpgradeFWByBBS os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5444</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RP_UpgradeFWByBBS of the file /goform/RP_UpgradeFWByBBS. The manipulation of the argument type/ch/ssidhex/security/extch/pwd/mode/ip/nm/gw leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 12:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46807 | File Descriptor Exhaustion in sslh-select and sslh-ev triggers SEGFAULT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46807</link><description>A Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in sslh allows attackers to easily exhaust the file descriptors in sslh and deny legitimate users service.This issue affects sslh before 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5443 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 wirelessAdvancedHidden os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5443</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. Affected is the function wirelessAdvancedHidden of the file /goform/wirelessAdvancedHidden. The manipulation of the argument ExtChSelector/24GSelector/5GSelector leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48957 | AstrBot Has Path Traversal Vulnerability in /api/chat/get_file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48957</link><description>AstrBot is a large language model chatbot and development framework. A path traversal vulnerability present in versions 3.4.4 through 3.5.12 may lead to information disclosure, such as API keys for LLM providers, account passwords, and other sensitive data. The vulnerability has been addressed in Pull Request #1676 and is included in version 3.5.13. As a workaround, users can edit the `cmd_config.json` file to disable the dashboard feature as a temporary workaround. However, it is strongly recommended to upgrade to version v3.5.13 or later to fully resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48958 | Froxlor has an HTML Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48958</link><description>Froxlor is open source server administration software. Prior to version 2.2.6, an HTML Injection vulnerability in the customer account portal allows an attacker to inject malicious HTML payloads in the email section. This can lead to phishing attacks, credential theft, and reputational damage by redirecting users to malicious external websites. The vulnerability has a medium severity, as it can be exploited through user input without authentication. Version 2.2.6 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48990 | NeKernel has Heap Overflow in `rt_copy_memory`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48990</link><description>NeKernal is a free and open-source operating system stack. Version 0.0.2 has a 1-byte heap overflow in `rt_copy_memory`, which unconditionally wrote a null terminator at `dst[len]`. When `len` equals the size of the destination buffer (256 bytes), that extra `'\0'` write overruns the buffer by one byte. To avoid breaking existing callers or changing the public API, the patch in commit fb7b7f658327f659c6a6da1af151cb389c2ca4ee takes a minimal approach: it simply removes the overflow-causing line without adding bounds checks or altering the function signature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48495 | Gokapi has stored XSS vulnerability in friendly name for API keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48495</link><description>Gokapi is a self-hosted file sharing server with automatic expiration and encryption support. By renaming the friendly name of an API key, an authenticated user could inject JS into the API key overview, which would also be executed when another user clicks on his API tab. Prior to version 2.0.0, there was no user permission system implemented, therefore all authenticated users were already able to see and modify all resources, even if end-to-end encrypted, as the encryption key had to be the same for all users of versions prior to 2.0.0. If a user is the only authenticated user using Gokapi, they are not affected. This issue has been fixed in v2.0.0. A workaround would be to not open the API page if it is possible that another user might have injected code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48955 | Para Server Logs Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48955</link><description>Para is a multitenant backend server/framework for object persistence and retrieval. A vulnerability that exists in versions prior to 1.50.8 exposes both access and secret keys in logs without redaction. These credentials are later reused in variable assignments for persistence but do not require logging for debugging or system health purposes. Version 1.50.8 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0073 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0073</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r53p0 before r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r53p0 before r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0819 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows access to already freed memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0819</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform valid GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r44p0 through r49p3, from r50p0 through r51p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r44p0 through r49p3, from r50p0 through r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r44p0 through r49p3, from r50p0 through r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1246 | Mali GPU Userspace Driver allows an Out-of-Bounds access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1246</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Userspace Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Userspace Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Userspace Driver allows a non-privileged user process to perform valid GPU processing operations, including via WebGL or WebGPU, to access outside of buffer bounds.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Userspace Driver: from r18p0 through r49p3, from r50p0 through r51p0; Valhall GPU Userspace Driver: from r28p0 through r49p3, from r50p0 through r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Userspace Driver: from r41p0 through r49p3, from r50p0 through r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47289 | Stored XSS in CE Phoenix Cart Testimonials Allows Account Takeover if Missing HttpOnly Flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47289</link><description>CE Phoenix is a free, open-source eCommerce platform. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in CE Phoenix versions 1.0.9.9 through 1.1.0.2 where an attacker can inject malicious JavaScript into the testimonial description field. Once submitted, if the shop owner (admin) approves the testimonial, the script executes in the context of any user visiting the testimonial page. Because the session cookies are not marked with the `HttpOnly` flag, they can be exfiltrated by the attacker — potentially leading to account takeover. Version 1.1.0.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48494 | Gokapi vulnerable to stored XSS via uploading file with malicious file name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48494</link><description>Gokapi is a self-hosted file sharing server with automatic expiration and encryption support. When using end-to-end encryption, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability can be exploited by uploading a file with JavaScript code embedded in the filename. After upload and every time someone opens the upload list, the script is then parsed. Prior to version 2.0.0, there was no user permission system implemented, therefore all authenticated users were already able to see and modify all resources, even if end-to-end encrypted, as the encryption key had to be the same for all users using a version prior to 2.0.0. If a user is the only authenticated user using Gokapi, they are not affected. This issue has been fixed in v2.0.0. A possible workaround would be to disable end-to-end encryption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5442 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 RP_pingGatewayByBBS os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5442</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This issue affects the function RP_pingGatewayByBBS of the file /goform/RP_pingGatewayByBBS. The manipulation of the argument ip/nm/gw leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47272 | PhoenixCart Vulnerable to Account Deletion Without Password Confirmation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47272</link><description>The CE Phoenix eCommerce platform, starting in version 1.0.9.7 and prior to version 1.1.0.3, allowed logged-in users to delete their accounts without requiring password re-authentication. An attacker with temporary access to an authenticated session (e.g., on a shared/public machine) could permanently delete the user’s account without knowledge of the password. This bypass of re-authentication puts users at risk of account loss and data disruption. Version 1.1.0.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29785 | quic-go Has Panic in Path Probe Loss Recovery Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29785</link><description>quic-go is an implementation of the QUIC protocol in Go. The loss recovery logic for path probe packets that was added in the v0.50.0 release can be used to trigger a nil-pointer dereference by a malicious QUIC client. In order to do so, the attacker first sends valid QUIC packets from different remote addresses (thereby triggering the newly added path validation logic: the server sends path probe packets), and then sending ACKs for packets received from the server specifically crafted to trigger the nil-pointer dereference. v0.50.1 contains a patch that fixes the vulnerability. This release contains a test that generates random sequences of sent packets (both regular and path probe packets), that was used to verify that the patch actually covers all corner cases. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3454 | This vulnerability in Grafana's datasource proxy API allows authorization checks to be bypassed by adding an extra slash character in the UR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3454</link><description>This vulnerability in Grafana's datasource proxy API allows authorization checks to be bypassed by adding an extra slash character in the URL path.

Users with minimal permissions could gain unauthorized read access to GET endpoints in Alertmanager and Prometheus datasources.

The issue primarily affects datasources that implement route-specific permissions, including Alertmanager and certain Prometheus-based datasources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5441 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 setDeviceURL os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5441</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This vulnerability affects the function setDeviceURL of the file /goform/setDeviceURL. The manipulation of the argument DeviceURL leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1750 | SQL Injection in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1750</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the delete function of DuckDBVectorStore in run-llama/llama_index version v0.12.19. This vulnerability allows an attacker to manipulate the ref_doc_id parameter, enabling them to read and write arbitrary files on the server, potentially leading to remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3260 | A security vulnerability in the /apis/dashboard.grafana.app/* endpoints allows authenticated users to bypass dashboard and folder permission...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3260</link><description>A security vulnerability in the /apis/dashboard.grafana.app/* endpoints allows authenticated users to bypass dashboard and folder permissions. The vulnerability affects all API versions (v0alpha1, v1alpha1, v2alpha1).

Impact:

- Viewers can view all dashboards/folders regardless of permissions

- Editors can view/edit/delete all dashboards/folders regardless of permissions

- Editors can create dashboards in any folder regardless of permissions

- Anonymous users with viewer/editor roles are similarly affected

Organization isolation boundaries remain intact. The vulnerability only affects dashboard access and does not grant access to datasources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5440 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 NTP os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5440</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function NTP of the file /goform/NTP. The manipulation of the argument manual_year_select/manual_month_select/manual_day_select/manual_hour_select/manual_min_select/manual_sec_select leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5439 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 verifyFacebookLike os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5439</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function verifyFacebookLike of the file /goform/verifyFacebookLike. The manipulation of the argument uid/accessToken leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5438 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 WPS command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5438</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function WPS of the file /goform/WPS. The manipulation of the argument PIN leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 09:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5455 | Possible denial of service when passing malformed data in a URL to qDecodeDataUrl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5455</link><description>An issue was found in the private API function qDecodeDataUrl() in QtCore, which is used in QTextDocument and QNetworkReply, and, potentially, in user code.

If the function was called with malformed data, for example, an URL that
contained a "charset" parameter that lacked a value (such as
"data:charset,"), and Qt was built with assertions enabled, then it would hit an assertion, resulting in a denial of service
(abort).

This impacts Qt up to 5.15.18, 6.0.0-&gt;6.5.8, 6.6.0-&gt;6.8.3 and 6.9.0. This has been fixed in 5.15.19, 6.5.9, 6.8.4 and 6.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5437 | Multilaser Sirius RE016 Password Change cstecgi.cgi improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5437</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Multilaser Sirius RE016 MLT1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5436 | Multilaser Sirius RE016 cstecgi.cgi information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5436</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Multilaser Sirius RE016 MLT1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0324 | The VAPIX Device Configuration framework allowed a privilege escalation, enabling a lower-privileged user to gain administrator privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0324</link><description>The VAPIX Device Configuration framework allowed a privilege escalation, enabling a lower-privileged user to gain administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0325 | A Guard Tour VAPIX API parameter allowed the use of arbitrary values and can be incorrectly called, allowing an attacker to block access to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0325</link><description>A Guard Tour VAPIX API parameter allowed the use of arbitrary values and can be incorrectly called, allowing an attacker to block access to the guard tour configuration page in the web interface of the Axis device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0358 | During an annual penetration test conducted on behalf of Axis Communication, Truesec discovered a flaw in the VAPIX Device Configuration fra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0358</link><description>During an annual penetration test conducted on behalf of Axis Communication, Truesec discovered a flaw in the VAPIX Device Configuration framework that allowed a privilege escalation, enabling a lower-privileged user to gain administrator privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5435 | Marwal Infotech CMS page.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5435</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Marwal Infotech CMS 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /page.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5113 | Authenticated Remote Command Injection in Diviotec NBR IP Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5113</link><description>The Diviotec professional series exposes a web interface. One endpoint is vulnerable to arbitrary command injection and hardcoded passwords are used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4010 | Arbitrary Command Injection in Netcom NTC-6200 &amp;amp; NWL-222</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4010</link><description>The Netcom NTC 6200 and NWL 222 series expose a web interface to be configured and set up by operators. Multiple endpoints of the web interface are vulnerable to arbitrary command injection and use insecure hardcoded passwords. Remote authenticated attackers can gain arbitrary code execution with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5434 | Aem Solutions CMS page.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5434</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Aem Solutions CMS up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /page.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5433 | Fengoffice Feng Office index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fengoffice Feng Office 3.5.1.5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?c=account&amp;amp;a=set_timezone. The manipulation of the argument tz_offset leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1235 | WAGO: Switches affected by year 2k38 problem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1235</link><description>A low privileged attacker can set the date of the devices to the 19th of January 2038 an therefore exceed the 32-Bit time limit. This causes the date of the switch to be set back to January 1st, 1970.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1485 | Real Cookie Banner &amp;lt; 5.1.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1485</link><description>The Real Cookie Banner: GDPR &amp; ePrivacy Cookie Consent WordPress plugin before 5.1.6, real-cookie-banner-pro WordPress plugin before 5.1.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3951 | WP-Optimize &amp;lt; 4.2.0 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3951</link><description>The WP-Optimize  WordPress plugin before 4.2.0 does not properly escape user input when checking image compression statuses, which could allow users with the administrator role to conduct SQL Injection attacks in the context of Multi-Site WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5432 | AssamLook CMS view_tender.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5432</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in AssamLook CMS 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view_tender.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5431 | AssamLook CMS department-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5431</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in AssamLook CMS 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /department-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 05:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5430 | AssamLook CMS product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5430</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in AssamLook CMS 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /product.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 05:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49113 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.10 and 1.6.x before 1.6.11 allows remote code execution by authenticated users because the _from parameter in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49113</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.10 and 1.6.x before 1.6.11 allows remote code execution by authenticated users because the _from parameter in a URL is not validated in program/actions/settings/upload.php, leading to PHP Object Deserialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5429 | juzaweb CMS Plugins Page install access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5429</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin-cp/plugin/install of the component Plugins Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25179 | GPU DDK - Freelist GPU VA can be remapped to another reservation/PMR to trigger GPU arbitrary write to physical memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25179</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to subvert GPU HW to write to arbitrary physical memory pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49112 | setDeferredReply in networking.c in Valkey through 8.1.1 has an integer underflow for prev-&gt;size - prev-&gt;used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49112</link><description>setDeferredReply in networking.c in Valkey through 8.1.1 has an integer underflow for prev-&gt;size - prev-&gt;used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5428 | juzaweb CMS Error Logs Page log-viewer access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5428</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin-cp/log-viewer of the component Error Logs Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11857 | Realtek Bluetooth HCI Adaptor - Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11857</link><description>Bluetooth HCI Adaptor from Realtek has a Link Following vulnerability. Local attackers with regular privileges can create a symbolic link with the same name as a specific file, causing the product to delete arbitrary files pointed to by the link. Subsequently, attackers can leverage arbitrary file deletion to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5427 | juzaweb CMS Permalinks Page permalinks access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5427</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/permalinks of the component Permalinks Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20672 | In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20672</link><description>In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00412257; Issue ID: MSV-3292.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20673 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20673</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00413200; Issue ID: MSV-3304.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20674 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible way to inject arbitrary packet due to a missing permission check. This could lead to remote escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20674</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible way to inject arbitrary packet due to a missing permission check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00413202; Issue ID: MSV-3303.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20675 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20675</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00413201; Issue ID: MSV-3302.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20676 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20676</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00412240; Issue ID: MSV-3293.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20677 | In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20677</link><description>In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00412256; Issue ID: MSV-3284.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20678 | In ims service, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20678</link><description>In ims service, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01394606; Issue ID: MSV-2739.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5425 | juzaweb CMS Theme Editor Page default access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5425</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-cp/theme/editor/default of the component Theme Editor Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5426 | juzaweb CMS Menu Page menus access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5426</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/menus of the component Menu Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5424 | juzaweb CMS Media Page media access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5424</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin-cp/media of the component Media Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5423 | juzaweb CMS General Setting Page general access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5423</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin-cp/setting/system/general of the component General Setting Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5422 | juzaweb CMS Email Logs Page email access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5422</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin-cp/logs/email of the component Email Logs Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 01:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5421 | juzaweb CMS Plugin Editor Page editor access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5421</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/plugin/editor of the component Plugin Editor Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 01:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5420 | juzaweb CMS Profile Page upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5420</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/file-manager/upload of the component Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument Upload leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 01:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>