<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-2658 | Local privilege escalation in FlexNet Publisher</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2658</link><description>A misconfiguration in lmadmin.exe of FlexNet Publisher versions prior to 2024 R1 (11.19.6.0) allows the OpenSSL configuration file to load from a non-existent directory. An unauthorized, locally authenticated user with low privileges can potentially create the directory and load a specially crafted openssl.conf file leading to the execution of a malicious DLL (Dynamic-Link Library) with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0367 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in Splunk Supporting Add-on for Active Directory (SA-ldapsearch)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0367</link><description>In versions 3.1.0 and lower of the Splunk Supporting Add-on for Active Directory, also known as SA-ldapsearch, a vulnerable regular expression pattern could lead to a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0873 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System customeredit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0873</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /customeredit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/address/fullname/phonenumber/email/city/comment leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24099 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24099</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0872 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System addpayment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0872</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addpayment.php. The manipulation of the argument id/amount/desc/inccat leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24883 | go-ethereum has a DoS via malicious p2p message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24883</link><description>go-ethereum (geth) is a golang execution layer implementation of the Ethereum protocol. A vulnerable node can be forced to shutdown/crash using a specially crafted message. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.14.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24376 | The kubewarden-controller AdmissionPolicy and AdmissionPolicyGroup policies can be used to alter PolicyReport resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24376</link><description>kubewarden-controller is a Kubernetes controller that allows you to dynamically register Kubewarden admission policies. By design, AdmissionPolicy and AdmissionPolicyGroup can evaluate only namespaced resources. The resources to be evaluated are determined by the rules provided by the user when defining the policy. There might be Kubernetes namespaced resources that should not be validated by AdmissionPolicy and by the AdmissionPolicyGroup policies because of their sensitive nature. For example, PolicyReport are namespaced resources that contain the list of non compliant objects found inside of a namespace. An attacker can use either an AdmissionPolicy or an AdmissionPolicyGroup to prevent the creation and update of PolicyReport objects to hide non-compliant resources. Moreover, the same attacker might use a mutating AdmissionPolicy to alter the contents of the PolicyReport created inside of the namespace. Starting from the 1.21.0 release, the validation rules applied to AdmissionPolicy and AdmissionPolicyGroup have been tightened to prevent them from validating sensitive types of namespaced resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24784 | kubewarden-controller has an Information leak via AdmissionPolicyGroup Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24784</link><description>kubewarden-controller is a Kubernetes controller that allows you to dynamically register Kubewarden admission policies. The policy group feature, added to by the 1.17.0 release. By being namespaced, the AdmissionPolicyGroup has a well constrained impact on cluster resources. Hence, it’s considered safe to allow non-admin users to create and manage these resources in the namespaces they own. Kubewarden policies can be allowed to query the Kubernetes API at evaluation time; these types of policies are called “context aware“. Context aware policies can perform list and get operations against a Kubernetes cluster. The queries are done using the ServiceAccount of the Policy Server instance that hosts the policy. That means that access to the cluster is determined by the RBAC rules that apply to that ServiceAccount. The AdmissionPolicyGroup CRD allowed the deployment of context aware policies. This could allow an attacker to obtain information about resources that are out of their reach, by leveraging a higher access to the cluster granted to the ServiceAccount token used to run the policy. The impact of this vulnerability depends on the privileges that have been granted to the ServiceAccount used to run the Policy Server and assumes that users are using the recommended best practices of keeping the Policy Server's ServiceAccount least privileged. By default, the Kubewarden helm chart grants access to the following resources (cluster wide) only: Namespace, Pod, Deployment and Ingress. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.21.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22219 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2025-22219)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22219</link><description>VMware Aria Operations for Logs contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges may be able to inject a malicious script that  (can perform stored cross-site scripting) may lead to arbitrary operations as admin user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22220 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs broken access control vulnerability (CVE-2025-22220)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22220</link><description>VMware Aria Operations for Logs contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges and network access to Aria Operations for Logs API may be able to perform certain operations in the context of an admin user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22221 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2025-22221)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22221</link><description>VMware Aria Operation for Logs contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges to VMware Aria Operations for Logs may be able to inject a malicious script that could be executed in a victim's browser when performing a delete action in the Agent Configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22222 | VMware Aria Operations information disclosure vulnerability (CVE-2025-22222)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22222</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious user with non-administrative privileges may exploit this vulnerability to retrieve credentials for an outbound plugin if a valid service credential ID is known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23216 | Argo CD does not scrub secret values from patch errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23216</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. A vulnerability was discovered in Argo CD that exposed secret values in error messages and the diff view when an invalid Kubernetes Secret resource was synced from a repository. The vulnerability assumes the user has write access to the repository and can exploit it, either intentionally or unintentionally, by committing an invalid Secret to repository and triggering a Sync. Once exploited, any user with read access to Argo CD can view the exposed secret data. The vulnerability is fixed in v2.13.4, v2.12.10, and v2.11.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53615 | A command injection vulnerability in the video thumbnail rendering component of Karl Ward's files.gallery v0.3.0 through 0.11.0 allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53615</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the video thumbnail rendering component of Karl Ward's files.gallery v0.3.0 through 0.11.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted video file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55415 | DevDojo Voyager through 1.8.0 is vulnerable to path traversal at the /admin/compass.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55415</link><description>DevDojo Voyager through 1.8.0 is vulnerable to path traversal at the /admin/compass.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55416 | DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to reflected XSS via /admin/compass. By manipulating an authenticated user to click on a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55416</link><description>DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to reflected XSS via /admin/compass. By manipulating an authenticated user to click on a link, arbitrary Javascript can be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55417 | DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to bypassing the file type verification when an authenticated user uploads a file via /a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55417</link><description>DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to bypassing the file type verification when an authenticated user uploads a file via /admin/media/upload. An authenticated user can upload a web shell causing arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0871 | Maybecms Add Article index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0871</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Maybecms 1.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /mb/admin/index.php?u=article-edit of the component Add Article. The manipulation of the argument data_info[content] leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23367 | Org.wildfly.core:wildfly-server: wildfly improper rbac permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23367</link><description>A flaw was found in the Wildfly Server Role Based Access Control (RBAC) provider. When authorization to control management operations is secured using the Role Based Access Control provider, a user without the required privileges can suspend or resume the server. A user with a Monitor or Auditor role is supposed to have only read access permissions and should not be able to suspend the server. 
The vulnerability is caused by the Suspend and Resume handlers not performing authorization checks to validate whether the current user has the required permissions to proceed with the action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22218 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22218</link><description>VMware Aria Operations for Logs contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with View Only Admin permissions may be able to read the credentials of a VMware product integrated with VMware Aria Operations for Logs</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10591 | MWB HubSpot for WooCommerce – CRM, Abandoned Cart, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10591</link><description>The MWB HubSpot for WooCommerce – CRM, Abandoned Cart, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation &amp; Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the hubwoo_save_updates() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10847 | Storely &amp;lt;= 16.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10847</link><description>The Storely theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a malicious display name in all versions up to, and including, 16.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11583 | Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Missing Authorization to Icon Font Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11583</link><description>The Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'remove_zipped_font' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete icon fonts that were previously uploaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11600 | Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11600</link><description>The Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9 via the 'write_config' function. This is due to a lack of sanitization on an imported JSON file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12102 | Typer Core &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12102</link><description>The Typer Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.6 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12129 | Royal Core &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12129</link><description>The Royal Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'royal_restore_backup' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12177 | Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12177</link><description>The Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12269 | Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.17 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Database Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12269</link><description>The Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_db() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.17. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve a complete dump of the site's database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12299 | System Dashboard &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Filename Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12299</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the Filename parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick an administrative user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12320 | Team Rosters &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;tab&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12320</link><description>The Team Rosters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tab’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12444 | WP Dispensary &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12444</link><description>The WP Dispensary plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpd_menu' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12451 | HTML5 chat &amp;lt;= 1.04 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12451</link><description>The HTML5 chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'HTML5CHAT' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.04 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12821 | Media Manager for UserPro &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12821</link><description>The Media Manager for UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the upm_upload_media() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12822 | Media Manager for UserPro &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12822</link><description>The Media Manager for UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the add_capto_img() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12861 | W2S – Migrate WooCommerce to Shopify &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12861</link><description>The W2S – Migrate WooCommerce to Shopify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 via the 'viw2s_view_log' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13349 | Stockdio Historical Chart &amp;lt;= 2.8.18 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13349</link><description>The Stockdio Historical Chart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'stockdio-historical-chart' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13400 | Kona Gallery Block &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13400</link><description>The Kona Gallery Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the "Kona: Instagram for Gutenberg" Block, specifically in the "align" attribute, in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13460 | WE – Testimonial Slider &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13460</link><description>The WE – Testimonial Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Testimonial Author Names in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13512 | Wonder FontAwesome &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13512</link><description>The Wonder FontAwesome plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on one of its functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13549 | All Bootstrap Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.3.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13549</link><description>The All Bootstrap Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the "Accordion" widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13596 | WordPress Survey &amp;amp; Poll – Quiz, Survey and Poll Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13596</link><description>The WordPress Survey &amp; Poll – Quiz, Survey and Poll Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' attribute of the 'survey' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13646 | Single-user-chat &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13646</link><description>The Single-user-chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to insufficient validation on the 'single_user_chat_update_login' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'login' on the WordPress site. This may be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13652 | ECPay Ecommerce for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.2411060 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13652</link><description>The ECPay Ecommerce for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'clear_ecpay_debug_log' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2411060. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear the plugin's log files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13661 | Table Editor &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13661</link><description>The Table Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wptableeditor_vtabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13664 | WP Post List Table &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13664</link><description>The WP Post List Table plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpb_post_list_table' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13670 | Music Sheet Viewer &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13670</link><description>The Music Sheet Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'pn_msv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13671 | Music Sheet Viewer &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13671</link><description>The Music Sheet Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 via the read_score_file() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13700 | Embed Swagger UI &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13700</link><description>The Embed Swagger UI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpsgui' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13705 | StageShow &amp;lt;= 9.8.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13705</link><description>The StageShow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 9.8.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13707 | WP Image Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13707</link><description>The WP Image Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the gky_image_uploader_main_function() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13715 | zStore Manager Basic &amp;lt;= 3.311 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Cache Clearing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13715</link><description>The zStore Manager Basic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the zstore_clear_cache() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.311. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear the plugin's cache.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13720 | WP Image Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13720</link><description>The WP Image Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the gky_image_uploader_main_function() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13742 | iControlWP – Multiple WordPress Site Manager &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13742</link><description>The iControlWP – Multiple WordPress Site Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via deserialization of untrusted input from the reqpars parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8494 | Elementor Website Builder Pro – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.25.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8494</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.10 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the content of Private, Pending, and Draft Templates. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 3.24.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0869 | Cianet ONU GW24AC Login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0869</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Cianet ONU GW24AC up to 20250127. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument browserLang leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0870 | Axiomatic Bento4 Ap4DataBuffer.h GetData heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0870</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4 up to 1.6.0-641. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function AP4_DataBuffer::GetData in the library Ap4DataBuffer.h. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13380 | Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13380</link><description>The Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rr_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13466 | Automatically Hierarchic Categories in Menu &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13466</link><description>The Automatically Hierarchic Categories in Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'autocategorymenu' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43916 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container improper communications restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43916</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container 7.1, 7.2, 8.0, 8.1, 8.2, 9.0, 9.1, 9.2, 10.0, 10.1, 11.0, 11.1, 11.2, 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, 11.6, 12.0, 12.1, 12.2, 12.3, 12.4, 12.5, 12.6, and 12.7 Pods do not restrict network egress for Pods that are used for internal infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0742 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0742</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to obtain files stored by others users by changing the "FILE_ID" of the endpoint "/embedai/files/show/".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0743 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0743</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to leverage the endpoint "/embedai/visits/show/" to obtain information about the visits made by other users. The information provided by this endpoint includes IP address, userAgent and location of the user that visited the web page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0744 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0744</link><description>an Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker change his subscription plan without paying by making a POST request changing the parameters of the "/demos/embedai/pmt_cash_on_delivery/pay" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0745 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0745</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to obtain the backups of the database by requesting the "/embedai/app/uploads/database/" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0746 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0746</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to craft a malicious URL leveraging the"/embedai/users/show/</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0747 | Stored Cross-Site vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0747</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to inject a malicious JavaScript code into a message that will be executed when a user opens the chat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12409 | Simple:Press Forum &amp;lt;= 6.10.11 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12409</link><description>The Simple:Press Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.10.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12524 | Clinked Client Portal &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12524</link><description>The Clinked Client Portal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'clinked-login-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13453 | Contact Form &amp;amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13453</link><description>The The Contact Form &amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13706 | WP Image Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13706</link><description>The WP Image Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'file' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0739 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0739</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to show subscription's information of others users by changing the "SUSCBRIPTION_ID" param of the endpoint "/demos/embedai/subscriptions/show/".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0740 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0740</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI

 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to obtain chat messages belonging to other users by changing the “CHAT_ID” of the endpoint "/embedai/chats/load_messages?chat_id=".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0741 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0741</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI

 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to write messages into other users chat by changing the parameter "chat_id" of the POST request "/embedai/chats/send_message".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23007 | A vulnerability in the NetExtender Windows client log export function allows unauthorized access to sensitive Windows system files, potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23007</link><description>A vulnerability in the NetExtender Windows client log export function allows unauthorized access to sensitive Windows system files, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0860 | VR-Frases (collect &amp;amp; share quotes) &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0860</link><description>The VR-Frases (collect &amp; share quotes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0861 | VR-Frases (collect &amp;amp; share quotes) &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0861</link><description>The VR-Frases (collect &amp; share quotes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21107 | Dell NetWorker, version(s) prior to 19.11.0.3, all versions of 19.10 &amp; prior versions contain(s) an Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21107</link><description>Dell NetWorker, version(s) prior to 19.11.0.3, all versions of 19.10 &amp; prior versions contain(s) an Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0834 | Wondershare Dr.Fone Privilege Scalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0834</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability has been found in Wondershare Dr.Fone version 13.5.21. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to escalate privileges by replacing the binary ‘C:\ProgramData\Wondershare\wsServices\ElevationService.exe’ with a malicious binary. This binary will be executed by SYSTEM automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13694 | WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Unauthenticated Wishlist Disclosure via download_pdf_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13694</link><description>The WooCommerce Wishlist (High customization, fast setup,Free Elementor Wishlist, most features) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7 via the download_pdf_file() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from wishlists that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 08:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13732 | Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via section_tag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13732</link><description>The Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘section_tag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 08:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13758 | CP Contact Form with PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.3.52 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13758</link><description>The CP Contact Form with PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.52. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cp_contact_form_paypal_check_init_actions() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add discount codes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 08:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13470 | Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You &amp;lt;= 3.8.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13470</link><description>The Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 07:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13457 | Event Tickets &amp;lt;= 5.18.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13457</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.18.1 via the tc-order-id parameter due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view order details of orders they did not place, which includes ticket prices, user emails and order date.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13642 | Stratum – Elementor Widgets &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability via Image Hotspot Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13642</link><description>The Stratum – Elementor Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Hotspot widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10309 | Tracking Code Manager &amp;lt; 2.4.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10309</link><description>The Tracking Code Manager WordPress plugin before 2.4.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its metabox settings when outputing them in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as Contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12163 | GoodLayers Core &amp;lt; 2.1.3 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12163</link><description>The goodlayers-core WordPress plugin before 2.1.3 allows users with a subscriber role and above to upload SVGs containing malicious payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12400 | Tourmaster &amp;lt; 5.3.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12400</link><description>The tourmaster WordPress plugin before 5.3.5 does not escape generated URLs before outputting them in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12638 | Bulk Me Now &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12638</link><description>The Bulk Me Now! WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12708 | Bulk Me Now &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12708</link><description>The Bulk Me Now! WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12709 | Bulk Me Now &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Message Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12709</link><description>The Bulk Me Now! WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12921 | EthereumICO &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ethereum-ico Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12921</link><description>The EthereumICO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ethereum-ico shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 05:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0373 | Buffer overflow in some filesystems via NFS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0373</link><description>On 64-bit systems, the implementation of VOP_VPTOFH() in the cd9660, tarfs and ext2fs filesystems overflows the destination FID buffer by 4 bytes, a stack buffer overflow.

A NFS server that exports a cd9660, tarfs, or ext2fs file system can be made to panic by mounting and accessing the export with an NFS client.  Further exploitation (e.g., bypassing file permission checking or remote kernel code execution) is potentially possible, though this has not been demonstrated.  In particular, release kernels are compiled with stack protection enabled, and some instances of the overflow are caught by this mechanism, causing a panic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0374 | Unprivileged access to system files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0374</link><description>When etcupdate encounters conflicts while merging files, it saves a version containing conflict markers in /var/db/etcupdate/conflicts.  This version does not preserve the mode of the input file, and is world-readable.  This applies to files that would normally have restricted visibility, such as /etc/master.passwd.

An unprivileged local user may be able to read encrypted root and user passwords from the temporary master.passwd file created in /var/db/etcupdate/conflicts.  This is possible only when conflicts within the password file arise during an update, and the unprotected file is deleted when conflicts are resolved.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0662 | Uninitialized kernel memory disclosure via ktrace(2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0662</link><description>In some cases, the ktrace facility will log the contents of kernel structures to userspace.  In one such case, ktrace dumps a variable-sized sockaddr to userspace.  There, the full sockaddr is copied, even when it is shorter than the full size.  This can result in up to 14 uninitialized bytes of kernel memory being copied out to userspace.

It is possible for an unprivileged userspace program to leak 14 bytes of a kernel heap allocation to userspace.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23374 | Dell Networking Switches running Enterprise SONiC OS, version(s) prior to 4.4.1 and 4.2.3, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23374</link><description>Dell Networking Switches running Enterprise SONiC OS, version(s) prior to 4.4.1 and 4.2.3, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0847 | 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0847</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0848 | Tenda A18 HTTP POST Request SetCmdlineRun stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0848</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A18 up to 15.13.07.09. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function SetCmdlineRun of the file /goform/SetCmdlineRun of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0849 | CampCodes School Management Software Staff edit-staff improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0849</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit-staff/ of the component Staff Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0846 | 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System AdminLogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0846</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/AdminLogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0844 | needyamin Library Card System Registration Page signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0844</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file signup.php of the component Registration Page. The manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/email/borrow/user_address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 23:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21396 | Microsoft Account Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21396</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 23:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0843 | needyamin Library Card System Admin Panel admindashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file admindashboard.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 23:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21415 | Azure AI Face Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21415</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57665 | JFinalCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rc/main/java/com/cms/entity/Content.java. The cause of the vulnerability is that the title p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57665</link><description>JFinalCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rc/main/java/com/cms/entity/Content.java. The cause of the vulnerability is that the title parameter is controllable and is concatenated directly into filterSql without filtering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51182 | HTML Injection vulnerability in Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 allows a remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTML code via the "erro" p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51182</link><description>HTML Injection vulnerability in Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 allows a remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTML code via the "erro" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48761 | The specific component in Celk Saude 3.1.252.1 that processes user input and returns error messages to the client is vulnerable due to impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48761</link><description>The specific component in Celk Saude 3.1.252.1 that processes user input and returns error messages to the client is vulnerable due to improper validation or sanitization of the "erro" parameter. This parameter appears as a response when incorrect credentials are entered during login. The lack of proper validation or sanitization makes the component susceptible to injection attacks, potentially allowing attackers to manipulate the input and exploit the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11187 | Many records in the additional section cause CPU exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11187</link><description>It is possible to construct a zone such that some queries to it will generate responses containing numerous records in the Additional section. An attacker sending many such queries can cause either the authoritative server itself or an independent resolver to use disproportionate resources processing the queries. Zones will usually need to have been deliberately crafted to attack this exposure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.32, 9.20.0 through 9.20.4, 9.21.0 through 9.21.3, 9.11.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.32-S1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12705 | DNS-over-HTTPS implementation suffers from multiple issues under heavy query load</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12705</link><description>Clients using DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH) can exhaust a DNS resolver's CPU and/or memory by flooding it with crafted valid or invalid HTTP/2 traffic.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.0 through 9.18.32, 9.20.0 through 9.20.4, 9.21.0 through 9.21.3, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.32-S1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54851 | Teedy &lt;= 1.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF), due to the lack of CSRF protection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54851</link><description>Teedy &lt;= 1.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF), due to the lack of CSRF protection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54852 | When LDAP connection is activated in Teedy versions between 1.9 to 1.12, the username field of the login form is vulnerable to LDAP injectio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54852</link><description>When LDAP connection is activated in Teedy versions between 1.9 to 1.12, the username field of the login form is vulnerable to LDAP injection. Due to improper sanitization of user input, an unauthenticated attacker is then able to perform various malicious actions, such as creating arbitrary accounts and spraying passwords.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0842 | needyamin Library Card System Login admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0842</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23733 | The /WmAdmin/,/invoke/vm.server/login login page in the Integration Server in Software AG webMethods 10.15.0 before Core_Fix7 allows remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23733</link><description>The /WmAdmin/,/invoke/vm.server/login login page in the Integration Server in Software AG webMethods 10.15.0 before Core_Fix7 allows remote attackers to reach the administration panel and discover hostname and version information by sending an arbitrary username and a blank password to the /WmAdmin/#/login/ URI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57395 | Password Vulnerability in Safety production process management system v1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges, execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57395</link><description>Password Vulnerability in Safety production process management system v1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the password and account number parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57509 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57509</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_File::ParseStream and related functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57510 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57510</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_MemoryByteStream::WritePartial.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57513 | A floating-point exception (FPE) vulnerability exists in the AP4_TfraAtom::AP4_TfraAtom function in Bento4.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57513</link><description>A floating-point exception (FPE) vulnerability exists in the AP4_TfraAtom::AP4_TfraAtom function in Bento4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0851 | Path traversal issue in Deep Java Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0851</link><description>A path traversal issue in ZipUtils.unzip and TarUtils.untar in Deep Java Library (DJL) on all platforms allows a bad actor to write files to arbitrary locations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0841 | Aridius XYZ News loadMore deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0841</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Aridius XYZ up to 20240927 on OpenCart and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function loadMore of the component News. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24795 | The Snowflake Connector for Python uses insecure cache files permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24795</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for Python. On Linux systems, when temporary credential caching is enabled, the Snowflake Connector for Python will cache temporary credentials locally in a world-readable file. This vulnerability affects versions 2.3.7 through 3.13.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24788 | Snowflake Connector for .NET has weak temporary files permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24788</link><description>snowflake-connector-net is the Snowflake Connector for .NET. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for .NET in which files downloaded from stages are temporarily placed in a world-readable local directory, making them accessible to unauthorized users on the same machine. This vulnerability affects versions 2.0.12 through 4.2.0 on Linux and macOS. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24793 | Snowflake Connector for Python has an SQL Injection in write_pandas</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24793</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for Python. A function from the snowflake.connector.pandas_tools module is vulnerable to SQL injection. This vulnerability affects versions 2.2.5 through 3.13.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24794 | The Snowflake Connector for Python uses insecure deserialization of the OCSP response cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24794</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for Python. The OCSP response cache uses pickle as the serialization format, potentially leading to local privilege escalation. This vulnerability affects versions 2.7.12 through 3.13.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24884 | kube-audit-rest&amp;#x27;s example logging configuration could disclose secret values in the audit log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24884</link><description>kube-audit-rest is a simple logger of mutation/creation requests to the k8s api. If the "full-elastic-stack" example vector configuration was used for a real cluster, the previous values of kubernetes secrets would have been disclosed in the audit messages. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0840 | GNU Binutils objdump.c disassemble_bytes stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0840</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GNU Binutils up to 2.43. This affects the function disassemble_bytes of the file binutils/objdump.c. The manipulation of the argument buf leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.44 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is baac6c221e9d69335bf41366a1c7d87d8ab2f893. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20061 | mySCADA myPRO Manager OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20061</link><description>mySCADA myPRO does not properly neutralize POST requests sent to a specific port with email information. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20014 | mySCADA myPRO Manager OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20014</link><description>mySCADA myPRO does not properly neutralize POST requests sent to a specific port with version information. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48852 | Information disclosures</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48852</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability observed in FLEXON. Some information may be improperly disclosed through https access.
 

This issue affects FLXEON through &lt;= 9.3.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10001 | Code Injection Vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server Allows Arbitrary Code Execution via Message Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10001</link><description>A Code Injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed attackers to inject malicious code into the query selector via the identity property in the message handling function. This enabled the exfiltration of sensitive data by manipulating the DOM, including authentication tokens. To execute the attack, the victim must be logged into GitHub and interact with the attacker controlled malicious webpage containing the hidden iframe. This vulnerability occurs due to an improper sequence of validation, where the origin check occurs after accepting the user-controlled identity property. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.11.16, 3.12.10, 3.13.5, 3.14.2, and 3.15.0. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48849 | Authentication and Authorization Issues</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48849</link><description>Missing Origin Validation in WebSockets vulnerability in FLXEON. Session management was not sufficient to prevent unauthorized HTTPS requests. This issue affects FLXEON: through &lt;= 9.3.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24790 | Snowflake JDBC uses insecure temporary credential cache file permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24790</link><description>Snowflake JDBC provides a JDBC type 4 driver that supports core functionality, allowing Java program to connect to Snowflake. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake JDBC Driver. On Linux systems, when temporary credential caching is enabled, the Snowflake JDBC Driver will cache temporary credentials locally in a world-readable file. This vulnerability affects versions 3.6.8 through 3.21.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24789 | Snowflake JDBC allows an untrusted search path on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24789</link><description>Snowflake JDBC provides a JDBC type 4 driver that supports core functionality, allowing Java program to connect to Snowflake. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake JDBC Driver. When the EXTERNALBROWSER authentication method is used on Windows, an attacker with write access to a directory in the %PATH% can escalate their privileges to the user that runs the vulnerable JDBC Driver version. This vulnerability affects versions 3.2.3 through 3.21.0 on Windows. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24882 | regclient may ignore pinned manifest digests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24882</link><description>regclient is a Docker and OCI Registry Client in Go. A malicious registry could return a different digest for a pinned manifest without detection. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24791 | snowflake-connector-nodejs has incorrect validation of temporary credential cache file permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24791</link><description>snowflake-connector-nodejs is a NodeJS driver for Snowflake. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake NodeJS Driver. File permissions checks of the temporary credential cache could be bypassed by an attacker with write access to the local cache directory. This vulnerability affects versions 1.12.0 through 2.0.1 on Linux. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35907 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35907</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37398 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37398</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37412 | IBM Aspera Faspex improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37412</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 could allow a privileged user to make system changes without proper access controls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37413 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37413</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 could disclose sensitive username information due to an observable response discrepancy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24527 | An issue was discovered in Akamai Enterprise Application Access (EAA) before 2025-01-17. If an admin knows another tenant's 128-bit connecto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24527</link><description>An issue was discovered in Akamai Enterprise Application Access (EAA) before 2025-01-17. If an admin knows another tenant's 128-bit connector GUID, they can execute debug commands on that connector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24374 | Twig fixes a security issue where escaping was missing when using null coalesce operator (??)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24374</link><description>Twig is a template language for PHP. When using the ?? operator, output escaping was missing for the expression on the left side of the operator. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.19.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24792 | Snowflake PHP PDO Driver has a Signed-to-Unsigned Conversion Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24792</link><description>Snowflake PHP PDO Driver is a driver that uses the PHP Data Objects (PDO) extension to connect to the Snowflake database. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake PHP PDO Driver where executing unsupported queries like PUT or GET on stages causes a signed-to-unsigned conversion error that crashes the application using the Driver. This vulnerability affects versions 0.2.0 through 3.0.3. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 15:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57436 | RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to allow unauthorized attackers to view the session ID of the admin in the system monitoring. This issue can all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57436</link><description>RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to allow unauthorized attackers to view the session ID of the admin in the system monitoring. This issue can allow attackers to impersonate Admin users via using a crafted cookie.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57437 | RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderby parameter at /monitor/online/list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57437</link><description>RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderby parameter at /monitor/online/list.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57438 | Insecure permissions in RuoYi v4.8.0 allows authenticated attackers to escalate privileges by assigning themselves higher level roles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57438</link><description>Insecure permissions in RuoYi v4.8.0 allows authenticated attackers to escalate privileges by assigning themselves higher level roles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57439 | An issue in the reset password interface of ruoyi v4.8.0 allows attackers with Admin privileges to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by duplic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57439</link><description>An issue in the reset password interface of ruoyi v4.8.0 allows attackers with Admin privileges to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by duplicating the login name of the account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54461 | Unsanitized Filenames in Flutter package file_selector_android Allow File Overwrites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54461</link><description>The file names constructed within file_selector are missing sanitization checks leaving them vulnerable to malicious document providers. This may result in cases where a user with a malicious document provider installed can select a document file from that provider while using your app and could potentially override internal files in your app cache. Issue patched in 0.5.1+12. It is recommended to update to the latest version of file_selector_android that contains the changes to address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54462 | Unsanitized Filenames in Flutter package image_picker_android Allow File Overwrites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54462</link><description>The file names constructed within image_picker are missing sanitization checks leaving them vulnerable to malicious document providers. This may result in cases where a user with a malicious document provider installed can select an image file from that provider while using your app and could potentially override internal files in your app cache. Issue patched in 0.8.12+18. It is recommended to update to the latest version of image_picker_android that contains the changes to address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13561 | Target Video Easy Publish &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via brid_override_yt Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13561</link><description>The Target Video Easy Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's brid_override_yt shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41140 | Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41140</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 174000 and prior are vulnerable to the incorrect authorization in the update user function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0353 | Divi Torque Lite &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0353</link><description>The Divi Torque Lite – Best Divi Addon, Extensions, Modules &amp; Social Modules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0762 | Use after free in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0762</link><description>Use after free in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0617 | An attacker with access to an HX 10.0.0  and previous versions, may send specially-crafted data to the HX console.  The malicious detection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0617</link><description>An attacker with access to an HX 10.0.0  and previous versions, may send specially-crafted data to the HX console.  The malicious detection would then trigger file parsing containing exponential entity expansions in the consumer process thus causing a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-3978 | Improper Preservation of Permissions in github.com/cloudflare/cfrpki/cmd/octorpki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3978</link><description>When copying files with rsync, octorpki uses the "-a" flag 0, which forces rsync to copy binaries with the suid bit set as root. Since the provided service definition defaults to root ( https://github.com/cloudflare/cfrpki/blob/master/package/octorpki.service ) this could allow for a vector, when combined with another vulnerability that causes octorpki to process a malicious TAL file, for a local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57965 | In axios before 1.7.8, lib/helpers/isURLSameOrigin.js does not use a URL object when determining an origin, and has a potentially unwanted s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57965</link><description>In axios before 1.7.8, lib/helpers/isURLSameOrigin.js does not use a URL object when determining an origin, and has a potentially unwanted setAttribute('href',href) call. NOTE: some parties feel that the code change only addresses a warning message from a SAST tool and does not fix a vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 09:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7695 | Out-of-bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7695</link><description>Multiple switches are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. This vulnerability is caused by insufficient input validation, which allows data to be written to memory outside the bounds of the buffer. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could result in a denial-of-service attack. 

This vulnerability poses a significant remote threat if the affected products are exposed to publicly accessible networks. Attackers could potentially disrupt operations by shutting down the affected systems. Due to the critical nature of this security risk, we strongly recommend taking immediate action to prevent its potential exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 07:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13696 | Flexible Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.25 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wishlist_name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13696</link><description>The Flexible Wishlist for WooCommerce – Ecommerce Wishlist &amp; Save for later plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wishlist_name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.25 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 07:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12749 | Competition Form &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12749</link><description>The Competition Form WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 06:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0804 | ClickWhale – Link Manager, Link Shortener and Click Tracker for Affiliate Links &amp;amp; Link Pages &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0804</link><description>The ClickWhale – Link Manager, Link Shortener and Click Tracker for Affiliate Links &amp; Link Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via link titles in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 03:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0806 | code-projects Job Recruitment _call_job_search_ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0806</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file _call_job_search_ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument job_type leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0798 | MicroWorld eScan Antivirus Quarantine rtscanner os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0798</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroWorld eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file rtscanner of the component Quarantine Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0800 | SourceCodester Online Courseware Edit Teacher saveeditt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0800</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pcci/admin/saveeditt.php of the component Edit Teacher. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0802 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Administrative Endpoint View_user.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0802</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/View_user.php of the component Administrative Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0803 | Codezips Gym Management System submit_plan_new.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0803</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/admin/submit_plan_new.php. The manipulation of the argument planid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23362 | The old versions of EXIF Viewer Classic contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability caused by improper handling of EXIF meta data. When an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23362</link><description>The old versions of EXIF Viewer Classic contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability caused by improper handling of EXIF meta data. When an image is rendered and crafted EXIF meta data is processed, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser. Versions 2.3.2 and 2.4.0 were reported as vulnerable. According to the vendor, the product has been refactored after those old versions and the version 3.0.1 is not vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33838 | IBM Security Verify Governance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33838</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 Identity Manager 

uses a one-way cryptographic hash against an input that should not be reversible, such as a password, but the product does not also use a salt as part of the input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0795 | ESAFENET CDG todolistjump.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0795</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /todolistjump.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0797 | MicroWorld eScan Antivirus Quarantine Microworld default permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroWorld eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /var/Microworld/ of the component Quarantine Handler. The manipulation leads to incorrect default permissions. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0793 | ESAFENET CDG todoDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0793</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG V5 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /todoDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0794 | ESAFENET CDG todoDetail.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /todoDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument curpage leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35017 | IBM Security Verify Governance information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35017</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 Identity Manager can transmit user credentials in clear text that could be obtained by an attacker using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0792 | ESAFENET CDG sdTodoDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0792</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sdTodoDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0790 | ESAFENET CDG doneDetail.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0790</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /doneDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument curpage leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0791 | ESAFENET CDG sdDoneDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0791</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ESAFENET CDG V5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /sdDoneDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0789 | ESAFENET CDG doneDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0789</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG V5. This affects an unknown part of the file /doneDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56529 | Mailcow through 2024-11b has a session fixation vulnerability in the web panel. It allows remote attackers to set a session identifier when ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56529</link><description>Mailcow through 2024-11b has a session fixation vulnerability in the web panel. It allows remote attackers to set a session identifier when HSTS is disabled on a victim's browser. After a user logs in, they are authenticated and the session identifier is valid. Then, a remote attacker can access the victim's web panel with the same session identifier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57519 | An issue in Open5GS v.2.7.2 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the ogs_dbi_auth_info function in lib/dbi/subscription...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57519</link><description>An issue in Open5GS v.2.7.2 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the ogs_dbi_auth_info function in lib/dbi/subscription.c file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0788 | ESAFENET CDG content_top.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0788</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /content_top.jsp. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48310 | AutoLib Software Systems OPAC v20.10 was discovered to have multiple API keys exposed within the source code. Attackers may use these keys t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48310</link><description>AutoLib Software Systems OPAC v20.10 was discovered to have multiple API keys exposed within the source code. Attackers may use these keys to access the backend API or other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0786 | ESAFENET CDG appDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /appDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0787 | ESAFENET CDG appDetail.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0787</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /appDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument curpage leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57514 | The TP-Link Archer A20 v3 router is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) due to improper handling of directory listing paths in the web ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57514</link><description>The TP-Link Archer A20 v3 router is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) due to improper handling of directory listing paths in the web interface. When a specially crafted URL is visited, the router's web page renders the directory listing and executes arbitrary JavaScript embedded in the URL. This allows the attacker to inject malicious code into the page, executing JavaScript on the victim's browser, which could then be used for further malicious actions. The vulnerability was identified in the 1.0.6 Build 20231011 rel.85717(5553) version.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57376 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in D-Link DSR-150, DSR-150N, DSR-250, DSR-250N, DSR-500N, DSR-1000N from 3.13 to 3.17B901C allows unauthentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57376</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in D-Link DSR-150, DSR-150N, DSR-250, DSR-250N, DSR-500N, DSR-1000N from 3.13 to 3.17B901C allows unauthenticated users to execute remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29869 | Apache Hive: Credentials file created with non restrictive permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29869</link><description>Hive creates a credentials file to a temporary directory in the file system with permissions 644 by default when the file permissions are not set explicitly. Any unauthorized user having access to the directory can read the sensitive information written into this file. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55968 | An issue was discovered in DTEX DEC-M (DTEX Forwarder) 6.1.1. The com.dtexsystems.helper service, responsible for handling privileged operat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55968</link><description>An issue was discovered in DTEX DEC-M (DTEX Forwarder) 6.1.1. The com.dtexsystems.helper service, responsible for handling privileged operations within the macOS DTEX Event Forwarder agent, fails to implement critical client validation during XPC interprocess communication (IPC). Specifically, the service does not verify the code requirements, entitlements, security flags, or version of any client attempting to establish a connection. This lack of proper logic validation allows malicious actors to exploit the service's methods via unauthorized client connections, and escalate privileges to root by abusing the DTConnectionHelperProtocol protocol's submitQuery method over an unauthorized XPC connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0785 | ESAFENET CDG SysConfig.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0785</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /SysConfig.jsp. The manipulation of the argument help leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22917 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Audemium ERP &lt;=0.9.0 allows remote attackers to execute an arbitrary JavaScript payl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22917</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Audemium ERP &lt;=0.9.0 allows remote attackers to execute an arbitrary JavaScript payload in the web browser of a user by including a malicious payload into the 'type' parameter of list.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24482 | FactoryTalk® View Site Edition - Local Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24482</link><description>A Local Code Injection Vulnerability exists in the product and version listed above. The vulnerability is due to incorrect default permissions and allows for DLLs to be executed with higher level permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24481 | FactoryTalk® View Site Edition - Incorrect Permission Assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24481</link><description>An Incorrect Permission Assignment Vulnerability exists in the product and version listed above. The vulnerability is due to incorrect permissions being assigned to the remote debugger port and can allow for unauthenticated access to the system configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24826 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24826</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before build 4625.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0784 | Intelbras InControl Registered User usuario cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0784</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Intelbras InControl up to 2.21.58 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /v1/usuario/ of the component Registered User Handler. The manipulation leads to cleartext transmission of sensitive information. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.21.59 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34732 | In RGXMMUCacheInvalidate of rgxmem.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34732</link><description>In RGXMMUCacheInvalidate of rgxmem.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34733 | In DevmemXIntMapPages of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to an integer overflow. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34733</link><description>In DevmemXIntMapPages of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible arbitrary code execution due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34748 | In _DevmemXReservationPageAddress of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible use-after-free due to improper casting. This could lead to loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34748</link><description>In _DevmemXReservationPageAddress of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible use-after-free due to improper casting. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40649 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use-after-free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40649</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use-after-free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40651 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use-after-free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40651</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use-after-free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40669 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40669</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40670 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40670</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40672 | In onCreate of ChooserActivity.java, there is a possible way to bypass factory reset protections due to a missing permission check. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40672</link><description>In onCreate of ChooserActivity.java, there is a possible way to bypass factory reset protections due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40673 | In Source of ZipFile.java, there is a possible way for an attacker to execute arbitrary code by manipulating Dynamic Code Loading due to imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40673</link><description>In Source of ZipFile.java, there is a possible way for an attacker to execute arbitrary code by manipulating Dynamic Code Loading due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40674 | In validateSsid of WifiConfigurationUtil.java, there is a possible way to overflow a system configuration file due to a logic error in the c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40674</link><description>In validateSsid of WifiConfigurationUtil.java, there is a possible way to overflow a system configuration file due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40675 | In parseUriInternal of Intent.java, there is a possible infinite loop due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40675</link><description>In parseUriInternal of Intent.java, there is a possible infinite loop due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40676 | In checkKeyIntent of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass intent security check and install an unknown app due to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40676</link><description>In checkKeyIntent of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass intent security check and install an unknown app due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40677 | In shouldSkipForInitialSUW of AdvancedPowerUsageDetail.java, there is a possible way to bypass factory reset protections due to a missing pe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40677</link><description>In shouldSkipForInitialSUW of AdvancedPowerUsageDetail.java, there is a possible way to bypass factory reset protections due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24480 | FactoryTalk® View Machine Editon - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24480</link><description>A Remote Code Execution Vulnerability exists in the product and version listed above. The vulnerability is due to lack of input sanitation and could allow a remote attacker to run commands or code as a high privileged user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24479 | FactoryTalk® View Machine Edition - Local Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24479</link><description>A Local Code Execution Vulnerability exists in the product and version listed above. The vulnerability is due to a default setting in Windows and allows access to the Command Prompt as a higher privileged user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24478 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability could allow a remote, non-privileged user to send malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24478</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability could allow a remote, non-privileged user to send malicious requests resulting in a major nonrecoverable fault causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0783 | pankajindevops scale API Endpoint access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0783</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in pankajindevops scale up to 20241113. This affects an unknown part of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22217 | Avi Load Balancer contains an unauthenticated blind SQL Injection vulnerability which was privately reported to VMware. Patches are availabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22217</link><description>Avi Load Balancer contains an unauthenticated blind SQL Injection vulnerability which was privately reported to VMware. Patches are available to remediate this vulnerability in affected VMware products. 

A malicious user with network access may be able to use specially crafted SQL queries to gain database access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0631 | PowerFlex® 755 Credential Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0631</link><description>A Credential Exposure Vulnerability exists in the above-mentioned product and version. The vulnerability is due to using HTTP resulting in credentials being sent in clear text.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13484 | Argocd: namespace isolation break</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13484</link><description>A flaw was found in ArgoCD. The openshift.io/cluster-monitoring label is applied to all namespaces that deploy an ArgoCD CR instance, allowing the namespace to create a rogue PrometheusRule. This issue can have adverse effects on the platform monitoring stack, as the rule is rolled out cluster-wide when the label is applied.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23053 | Authenticated privilege escalation via broken access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23053</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated low privilege operator user to change the state of certain settings of a vulnerable system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23054 | Authenticated Response Manipulation allows Unauthorized Actions in Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23054</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated low privilege operator user to perform operations not allowed by their privilege level. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to manipulate user generated files, potentially leading to unauthorized changes in critical system configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23055 | Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23055</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. If successfully exploited, a threat actor could run arbitrary script code in a victim's web browser within the context of the compromised interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23056 | Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23056</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. If successfully exploited, a threat actor could run arbitrary script code in a victim's web browser within the context of the compromised interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23057 | Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23057</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. If successfully exploited, a threat actor could run arbitrary script code in a victim's web browser within the context of the compromised interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13317 | In HeifDecoderImpl::getScanline of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13317</link><description>In HeifDecoderImpl::getScanline of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13318 | In HeifDataSource::readAt of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13318</link><description>In HeifDataSource::readAt of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9373 | In TdlsexRxFrameHandle of the MTK WLAN driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9373</link><description>In TdlsexRxFrameHandle of the MTK WLAN driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9378 | In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9378</link><description>In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8401 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an authenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8401</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an authenticated attacker modifies folder names within the context of
the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0781 | Incorrect Authorization in SimGear</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0781</link><description>An attacker can bypass the sandboxing of Nasal scripts and arbitrarily write to any file path that the user has permission to modify at the operating-system level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23385 | In JetBrains ReSharper before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, Rider before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, dotTrace before 2024.3.4, 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23385</link><description>In JetBrains ReSharper before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, Rider before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, dotTrace before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, ETW Host Service before 16.43, Local Privilege Escalation via the ETW Host Service was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0432 | HMS Networks Ewon Flexy 202 Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0432</link><description>EWON Flexy 202 transmits user credentials in clear text with no encryption when a user is added, or user credentials are changed via its webpage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24800 | Critical vulnerability in `ismp-grandpa` &amp;lt;v15.0.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24800</link><description>Hyperbridge is a hyper-scalable coprocessor for verifiable, cross-chain interoperability. A critical vulnerability was discovered in the ismp-grandpa crate, that allowed a malicious prover easily convince the verifier of the finality of arbitrary headers. This could be used to steal funds or compromise other kinds of cross-chain applications. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23212 | Tandoor Recipes - Local file disclosure - Users can read the content of any file on the server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23212</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. The external storage feature allows any user to enumerate the name and content of files on the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23213 | Tandoor Recipes - Stored XSS through Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23213</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. The file upload feature allows to upload arbitrary files, including html and svg. Both can contain malicious content (XSS Payloads). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23045 | CVAT allows remote code execution via tracker Nuclio functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23045</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. An attacker with an account on an affected CVAT instance is able to run arbitrary code in the context of the Nuclio function container. This vulnerability affects CVAT deployments that run any of the serverless functions of type tracker from the CVAT Git repository, namely TransT and SiamMask. Deployments with custom functions of type tracker may also be affected, depending on how they handle state serialization. If a function uses an unsafe serialization library such as pickle or jsonpickle, it's likely to be vulnerable. Upgrade to CVAT 2.26.0 or later. If you are unable to upgrade, shut down any instances of the TransT or SiamMask functions you're running.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23211 | Tandoor Recipes - SSTI - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23211</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. A Jinja2 SSTI vulnerability allows any user to execute commands on the server. In the case of the provided Docker Compose file as root. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.24.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0659 | Path Traversal and Rockwell Automation Third-party Vulnerability in DataMosaix™ Private Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0659</link><description>A path
traversal vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation DataEdge Platform DataMosaix Private Cloud. By specifying the character
sequence in the body of the vulnerable endpoint, it is possible to overwrite
files outside of the intended directory. A threat actor with admin privileges could
leverage this vulnerability to overwrite reports including user projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7881 | An unprivileged context can trigger a data
memory-dependent prefetch engine to fetch the contents of a privileged location
and consume those...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7881</link><description>An unprivileged context can trigger a data
memory-dependent prefetch engine to fetch the contents of a privileged location
and consume those contents as an address that is also dereferenced.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6351 | Malformed packet leads to denial of service in NWK/APS layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6351</link><description>A malformed packet can cause a buffer overflow in the NWK/APS layer of the Ember ZNet stack and lead to an assert</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11956 | Pimcore customer-data-framework list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11956</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Pimcore customer-data-framework up to 4.2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/customermanagementframework/customers/list. The manipulation of the argument filterDefinition/filter leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.2.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11954 | Pimcore Search Document cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11954</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Pimcore 11.4.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Search Document. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0065 | Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in TeamViewer Clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0065</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in the TeamViewer_service.exe component of TeamViewer Clients prior version 15.62 for Windows allows an attacker with local unprivileged access on a Windows system to elevate privileges via argument injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 10:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0754 | Envoyproxy: openshift service mesh 2.6.3 and 2.5.6 envoy header handling allows log injection and potential spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0754</link><description>The vulnerability was found in OpenShift Service Mesh 2.6.3 and 2.5.6. This issue occurs due to improper sanitization of HTTP headers by Envoy, particularly the x-forwarded-for header. This lack of sanitization can allow attackers to inject malicious payloads into service mesh logs, leading to log injection and spoofing attacks. Such injections can mislead logging mechanisms, enabling attackers to manipulate log entries or execute reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0750 | Cri-o: cri-o path traversal in log handling functions allows arbitrary unmounting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0750</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CRI-O. A path traversal issue in the log management functions (UnMountPodLogs and LinkContainerLogs) may allow an attacker with permissions to create and delete Pods to unmount arbitrary host paths, leading to node-level denial of service by unmounting critical system directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0752 | Envoyproxy: openshift service mesh envoy http header sanitization bypass leading to dos and unauthorized access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0752</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Service Mesh 2.6.3 and 2.5.6. Rate-limiter avoidance, access-control bypass, CPU and memory exhaustion, and replay attacks may be possible due to improper HTTP header sanitization in Envoy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23953 | Apache Hive: Timing Attack Against Signature in LLAP util</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23953</link><description>Use of Arrays.equals() in LlapSignerImpl in Apache Hive to compare message signatures allows attacker to forge a valid signature for an arbitrary message byte by byte. The attacker should be an authorized user of the product to perform this attack. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes this issue.

The problem occurs when an application doesn’t use a constant-time algorithm for validating a signature. The method Arrays.equals() returns false right away when it sees that one of the input’s bytes are different. It means that the comparison time depends on the contents of the arrays. This little thing may allow an attacker to forge a valid signature for an arbitrary message byte by byte. So it might allow malicious users to submit splits/work with selected signatures to LLAP without running as a privileged user, potentially leading to DDoS attack.

More details in the reference section.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0736 | Org.infinispan-infinispan-parent: exposure of sensitive information in application logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0736</link><description>A flaw was found in Infinispan, when using JGroups with JDBC_PING. This issue occurs when an application inadvertently exposes sensitive information, such as configuration details or credentials, through logging mechanisms. This exposure can lead to unauthorized access and exploitation by malicious actors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0290 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (&amp;#x27;Infinite Loop&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0290</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.0 prior to 17.5.5, from 17.6 prior to 17.6.3, and from 17.7 prior to 17.7.1. Under certain conditions, processing of CI artifacts metadata could cause background jobs to become unresponsive.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13527 | Philantro – Donations and Donor Management &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via donate Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13527</link><description>The Philantro – Donations and Donor Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes like 'donate' in all versions up to, and including, 5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 08:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13521 | MailUp Auto Subscription &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13521</link><description>The MailUp Auto Subscription plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the mas_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0321 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.7.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0321</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13448 | ThemeREX Addons &amp;lt;= 2.32.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload in trx_addons_uploads_save_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13448</link><description>The ThemeREX Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'trx_addons_uploads_save_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.32.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13509 | WS Form LITE – Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.10.13 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13509</link><description>The WS Form LITE – Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.10.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability is partially fixed in 1.10.13 and completely fixed in 1.10.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12723 | Infility Global &amp;lt;= 2.9.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12723</link><description>The Infility Global WordPress plugin through 2.9.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12807 | Social Share Buttons for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12807</link><description>The Social Share Buttons for WordPress plugin through 2.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24810 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Simple Image Sizes 3.2.3 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24810</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Simple Image Sizes 3.2.3 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product with the administrative privilege and accessing the settings screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23084 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, specifically affecting the handling of drive names in the Windows environment. Certain Node....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23084</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, specifically affecting the handling of drive names in the Windows environment. Certain Node.js functions do not treat drive names as special on Windows. As a result, although Node.js assumes a relative path, it actually refers to the root directory.

On Windows, a path that does not start with the file separator is treated as relative to the current directory. 

This vulnerability affects Windows users of `path.join` API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11135 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11135</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'event' parameter in the 'eventer_get_attendees' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0146 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause memory corruption. A successfu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0146</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause memory corruption. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53869 | NVIDIA Unified Memory driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could leak uninitialized memory. A successful exploit of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53869</link><description>NVIDIA Unified Memory driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could leak uninitialized memory. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53881 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the host driver, where it can allow a guest to cause an interrupt storm on the host, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53881</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the host driver, where it can allow a guest to cause an interrupt storm on the host, which may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0149 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow an attacker unauthorized access to files. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0149</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow an attacker unauthorized access to files. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to limited information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0147 | NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where referencing memory after it has been freed can lead to denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0147</link><description>NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where referencing memory after it has been freed can lead to denial of service or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0150 | NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where data is written past the end or before the beginning of a buf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0150</link><description>NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where data is written past the end or before the beginning of a buffer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, denial of service, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0140 | NVIDIA RAPIDS contains a vulnerability in cuDF and cuML, where a user could cause a deserialization of untrusted data issue. A successful ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0140</link><description>NVIDIA RAPIDS contains a vulnerability in cuDF and cuML, where a user could cause a deserialization of untrusted data issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0135 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to modification o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0135</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to modification of a host binary. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0136 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0136</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code obtaining read and write access to host devices. This vulnerability is present only when the NVIDIA Container Toolkit is configured in a nondefault way. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0137 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0137</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code running in the host’s network namespace. This vulnerability is present only when the NVIDIA Container Toolkit is configured in a nondefault way. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22315 | IBM Fusion improper communication restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22315</link><description>IBM Fusion and IBM Fusion HCI 2.3.0 through 2.8.2 is vulnerable to insecure network connection by allowing an attacker who gains access to a Fusion container to establish an external network connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45336 | Sensitive headers incorrectly sent after cross-domain redirect in net/http</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45336</link><description>The HTTP client drops sensitive headers after following a cross-domain redirect. For example, a request to a.com/ containing an Authorization header which is redirected to b.com/ will not send that header to b.com. In the event that the client received a subsequent same-domain redirect, however, the sensitive headers would be restored. For example, a chain of redirects from a.com/, to b.com/1, and finally to b.com/2 would incorrectly send the Authorization header to b.com/2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45339 | Vulnerability when creating log files in github.com/golang/glog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45339</link><description>When logs are written to a widely-writable directory (the default), an unprivileged attacker may predict a privileged process's log file path and pre-create a symbolic link to a sensitive file in its place. When that privileged process runs, it will follow the planted symlink and overwrite that sensitive file. To fix that, glog now causes the program to exit (with status code 2) when it finds that the configured log file already exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45340 | GOAUTH credential leak in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45340</link><description>Credentials provided via the new GOAUTH feature were not being properly segmented by domain, allowing a malicious server to request credentials they should not have access to. By default, unless otherwise set, this only affected credentials stored in the users .netrc file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45341 | Usage of IPv6 zone IDs can bypass URI name constraints in crypto/x509</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45341</link><description>A certificate with a URI which has a IPv6 address with a zone ID may incorrectly satisfy a URI name constraint that applies to the certificate chain. Certificates containing URIs are not permitted in the web PKI, so this only affects users of private PKIs which make use of URIs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22865 | ParsePKCS1PrivateKey panic with partial keys in crypto/x509</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22865</link><description>Using ParsePKCS1PrivateKey to parse a RSA key that is missing the CRT values would panic when verifying that the key is well formed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12647 | Buffer overflow in CPCA font download processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12647</link><description>Buffer overflow in CPCA font download processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera MF656Cdw/Satera MF654Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF656Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF654Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF653Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF652Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP633Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP632Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF657Cdw/i-SENSYS MF655Cdw/i-SENSYS MF651Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP633Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP631Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12648 | Buffer overflow in TIFF data EXIF tag processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12648</link><description>Buffer overflow in TIFF data EXIF tag processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera MF656Cdw/Satera MF654Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF656Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF654Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF653Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF652Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP633Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP632Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF657Cdw/i-SENSYS MF655Cdw/i-SENSYS MF651Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP633Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP631Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12649 | Buffer overflow in XPS data font processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12649</link><description>Buffer overflow in XPS data font processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera MF656Cdw/Satera MF654Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF656Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF654Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF653Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF652Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP633Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP632Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF657Cdw/i-SENSYS MF655Cdw/i-SENSYS MF651Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP633Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP631Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3365 | Emote Interactive Remote Mouse Server command injection due to weak encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3365</link><description>Due to reliance on a trivial substitution cipher, sent in cleartext, and the reliance on a default password when the user does not set a password, the Remote Mouse Server by Emote Interactive can be abused by attackers to inject OS commands over theproduct's custom control protocol. A Metasploit module was written and tested against version 4.110, the current version when this CVE was reserved.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50316 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50316</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1
is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify or delete information in the back-end database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27263 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27263</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information from the dashboard UI using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>