<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:55:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-2313 | If kernel headers need to be extracted, bpftrace will attempt to load them from a temporary directory. An unprivileged attacker could use th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2313</link><description>If kernel headers need to be extracted, bpftrace will attempt to load them from a temporary directory. An unprivileged attacker could use this to force bcc to load compromised linux headers. Linux distributions which provide kernel headers by default are not affected by default.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2363 | AOL AIM Triton Invite denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2363</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in AOL AIM Triton 1.0.4. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Invite Handler. The manipulation of the argument CSeq leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256318 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2355 | keerti1924 Secret-Coder-PHP-Project secret_coder.sql inclusion of sensitive information in source code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2355</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in keerti1924 Secret-Coder-PHP-Project 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /secret_coder.sql. The manipulation leads to inclusion of sensitive information in source code. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256315. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2354 | Dreamer CMS toEdit cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2354</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/menu/toEdit. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256314 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2353 | Totolink X6000R shttpd cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28757 | libexpat through 2.6.1 allows an XML Entity Expansion attack when there is isolated use of external parsers (created via XML_ExternalEntityP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28757</link><description>libexpat through 2.6.1 allows an XML Entity Expansion attack when there is isolated use of external parsers (created via XML_ExternalEntityParserCreate).</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 04:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2352 | 1Panel swap baseApi.UpdateDeviceSwap command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2352</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1Panel up to 1.10.1-lts. Affected by this issue is the function baseApi.UpdateDeviceSwap of the file /api/v1/toolbox/device/update/swap. The manipulation of the argument Path with the input 123123123\nopen -a Calculator leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256304.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2351 | CodeAstro Ecommerce Site Search action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2351</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CodeAstro Ecommerce Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file action.php of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument cat_id/brand_id/keyword leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256303.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 22:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2333 | CodeAstro Membership Management System add_members.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2333</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add_members.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256284.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2332 | SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store HTTP GET Request manage_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/maintenance/manage_category.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256283.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2331 | SourceCodester Tourist Reservation System System.cpp ad_writedata buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tourist Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function ad_writedata of the file System.cpp. The manipulation of the argument ad_code leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256282 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 10:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1870 | The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1870</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the callActivateLicenseEndpoint function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.260. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to update the license key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2330 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2330</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /protocol/index.php. The manipulation of the argument IPAddr leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256281 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2329 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2329</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/list_resource_icon.php?action=delete. The manipulation of the argument IconId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256280. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25501 | An issue WinMail v.7.1 and v.5.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the email parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25501</link><description>An issue WinMail v.7.1 and v.5.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the email parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1123 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a miss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1123</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_frontend_event_submission() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the title and content of arbitrary posts. This can also be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when the allow_submission_by_anonymous_user setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1124 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending due to a missing cap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1124</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending due to a missing capability check on the ep_send_attendees_email() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to send arbitrary emails with arbitrary content from the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1125 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1125</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the calendar_events_delete() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1320 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'offline_st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1320</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'offline_status' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1767 | The Blocksy theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1767</link><description>The Blocksy theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'className' and 'radius'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28089 | Hitron CODA-4582 2AHKM-CODA4589 7.2.4.5.1b8 devices allow a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity (who has access to the router admin panel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28089</link><description>Hitron CODA-4582 2AHKM-CODA4589 7.2.4.5.1b8 devices allow a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity (who has access to the router admin panel) to conduct a DOM-based stored XSS attack that can fetch remote resources. The payload is executed at index.html#advanced_location (aka the Device Location page). This can cause a denial of service or lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 06:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25951 | A command injection vulnerability exists in local RACADM. A malicious authenticated user could gain control of the underlying operating syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25951</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in local RACADM. A malicious authenticated user could gain control of the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 06:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46427 | An issue was discovered in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46427</link><description>An issue was discovered in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), and obtain sensitive information via null pointer deference in gf_dash_setup_period component in media_tools/dash_client.c.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46426 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46426</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via gf_fwrite component in at utils/os_file.c.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50015 | An issue was discovered in Grandstream GXP14XX 1.0.8.9 and GXP16XX 1.0.7.13, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges via incorrect ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50015</link><description>An issue was discovered in Grandstream GXP14XX 1.0.8.9 and GXP16XX 1.0.7.13, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges via incorrect access control using an end-user session-identity token.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49340 | An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to escalate privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49340</link><description>An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and bypass authentication via incorrect access control in the web management portal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 04:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49341 | An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49341</link><description>An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via cleartext credential storage in backup.htm component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 04:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28122 |  JWX vulnerable to a denial of service attack using compressed JWE message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28122</link><description>JWX is Go module implementing various JWx (JWA/JWE/JWK/JWS/JWT, otherwise known as JOSE) technologies. This vulnerability allows an attacker with a trusted public key to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition by crafting a malicious JSON Web Encryption (JWE) token with an exceptionally high compression ratio. This issue has been patched in versions 1.2.29 and 2.0.21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28176 | jose vulnerable to resource exhaustion via specifically crafted JWE with compressed plaintext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28176</link><description>jose is JavaScript module for JSON Object Signing and Encryption, providing support for JSON Web Tokens (JWT), JSON Web Signature (JWS), JSON Web Encryption (JWE), JSON Web Key (JWK), JSON Web Key Set (JWKS), and more. A vulnerability has 
 been identified in the JSON Web Encryption (JWE) decryption interfaces, specifically related to the support for decompressing plaintext after its decryption. Under certain conditions it is possible to have the user's environment consume unreasonable amount of CPU time or memory during JWE Decryption operations. This issue has been patched in versions 2.0.7 and 4.15.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28180 | Go JOSE vulnerable to Improper Handling of Highly Compressed Data (Data Amplification)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28180</link><description>Package jose aims to provide an implementation of the Javascript Object Signing and Encryption set of standards. An attacker could send a JWE containing compressed data that used large amounts of memory and CPU when decompressed by Decrypt or DecryptMulti. Those functions now return an error if the decompressed data would exceed 250kB or 10x the compressed size (whichever is larger). This vulnerability has been patched in versions 4.0.1, 3.0.3 and 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28184 | WeasyPrint allows the attachment of arbitrary files and URLs to a PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28184</link><description>WeasyPrint helps web developers to create PDF documents. Since version 61.0, there's a vulnerability which allows attaching content of arbitrary files and URLs to a generated PDF document, even if `url_fetcher` is configured to prevent access to files and URLs. This vulnerability has been patched in version 61.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28753 | RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to read the /etc/passwd file via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28753</link><description>RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to read the /etc/passwd file via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28754 | RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to cause a persistent denial of service (bricking) via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28754</link><description>RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to cause a persistent denial of service (bricking) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 23:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28123 | Wasmi Out-of-bounds Write for host to Wasm calls with more than 128 Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28123</link><description>Wasmi is an efficient and lightweight WebAssembly interpreter with a focus on constrained and embedded systems. In the WASMI Interpreter, an Out-of-bounds Buffer Write will arise if the host calls or resumes a Wasm function with more parameters than the default limit (128), as it will surpass the stack value. This doesn’t affect calls from Wasm to Wasm, only from host to Wasm. This vulnerability was patched in version 0.31.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 21:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32264 | CWE-1385 vulnerability in OpenText Documentum D2 affecting versions16.5.1 to CE 23.2. The vulnerability could allow upload arbitrary code an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32264</link><description>CWE-1385 vulnerability in OpenText Documentum D2 affecting versions16.5.1 to CE 23.2. The vulnerability could allow upload arbitrary code and execute it on the client's computer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2338 | SQL Injection in PostgreSQL Anonymizer 1.2 allows table owner to gain superuser privileges via masking rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2338</link><description>PostgreSQL Anonymizer v1.2 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows a user who owns a table to elevate to superuser when dynamic masking is enabled. PostgreSQL Anonymizer enables users to set security labels on tables to mask specified columns. There is a flaw that allows complex expressions to be provided as a value. This expression is then later used as it to create the masked views leading to SQL Injection. If dynamic masking is enabled, this will lead to privilege escalation to superuser after the label is created. Users that don't own a table, especially masked users cannot exploit this vulnerability. The problem is resolved in v1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2339 | Improper Input Validation in PostgreSQL Anonymizer 1.2 allows table owner to gain superuser privileges via masking rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2339</link><description>PostgreSQL Anonymizer v1.2 contains a vulnerability  that allows a user who owns a table to elevate to superuser. A user can define a masking function for a column and place malicious code in that function. When a privileged user applies the masking rules using the static masking or the anonymous dump method, the malicious code is executed and can grant escalated privileges to the malicious user. PostgreSQL Anonymizer v1.2 does provide a protection against this risk with the restrict_to_trusted_schemas option, but that protection is incomplete. Users that don't own a table, especially masked users cannot exploit this vulnerability. The problem is resolved in v1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43855 | IBM SPSS Statistics denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43855</link><description>IBM SPSS Statistics 26.0, 27.0.1, and 28.0 could allow a local user to create multiple files that could exhaust the file handles capacity and cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  230235.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21899 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21899</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21900 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21900</link><description>An injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21901 | myQNAPcloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21901</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect myQNAPcloud. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
myQNAPcloud 1.0.52 ( 2023/11/24 ) and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32969 | Network &amp;amp; Virtual Switch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32969</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Network &amp; Virtual Switch. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34980 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34980</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47221 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47221</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.2 ( 2023/12/15 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2319 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in Django MarkdownX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2319</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Django MarkdownX project, affecting version 4.0.2. An attacker could store a specially crafted JavaScript payload in the upload functionality due to lack of proper sanitisation of JavaScript elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2318 | ZKTeco ZKBio Media Service Port 9999 download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2318</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZKTeco ZKBio Media 2.0.0_x64_2024-01-29-1028. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pro/common/download of the component Service Port 9999. The manipulation of the argument fileName with the input ../../../../zkbio_media.sql leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256272. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2317 | Bdtask Hospital AutoManager Prescription Page improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2317</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager up to 20240227 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /prescription/prescription/delete/ of the component Prescription Page. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 12:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2316 | Bdtask Hospital AutoManager Update Bill Page cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2316</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager up to 20240227 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /billing/bill/edit/ of the component Update Bill Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 11:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1851 | The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1851</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the atkp_create_list() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to to perform unauthorized actions such as creating product lists.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2298 | The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2298</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the atkp_import_product() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to to perform unauthorized actions such as creating importing products.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27612 | Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles editing of themes and extensions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27612</link><description>Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles editing of themes and extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27613 | Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles reading of themes and extensions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27613</link><description>Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles reading of themes and extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1987 | The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1987</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 05:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2285 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System member_edit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2285</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /member/member_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2284 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System Chat Book chat.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2284</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /member/chat.php of the component Chat Book. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256051. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6268 | RAD SecFlow-2 devices with Hardware 0202, Firmware 4.1.01.63, and U-Boot 2010.12 allow URIs beginning with /.. for Directory Traversal, as d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6268</link><description>RAD SecFlow-2 devices with Hardware 0202, Firmware 4.1.01.63, and U-Boot 2010.12 allow URIs beginning with /.. for Directory Traversal, as demonstrated by reading /etc/shadow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26309 | Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26309</link><description>Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could potentially obtain access to sensitive information via an internal URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26313 | Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authenticated malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26313</link><description>Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.13.P3 HF1 (6.13.0.3.1) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2283 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2283</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /member/view.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256050 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25845 | In the module "CD Custom Fields 4 Orders" (cdcustomfields4orders) &lt;= 1.0.0 from Cleanpresta.com for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL inje...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25845</link><description>In the module "CD Custom Fields 4 Orders" (cdcustomfields4orders) &lt;= 1.0.0 from Cleanpresta.com for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25848 | In the module "Ever Ultimate SEO" (everpsseo) &lt;= 8.1.2 from Team Ever for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25848</link><description>In the module "Ever Ultimate SEO" (everpsseo) &lt;= 8.1.2 from Team Ever for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25849 | In the module "Make an offer" (makeanoffer) &lt;= 1.7.1 from PrestaToolKit for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection via MakeOffers::ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25849</link><description>In the module "Make an offer" (makeanoffer) &lt;= 1.7.1 from PrestaToolKit for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection via MakeOffers::checkUserExistingOffer()` and `MakeOffers::addUserOffer()` .</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28826 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, macOS Monter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28826</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0258 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0258</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code out of its sandbox or with certain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23201 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23201</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23205 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23205</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23216 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23216</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to overwrite arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23220 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23220</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23226 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, wat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23226</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, tvOS 17.4. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23227 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23227</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23230 | This issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23230</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23231 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23231</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23232 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to cap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23232</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to capture a user's screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23233 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Entitlements and privacy permissions granted to thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23233</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Entitlements and privacy permissions granted to this app may be used by a malicious app.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23234 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23234</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23235 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23235</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23238 | An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to edit NVRAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23238</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to edit NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23239 | A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23239</link><description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23240 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Shake-to-undo may allow a deleted photo to be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23240</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Shake-to-undo may allow a deleted photo to be re-surfaced without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23241 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23241</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23242 | A privacy issue was addressed by not logging contents of text fields. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23242</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by not logging contents of text fields. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to view Mail data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23244 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app from a stand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23244</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app from a standard user account may be able to escalate privilege after admin user login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23245 | This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23245</link><description>This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. Third-party shortcuts may use a legacy action from Automator to send events to apps without user consent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23246 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23246</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23247 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23247</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. Processing a file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23248 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23248</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-service or potentially disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23249 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23249</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-service or potentially disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23250 | An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23250</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to access Bluetooth-connected microphones without user permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23252 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23252</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23253 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23253</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access a user's Photos Library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23254 | The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23254</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, Safari 17.4. A malicious website may exfiltrate audio data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23255 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23255</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Photos in the Hidden Photos Album may be viewed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23257 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23257</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6. Processing an image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23258 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing an im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23258</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23259 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23259</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23260 | This issue was addressed by removing additional entitlements. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23260</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing additional entitlements. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23262 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, iOS 16.7.6 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23262</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6. An app may be able to spoof system notifications and UI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23263 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23263</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, Safari 17.4. Processing maliciously crafted web content may prevent Content Security Policy from being enforced.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23264 | A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23264</link><description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23265 | A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23265</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23266 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23266</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23267 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23267</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23268 | An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Vent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23268</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23269 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23269</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23270 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23270</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23272 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. A u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23272</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. A user may gain access to protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23273 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23273</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Private Browsing tabs may be accessed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23274 | An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Vent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23274</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23275 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23275</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23276 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23276</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23277 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An attacker in a privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23277</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to inject keystrokes by spoofing a keyboard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23278 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23278</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23279 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23279</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23280 | An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23280</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, tvOS 17.4. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23281 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access sensitive us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23281</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23283 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23283</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23284 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23284</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, Safari 17.4. Processing maliciously crafted web content may prevent Content Security Policy from being enforced.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23285 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to create symlinks...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23285</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to create symlinks to protected regions of the disk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23286 | A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23286</link><description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23287 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23287</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23288 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, wat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23288</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23289 | A lock screen issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23289</link><description>A lock screen issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. A person with physical access to a device may be able to use Siri to access private calendar information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23290 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23290</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23291 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23291</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. A malicious app may be able to observe user data in log entries related to accessibility notifications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23292 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23292</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to access information about a user's contacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23293 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23293</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An attacker with physical access may be able to use Siri to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23294 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing malicious input may lead to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23294</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing malicious input may lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23295 | A permissions issue was addressed to help ensure Personas are always protected This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1. An unauthenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23295</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed to help ensure Personas are always protected This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1. An unauthenticated user may be able to use an unprotected Persona.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23297 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4. A malicious applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23297</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4. A malicious application may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2282 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System Login Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2282</link><description>A vulnerability was found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument useremail leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256049 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2277 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software Password Reset change_password_save cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2277</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Setting/change_password_save of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256046 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2281 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System Setting index.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2281</link><description>A vulnerability was found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256048. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2276 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software Edit Venue Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2276</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Venue_controller/edit_venue/ of the component Edit Venue Page. The manipulation of the argument Venue map leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256045 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2274 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software Prescription Dashboard Index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2274</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Home/Index of the component Prescription Dashboard. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256043. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2275 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software OBS Patient/Gynee Prescription cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2275</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component OBS Patient/Gynee Prescription. The manipulation of the argument Patient Title/Full Name/Address/Cheif Complain/LMP/Menstrual Edd/OBS P/OBS Alc/Medicine Name/Medicine Type/Ml/Dose/Days/Comments/Template Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256044. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>