<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2018-25099 | In the CryptX module before 0.062 for Perl, gcm_decrypt_verify() and chacha20poly1305_decrypt_verify() do not verify the tag.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25099</link><description>In the CryptX module before 0.062 for Perl, gcm_decrypt_verify() and chacha20poly1305_decrypt_verify() do not verify the tag.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47154 | The Net::CIDR::Lite module before 0.22 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters at the beginning of an IP address stri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47154</link><description>The Net::CIDR::Lite module before 0.22 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters at the beginning of an IP address string, which (in some situations) allows attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47155 | The Net::IPV4Addr module 0.10 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (in some situati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47155</link><description>The Net::IPV4Addr module 0.10 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (in some situations) allows attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47156 | The Net::IPAddress::Util module before 5.000 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47156</link><description>The Net::IPAddress::Util module before 5.000 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (in some situations) allows attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47157 | The Kossy module before 0.60 for Perl allows JSON hijacking because of X-Requested-With mishandling.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47157</link><description>The Kossy module before 0.60 for Perl allows JSON hijacking because of X-Requested-With mishandling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27757 | flusity CMS through 2.45 allows tools/addons_model.php Gallery Name XSS. The reporter indicates that this product "ceased its development as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27757</link><description>flusity CMS through 2.45 allows tools/addons_model.php Gallery Name XSS. The reporter indicates that this product "ceased its development as of February 2024."</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28745 | Improper export of Android application components issue exists in 'ABEMA' App for Android prior to 10.65.0 allowing another app installed on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28745</link><description>Improper export of Android application components issue exists in 'ABEMA' App for Android prior to 10.65.0 allowing another app installed on the user's device to access an arbitrary URL on 'ABEMA' App for Android via Intent. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary website may be displayed on the app, and as a result, the user may become a victim of a phishing attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47037 | Siklu TG Terragraph devices before 2.1.1 allow attackers to discover valid, randomly generated credentials via GetCredentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47037</link><description>Siklu TG Terragraph devices before 2.1.1 allow attackers to discover valid, randomly generated credentials via GetCredentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47036 | Siklu TG Terragraph devices before approximately 2.1.1 have a hardcoded root password that has been revealed via a brute force attack on an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47036</link><description>Siklu TG Terragraph devices before approximately 2.1.1 have a hardcoded root password that has been revealed via a brute force attack on an MD5 hash. It can be used for "debug login" by an admin. NOTE: the vulnerability is not fixed by the 2.1.1 firmware; instead, it is fixed in newer hardware, which would typically be used with firmware 2.1.1 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2581 | Tenda AC10 SetStaticRouteCfg fromSetRouteStatic stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function fromSetRouteStatic of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257081 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24539 | FusionPBX before 5.2.0 does not validate a session.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24539</link><description>FusionPBX before 5.2.0 does not validate a session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2577 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-employee.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2577</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /update-employee.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257080.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2575 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System task-details.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2575</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /task-details.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257078 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2576 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-admin.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2576</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /update-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to authorization bypass. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257079.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52159 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in gross 0.9.3 through 1.x before 1.0.4 allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52159</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in gross 0.9.3 through 1.x before 1.0.4 allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (grossd daemon crash) or potentially execute arbitrary code in grossd via crafted SMTP transaction parameters that cause an incorrect strncat for a log entry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24230 | Komm.One CMS 10.4.2.14 has a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability via the Velocity template engine. It allows remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24230</link><description>Komm.One CMS 10.4.2.14 has a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability via the Velocity template engine. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a URL that specifies java.lang.Runtime in conjunction with getRuntime().exec followed by an OS command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2574 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System edit-task.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2574</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257077 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2572 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System task-details.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2572</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /task-details.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257075.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2573 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System task-info.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2573</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /task-info.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257076.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39223 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in CGIs included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39223</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in CGIs included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on a logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39933 | Insufficient verification vulnerability exists in Broadcast Mail CGI (pmc.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 product...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39933</link><description>Insufficient verification vulnerability exists in Broadcast Mail CGI (pmc.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user who can upload files through the product may execute an arbitrary executable file with the web server's execution privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40160 | Directory traversal vulnerability exists in Mailing List Search CGI (pmmls.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 produc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40160</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability exists in Mailing List Search CGI (pmmls.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40747 | Directory traversal vulnerability exists in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products' CGIs included in Internal Simple Webserver. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40747</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability exists in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products' CGIs included in Internal Simple Webserver. If this vulnerability is exploited, a  remote attacker may access arbitrary files outside DocumentRoot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2571 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System manage-admin.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2571</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage-admin.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257074 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23138 | A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed through Autodesk DWG TrueView can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23138</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed through Autodesk DWG TrueView can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23139 | An Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk FBX Review version 1.5.3.0 and prior may lead to code execution or information disclosure t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23139</link><description>An Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk FBX Review version 1.5.3.0 and prior may lead to code execution or information disclosure through maliciously crafted ActionScript Byte Code “ABC” files. ABC files are created by the Flash compiler and contain executable code. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2570 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System edit-task.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit-task.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257073 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2569 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System admin-manage-user.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2569</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-manage-user.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257072.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2568 | heyewei JFinalCMS Custom Data Page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2568</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in heyewei JFinalCMS 5.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/div_data/delete?divId=9 of the component Custom Data Page. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257071.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2567 | jurecapuder AndroidWeatherApp Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2567</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in jurecapuder AndroidWeatherApp 1.0.0 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257070 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: The code maintainer was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. Instead the GitHub repository got deleted after a few days. We have to assume that the product is not supported anymore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27961 | WordPress AntiSpam for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27961</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codekraft AntiSpam for Contact Form 7 allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AntiSpam for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 0.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27960 | WordPress Email Subscription Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27960</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in I Thirteen Web Solution Email Subscription Popup allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Email Subscription Popup: from n/a through 1.2.20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27957 | WordPress Pie Register plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27957</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Pie Register.This issue affects Pie Register: from n/a through 3.8.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27958 | WordPress Visualizer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27958</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeisle Visualizer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Visualizer: from n/a through 3.10.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27959 | WordPress APIExperts Square for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27959</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wpexpertsio WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management: from n/a through 4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25591 | WordPress WP Editor plugin &amp;lt;=1.2.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25591</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Benjamin Rojas WP Editor.This issue affects WP Editor: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25903 | WordPress Frontend File Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 22.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25903</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in N-Media Frontend File Manager.This issue affects Frontend File Manager: from n/a through 22.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24867 | WordPress WP Stats Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24867</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Osamaesh WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic).This issue affects WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic): from n/a through 6.9.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25933 | WordPress PeproDev Ultimate Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25933</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev Ultimate Invoice.This issue affects PeproDev Ultimate Invoice: from n/a through 1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2566 | Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform get_extension_yl.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2566</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240313. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/client/get_extension_yl.php. The manipulation of the argument imei leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257065 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2565 | PandaXGO PandaX File Extension upload.go unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2565</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /apps/system/router/upload.go of the component File Extension Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257064.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2564 | PandaXGO PandaX user.go ExportUser path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2564</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function ExportUser of the file /apps/system/api/user.go. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257063.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2563 | PandaXGO PandaX upload.go DeleteImage path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2563</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function DeleteImage of the file /apps/system/router/upload.go. The manipulation of the argument fileName with the input ../../../../../../../../../tmp/1.txt leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257062 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 12:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2562 | PandaXGO PandaX role_menu.go InsertRole sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2562</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310. This affects the function InsertRole of the file /apps/system/services/role_menu.go. The manipulation of the argument roleKey leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257061 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2561 | 74CMS Company Logo Index.php#sendCompanyLogo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2561</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 74CMS 3.28.0. Affected by this issue is the function sendCompanyLogo of the file /controller/company/Index.php#sendCompanyLogo of the component Company Logo Handler. The manipulation of the argument imgBase64 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257060.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2560 | Tenda AC18 SysToolRestoreSet fromSysToolRestoreSet cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2560</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSysToolRestoreSet of the file /goform/SysToolRestoreSet. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257059. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 10:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2559 | Tenda AC18 SysToolReboot fromSysToolReboot cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2559</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function fromSysToolReboot of the file /goform/SysToolReboot. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257058 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2558 | Tenda AC18 execCommand formexeCommand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2558</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257057 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2557 | kishor-23 Food Waste Management System admin.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2557</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kishor-23 Food Waste Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/admin.php. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257056. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2556 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System attendance-info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2556</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257055.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2555 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2555</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file update-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257054 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2554 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-employee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2554</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file update-employee.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257053 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2553 | SourceCodester Product Review Rating System Rate Product cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2553</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Product Review Rating System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Rate Product Handler. The manipulation of the argument Your Name/Comment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257052.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2547 | Tenda AC18 R7WebsSecurityHandler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2547</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function R7WebsSecurityHandler. The manipulation of the argument password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257000. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2546 | Tenda AC18 fromSetWirelessRepeat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2546</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC18 15.13.07.09 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256999. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 01:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2535 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2535</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256972. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 01:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2534 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2534</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256971. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 23:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2533 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2533</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256970 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 22:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2532 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2532</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256969 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 22:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2531 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-rooms.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2531</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update-rooms.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256968. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 21:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2530 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-rooms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2530</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update-rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256967. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 21:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2529 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2529</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256966 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 20:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2528 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-rooms.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2528</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update-rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256965 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 19:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2527 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2527</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256964. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 19:07:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2526 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2526</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256963. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2525 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System receipt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2525</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256962 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2524 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2524</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256961 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2523 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System booktime.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2523</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/booktime.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256960. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2522 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System booktime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2522</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/booktime.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256959. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2521 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System bookdate.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2521</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bookdate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256958 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2520 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System bookdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2520</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/bookdate.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256957 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2519 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System navbar.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2519</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file navbar.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256956. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 14:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2518 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System book_history.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2518</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file book_history.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256955. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2517 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System book_history.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2517</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file book_history.php. The manipulation of the argument del_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256954 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2516 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2516</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file home.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256953 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 11:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2515 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System home.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2515</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file home.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256952. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1857 | The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce – Create, Redeem &amp; Manage Digital Gift Certificates with Personalized Templates plugin for WordPress...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1857</link><description>The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce – Create, Redeem &amp; Manage Digital Gift Certificates with Personalized Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 via the wps_wgm_preview_email_template(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read password protected and draft posts that may contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22513 | djangorestframework-simplejwt version 5.3.1 and before is vulnerable to information disclosure. A user can access web application resources ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22513</link><description>djangorestframework-simplejwt version 5.3.1 and before is vulnerable to information disclosure. A user can access web application resources even after their account has been disabled due to missing user validation checks via the for_user method.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28640 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022 allows a remote attacker to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28640</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service (D0S) via the command field.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28639 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022, allow remote attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28639</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022, allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via the IP field.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24156 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard g6 before Github commit 58c737a263ac0c523592fd87ff71b9e3c07d7cf5, allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24156</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard g6 before Github commit 58c737a263ac0c523592fd87ff71b9e3c07d7cf5, allows remote attackers execute arbitrary code via the wr_content parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1685 | The Social Media Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1685</link><description>The Social Media Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input through the attachmentUrl parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1733 | The Word Replacer Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the word_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1733</link><description>The Word Replacer Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the word_replacer_ultra() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary content on the affected WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28070 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28070</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack due to insufficient input validation. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28069 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28069</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct an information disclosure attack due to improper configuration. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and potentially conduct unauthorized actions within the vulnerable component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36483 | An authorization bypass was discovered in the Carrier MASmobile Classic application through 1.16.18 for Android, MASmobile Classic app throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36483</link><description>An authorization bypass was discovered in the Carrier MASmobile Classic application through 1.16.18 for Android, MASmobile Classic app through 1.7.24 for iOS, and MAS ASP.Net Services through 1.9. It can be achieved via session ID prediction, allowing remote attackers to retrieve sensitive data including customer data, security system status, and event history. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. The affected products cannot simply be updated; they must be removed, but can be replaced by other Carrier software as explained in the Carrier advisory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22259 | CVE-2024-22259: Spring Framework URL Parsing with Host Validation (2nd report)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22259</link><description>Applications that use UriComponentsBuilder in Spring Framework to parse an externally provided URL (e.g. through a query parameter) AND perform validation checks on the host of the parsed URL may be vulnerable to a  open redirect https://cwe.mitre.org/data/definitions/601.html  attack or to a SSRF attack if the URL is used after passing validation checks.

This is the same as  CVE-2024-22243 https://spring.io/security/cve-2024-22243 , but with different input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23523 | WordPress Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19.2 - Contributor+ Arbitrary User Meta Data Retrieval vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23523</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Elementor Pro.This issue affects Elementor Pro: from n/a through 3.19.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24845 | WordPress Post Thumbnail Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24845</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Sewpafly Post Thumbnail Editor.This issue affects Post Thumbnail Editor: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6525 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6525</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This primarily affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1239 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1239</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2042 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2042</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2294 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2294</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 via the backup_name parameter in the backuply_download_backup function. This makes it possible for attackers to have an account with only activate_plugins capability to access arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information. This only impacts sites hosted on Windows servers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2308 | The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link in the EliSlid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2308</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link in the EliSlider in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51474 | WordPress TerraClassifieds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51474</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pixelemu TerraClassifieds.This issue affects TerraClassifieds: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51486 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder, Create invoices, packing slips and more plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.101 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51486</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RedNao WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder: from n/a through 1.2.101.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51487 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.32 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51487</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz.This issue affects ARI Stream Quiz: from n/a through 1.2.32.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27194 | WordPress Fontific plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.6 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27194</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Andrei Ivasiuc Fontific | Google Fonts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fontific | Google Fonts: from n/a through 0.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27195 | WordPress Watermark RELOADED plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27195</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sandi Verdev Watermark RELOADED allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Watermark RELOADED: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27197 | WordPress BeePress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.8 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27197</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Bee BeePress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BeePress: from n/a through 6.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51407 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51407</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rocket Elements Split Test For Elementor.This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51489 | WordPress Crowdsignal Polls &amp;amp; Ratings plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51489</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic, Inc. Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more.This issue affects Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more: from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51491 | WordPress Depicter Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51491</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Averta Depicter Slider.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51510 | WordPress Export Media URLs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51510</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Atlas Gondal Export Media URLs.This issue affects Export Media URLs: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51512 | WordPress Product Table by WBW plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51512</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WBW Product Table by WBW.This issue affects Product Table by WBW: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51521 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.18 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51521</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through 8.1.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>