<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:52:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-56326 | Jinja has a sandbox breakout through indirect reference to format method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56326</link><description>Jinja is an extensible templating engine. Prior to 3.1.5, An oversight in how the Jinja sandboxed environment detects calls to str.format allows an attacker that controls the content of a template to execute arbitrary Python code. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker needs to control the content of a template. Whether that is the case depends on the type of application using Jinja. This vulnerability impacts users of applications which execute untrusted templates. Jinja's sandbox does catch calls to str.format and ensures they don't escape the sandbox. However, it's possible to store a reference to a malicious string's format method, then pass that to a filter that calls it. No such filters are built-in to Jinja, but could be present through custom filters in an application. After the fix, such indirect calls are also handled by the sandbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56201 | Jinja has a sandbox breakout through malicious filenames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56201</link><description>Jinja is an extensible templating engine. Prior to 3.1.5, a bug in the Jinja compiler allows an attacker that controls both the content and filename of a template to execute arbitrary Python code, regardless of if Jinja's sandbox is used. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker needs to control both the filename and the contents of a template. Whether that is the case depends on the type of application using Jinja. This vulnerability impacts users of applications which execute untrusted templates where the template author can also choose the template filename. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45387 | Apache Traffic Control: SQL Injection in Traffic Ops endpoint PUT deliveryservice_request_comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45387</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in Traffic Ops in Apache Traffic Control &lt;= 8.0.1, &gt;= 8.0.0 allows a privileged user with role "admin", "federation", "operations", "portal", or "steering" to execute arbitrary SQL against the database by sending a specially-crafted PUT request.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version Apache Traffic Control 8.0.2 if you run an affected version of Traffic Ops.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23945 | Apache Hive, Apache Spark, Apache Spark: CookieSigner exposes the correct signature when message verification fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23945</link><description>Signing cookies is an application security feature that adds a digital signature to cookie data to verify its authenticity and integrity. The signature helps prevent malicious actors from modifying the cookie value, which can lead to security vulnerabilities and exploitation. Apache Hive’s service component accidentally exposes the signed cookie to the end user when there is a mismatch in signature between the current and expected cookie. Exposing the correct cookie signature can lead to further exploitation.

The vulnerable CookieSigner logic was introduced in Apache Hive by HIVE-9710 (1.2.0) and in Apache Spark by SPARK-14987 (2.0.0). The affected components are the following:
* org.apache.hive:hive-service
* org.apache.spark:spark-hive-thriftserver_2.11
* org.apache.spark:spark-hive-thriftserver_2.12</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54148 | Gogs has a Path Traversal in file editing UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54148</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. A malicious user is able to commit and edit a crafted symlink file to a repository to gain SSH access to the server. The vulnerability is fixed in 0.13.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55947 | Gogs has a Path Traversal in file update API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55947</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. A malicious user is able to write a file to an arbitrary path on the server to gain SSH access to the server. The vulnerability is fixed in 0.13.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53256 | Rizin has a command injection via RzBinInfo bclass due legacy code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53256</link><description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. `rizin.c` still had an old snippet of code which suffered a command injection due the usage of `rz_core_cmdf` to invoke the command `m` which was removed in v0.1.x. A malicious binary defining `bclass` (part of RzBinInfo) is executed if `rclass` (part of RzBinInfo) is set to `fs`; the vulnerability can be exploited by any bin format where `bclass` and `rclass` are user defined. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.7.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55539 | Weak algorithm used to sign RPM package. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux) before build 39185.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55539</link><description>Weak algorithm used to sign RPM package. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux) before build 39185.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12903 | Incorrect default permissions in Biamp Evoko Home</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12903</link><description>Incorrect default permissions vulnerability in Evoko Home, affecting version 2.4.2 to 2.7.4. A non-admin user could exploit weak file and folder permissions to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code and maintain persistence on the compromised machine. It has been identified that full control permissions exist on the ‘Everyone’ group (i.e. any user who has local access to the operating system regardless of their privileges).</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 13:02:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12902 | Global Wisdom Software ANCHOR - Undocumented Privileged Account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12902</link><description>ANCHOR from Global Wisdom Software is an integrated product running on a Windows virtual machine. The underlying Windows OS of the product contains high-privilege service accounts. If these accounts use default passwords, attackers could remotely log in to the virtual machine using the default credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 10:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11230 | Elementor Header &amp;amp; Footer Builder &amp;lt;= 1.6.46 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Page Title Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11230</link><description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘size’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.46 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 04:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12901 | FoxCMS API Endpoint Site.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12901</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FoxCMS up to 1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /app/api/controller/Site.php of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument password leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12900 | FoxCMS Configuration File installdb.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12900</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FoxCMS up to 1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /install/installdb.php of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation of the argument database password leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 02:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12899 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System course_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12899</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/course_action.php. The manipulation of the argument course_code leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45721 | home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the HOST name configuration sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45721</link><description>home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the HOST name configuration screen. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by an administrative user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46873 | Multiple SHARP routers leave the hidden debug function enabled. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by a remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46873</link><description>Multiple SHARP routers leave the hidden debug function enabled. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47864 | home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the hidden debug function. A remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47864</link><description>home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the hidden debug function. A remote unauthenticated attacker may get the web console of the product down.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52321 | Multiple SHARP routers contain an improper authentication vulnerability in the configuration backup function. The product's backup files con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52321</link><description>Multiple SHARP routers contain an improper authentication vulnerability in the configuration backup function. The product's backup files containing sensitive information may be retrieved by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54082 | home 5G HR02 and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the configuration restore function. An arbitrary OS c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54082</link><description>home 5G HR02 and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the configuration restore function. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by an administrative user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12898 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System faculty_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12898</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/faculty_action.php. The manipulation of the argument faculty_course_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12897 | Intelbras VIP S4320 G2 Web Interface Sha1Account1 path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12897</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Intelbras VIP S3020 G2, VIP S4020 G2, VIP S4020 G3 and VIP S4320 G2 up to 20241222. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file ../mtd/Config/Sha1Account1 of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56378 | libpoppler.so in Poppler through 24.12.0 has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability within the JBIG2Bitmap::combine function in JBIG2Stream.cc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56378</link><description>libpoppler.so in Poppler through 24.12.0 has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability within the JBIG2Bitmap::combine function in JBIG2Stream.cc.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 23:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12896 | Intelbras VIP S4320 G2 Web Interface webCapsConfig information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12896</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Intelbras VIP S3020 G2, VIP S4020 G2, VIP S4020 G3 and VIP S4320 G2 up to 20241222 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /web_caps/webCapsConfig of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor assesses that "the information disclosed in the URL is not sensitive or poses any risk to the user".</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 23:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56375 | An integer underflow was discovered in Fort 1.6.3 and 1.6.4 before 1.6.5. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56375</link><description>An integer underflow was discovered in Fort 1.6.3 and 1.6.4 before 1.6.5. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a Manifest RPKI object containing an empty fileList. Fort dereferences (and, shortly afterwards, writes to) this array during a shuffle attempt, before the validation that would normally reject it when empty. This out-of-bounds access is caused by an integer underflow that causes the surrounding loop to iterate infinitely. Because the product is permanently stuck attempting to overshuffle an array that doesn't actually exist, a crash is nearly guaranteed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56312 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Dashboard name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to injec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56312</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Dashboard name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into the name field of a Project Dashboard. When a user clicks on the project Dashboard name, the crafted payload is executed, potentially enabling the execution of arbitrary web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56313 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar feature of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56313</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar feature of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into the Notes field of a calendar event. When the event is viewed, the crafted payload is executed, potentially enabling the execution of arbitrary web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56314 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56314</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into the name field of a Project. When a user clicks on the project name to access it, the crafted payload is executed, potentially enabling the execution of arbitrary web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56310 | REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Project Dashboards name, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56310</link><description>REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Project Dashboards name, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. An attacker can exploit this by luring users into clicking on a Project Dashboards name that contains the malicious payload, which triggers a logout request and terminates their session. This vulnerability stems from the absence of CSRF protections on the logout functionality, allowing malicious actions to be executed without user consent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56311 | REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Notes section of calendar events, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56311</link><description>REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Notes section of calendar events, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. An attacker can exploit this by luring users into accessing a calendar event's notes, which triggers a logout request and terminates their session. This vulnerability stems from the absence of CSRF protections on the logout functionality, allowing malicious actions to be executed without user consent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12895 | TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt checkflag.php console_log sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12895</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt up to 963e0e0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function console_log of the file TreasureHunt/checkflag.php. The manipulation of the argument problema leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier of the patch is 8bcc649abc35b7734951be084bb522a532faac4e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 14:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12894 | TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt acesso.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12894</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt up to 963e0e0. Affected is an unknown function of the file TreasureHunt/acesso.php. The manipulation of the argument usuario leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 8bcc649abc35b7734951be084bb522a532faac4e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 12:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12893 | Portabilis i-Educar Tipo de Usuário Page 2 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12893</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /usuarios/tipos/2 of the component Tipo de Usuário Page. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 08:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12892 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System sign.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12892</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sign.php?q=account.php. The manipulation of the argument name/gender/college leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 07:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12891 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12891</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /account.php?q=quiz&amp;amp;step=2. The manipulation of the argument eid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 06:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12890 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12890</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /update.php?q=quiz&amp;amp;step=2. The manipulation of the argument eid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 06:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11852 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.10.12 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11852</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid, Carousel and Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the get_layouts() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to obtain a detailed listing of layout templates.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 02:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12884 | Codezips E-Commerce Website login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12884</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips E-Commerce Website 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 14:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51463 | IBM i server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51463</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 

is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51464 | IBM i improper HTTP header neutralization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51464</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 is vulnerable to bypassing Navigator for i interface restrictions.  By sending a specially crafted request, an authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to remotely perform operations that the user is not allowed to perform when using Navigator for i.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12883 | code-projects Job Recruitment _email.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12883</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /_email.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 13:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12875 | Easy Digital Downloads &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12875</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 via the file download functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 11:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10453 | Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.25.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Typography Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10453</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Typography Settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11688 | LaTeX2HTML &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11688</link><description>The LaTeX2HTML plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ver' or 'date' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11722 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11722</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This requires an unauthenticated user to have been given permission to view form submissions, and the form submission shortcode be added to a page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12408 | WP on AWS &amp;lt;= 5.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12408</link><description>The WP on AWS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_POST data in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12558 | WP BASE Booking of Appointments, Services and Events &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure via app_export_db</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12558</link><description>The WP BASE Booking of Appointments, Services and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_db function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to expose sensitive information from the database, such as the hashed administrator password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12591 | MagicPost &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wb_share_social Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12591</link><description>The MagicPost plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wb_share_social shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10797 | Full Screen Menu for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10797</link><description>The Full Screen Menu for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 via the  Full Screen Menu Elementor Widget due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11808 | Pingmeter Uptime Monitoring &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11808</link><description>The Pingmeter Uptime Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_wpnonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12588 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Staff Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12588</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Staff widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9545 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via aux_contact_box and aux_gmaps Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9545</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aux_contact_box and aux_gmaps shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11196 | Multi-column Tag Map &amp;lt;= 17.0.33 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mctagmap Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11196</link><description>The Multi-column Tag Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's mctagmap shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 17.0.33 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11287 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8001 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11287</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.8001. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11682 | G Web Pro Store Locator &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11682</link><description>The G Web Pro Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'q' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11938 | One Click Upsell Funnel for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wps_wocuf_pro_yes Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11938</link><description>The One Click Upsell Funnel for WooCommerce –  Funnel Builder for WordPress, Create WooCommerce Upsell, Post-Purchase Upsell &amp; Cross Sell Offers that Boost Sales &amp; Increase Profits with Sales Funnel Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wps_wocuf_pro_yes shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11975 | Reactflow Visitor Recording and Heatmaps &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11975</link><description>The Reactflow Visitor Recording and Heatmaps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation affecting the _wpnonce parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts  via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12066 | SMSA Shipping(official) &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12066</link><description>The SMSA Shipping(official) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the smsa_delete_label() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12262 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8001 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;step&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12262</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'step' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.8001 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12635 | WP Docs &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Time-Based SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;dir_id&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12635</link><description>The WP Docs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'dir_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12697 | real.Kit &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12697</link><description>The real.Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12721 | Custom Product Tabs For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12721</link><description>The Custom Product Tabs For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'wb_custom_tabs' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12771 | eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.3.43 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12771</link><description>The eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.43. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'customer_panel_password_reset' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the password of any administrator or customer account via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11607 | GTPayment Donations &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11607</link><description>The GTPayment Donations WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11977 | kk Star Ratings – Rate Post &amp;amp; Collect User Feedbacks &amp;lt;= 5.4.10 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11977</link><description>The The kk Star Ratings – Rate Post &amp; Collect User Feedbacks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.10. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 05:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12846 | Emlog Pro link.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12846</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/link.php. The manipulation of the argument siteurl/icon leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11349 | AdForest &amp;lt;= 5.1.6 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11349</link><description>The AdForest theme for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them through the sb_login_user_with_otp_fun() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as arbitrary users, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 04:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>