<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 22:42:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-28982 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28982</link><description>Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.1.0.0 and 9.3.0.7, including 8.3.x do not correctly protect the ACL service endpoint of the Pentaho User Console against XML External Entity Reference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 22:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37734 | An issue in OpenEMR 7.0.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges viaa crafted POST request using the noteid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37734</link><description>An issue in OpenEMR 7.0.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges viaa crafted POST request using the noteid parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37247 | WordPress jQuery T(-) Countdown Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37247</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in twinpictures, baden03 jQuery T(-) Countdown Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects jQuery T(-) Countdown Widget: from n/a through 2.3.25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37248 | WordPress Anima theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37248</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Anima allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Anima: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37571 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SAS Broker 9.2 build 1495 allows attackers to cause denial of service or obtain sensitive information via c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37571</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SAS Broker 9.2 build 1495 allows attackers to cause denial of service or obtain sensitive information via crafted payload to the '_debug' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36829 | Incorrect access control in Teldat M1 v11.00.05.50.01 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via a crafted query string.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36829</link><description>Incorrect access control in Teldat M1 v11.00.05.50.01 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via a crafted query string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23767 | An issue was discovered on HMS Anybus X-Gateway AB7832-F firmware version 3. The HICP protocol allows unauthenticated changes to a device's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23767</link><description>An issue was discovered on HMS Anybus X-Gateway AB7832-F firmware version 3. The HICP protocol allows unauthenticated changes to a device's network configurations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6355 | Genexis Tilgin Fiber Home Gateway HG1522 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Genexis Tilgin Fiber Home Gateway HG1522 CSx000-01_09_01_12. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /status/product_info/. The manipulation of the argument product_info leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269755. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23766 | An issue was discovered on HMS Anybus X-Gateway AB7832-F 3 devices. The gateway exposes a web interface on port 80. An unauthenticated GET r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23766</link><description>An issue was discovered on HMS Anybus X-Gateway AB7832-F 3 devices. The gateway exposes a web interface on port 80. An unauthenticated GET request to a specific URL triggers the reboot of the Anybus gateway (or at least most of its modules). An attacker can use this feature to carry out a denial of service attack by continuously sending GET requests to that URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23765 | An issue was discovered on HMS Anybus X-Gateway AB7832-F 3 devices. The gateway exposes an unidentified service on port 7412 on the network....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23765</link><description>An issue was discovered on HMS Anybus X-Gateway AB7832-F 3 devices. The gateway exposes an unidentified service on port 7412 on the network. All the network services of the gateway become unresponsive after sending 85 requests to this port. The content and length of the frame does not matter. The device needs to be restarted to resume operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1839 | Intrado 911 Emergency Gateway login form is vulnerable to an unauthenticated blind time-based SQL injection, which may allow an unauthentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1839</link><description>Intrado 911 Emergency Gateway login form is vulnerable to an unauthenticated blind time-based SQL injection, which may allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute malicious code, exfiltrate data, or manipulate the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38949 | Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Libde265 v1.0.15 allows attackers to crash the application via crafted payload to display444as420 func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38949</link><description>Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Libde265 v1.0.15 allows attackers to crash the application via crafted payload to display444as420 function at sdl.cc</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38950 | Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Libde265 v1.0.15 allows attackers to crash the application via crafted payload to __interceptor_memcpy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38950</link><description>Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Libde265 v1.0.15 allows attackers to crash the application via crafted payload to __interceptor_memcpy function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38527 | Cross-site Scripting in ZenUML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38527</link><description>ZenUML is JavaScript-based diagramming tool that requires no server, using Markdown-inspired text definitions and a renderer to create and modify sequence diagrams. Markdown-based comments in the ZenUML diagram syntax are susceptible to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The comment feature allows the user to attach small notes for reference. This feature allows the user to enter in their comment in markdown comment, allowing them to use common markdown features, such as `**` for bolded text. However, the markdown text is currently not sanitized before rendering, allowing an attacker to enter a malicious payload for the comment which leads to XSS. This puts existing applications that use ZenUML unsandboxed at risk of arbitrary JavaScript execution when rendering user-controlled diagrams. This vulnerability was patched in version 3.23.25,</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39243 | An issue discovered in skycaiji 2.8 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted POST request to /index.php?s=/admin/develop/editor_sa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39243</link><description>An issue discovered in skycaiji 2.8 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted POST request to /index.php?s=/admin/develop/editor_save.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39241 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in skycaiji 2.8 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via /admin/tool/preview.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39241</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in skycaiji 2.8 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via /admin/tool/preview.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26877 | File upload vulnerability found in Softexpert Excellence Suite v.2.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a .php file upload to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26877</link><description>File upload vulnerability found in Softexpert Excellence Suite v.2.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a .php file upload to the form/efms_exec_html/file_upload_parser.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39242 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in skycaiji v2.8 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39242</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in skycaiji v2.8 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload using eval(String.fromCharCode()).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33326 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component XsltResultControllerHtml.jsp of Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33326</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component XsltResultControllerHtml.jsp of Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the lumPageID parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33327 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component UrlAccessibilityEvaluation.jsp of Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33327</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component UrlAccessibilityEvaluation.jsp of Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the contentHtml parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33328 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component main.jsp of Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary web...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33328</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component main.jsp of Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the pageId parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33329 | A hardcoded privileged ID within Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to bypass authentication and access internal pages and other se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33329</link><description>A hardcoded privileged ID within Lumisxp v15.0.x to v16.1.x allows attackers to bypass authentication and access internal pages and other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38520 | SoftEther VPN with L2TP - 2.75x Amplification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38520</link><description>SoftEtherVPN is a an open-source cross-platform multi-protocol VPN Program. When SoftEtherVPN is deployed with L2TP enabled on a device, it introduces the possibility of the host being used for amplification/reflection traffic generation because it will respond to every packet with two response packets that are larger than the request packet size. These sorts of techniques are used by external actors who generate spoofed source IPs to target a destination on the internet. This vulnerability has been patched in version 5.02.5185.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38375 | @fastly/js-compute use-after-free in some host call implementations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38375</link><description>@fastly/js-compute is a JavaScript SDK and runtime for building Fastly Compute applications. The implementation of several functions were determined to include a use-after-free bug. This bug could allow for unintended data loss if the result of the preceding functions were sent anywhere else, and often results in a guest trap causing services to return a 500. This bug has been fixed in version 3.16.0 of the `@fastly/js-compute` package.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35545 | MAP-OS v4.45.0 and earlier was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35545</link><description>MAP-OS v4.45.0 and earlier was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39458 | When Jenkins Structs Plugin 337.v1b_04ea_4df7c8 and earlier fails to configure a build step, it logs a warning message containing diagnostic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39458</link><description>When Jenkins Structs Plugin 337.v1b_04ea_4df7c8 and earlier fails to configure a build step, it logs a warning message containing diagnostic information that may contain secrets passed as step parameters, potentially resulting in accidental exposure of secrets through the default system log.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39459 | In rare cases Jenkins Plain Credentials Plugin 182.v468b_97b_9dcb_8 and earlier stores secret file credentials unencrypted (only Base64 enco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39459</link><description>In rare cases Jenkins Plain Credentials Plugin 182.v468b_97b_9dcb_8 and earlier stores secret file credentials unencrypted (only Base64 encoded) on the Jenkins controller file system, where they can be viewed by users with access to the Jenkins controller file system (global credentials) or with Item/Extended Read permission (folder-scoped credentials).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39460 | Jenkins Bitbucket Branch Source Plugin 886.v44cf5e4ecec5 and earlier prints the Bitbucket OAuth access token as part of the Bitbucket URL in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39460</link><description>Jenkins Bitbucket Branch Source Plugin 886.v44cf5e4ecec5 and earlier prints the Bitbucket OAuth access token as part of the Bitbucket URL in the build log in some cases.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6354 | Improper access control in PAM dashboard in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.11 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6354</link><description>Improper access control in PAM dashboard in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.11 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user to bypass the execute permission via the use of the PAM dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25637 | Reflected XSS via X-October-Request-Handler Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25637</link><description>October is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. The X-October-Request-Handler Header does not sanitize the AJAX handler name and allows unescaped HTML to be reflected back. There is no impact since this vulnerability cannot be exploited through normal browser interactions. This unescaped value is only detectable when using a proxy interception tool. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.15.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38271 | Denial of Service in Quickshare</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38271</link><description>There exists a vulnerability in Quickshare/Nearby where an attacker can force the a victim to stay connected to a temporary hotspot created for the share. As part of the sequence of packets in a QuickShare connection over Bluetooth, the attacker forces the victim to connect to the attacker’s WiFi network and then sends an OfflineFrame that crashes Quick Share.
This makes the Wifi connection to the attacker’s network last instead of returning to the old network when the Quick Share session is done allowing the attacker to be a MiTM. We recommend upgrading to version 1.0.1724.0 of Quickshare or above</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38272 | Auth Bypass in Quickshare</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38272</link><description>There exists a vulnerability in Quickshare/Nearby where an attacker can bypass the accept file dialog on QuickShare Windows. Normally in QuickShare Windows app we can't send a file without the user accept from the receiving device if the visibility is set to everyone mode or contacts mode. We recommend upgrading to version 1.0.1724.0 of Quickshare or above</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4604 | Open Redirect in Magarsus Consultancy&amp;#x27;s SSO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4604</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Magarsus Consultancy SSO (Single Sign On) allows Manipulating Hidden Fields.This issue affects SSO (Single Sign On): from 1.0 before 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4228 | SQLi in Magarsus Consultancy&amp;#x27;s SSO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection'), CWE - 200 - Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, CWE - 522 - Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Magarsus Consultancy SSO (Single Sign On) allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SSO (Single Sign On): from 1.0 before 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37098 | WordPress BlossomThemes Email Newsletter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37098</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Blossom Themes BlossomThemes Email Newsletter.This issue affects BlossomThemes Email Newsletter: from n/a through 2.2.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6344 | ZKTeco ZKBio CVSecurity V5000 Push Configuration Section cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6344</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ZKTeco ZKBio CVSecurity V5000 4.1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Push Configuration Section. The manipulation of the argument Configuration Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-269733 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37252 | WordPress Email Subscribers by Icegram Express plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.25 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37252</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Icegram Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters.This issue affects Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters: from n/a through 5.7.25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28830 | Automation user secrets written to audit log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28830</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p7, &lt;2.2.0p28, &lt;2.1.0p45 and &lt;=2.0.0p39 (EOL) causes automation user secrets to be written to audit log files accessible to administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 08:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5215 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5215</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3633 | WebP &amp;amp; SVG Support &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3633</link><description>The WebP &amp; SVG Support WordPress plugin through 1.4.0 does not sanitise uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4758 | Muslim Prayer Time BD &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Settings Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4758</link><description>The Muslim Prayer Time BD WordPress plugin through 2.4 does not have CSRF check in place when reseting its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin reset them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4957 | Frontend Checklist &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4957</link><description>The Frontend Checklist WordPress plugin through 2.3.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4959 | Frontend Checklist &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Items</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4959</link><description>The Frontend Checklist WordPress plugin through 2.3.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5071 | Bookster &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Unauthenticated Appointment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5071</link><description>The Bookster  WordPress plugin through 1.1.0 allows adding sensitive parameters when validating appointments allowing attackers to manipulate the data sent when booking an appointment (the request body) to change its status from pending to approved.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5169 | Video Widget &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5169</link><description>The Video Widget WordPress plugin through 1.2.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5199 | Spotify Play Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5199</link><description>The Spotify Play Button WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5473 |  Simple Photoswipe &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5473</link><description>The Simple Photoswipe WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5573 | Easy Table of Contents &amp;lt; 2.0.66 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5573</link><description>The Easy Table of Contents WordPress plugin before 2.0.66 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5332 | Exclusive Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.6.9.8 - Authenticated (Contibutor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Card Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5332</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Card widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4106 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS and CI Server. The affected products have built-in accounts with no passwords set. Therefore, i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS and CI Server. The affected products have built-in accounts with no passwords set. Therefore, if the product is operated without a password set by default, an attacker can break into the affected product.
The affected products and versions are as follows:
FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to R10.04
CI Server R1.01.00 to R1.03.00</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4105 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS and CI Server. The affected product's WEB HMI server's function to process HTTP requests has a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4105</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS and CI Server. The affected product's WEB HMI server's function to process HTTP requests has a security flaw (Reflected XSS) that allows the execution of malicious scripts. Therefore, if a client PC with inadequate security measures accesses a product URL containing a malicious request, the malicious script may be executed on the client PC.
The affected products and versions are as follows:
FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to R10.04
CI Server R1.01.00 to R1.03.00</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21520 | Versions of the package djangorestframework before 3.15.2 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the break_long_headers template f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21520</link><description>Versions of the package djangorestframework before 3.15.2 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the break_long_headers template filter due to improper input sanitization before splitting and joining with &lt;br /&gt; tags.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34580 | Apache XML Security for C++ through 2.0.4 implements the XML Signature Syntax and Processing (XMLDsig) specification without protection agai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34580</link><description>Apache XML Security for C++ through 2.0.4 implements the XML Signature Syntax and Processing (XMLDsig) specification without protection against an SSRF payload in a KeyInfo element. NOTE: the supplier disputes this CVE Record on the grounds that they are implementing the specification "correctly" and are not "at fault."</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34581 | The W3C XML Signature Syntax and Processing (XMLDsig) specification, starting with 1.0, was originally published with a "RetrievalMethod is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34581</link><description>The W3C XML Signature Syntax and Processing (XMLDsig) specification, starting with 1.0, was originally published with a "RetrievalMethod is a URI ... that may be used to obtain key and/or certificate information" statement and no accompanying information about SSRF risks, and this may have contributed to vulnerable implementations such as those discussed in CVE-2023-36661 and CVE-2024-21893. NOTE: this was mitigated in 1.1 and 2.0 via a directly referenced Best Practices document that calls on implementers to be wary of SSRF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37140 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain an OS command injection vulnerability in an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37140</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain an OS command injection vulnerability in an admin operation. A remote low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the system application's underlying OS with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to a system take over by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 04:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37141 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain an open redirect vulnerability. A remote low ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37141</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain an open redirect vulnerability. A remote low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 04:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37139 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain an Improper Control of a Resource Through its...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37139</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain an Improper Control of a Resource Through its Lifetime vulnerability in an admin operation. A remote low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to temporary resource constraint of system application. Exploitation may lead to denial of service of the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37138 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 on DDMC contain a relative path traversal vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37138</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 on DDMC contain a relative path traversal vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the application sending over an unauthorized file to the managed system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27867 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in AirPods Firmware Update 6A326, AirPods Firmware...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27867</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in AirPods Firmware Update 6A326, AirPods Firmware Update 6F8, and Beats Firmware Update 6F8. When your headphones are seeking a connection request to one of your previously paired devices, an attacker in Bluetooth range might be able to spoof the intended source device and gain access to your headphones.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29174 | Dell Data Domain, versions prior to 7.13.0.0, LTS 7.7.5.30, LTS 7.10.1.20 contain an SQL Injection vulnerability. A local low privileged att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29174</link><description>Dell Data Domain, versions prior to 7.13.0.0, LTS 7.7.5.30, LTS 7.10.1.20 contain an SQL Injection vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of certain SQL commands on the application's backend database causing unauthorized access to application data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29175 | Dell PowerProtect Data Domain, versions prior to 7.13.0.0, LTS 7.7.5.40, LTS 7.10.1.30 contain an weak cryptographic algorithm vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29175</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Domain, versions prior to 7.13.0.0, LTS 7.7.5.40, LTS 7.10.1.30 contain an weak cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to man-in-the-middle attack that exposes sensitive session information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29173 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29173</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to disclosure of information on the application or remote client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5181 | Command Injection in mudler/localai</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5181</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the mudler/localai version 2.14.0. The vulnerability arises from the application's handling of the backend parameter in the configuration file, which is used in the name of the initialized process. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the path of the vulnerable binary file specified in the backend parameter, allowing the execution of arbitrary code on the system. This issue is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command, leading to potential full control over the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29177 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a disclosure of temporary sensitive informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29177</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a disclosure of temporary sensitive information vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the reuse of disclosed information to gain unauthorized access to the application report.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28973 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28973</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the storage of malicious HTML or JavaScript codes in a trusted application data store. When a high privileged victim user accesses the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29176 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. A remote low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29176</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to 8.0, LTS 7.13.1.0, LTS 7.10.1.30, LTS 7.7.5.40 contain a buffer overflow vulnerability. A remote low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to an application crash or execution of arbitrary code on the vulnerable application's underlying operating system with privileges of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5173 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Player Widget Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5173</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Video player widget settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24764 | October Open Redirect for Administrator Accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24764</link><description>October is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. This issue affects authenticated administrators who may be redirected to an untrusted URL using the PageFinder schema.  The resolver for the page finder link schema (`october://`) allowed external links, therefore allowing an open redirect outside the scope of the active host. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.5.15.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38526 | pdoc embeds link to malicious CDN if math mode is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38526</link><description>pdoc provides API Documentation for Python Projects. Documentation generated with `pdoc --math` linked to JavaScript files from polyfill.io. The polyfill.io CDN has been sold and now serves malicious code. This issue has been fixed in pdoc 14.5.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5460 | Brocade Fabric OS versions prior to v9.0 have default community strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5460</link><description>A vulnerability in the default configuration of the Simple Network 
Management Protocol (SNMP) feature of Brocade Fabric OS versions before 
v9.0.0 could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read data from 
an affected device via SNMP. The vulnerability is due to hard-coded, 
default community string in the configuration file for the SNMP daemon. 
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the static 
community string in SNMP version 1 queries to an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38364 | DSpace Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via a deposited HTML/XML document</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38364</link><description>DSpace is an open source software is a turnkey repository application used by more than 2,000 organizations and institutions worldwide to provide durable access to digital resources. In DSpace 7.0 through 7.6.1, when an HTML, XML or JavaScript Bitstream is downloaded, the user's browser may execute any embedded JavaScript. If that embedded JavaScript is malicious, there is a risk of an XSS attack. This vulnerability has been patched in version 7.6.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29954 | password management API prints sensitive information in log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29954</link><description>A vulnerability in a password management API in Brocade Fabric OS versions before v9.2.1, v9.2.0b, v9.1.1d, and v8.2.3e prints sensitive information in log files. This could allow an authenticated user to view the server passwords for protocols such as scp and sftp.

Detail.
When the firmwaredownload command is incorrectly entered or points to an erroneous file, the firmware download log captures the failed command, including any password entered in the command line.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4869 | WP Cookie Consent ( for GDPR, CCPA &amp;amp; ePrivacy ) &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Client-IP header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4869</link><description>The WP Cookie Consent ( for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘Client-IP’ header in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29953 | Encoded session passwords on session storage for Virtual Fabric platforms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29953</link><description>A vulnerability in the web interface in Brocade Fabric OS before v9.2.1, v9.2.0b, and v9.1.1d prints encoded session passwords on session storage for Virtual Fabric platforms. 
This could allow an authenticated user to view other users' session encoded passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37742 | An issue in Safe Exam Browser for Windows before 3.6 allows an attacker to share clipboard data between the SEB kiosk mode and the underlyin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37742</link><description>An issue in Safe Exam Browser for Windows before 3.6 allows an attacker to share clipboard data between the SEB kiosk mode and the underlying system, compromising exam integrity which may lead to arbitrary code execution and obtaining sensitive information via the Clipboard Management component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6060 | An information disclosure vulnerability in Phloc Webscopes 7.0.0 allows local attackers with access to the log files to view logged HTTP req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6060</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Phloc Webscopes 7.0.0 allows local attackers with access to the log files to view logged HTTP requests that contain user passwords or other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30112 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30112</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting attack where an attacker may leverage this issue to execute arbitrary script code in the browser of an unsuspecting user which leads to executing malicious script code. This may let the attacker steal cookie-based authentication credentials and comprise user's account then launch other attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30931 | Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Emby Media Server Emby Media Server 4.8.3.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30931</link><description>Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Emby Media Server Emby Media Server 4.8.3.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the notifications.html component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35527 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /fileupload/upload.cfm in Daemon PTY Limited FarCry Core framework before 7.2.14 allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35527</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /fileupload/upload.cfm in Daemon PTY Limited FarCry Core framework before 7.2.14 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted .cfm file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35526 | An issue in Daemon PTY Limited FarCry Core framework before 7.2.14 allows attackers to access sensitive information in the /facade directory...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35526</link><description>An issue in Daemon PTY Limited FarCry Core framework before 7.2.14 allows attackers to access sensitive information in the /facade directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34400 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Kanban Board Web Part before 5.3.5.1 for SharePoint 2019. There is /_layouts/15/Virto.KanbanT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34400</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Kanban Board Web Part before 5.3.5.1 for SharePoint 2019. There is /_layouts/15/Virto.KanbanTaskManager/api/KanbanData.ashx LinkTitle2 XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21739 | Geehy APM32F103CCT6, APM32F103RCT6, APM32F103RCT7, and APM32F103VCT6 devices have Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21739</link><description>Geehy APM32F103CCT6, APM32F103RCT6, APM32F103RCT7, and APM32F103VCT6 devices have Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21740 | Artery AT32F415CBT7 and AT32F421C8T7 devices have Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21740</link><description>Artery AT32F415CBT7 and AT32F421C8T7 devices have Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21741 | GigaDevice GD32E103C8T6 devices have Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21741</link><description>GigaDevice GD32E103C8T6 devices have Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37843 | Craft CMS up to v3.7.31 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the GraphQL API endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37843</link><description>Craft CMS up to v3.7.31 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the GraphQL API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37855 | An issue in Nepstech Wifi Router xpon (terminal) NTPL-Xpon1GFEVN, hardware verstion 1.0 firmware 2.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37855</link><description>An issue in Nepstech Wifi Router xpon (terminal) NTPL-Xpon1GFEVN, hardware verstion 1.0 firmware 2.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the router's Telnet port 2345 without requiring authentication credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5019 | WhatsUp Gold LoadCSSUsingBasePath Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5019</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, 

an unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read issue exists in Wug.UI.Areas.Wug.Controllers.SessionController.CachedCSS. This vulnerability allows reading of any file with iisapppool\NmConsole privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5016 | WhatsUp Gold OnMessage Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5016</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, Distributed Edition installations can be exploited by using a deserialization tool to achieve a Remote Code Execution as SYSTEM. 
The vulnerability exists in the main message processing routines NmDistributed.DistributedServiceBehavior.OnMessage for server and NmDistributed.DistributedClient.OnMessage for clients.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5017 | WhatsUp Gold AppProfileImport path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5017</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, a path traversal vulnerability exists. A specially crafted unauthenticated HTTP request to AppProfileImport can lead can lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5018 | WhatsUp Gold LoadUsingBasePath Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5018</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an unauthenticated Path Traversal vulnerability exists Wug.UI.Areas.Wug.Controllers.SessionController.LoadNMScript. This allows allows reading of any file from the applications web-root directory .</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38516 | Aimeos HTML client may potentially reveal sensitive information in error log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38516</link><description>ai-client-html is an Aimeos e-commerce HTML client component. Debug information revealed sensitive information from environment variables in error log. This issue has been patched in versions 2024.04.7, 2023.10.15, 2022.10.13 and 2021.10.22.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5012 | WhatsUp Gold Missing Authentication GetWindowsCredential Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5012</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, there is a missing authentication vulnerability in WUGDataAccess.Credentials. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to disclose Windows Credentials stored in the product Credential Library.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5013 | WhatsUp Gold InstallController Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5013</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an unauthenticated Denial of Service 

vulnerability was identified. An unauthenticated attacker can put the application into the SetAdminPassword installation step, which renders the application non-accessible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5014 | WhatsUp Gold GetASPReport Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5014</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, a Server Side Request Forgery vulnerability exists in the GetASPReport feature. This allows any authenticated user to retrieve ASP reports from an HTML form.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5015 | WhatsUp Gold SessionControler Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5015</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an authenticated SSRF vulnerability in Wug.UI.Areas.Wug.Controllers.SessionControler.Update allows a low privileged user to chain this SSRF with an Improper Access Control vulnerability. This can be used to escalate privileges to Admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5011 | WhatsUp Gold TestController Chart denial of service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5011</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability exists. A specially crafted unauthenticated HTTP request to the TestController Chart functionality can lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6206 | A security vulnerability has been identified in HPE Athonet Mobile Core software. The core application contains a code injection vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6206</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in HPE Athonet Mobile Core software. The core application contains a code injection vulnerability where a threat actor could execute arbitrary commands with the privilege of the underlying container leading to complete takeover of the target system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5009 | WhatsUp Gold SetAdminPassword Improper Access Control Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5009</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an Improper Access Control vulnerability in Wug.UI.Controllers.InstallController.SetAdminPassword allows local attackers to modify admin's password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5010 | WhatsUp Gold TestController multiple information disclosure vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5010</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, a vulnerability exists in the TestController functionality.  A specially crafted 

unauthenticated

HTTP request can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4498 | Path Traversal and RFI Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4498</link><description>A Path Traversal and Remote File Inclusion (RFI) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting versions v9.7 to the latest. The vulnerability arises from insufficient input validation in the `/apply_settings` function, allowing an attacker to manipulate the `discussion_db_name` parameter to traverse the file system and include arbitrary files. This issue is compounded by the bypass of input filtering in the `install_binding`, `reinstall_binding`, and `unInstall_binding` endpoints, despite the presence of a `sanitize_path_from_endpoint(data.name)` filter. Successful exploitation enables an attacker to upload and execute malicious code on the victim's system, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4885 | WhatsUp Gold GetFileWithoutZip Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4885</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an unauthenticated Remote Code Execution vulnerability in Progress WhatsUpGold.  The 

WhatsUp.ExportUtilities.Export.GetFileWithoutZip



 allows execution of commands with iisapppool\nmconsole privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5008 | WhatsUp Gold APM Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5008</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, 

an authenticated user with certain permissions can upload an arbitrary file and obtain RCE using Apm.UI.Areas.APM.Controllers.Api.Applications.AppProfileImportController.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37894 | Squid vulnerable to heap corruption in ESI assign</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37894</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to an Out-of-bounds Write error when assigning ESI variables, Squid is susceptible to a Memory Corruption error. This error can lead to a Denial of Service attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4883 | WhatsUp Gold WriteDataFile Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4883</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, a Remote Code Execution issue exists in Progress WhatsUp Gold. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve the RCE as a service account through NmApi.exe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4884 | WhatsUp Gold CommunityController Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4884</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2023.1.3, an unauthenticated Remote Code Execution vulnerability in Progress WhatsUpGold.  The Apm.UI.Areas.APM.Controllers.CommunityController

 allows execution of commands with iisapppool\nmconsole privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37167 | Tuleap has improper permissions of the backlog items</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37167</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Users are able to see backlog items that they should not see. This issue has been patched in Tuleap Community Edition version 15.9.99.97.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5276 | SQL Injection Vulnerability in FileCatalyst Workflow 5.1.6 Build 135 (and earlier)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5276</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in Fortra FileCatalyst Workflow allows an attacker to modify application data.  Likely impacts include creation of administrative users and deletion or modification of data in the application database. Data exfiltration via SQL injection is not possible using this vulnerability. Successful unauthenticated exploitation requires a Workflow system with anonymous access enabled, otherwise an authenticated user is required. This issue affects all versions of FileCatalyst Workflow from 5.1.6 Build 135 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37820 | A nil pointer dereference in PingCAP TiDB v8.2.0-alpha-216-gfe5858b allows attackers to crash the application via expression.inferCollation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37820</link><description>A nil pointer dereference in PingCAP TiDB v8.2.0-alpha-216-gfe5858b allows attackers to crash the application via expression.inferCollation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36819 | MAP-OS 4.45.0 and earlier is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allows malicious users to insert a malicious paylo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36819</link><description>MAP-OS 4.45.0 and earlier is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This vulnerability allows malicious users to insert a malicious payload into the "Client Name" input. When a service order from this client is created, the malicious payload is displayed on the administrator and employee dashboards, resulting in unauthorized script execution whenever the dashboard is loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6308 | itsourcecode Simple Online Hotel Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6308</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 17:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6257 | HashiCorp go-getter Vulnerable to Code Execution On Git Update Via Git Config Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6257</link><description>HashiCorp’s go-getter library can be coerced into executing Git update on an existing maliciously modified Git Configuration, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5990 | ThinManager® ThinServer™ Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link><description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6238 | pgAdmin 4 Installation Directory permission issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6238</link><description>pgAdmin &lt;= 8.8 has an installation Directory permission issue. Because of this issue, attackers can gain unauthorised access to the installation directory on the Debian or RHEL 8 platforms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5989 | Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™ Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link><description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5988 | Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™ Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link><description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0171 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS contains an TOCTOU race condition vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0171</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS contains an TOCTOU race condition vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain access to otherwise unauthorized resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37541 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to a broken access control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37541</link><description>HCL Connections contains a broken access control vulnerability that may allow unauthorized user to update data in certain scenarios.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5805 | MOVEit Gateway Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5805</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Gateway (SFTP modules) allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MOVEit Gateway: 2024.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5806 | MOVEit Transfer Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5806</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Transfer (SFTP module) can lead to Authentication Bypass in limited scenarios.This issue affects MOVEit Transfer: from 2023.0.0 before 2023.0.11, from 2023.1.0 before 2023.1.6, from 2024.0.0 before 2024.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4440 | x86/xen: Drop USERGS_SYSRET64 paravirt call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4440</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/xen: Drop USERGS_SYSRET64 paravirt call

commit afd30525a659ac0ae0904f0cb4a2ca75522c3123 upstream.

USERGS_SYSRET64 is used to return from a syscall via SYSRET, but
a Xen PV guest will nevertheless use the IRET hypercall, as there
is no sysret PV hypercall defined.

So instead of testing all the prerequisites for doing a sysret and
then mangling the stack for Xen PV again for doing an iret just use
the iret exit from the beginning.

This can easily be done via an ALTERNATIVE like it is done for the
sysenter compat case already.

It should be noted that this drops the optimization in Xen for not
restoring a few registers when returning to user mode, but it seems
as if the saved instructions in the kernel more than compensate for
this drop (a kernel build in a Xen PV guest was slightly faster with
this patch applied).

While at it remove the stale sysret32 remnants.

  [ pawan: Brad Spengler and Salvatore Bonaccorso 
	   reported a problem with the 5.10 backport commit edc702b4a820
	   ("x86/entry_64: Add VERW just before userspace transition").

	   When CONFIG_PARAVIRT_XXL=y, CLEAR_CPU_BUFFERS is not executed in
	   syscall_return_via_sysret path as USERGS_SYSRET64 is runtime
	   patched to:

	.cpu_usergs_sysret64    = { 0x0f, 0x01, 0xf8,
				    0x48, 0x0f, 0x07 }, // swapgs; sysretq

	   which is missing CLEAR_CPU_BUFFERS. It turns out dropping
	   USERGS_SYSRET64 simplifies the code, allowing CLEAR_CPU_BUFFERS
	   to be explicitly added to syscall_return_via_sysret path. Below
	   is with CONFIG_PARAVIRT_XXL=y and this patch applied:

	   syscall_return_via_sysret:
	   ...
	   &lt;+342&gt;:   swapgs
	   &lt;+345&gt;:   xchg   %ax,%ax
	   &lt;+347&gt;:   verw   -0x1a2(%rip)  &lt;------
	   &lt;+354&gt;:   sysretq
  ]</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48772 | media: lgdt3306a: Add a check against null-pointer-def</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48772</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: lgdt3306a: Add a check against null-pointer-def

The driver should check whether the client provides the platform_data.

The following log reveals it:

[   29.610324] BUG: KASAN: null-ptr-deref in kmemdup+0x30/0x40
[   29.610730] Read of size 40 at addr 0000000000000000 by task bash/414
[   29.612820] Call Trace:
[   29.613030]  
[   29.613201]  dump_stack_lvl+0x56/0x6f
[   29.613496]  ? kmemdup+0x30/0x40
[   29.613754]  print_report.cold+0x494/0x6b7
[   29.614082]  ? kmemdup+0x30/0x40
[   29.614340]  kasan_report+0x8a/0x190
[   29.614628]  ? kmemdup+0x30/0x40
[   29.614888]  kasan_check_range+0x14d/0x1d0
[   29.615213]  memcpy+0x20/0x60
[   29.615454]  kmemdup+0x30/0x40
[   29.615700]  lgdt3306a_probe+0x52/0x310
[   29.616339]  i2c_device_probe+0x951/0xa90</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37078 | nilfs2: fix potential kernel bug due to lack of writeback flag waiting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37078</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix potential kernel bug due to lack of writeback flag waiting

Destructive writes to a block device on which nilfs2 is mounted can cause
a kernel bug in the folio/page writeback start routine or writeback end
routine (__folio_start_writeback in the log below):

 kernel BUG at mm/page-writeback.c:3070!
 Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN PTI
 ...
 RIP: 0010:__folio_start_writeback+0xbaa/0x10e0
 Code: 25 ff 0f 00 00 0f 84 18 01 00 00 e8 40 ca c6 ff e9 17 f6 ff ff
  e8 36 ca c6 ff 4c 89 f7 48 c7 c6 80 c0 12 84 e8 e7 b3 0f 00 90 &lt;0f&gt;
  0b e8 1f ca c6 ff 4c 89 f7 48 c7 c6 a0 c6 12 84 e8 d0 b3 0f 00
 ...
 Call Trace:
  
  nilfs_segctor_do_construct+0x4654/0x69d0 [nilfs2]
  nilfs_segctor_construct+0x181/0x6b0 [nilfs2]
  nilfs_segctor_thread+0x548/0x11c0 [nilfs2]
  kthread+0x2f0/0x390
  ret_from_fork+0x4b/0x80
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
  

This is because when the log writer starts a writeback for segment summary
blocks or a super root block that use the backing device's page cache, it
does not wait for the ongoing folio/page writeback, resulting in an
inconsistent writeback state.

Fix this issue by waiting for ongoing writebacks when putting
folios/pages on the backing device into writeback state.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37354 | btrfs: fix crash on racing fsync and size-extending write into prealloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37354</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix crash on racing fsync and size-extending write into prealloc

We have been seeing crashes on duplicate keys in
btrfs_set_item_key_safe():

  BTRFS critical (device vdb): slot 4 key (450 108 8192) new key (450 108 8192)
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  kernel BUG at fs/btrfs/ctree.c:2620!
  invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 0 PID: 3139 Comm: xfs_io Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.9.0 #6
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:btrfs_set_item_key_safe+0x11f/0x290 [btrfs]

With the following stack trace:

  #0  btrfs_set_item_key_safe (fs/btrfs/ctree.c:2620:4)
  #1  btrfs_drop_extents (fs/btrfs/file.c:411:4)
  #2  log_one_extent (fs/btrfs/tree-log.c:4732:9)
  #3  btrfs_log_changed_extents (fs/btrfs/tree-log.c:4955:9)
  #4  btrfs_log_inode (fs/btrfs/tree-log.c:6626:9)
  #5  btrfs_log_inode_parent (fs/btrfs/tree-log.c:7070:8)
  #6  btrfs_log_dentry_safe (fs/btrfs/tree-log.c:7171:8)
  #7  btrfs_sync_file (fs/btrfs/file.c:1933:8)
  #8  vfs_fsync_range (fs/sync.c:188:9)
  #9  vfs_fsync (fs/sync.c:202:9)
  #10 do_fsync (fs/sync.c:212:9)
  #11 __do_sys_fdatasync (fs/sync.c:225:9)
  #12 __se_sys_fdatasync (fs/sync.c:223:1)
  #13 __x64_sys_fdatasync (fs/sync.c:223:1)
  #14 do_syscall_x64 (arch/x86/entry/common.c:52:14)
  #15 do_syscall_64 (arch/x86/entry/common.c:83:7)
  #16 entry_SYSCALL_64+0xaf/0x14c (arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:121)

So we're logging a changed extent from fsync, which is splitting an
extent in the log tree. But this split part already exists in the tree,
triggering the BUG().

This is the state of the log tree at the time of the crash, dumped with
drgn (https://github.com/osandov/drgn/blob/main/contrib/btrfs_tree.py)
to get more details than btrfs_print_leaf() gives us:

  &gt;&gt;&gt; print_extent_buffer(prog.crashed_thread().stack_trace()[0]["eb"])
  leaf 33439744 level 0 items 72 generation 9 owner 18446744073709551610
  leaf 33439744 flags 0x100000000000000
  fs uuid e5bd3946-400c-4223-8923-190ef1f18677
  chunk uuid d58cb17e-6d02-494a-829a-18b7d8a399da
          item 0 key (450 INODE_ITEM 0) itemoff 16123 itemsize 160
                  generation 7 transid 9 size 8192 nbytes 8473563889606862198
                  block group 0 mode 100600 links 1 uid 0 gid 0 rdev 0
                  sequence 204 flags 0x10(PREALLOC)
                  atime 1716417703.220000000 (2024-05-22 15:41:43)
                  ctime 1716417704.983333333 (2024-05-22 15:41:44)
                  mtime 1716417704.983333333 (2024-05-22 15:41:44)
                  otime 17592186044416.000000000 (559444-03-08 01:40:16)
          item 1 key (450 INODE_REF 256) itemoff 16110 itemsize 13
                  index 195 namelen 3 name: 193
          item 2 key (450 XATTR_ITEM 1640047104) itemoff 16073 itemsize 37
                  location key (0 UNKNOWN.0 0) type XATTR
                  transid 7 data_len 1 name_len 6
                  name: user.a
                  data a
          item 3 key (450 EXTENT_DATA 0) itemoff 16020 itemsize 53
                  generation 9 type 1 (regular)
                  extent data disk byte 303144960 nr 12288
                  extent data offset 0 nr 4096 ram 12288
                  extent compression 0 (none)
          item 4 key (450 EXTENT_DATA 4096) itemoff 15967 itemsize 53
                  generation 9 type 2 (prealloc)
                  prealloc data disk byte 303144960 nr 12288
                  prealloc data offset 4096 nr 8192
          item 5 key (450 EXTENT_DATA 8192) itemoff 15914 itemsize 53
                  generation 9 type 2 (prealloc)
                  prealloc data disk byte 303144960 nr 12288
                  prealloc data offset 8192 nr 4096
  ...

So the real problem happened earlier: notice that items 4 (4k-12k) and 5
(8k-12k) overlap. Both are prealloc extents. Item 4 straddles i_size and
item 5 starts at i_size.

Here is the state of 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38306 | btrfs: protect folio::private when attaching extent buffer folios</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38306</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: protect folio::private when attaching extent buffer folios

[BUG]
Since v6.8 there are rare kernel crashes reported by various people,
the common factor is bad page status error messages like this:

  BUG: Bad page state in process kswapd0  pfn:d6e840
  page: refcount:0 mapcount:0 mapping:000000007512f4f2 index:0x2796c2c7c
  pfn:0xd6e840
  aops:btree_aops ino:1
  flags: 0x17ffffe0000008(uptodate|node=0|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x3fffff)
  page_type: 0xffffffff()
  raw: 0017ffffe0000008 dead000000000100 dead000000000122 ffff88826d0be4c0
  raw: 00000002796c2c7c 0000000000000000 00000000ffffffff 0000000000000000
  page dumped because: non-NULL mapping

[CAUSE]
Commit 09e6cef19c9f ("btrfs: refactor alloc_extent_buffer() to
allocate-then-attach method") changes the sequence when allocating a new
extent buffer.

Previously we always called grab_extent_buffer() under
mapping-&gt;i_private_lock, to ensure the safety on modification on
folio::private (which is a pointer to extent buffer for regular
sectorsize).

This can lead to the following race:

Thread A is trying to allocate an extent buffer at bytenr X, with 4
4K pages, meanwhile thread B is trying to release the page at X + 4K
(the second page of the extent buffer at X).

           Thread A                |                 Thread B
-----------------------------------+-------------------------------------
                                   | btree_release_folio()
				   | | This is for the page at X + 4K,
				   | | Not page X.
				   | |
alloc_extent_buffer()              | |- release_extent_buffer()
|- filemap_add_folio() for the     | |  |- atomic_dec_and_test(eb-&gt;refs)
|  page at bytenr X (the first     | |  |
|  page).                          | |  |
|  Which returned -EEXIST.         | |  |
|                                  | |  |
|- filemap_lock_folio()            | |  |
|  Returned the first page locked. | |  |
|                                  | |  |
|- grab_extent_buffer()            | |  |
|  |- atomic_inc_not_zero()        | |  |
|  |  Returned false               | |  |
|  |- folio_detach_private()       | |  |- folio_detach_private() for X
|     |- folio_test_private()      | |     |- folio_test_private()
      |  Returned true             | |     |  Returned true
      |- folio_put()               |       |- folio_put()

Now there are two puts on the same folio at folio X, leading to refcount
underflow of the folio X, and eventually causing the BUG_ON() on the
page-&gt;mapping.

The condition is not that easy to hit:

- The release must be triggered for the middle page of an eb
  If the release is on the same first page of an eb, page lock would kick
  in and prevent the race.

- folio_detach_private() has a very small race window
  It's only between folio_test_private() and folio_clear_private().

That's exactly when mapping-&gt;i_private_lock is used to prevent such race,
and commit 09e6cef19c9f ("btrfs: refactor alloc_extent_buffer() to
allocate-then-attach method") screwed that up.

At that time, I thought the page lock would kick in as
filemap_release_folio() also requires the page to be locked, but forgot
the filemap_release_folio() only locks one page, not all pages of an
extent buffer.

[FIX]
Move all the code requiring i_private_lock into
attach_eb_folio_to_filemap(), so that everything is done with proper
lock protection.

Furthermore to prevent future problems, add an extra
lockdep_assert_locked() to ensure we're holding the proper lock.

To reproducer that is able to hit the race (takes a few minutes with
instrumented code inserting delays to alloc_extent_buffer()):

  #!/bin/sh
  drop_caches () {
	  while(true); do
		  echo 3 &gt; /proc/sys/vm/drop_caches
		  echo 1 &gt; /proc/sys/vm/compact_memory
	  done
  }

  run_tar () {
	  while(true); do
		  for x in `seq 1 80` ; do
			  tar cf /dev/zero /mnt &gt; /dev/null &amp;
		  done
		  wait
	  done
  }

  mkfs.btrfs -f -d single -m single
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38385 | genirq/irqdesc: Prevent use-after-free in irq_find_at_or_after()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38385</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

genirq/irqdesc: Prevent use-after-free in irq_find_at_or_after()

irq_find_at_or_after() dereferences the interrupt descriptor which is
returned by mt_find() while neither holding sparse_irq_lock nor RCU read
lock, which means the descriptor can be freed between mt_find() and the
dereference:

    CPU0                            CPU1
    desc = mt_find()
                                    delayed_free_desc(desc)
    irq_desc_get_irq(desc)

The use-after-free is reported by KASAN:

    Call trace:
     irq_get_next_irq+0x58/0x84
     show_stat+0x638/0x824
     seq_read_iter+0x158/0x4ec
     proc_reg_read_iter+0x94/0x12c
     vfs_read+0x1e0/0x2c8

    Freed by task 4471:
     slab_free_freelist_hook+0x174/0x1e0
     __kmem_cache_free+0xa4/0x1dc
     kfree+0x64/0x128
     irq_kobj_release+0x28/0x3c
     kobject_put+0xcc/0x1e0
     delayed_free_desc+0x14/0x2c
     rcu_do_batch+0x214/0x720

Guard the access with a RCU read lock section.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38661 | s390/ap: Fix crash in AP internal function modify_bitmap()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38661</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/ap: Fix crash in AP internal function modify_bitmap()

A system crash like this

  Failing address: 200000cb7df6f000 TEID: 200000cb7df6f403
  Fault in home space mode while using kernel ASCE.
  AS:00000002d71bc007 R3:00000003fe5b8007 S:000000011a446000 P:000000015660c13d
  Oops: 0038 ilc:3 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
  Modules linked in: mlx5_ib ...
  CPU: 8 PID: 7556 Comm: bash Not tainted 6.9.0-rc7 #8
  Hardware name: IBM 3931 A01 704 (LPAR)
  Krnl PSW : 0704e00180000000 0000014b75e7b606 (ap_parse_bitmap_str+0x10e/0x1f8)
  R:0 T:1 IO:1 EX:1 Key:0 M:1 W:0 P:0 AS:3 CC:2 PM:0 RI:0 EA:3
  Krnl GPRS: 0000000000000001 ffffffffffffffc0 0000000000000001 00000048f96b75d3
  000000cb00000100 ffffffffffffffff ffffffffffffffff 000000cb7df6fce0
  000000cb7df6fce0 00000000ffffffff 000000000000002b 00000048ffffffff
  000003ff9b2dbc80 200000cb7df6fcd8 0000014bffffffc0 000000cb7df6fbc8
  Krnl Code: 0000014b75e7b5fc: a7840047            brc     8,0000014b75e7b68a
  0000014b75e7b600: 18b2                lr      %r11,%r2
  #0000014b75e7b602: a7f4000a            brc     15,0000014b75e7b616
  &gt;0000014b75e7b606: eb22d00000e6        laog    %r2,%r2,0(%r13)
  0000014b75e7b60c: a7680001            lhi     %r6,1
  0000014b75e7b610: 187b                lr      %r7,%r11
  0000014b75e7b612: 84960021            brxh    %r9,%r6,0000014b75e7b654
  0000014b75e7b616: 18e9                lr      %r14,%r9
  Call Trace:
  [&lt;0000014b75e7b606&gt;] ap_parse_bitmap_str+0x10e/0x1f8
  ([&lt;0000014b75e7b5dc&gt;] ap_parse_bitmap_str+0xe4/0x1f8)
  [&lt;0000014b75e7b758&gt;] apmask_store+0x68/0x140
  [&lt;0000014b75679196&gt;] kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x14e/0x1e8
  [&lt;0000014b75598524&gt;] vfs_write+0x1b4/0x448
  [&lt;0000014b7559894c&gt;] ksys_write+0x74/0x100
  [&lt;0000014b7618a440&gt;] __do_syscall+0x268/0x328
  [&lt;0000014b761a3558&gt;] system_call+0x70/0x98
  INFO: lockdep is turned off.
  Last Breaking-Event-Address:
  [&lt;0000014b75e7b636&gt;] ap_parse_bitmap_str+0x13e/0x1f8
  Kernel panic - not syncing: Fatal exception: panic_on_oops

occured when /sys/bus/ap/a[pq]mask was updated with a relative mask value
(like +0x10-0x12,+60,-90) with one of the numeric values exceeding INT_MAX.

The fix is simple: use unsigned long values for the internal variables. The
correct checks are already in place in the function but a simple int for
the internal variables was used with the possibility to overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39276 | ext4: fix mb_cache_entry&amp;#x27;s e_refcnt leak in ext4_xattr_block_cache_find()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39276</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: fix mb_cache_entry's e_refcnt leak in ext4_xattr_block_cache_find()

Syzbot reports a warning as follows:

============================================
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 5075 at fs/mbcache.c:419 mb_cache_destroy+0x224/0x290
Modules linked in:
CPU: 0 PID: 5075 Comm: syz-executor199 Not tainted 6.9.0-rc6-gb947cc5bf6d7
RIP: 0010:mb_cache_destroy+0x224/0x290 fs/mbcache.c:419
Call Trace:
 
 ext4_put_super+0x6d4/0xcd0 fs/ext4/super.c:1375
 generic_shutdown_super+0x136/0x2d0 fs/super.c:641
 kill_block_super+0x44/0x90 fs/super.c:1675
 ext4_kill_sb+0x68/0xa0 fs/ext4/super.c:7327
[...]
============================================

This is because when finding an entry in ext4_xattr_block_cache_find(), if
ext4_sb_bread() returns -ENOMEM, the ce's e_refcnt, which has already grown
in the __entry_find(), won't be put away, and eventually trigger the above
issue in mb_cache_destroy() due to reference count leakage.

So call mb_cache_entry_put() on the -ENOMEM error branch as a quick fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39293 | Revert &amp;quot;xsk: Support redirect to any socket bound to the same umem&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39293</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "xsk: Support redirect to any socket bound to the same umem"

This reverts commit 2863d665ea41282379f108e4da6c8a2366ba66db.

This patch introduced a potential kernel crash when multiple napi instances
redirect to the same AF_XDP socket. By removing the queue_index check, it is
possible for multiple napi instances to access the Rx ring at the same time,
which will result in a corrupted ring state which can lead to a crash when
flushing the rings in __xsk_flush(). This can happen when the linked list of
sockets to flush gets corrupted by concurrent accesses. A quick and small fix
is not possible, so let us revert this for now.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39296 | bonding: fix oops during rmmod</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39296</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bonding: fix oops during rmmod

"rmmod bonding" causes an oops ever since commit cc317ea3d927 ("bonding:
remove redundant NULL check in debugfs function").  Here are the relevant
functions being called:

bonding_exit()
  bond_destroy_debugfs()
    debugfs_remove_recursive(bonding_debug_root);
    bonding_debug_root = NULL; &lt;--------- SET TO NULL HERE
  bond_netlink_fini()
    rtnl_link_unregister()
      __rtnl_link_unregister()
        unregister_netdevice_many_notify()
          bond_uninit()
            bond_debug_unregister()
              (commit removed check for bonding_debug_root == NULL)
              debugfs_remove()
              simple_recursive_removal()
                down_write() -&gt; OOPS

However, reverting the bad commit does not solve the problem completely
because the original code contains a race that could cause the same
oops, although it was much less likely to be triggered unintentionally:

CPU1
  rmmod bonding
    bonding_exit()
      bond_destroy_debugfs()
        debugfs_remove_recursive(bonding_debug_root);

CPU2
  echo -bond0 &gt; /sys/class/net/bonding_masters
    bond_uninit()
      bond_debug_unregister()
        if (!bonding_debug_root)

CPU1
        bonding_debug_root = NULL;

So do NOT revert the bad commit (since the removed checks were racy
anyway), and instead change the order of actions taken during module
removal.  The same oops can also happen if there is an error during
module init, so apply the same fix there.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39298 | mm/memory-failure: fix handling of dissolved but not taken off from buddy pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39298</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/memory-failure: fix handling of dissolved but not taken off from buddy pages

When I did memory failure tests recently, below panic occurs:

page: refcount:0 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0x0 pfn:0x8cee00
flags: 0x6fffe0000000000(node=1|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x7fff)
raw: 06fffe0000000000 dead000000000100 dead000000000122 0000000000000000
raw: 0000000000000000 0000000000000009 00000000ffffffff 0000000000000000
page dumped because: VM_BUG_ON_PAGE(!PageBuddy(page))
------------[ cut here ]------------
kernel BUG at include/linux/page-flags.h:1009!
invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
RIP: 0010:__del_page_from_free_list+0x151/0x180
RSP: 0018:ffffa49c90437998 EFLAGS: 00000046
RAX: 0000000000000035 RBX: 0000000000000009 RCX: ffff8dd8dfd1c9c8
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000027 RDI: ffff8dd8dfd1c9c0
RBP: ffffd901233b8000 R08: ffffffffab5511f8 R09: 0000000000008c69
R10: 0000000000003c15 R11: ffffffffab5511f8 R12: ffff8dd8fffc0c80
R13: 0000000000000001 R14: ffff8dd8fffc0c80 R15: 0000000000000009
FS:  00007ff916304740(0000) GS:ffff8dd8dfd00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 000055eae50124c8 CR3: 00000008479e0000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
Call Trace:
 
 __rmqueue_pcplist+0x23b/0x520
 get_page_from_freelist+0x26b/0xe40
 __alloc_pages_noprof+0x113/0x1120
 __folio_alloc_noprof+0x11/0xb0
 alloc_buddy_hugetlb_folio.isra.0+0x5a/0x130
 __alloc_fresh_hugetlb_folio+0xe7/0x140
 alloc_pool_huge_folio+0x68/0x100
 set_max_huge_pages+0x13d/0x340
 hugetlb_sysctl_handler_common+0xe8/0x110
 proc_sys_call_handler+0x194/0x280
 vfs_write+0x387/0x550
 ksys_write+0x64/0xe0
 do_syscall_64+0xc2/0x1d0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
RIP: 0033:0x7ff916114887
RSP: 002b:00007ffec8a2fd78 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000001
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 000055eae500e350 RCX: 00007ff916114887
RDX: 0000000000000004 RSI: 000055eae500e390 RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 000055eae50104c0 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 000055eae50104c0
R10: 0000000000000077 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 0000000000000004
R13: 0000000000000004 R14: 00007ff916216b80 R15: 00007ff916216a00
 
Modules linked in: mce_inject hwpoison_inject
---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

And before the panic, there had an warning about bad page state:

BUG: Bad page state in process page-types  pfn:8cee00
page: refcount:0 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0x0 pfn:0x8cee00
flags: 0x6fffe0000000000(node=1|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x7fff)
page_type: 0xffffff7f(buddy)
raw: 06fffe0000000000 ffffd901241c0008 ffffd901240f8008 0000000000000000
raw: 0000000000000000 0000000000000009 00000000ffffff7f 0000000000000000
page dumped because: nonzero mapcount
Modules linked in: mce_inject hwpoison_inject
CPU: 8 PID: 154211 Comm: page-types Not tainted 6.9.0-rc4-00499-g5544ec3178e2-dirty #22
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x83/0xa0
 bad_page+0x63/0xf0
 free_unref_page+0x36e/0x5c0
 unpoison_memory+0x50b/0x630
 simple_attr_write_xsigned.constprop.0.isra.0+0xb3/0x110
 debugfs_attr_write+0x42/0x60
 full_proxy_write+0x5b/0x80
 vfs_write+0xcd/0x550
 ksys_write+0x64/0xe0
 do_syscall_64+0xc2/0x1d0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
RIP: 0033:0x7f189a514887
RSP: 002b:00007ffdcd899718 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000001
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: 00007f189a514887
RDX: 0000000000000009 RSI: 00007ffdcd899730 RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 00007ffdcd8997a0 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 00007ffdcd8994b2
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00007ffdcda199a8
R13: 0000000000404af1 R14: 000000000040ad78 R15: 00007f189a7a5040
 

The root cause should be the below race:

 memory_failure
  try_memory_failure_hugetlb
   me_huge_page
    __page_handle_poison
     dissolve_free_hugetlb_folio
     drain_all_pages -- Buddy page can be isolated e.g. for compaction.
     take_page_off_buddy -- Failed as page is not in the 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39301 | net/9p: fix uninit-value in p9_client_rpc()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39301</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/9p: fix uninit-value in p9_client_rpc()

Syzbot with the help of KMSAN reported the following error:

BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in trace_9p_client_res include/trace/events/9p.h:146 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in p9_client_rpc+0x1314/0x1340 net/9p/client.c:754
 trace_9p_client_res include/trace/events/9p.h:146 [inline]
 p9_client_rpc+0x1314/0x1340 net/9p/client.c:754
 p9_client_create+0x1551/0x1ff0 net/9p/client.c:1031
 v9fs_session_init+0x1b9/0x28e0 fs/9p/v9fs.c:410
 v9fs_mount+0xe2/0x12b0 fs/9p/vfs_super.c:122
 legacy_get_tree+0x114/0x290 fs/fs_context.c:662
 vfs_get_tree+0xa7/0x570 fs/super.c:1797
 do_new_mount+0x71f/0x15e0 fs/namespace.c:3352
 path_mount+0x742/0x1f20 fs/namespace.c:3679
 do_mount fs/namespace.c:3692 [inline]
 __do_sys_mount fs/namespace.c:3898 [inline]
 __se_sys_mount+0x725/0x810 fs/namespace.c:3875
 __x64_sys_mount+0xe4/0x150 fs/namespace.c:3875
 do_syscall_64+0xd5/0x1f0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6d/0x75

Uninit was created at:
 __alloc_pages+0x9d6/0xe70 mm/page_alloc.c:4598
 __alloc_pages_node include/linux/gfp.h:238 [inline]
 alloc_pages_node include/linux/gfp.h:261 [inline]
 alloc_slab_page mm/slub.c:2175 [inline]
 allocate_slab mm/slub.c:2338 [inline]
 new_slab+0x2de/0x1400 mm/slub.c:2391
 ___slab_alloc+0x1184/0x33d0 mm/slub.c:3525
 __slab_alloc mm/slub.c:3610 [inline]
 __slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3663 [inline]
 slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3835 [inline]
 kmem_cache_alloc+0x6d3/0xbe0 mm/slub.c:3852
 p9_tag_alloc net/9p/client.c:278 [inline]
 p9_client_prepare_req+0x20a/0x1770 net/9p/client.c:641
 p9_client_rpc+0x27e/0x1340 net/9p/client.c:688
 p9_client_create+0x1551/0x1ff0 net/9p/client.c:1031
 v9fs_session_init+0x1b9/0x28e0 fs/9p/v9fs.c:410
 v9fs_mount+0xe2/0x12b0 fs/9p/vfs_super.c:122
 legacy_get_tree+0x114/0x290 fs/fs_context.c:662
 vfs_get_tree+0xa7/0x570 fs/super.c:1797
 do_new_mount+0x71f/0x15e0 fs/namespace.c:3352
 path_mount+0x742/0x1f20 fs/namespace.c:3679
 do_mount fs/namespace.c:3692 [inline]
 __do_sys_mount fs/namespace.c:3898 [inline]
 __se_sys_mount+0x725/0x810 fs/namespace.c:3875
 __x64_sys_mount+0xe4/0x150 fs/namespace.c:3875
 do_syscall_64+0xd5/0x1f0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6d/0x75

If p9_check_errors() fails early in p9_client_rpc(), req-&gt;rc.tag
will not be properly initialized. However, trace_9p_client_res()
ends up trying to print it out anyway before p9_client_rpc()
finishes.

Fix this issue by assigning default values to p9_fcall fields
such as 'tag' and (just in case KMSAN unearths something new) 'id'
during the tag allocation stage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39362 | i2c: acpi: Unbind mux adapters before delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39362</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i2c: acpi: Unbind mux adapters before delete

There is an issue with ACPI overlay table removal specifically related
to I2C multiplexers.

Consider an ACPI SSDT Overlay that defines a PCA9548 I2C mux on an
existing I2C bus. When this table is loaded we see the creation of a
device for the overall PCA9548 chip and 8 further devices - one
i2c_adapter each for the mux channels. These are all bound to their
ACPI equivalents via an eventual invocation of acpi_bind_one().

When we unload the SSDT overlay we run into the problem. The ACPI
devices are deleted as normal via acpi_device_del_work_fn() and the
acpi_device_del_list.

However, the following warning and stack trace is output as the
deletion does not go smoothly:
------------[ cut here ]------------
kernfs: can not remove 'physical_node', no directory
WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 11 at fs/kernfs/dir.c:1674 kernfs_remove_by_name_ns+0xb9/0xc0
Modules linked in:
CPU: 1 PID: 11 Comm: kworker/u128:0 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc6+ #1
Hardware name: congatec AG conga-B7E3/conga-B7E3, BIOS 5.13 05/16/2023
Workqueue: kacpi_hotplug acpi_device_del_work_fn
RIP: 0010:kernfs_remove_by_name_ns+0xb9/0xc0
Code: e4 00 48 89 ef e8 07 71 db ff 5b b8 fe ff ff ff 5d 41 5c 41 5d e9 a7 55 e4 00 0f 0b eb a6 48 c7 c7 f0 38 0d 9d e8 97 0a d5 ff &lt;0f&gt; 0b eb dc 0f 1f 00 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90
RSP: 0018:ffff9f864008fb28 EFLAGS: 00010286
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff8ef90a8d4940 RCX: 0000000000000000
RDX: ffff8f000e267d10 RSI: ffff8f000e25c780 RDI: ffff8f000e25c780
RBP: ffff8ef9186f9870 R08: 0000000000013ffb R09: 00000000ffffbfff
R10: 00000000ffffbfff R11: ffff8f000e0a0000 R12: ffff9f864008fb50
R13: ffff8ef90c93dd60 R14: ffff8ef9010d0958 R15: ffff8ef9186f98c8
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8f000e240000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f48f5253a08 CR3: 00000003cb82e000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
Call Trace:
 
 ? kernfs_remove_by_name_ns+0xb9/0xc0
 ? __warn+0x7c/0x130
 ? kernfs_remove_by_name_ns+0xb9/0xc0
 ? report_bug+0x171/0x1a0
 ? handle_bug+0x3c/0x70
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x17/0x70
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
 ? kernfs_remove_by_name_ns+0xb9/0xc0
 ? kernfs_remove_by_name_ns+0xb9/0xc0
 acpi_unbind_one+0x108/0x180
 device_del+0x18b/0x490
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 device_unregister+0xd/0x30
 i2c_del_adapter.part.0+0x1bf/0x250
 i2c_mux_del_adapters+0xa1/0xe0
 i2c_device_remove+0x1e/0x80
 device_release_driver_internal+0x19a/0x200
 bus_remove_device+0xbf/0x100
 device_del+0x157/0x490
 ? __pfx_device_match_fwnode+0x10/0x10
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 device_unregister+0xd/0x30
 i2c_acpi_notify+0x10f/0x140
 notifier_call_chain+0x58/0xd0
 blocking_notifier_call_chain+0x3a/0x60
 acpi_device_del_work_fn+0x85/0x1d0
 process_one_work+0x134/0x2f0
 worker_thread+0x2f0/0x410
 ? __pfx_worker_thread+0x10/0x10
 kthread+0xe3/0x110
 ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
 ret_from_fork+0x2f/0x50
 ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30
 
---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
...
repeated 7 more times, 1 for each channel of the mux
...

The issue is that the binding of the ACPI devices to their peer I2C
adapters is not correctly cleaned up. Digging deeper into the issue we
see that the deletion order is such that the ACPI devices matching the
mux channel i2c adapters are deleted first during the SSDT overlay
removal. For each of the channels we see a call to i2c_acpi_notify()
with ACPI_RECONFIG_DEVICE_REMOVE but, because these devices are not
actually i2c_clients, nothing is done for them.

Later on, after each of the mux channels has been dealt with, we come
to delete the i2c_client representing the PCA9548 device. This is the
call stack we see above, whereby the kernel cleans up the i2c_client
including destruction of the mux and its channel adapters. At this
point we do attempt to unbind from the ACPI peers but those peers 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39371 | io_uring: check for non-NULL file pointer in io_file_can_poll()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39371</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: check for non-NULL file pointer in io_file_can_poll()

In earlier kernels, it was possible to trigger a NULL pointer
dereference off the forced async preparation path, if no file had
been assigned. The trace leading to that looks as follows:

BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 00000000000000b0
PGD 0 P4D 0
Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
CPU: 67 PID: 1633 Comm: buf-ring-invali Not tainted 6.8.0-rc3+ #1
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS unknown 2/2/2022
RIP: 0010:io_buffer_select+0xc3/0x210
Code: 00 00 48 39 d1 0f 82 ae 00 00 00 48 81 4b 48 00 00 01 00 48 89 73 70 0f b7 50 0c 66 89 53 42 85 ed 0f 85 d2 00 00 00 48 8b 13 &lt;48&gt; 8b 92 b0 00 00 00 48 83 7a 40 00 0f 84 21 01 00 00 4c 8b 20 5b
RSP: 0018:ffffb7bec38c7d88 EFLAGS: 00010246
RAX: ffff97af2be61000 RBX: ffff97af234f1700 RCX: 0000000000000040
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: ffff97aecfb04820 RDI: ffff97af234f1700
RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000200030 R09: 0000000000000020
R10: ffffb7bec38c7dc8 R11: 000000000000c000 R12: ffffb7bec38c7db8
R13: ffff97aecfb05800 R14: ffff97aecfb05800 R15: ffff97af2be5e000
FS:  00007f852f74b740(0000) GS:ffff97b1eeec0000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00000000000000b0 CR3: 000000016deab005 CR4: 0000000000370ef0
Call Trace:
 
 ? __die+0x1f/0x60
 ? page_fault_oops+0x14d/0x420
 ? do_user_addr_fault+0x61/0x6a0
 ? exc_page_fault+0x6c/0x150
 ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x22/0x30
 ? io_buffer_select+0xc3/0x210
 __io_import_iovec+0xb5/0x120
 io_readv_prep_async+0x36/0x70
 io_queue_sqe_fallback+0x20/0x260
 io_submit_sqes+0x314/0x630
 __do_sys_io_uring_enter+0x339/0xbc0
 ? __do_sys_io_uring_register+0x11b/0xc50
 ? vm_mmap_pgoff+0xce/0x160
 do_syscall_64+0x5f/0x180
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x46/0x4e
RIP: 0033:0x55e0a110a67e
Code: ba cc 00 00 00 45 31 c0 44 0f b6 92 d0 00 00 00 31 d2 41 b9 08 00 00 00 41 83 e2 01 41 c1 e2 04 41 09 c2 b8 aa 01 00 00 0f 05  90 89 30 eb a9 0f 1f 40 00 48 8b 42 20 8b 00 a8 06 75 af 85 f6

because the request is marked forced ASYNC and has a bad file fd, and
hence takes the forced async prep path.

Current kernels with the request async prep cleaned up can no longer hit
this issue, but for ease of backporting, let's add this safety check in
here too as it really doesn't hurt. For both cases, this will inevitably
end with a CQE posted with -EBADF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39461 | clk: bcm: rpi: Assign -&amp;gt;num before accessing -&amp;gt;hws</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39461</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

clk: bcm: rpi: Assign -&gt;num before accessing -&gt;hws

Commit f316cdff8d67 ("clk: Annotate struct clk_hw_onecell_data with
__counted_by") annotated the hws member of 'struct clk_hw_onecell_data'
with __counted_by, which informs the bounds sanitizer about the number
of elements in hws, so that it can warn when hws is accessed out of
bounds. As noted in that change, the __counted_by member must be
initialized with the number of elements before the first array access
happens, otherwise there will be a warning from each access prior to the
initialization because the number of elements is zero. This occurs in
raspberrypi_discover_clocks() due to -&gt;num being assigned after -&gt;hws
has been accessed:

  UBSAN: array-index-out-of-bounds in drivers/clk/bcm/clk-raspberrypi.c:374:4
  index 3 is out of range for type 'struct clk_hw *[] __counted_by(num)' (aka 'struct clk_hw *[]')

Move the -&gt;num initialization to before the first access of -&gt;hws, which
clears up the warning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39462 | clk: bcm: dvp: Assign -&amp;gt;num before accessing -&amp;gt;hws</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39462</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

clk: bcm: dvp: Assign -&gt;num before accessing -&gt;hws

Commit f316cdff8d67 ("clk: Annotate struct clk_hw_onecell_data with
__counted_by") annotated the hws member of 'struct clk_hw_onecell_data'
with __counted_by, which informs the bounds sanitizer about the number
of elements in hws, so that it can warn when hws is accessed out of
bounds. As noted in that change, the __counted_by member must be
initialized with the number of elements before the first array access
happens, otherwise there will be a warning from each access prior to the
initialization because the number of elements is zero. This occurs in
clk_dvp_probe() due to -&gt;num being assigned after -&gt;hws has been
accessed:

  UBSAN: array-index-out-of-bounds in drivers/clk/bcm/clk-bcm2711-dvp.c:59:2
  index 0 is out of range for type 'struct clk_hw *[] __counted_by(num)' (aka 'struct clk_hw *[]')

Move the -&gt;num initialization to before the first access of -&gt;hws, which
clears up the warning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39463 | 9p: add missing locking around taking dentry fid list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39463</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

9p: add missing locking around taking dentry fid list

Fix a use-after-free on dentry's d_fsdata fid list when a thread
looks up a fid through dentry while another thread unlinks it:

UAF thread:
refcount_t: addition on 0; use-after-free.
 p9_fid_get linux/./include/net/9p/client.h:262
 v9fs_fid_find+0x236/0x280 linux/fs/9p/fid.c:129
 v9fs_fid_lookup_with_uid linux/fs/9p/fid.c:181
 v9fs_fid_lookup+0xbf/0xc20 linux/fs/9p/fid.c:314
 v9fs_vfs_getattr_dotl+0xf9/0x360 linux/fs/9p/vfs_inode_dotl.c:400
 vfs_statx+0xdd/0x4d0 linux/fs/stat.c:248

Freed by:
 p9_fid_destroy (inlined)
 p9_client_clunk+0xb0/0xe0 linux/net/9p/client.c:1456
 p9_fid_put linux/./include/net/9p/client.h:278
 v9fs_dentry_release+0xb5/0x140 linux/fs/9p/vfs_dentry.c:55
 v9fs_remove+0x38f/0x620 linux/fs/9p/vfs_inode.c:518
 vfs_unlink+0x29a/0x810 linux/fs/namei.c:4335

The problem is that d_fsdata was not accessed under d_lock, because
d_release() normally is only called once the dentry is otherwise no
longer accessible but since we also call it explicitly in v9fs_remove
that lock is required:
move the hlist out of the dentry under lock then unref its fids once
they are no longer accessible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39464 | media: v4l: async: Fix notifier list entry init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39464</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: v4l: async: Fix notifier list entry init

struct v4l2_async_notifier has several list_head members, but only
waiting_list and done_list are initialized. notifier_entry was kept
'zeroed' leading to an uninitialized list_head.
This results in a NULL-pointer dereference if csi2_async_register() fails,
e.g. node for remote endpoint is disabled, and returns -ENOTCONN.
The following calls to v4l2_async_nf_unregister() results in a NULL
pointer dereference.
Add the missing list head initializer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39465 | media: mgb4: Fix double debugfs remove</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39465</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: mgb4: Fix double debugfs remove

Fixes an error where debugfs_remove_recursive() is called first on a parent
directory and then again on a child which causes a kernel panic.

[hverkuil: added Fixes/Cc tags]</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39466 | thermal/drivers/qcom/lmh: Check for SCM availability at probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39466</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

thermal/drivers/qcom/lmh: Check for SCM availability at probe

Up until now, the necessary scm availability check has not been
performed, leading to possible null pointer dereferences (which did
happen for me on RB1).

Fix that.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39467 | f2fs: fix to do sanity check on i_xattr_nid in sanity_check_inode()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39467</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: fix to do sanity check on i_xattr_nid in sanity_check_inode()

syzbot reports a kernel bug as below:

F2FS-fs (loop0): Mounted with checkpoint version = 48b305e4
==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in f2fs_test_bit fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:2933 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in current_nat_addr fs/f2fs/node.h:213 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in f2fs_get_node_info+0xece/0x1200 fs/f2fs/node.c:600
Read of size 1 at addr ffff88807a58c76c by task syz-executor280/5076

CPU: 1 PID: 5076 Comm: syz-executor280 Not tainted 6.9.0-rc5-syzkaller #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 03/27/2024
Call Trace:
 
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:88 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x241/0x360 lib/dump_stack.c:114
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:377 [inline]
 print_report+0x169/0x550 mm/kasan/report.c:488
 kasan_report+0x143/0x180 mm/kasan/report.c:601
 f2fs_test_bit fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:2933 [inline]
 current_nat_addr fs/f2fs/node.h:213 [inline]
 f2fs_get_node_info+0xece/0x1200 fs/f2fs/node.c:600
 f2fs_xattr_fiemap fs/f2fs/data.c:1848 [inline]
 f2fs_fiemap+0x55d/0x1ee0 fs/f2fs/data.c:1925
 ioctl_fiemap fs/ioctl.c:220 [inline]
 do_vfs_ioctl+0x1c07/0x2e50 fs/ioctl.c:838
 __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:902 [inline]
 __se_sys_ioctl+0x81/0x170 fs/ioctl.c:890
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xf5/0x240 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

The root cause is we missed to do sanity check on i_xattr_nid during
f2fs_iget(), so that in fiemap() path, current_nat_addr() will access
nat_bitmap w/ offset from invalid i_xattr_nid, result in triggering
kasan bug report, fix it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39468 | smb: client: fix deadlock in smb2_find_smb_tcon()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39468</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb: client: fix deadlock in smb2_find_smb_tcon()

Unlock cifs_tcp_ses_lock before calling cifs_put_smb_ses() to avoid such
deadlock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39469 | nilfs2: fix nilfs_empty_dir() misjudgment and long loop on I/O errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39469</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix nilfs_empty_dir() misjudgment and long loop on I/O errors

The error handling in nilfs_empty_dir() when a directory folio/page read
fails is incorrect, as in the old ext2 implementation, and if the
folio/page cannot be read or nilfs_check_folio() fails, it will falsely
determine the directory as empty and corrupt the file system.

In addition, since nilfs_empty_dir() does not immediately return on a
failed folio/page read, but continues to loop, this can cause a long loop
with I/O if i_size of the directory's inode is also corrupted, causing the
log writer thread to wait and hang, as reported by syzbot.

Fix these issues by making nilfs_empty_dir() immediately return a false
value (0) if it fails to get a directory folio/page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39470 | eventfs: Fix a possible null pointer dereference in eventfs_find_events()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39470</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

eventfs: Fix a possible null pointer dereference in eventfs_find_events()

In function eventfs_find_events,there is a potential null pointer
that may be caused by calling update_events_attr which will perform
some operations on the members of the ei struct when ei is NULL.

Hence,When ei-&gt;is_freed is set,return NULL directly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39471 | drm/amdgpu: add error handle to avoid out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39471</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: add error handle to avoid out-of-bounds

if the sdma_v4_0_irq_id_to_seq return -EINVAL, the process should
be stop to avoid out-of-bounds read, so directly return -EINVAL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37085 | VMware ESXi contains an authentication bypass vulnerability. A malicious actor with sufficient Active Directory (AD) permissions can gain fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37085</link><description>VMware ESXi contains an authentication bypass vulnerability. A malicious actor with sufficient Active Directory (AD) permissions can gain full access to an ESXi host that was previously  configured to use AD for user management https://blogs.vmware.com/vsphere/2012/09/joining-vsphere-hosts-to-active-directory.html  by re-creating the configured AD group ('ESXi Admins' by default) after it was deleted from AD.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37086 | VMware ESXi contains an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A
 malicious actor with local administrative privileges on a virtual 
machine with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37086</link><description>VMware ESXi contains an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A
 malicious actor with local administrative privileges on a virtual 
machine with an existing snapshot may trigger an out-of-bounds read 
leading to a denial-of-service condition of the host.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37087 | The vCenter Server contains a denial-of-service vulnerability. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may create a denial-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37087</link><description>The vCenter Server contains a denial-of-service vulnerability. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may create a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21827 | A leftover debug code vulnerability exists in the cli_server debug functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.4.1 Build 2024...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21827</link><description>A leftover debug code vulnerability exists in the cli_server debug functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.4.1 Build 20240117 Rel.57421. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5451 | The7 — Website and eCommerce Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 11.13.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5451</link><description>The The7 — Website and eCommerce Builder for WordPress theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute within the plugin's Icon and Heading widgets in all versions up to, and including, 11.13.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32111 | WordPress core &amp;lt; 6.5.5 - Auth. Arbitrary .html File Read (Windows Only) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32111</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Automattic WordPress allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects WordPress: from 6.5 through 6.5.4, from 6.4 through 6.4.4, from 6.3 through 6.3.4, from 6.2 through 6.2.5, from 6.1 through 6.1.6, from 6.0 through 6.0.8, from 5.9 through 5.9.9, from 5.8 through 5.8.9, from 5.7 through 5.7.11, from 5.6 through 5.6.13, from 5.5 through 5.5.14, from 5.4 through 5.4.15, from 5.3 through 5.3.17, from 5.2 through 5.2.20, from 5.1 through 5.1.18, from 5.0 through 5.0.21, from 4.9 through 4.9.25, from 4.8 through 4.8.24, from 4.7 through 4.7.28, from 4.6 through 4.6.28, from 4.5 through 4.5.31, from 4.4 through 4.4.32, from 4.3 through 4.3.33, from 4.2 through 4.2.37, from 4.1 through 4.1.40.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38951 | A buffer overflow in PX4-Autopilot v1.12.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MavLink message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38951</link><description>A buffer overflow in PX4-Autopilot v1.12.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MavLink message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38952 | PX4-Autopilot v1.14.3 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the topic_name parameter at /logger/logged_topics.cpp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38952</link><description>PX4-Autopilot v1.14.3 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the topic_name parameter at /logger/logged_topics.cpp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6299 | Use of a Key Past its Expiration Date in Conduit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6299</link><description>Lack of consideration of key expiry when validating signatures in Conduit, allowing an attacker which has compromised an expired key to forge requests as the remote server, as well as PDUs with timestamps past the expiry date</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6300 | Incomplete Cleanup in Conduit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6300</link><description>Incomplete cleanup when performing redactions in Conduit, allowing an attacker to check whether certain strings were present in the PDU before redaction</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6301 | Origin Validation Error in Conduit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6301</link><description>Lack of validation of origin in federation API in Conduit, allowing any remote server to impersonate any user from any server in most EDUs</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6302 | Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges  in Conduit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6302</link><description>Lack of privilege checking when processing a redaction in Conduit versions v0.6.0 and lower, allowing a local user to redact any message from users on the same server, given that they are able to send redaction events.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6303 | Missing Authorization in Conduit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6303</link><description>Missing authorization in Client-Server API in Conduit &lt;=0.7.0, allowing for any alias to be removed and added to another room, which can be used for privilege escalation by moving the #admins alias to a room which they control, allowing them to run commands resetting passwords, siging json with the server's key, deactivating users, and more</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31111 | WordPress Core &amp;lt; 6.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31111</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress: from 6.5 through 6.5.4, from 6.4 through 6.4.4, from 6.3 through 6.3.4, from 6.2 through 6.2.5, from 6.1 through 6.1.6, from 6.0 through 6.0.8, from 5.9 through 5.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5261 | TLS certificate are not properly verified when utilizing LibreOfficeKit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5261</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in LibreOffice "LibreOfficeKit" mode disables TLS certification verification

LibreOfficeKit can be used for accessing LibreOffice functionality 
through C/C++. Typically this is used by third party components to reuse
 LibreOffice as a library to convert, view or otherwise interact with 
documents.

LibreOffice internally makes use of "curl" to fetch remote resources such as images hosted on webservers.

In
 affected versions of LibreOffice, when used in LibreOfficeKit mode 
only, then curl's TLS certification verification was disabled 
(CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER of false)

In the fixed versions curl operates in LibreOfficeKit mode the same as in standard mode with CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER of true.

This issue affects LibreOffice before version 24.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4846 | Authentication bypass in the 2FA feature in Devolutions Server 2024.1.14.0 and earlier allows an authenticated attacker to authenticate to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4846</link><description>Authentication bypass in the 2FA feature in Devolutions Server 2024.1.14.0 and earlier allows an authenticated attacker to authenticate to another user without being asked for the 2FA via another browser tab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28831 | XSS in confirmation pop-up</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28831</link><description>Stored XSS in some confirmation pop-ups in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p7 and 2.2.0p28 allows Checkmk users to execute arbitrary scripts by injecting HTML elements into some user input fields that are shown in a confirmation pop-up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28832 | XSS in Crash Report Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28832</link><description>Stored XSS in the Crash Report page in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p7, 2.2.0p28, 2.1.0p45, and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows users with permission to change Global Settings to execute arbitrary scripts by injecting HTML elements into the Crash Report URL in the Global Settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6305 | WordPress Core &amp;lt; 6.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Template Part Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6305</link><description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Template Part Block in various versions up to 6.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'tagName' attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6306 | WordPress Core &amp;lt; 6.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6306</link><description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in various versions up to 6.5.5 via the Template Part block. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include arbitrary HTML Files on sites running Windows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6307 | WordPress Core &amp;lt; 6.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6307</link><description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the HTML API in various versions up to 6.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5216 | Denial of Service in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5216</link><description>A vulnerability in mintplex-labs/anything-llm allows for a Denial of Service (DoS) condition due to uncontrolled resource consumption. Specifically, the issue arises from the application's failure to limit the size of usernames, enabling attackers to create users with excessively bulky texts in the username field. This exploit results in the user management panel becoming unresponsive, preventing administrators from performing critical user management actions such as editing, suspending, or deleting users. The impact of this vulnerability includes administrative paralysis, compromised security, and operational disruption, as it allows malicious users to perpetuate their presence within the system indefinitely, undermines the system's security posture, and degrades overall system performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4640 | OnCell G3470A-LTE Series: Authenticated Command Injection via sendTestEmail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4640</link><description>OnCell G3470A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.7.7 and prior have been identified as vulnerable due to missing bounds checking on buffer operations. An attacker could write past the boundaries of allocated buffer regions in memory, causing a program crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4641 | OnCell G3470A-LTE Series: Authenticated Format String Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4641</link><description>OnCell G3470A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.7.7 and prior have been identified as vulnerable due to accepting a format string from an external source as an argument. An attacker could modify an externally controlled format string to cause a memory leak and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4639 | OnCell G3470A-LTE Series: Authenticated Command Injection via webDelIPSec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4639</link><description>OnCell G3470A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.7.7 and prior have been identified as vulnerable due to a lack of neutralized inputs in IPSec configuration. An attacker could modify the intended commands sent to target functions, which could cause malicious users to execute unauthorized commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34141 | AMS XSS - /libs/granite/backup/clientlibs/js/backup.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34141</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34142 | AMS XSS - /libs/dam/cfm/components/download/clientlib/js/download.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34142</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4638 | OnCell G3470A-LTE Series: Authenticated Command Injection via webUploadKey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4638</link><description>OnCell G3470A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.7.7 and prior have been identified as vulnerable due to a lack of neutralized inputs in the web key upload function. An attacker could modify the intended commands sent to target functions, which could cause malicious users to execute unauthorized commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6028 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 6.5.8.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;ays_questions&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6028</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'ays_questions' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.8.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3249 | Zita Elementor Site Library &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Missing Authorization to Page Creation and Options Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3249</link><description>The Zita Elementor Site Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the import_xml_data, xml_data_import, import_option_data, import_widgets, and import_customizer_settings functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create pages, update certain options, including WooCommerce page titles and Elementor settings, import widgets, and update the plugin's customizer settings and the WordPress custom CSS. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4757 | Logo Manager For Enamad &amp;lt;= 0.7.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4757</link><description>The Logo Manager For Enamad WordPress plugin through 0.7.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 06:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4759 | Mime Types Extended &amp;lt;= 0.11 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4759</link><description>The Mime Types Extended WordPress plugin through 0.11 does not sanitise uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 06:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5431 | WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.25 - Authenticated (Contributor+) File inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5431</link><description>The WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.25 via the reservation_extra_field shortcode parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include remote files on the server, potentially resulting in code execution</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 05:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32855 | Dell Client Platform BIOS contains an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32855</link><description>Dell Client Platform BIOS contains an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4197 | Avaya IP Office One-X Portal File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4197</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Avaya IP Office was discovered that could allow remote command or code execution via the One-X component. Affected versions include all versions prior to 11.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4196 | Avaya IP Office Web Control RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4196</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability  was discovered in Avaya IP Office that could allow remote command or code execution via a specially crafted web request to the Web Control component. Affected versions include all versions prior to 11.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23156 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23156</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23157 | A maliciously crafted SLDASM or SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23157</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDASM or SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23158 | A maliciously crafted IGES file, when parsed in ASMImport229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a use-after-free vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23158</link><description>A maliciously crafted IGES file, when parsed in ASMImport229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a use-after-free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23159 | A maliciously crafted STP file, when parsed in stp_aim_x64_vc15d.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23159</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file, when parsed in stp_aim_x64_vc15d.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36999 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36999</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37007 | A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37007</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6297 | Several WordPress.org Plugins &amp;lt;= Various Versions  - Injected Backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6297</link><description>Several plugins for WordPress hosted on WordPress.org have been compromised and injected with malicious PHP scripts. A malicious threat actor compromised the source code of various plugins and injected code that exfiltrates database credentials and is used to create new, malicious, administrator users and send that data back to a server. Currently, not all plugins have been patched and we strongly recommend uninstalling the plugins for the time being and running a complete malware scan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23151 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23151</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23152 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23152</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23153 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodx.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23153</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodx.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23154 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23154</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23155 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in atf_asm_interface.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Buff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23155</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in atf_asm_interface.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23150 | A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in odxug_dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23150</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in odxug_dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37003 | A maliciously crafted DWG and SLDPRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37003</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG and SLDPRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37004 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37004</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37005 | A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37005</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37006 | A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37006</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37000 | A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37000</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37001 | [A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37001</link><description>[A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37002 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dllthrough Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37002</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dllthrough Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23148 | A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23148</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23149 | A maliciously crafted SLDDRW file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23149</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDDRW file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23145 | A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23145</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23146 | A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23146</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23147 | A maliciously crafted CATPART, X_B and STEP, when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll and ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23147</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART, X_B and STEP, when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll and ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5038 | Unauthenticated DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5038</link><description>badmonkey, a Security Researcher has found a flaw that allows for a unauthenticated DoS attack on the camera. An attacker runs a crafted URL, nobody can access the web management page of the camera. and must manually restart the device or re-power it. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6295 | udn News App - Insecure Data Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6295</link><description>udn News Android APP stores the unencrypted user session in the local database when user log into the application. A malicious APP or an attacker with physical access to the Android device can retrieve this session and use it to log into the news APP and other services provided by udn.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23143 | A maliciously crafted 3DM, MODEL and X_B file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll and ASMBASE229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23143</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM, MODEL and X_B file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll and ASMBASE229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read and/or Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23144 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23144</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6294 | udn News App - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6294</link><description>udn News Android APP stores the user session in logcat file when user log into the APP. A malicious APP or an attacker with physical access to the Android device can retrieve this session and use it to log into the news APP and other services provided by udn.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6198 | Hard Coded Credential</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6198</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Baicells Snap Router BaiCE_BMI on EP3011 (User Passwords modules) allows unauthorized access to the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22385 | File and Directory Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Storage Provider for VMware vCenter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22385</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Storage Provider for VMware vCenter allows local users to read and write specific files.This issue affects Hitachi Storage Provider for VMware vCenter: from 3.1.0 before 3.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23141 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodxdll through Autodesk applications, can cause a double free. This vulnerability, along...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23141</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodxdll through Autodesk applications, can cause a double free. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23142 | A maliciously crafted CATPART, STP, and MODEL file, when parsed in atf_dwg_consumer.dll, rose_x64_vc15.dll and libodxdll through Autodesk ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23142</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART, STP, and MODEL file, when parsed in atf_dwg_consumer.dll, rose_x64_vc15.dll and libodxdll through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23140 | A maliciously crafted 3DM and MODEL file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and atf_api.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23140</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM and MODEL file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and atf_api.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22168 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on Western Digital My Cloud and SanDisk ibi Web Apps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22168</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the My Cloud, My Cloud Home, SanDisk ibi, and WD Cloud web apps was found which could allow an attacker to redirect the user to a crafted domain and reset their credentials, or to execute arbitrary client-side code in the user’s browser session to carry out malicious activities.The web apps for these devices have been automatically updated to resolve this vulnerability and improve the security of your devices and data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36683 | SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Products Alert" (productsalert) before 1.7.4 from Smart Modules for PrestaShop allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36683</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Products Alert" (productsalert) before 1.7.4 from Smart Modules for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and cause other impacts via the ProductsAlertAjaxProcessModuleFrontController::initContent method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36681 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Isotope" (pk_isotope) &lt;=1.7.3 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36681</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Isotope" (pk_isotope) &lt;=1.7.3 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and cause other impacts via `pk_isotope::saveData` and `pk_isotope::removeData` methods.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50029 | PHP Injection vulnerability in the module "M4 PDF Extensions" (m4pdf) up to version 3.3.2 from PrestaAddons for PrestaShop allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50029</link><description>PHP Injection vulnerability in the module "M4 PDF Extensions" (m4pdf) up to version 3.3.2 from PrestaAddons for PrestaShop allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the M4PDF::saveTemplate() method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34992 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Help Desk - Customer Support Management System" (helpdesk) up to version 2.4.0 from FME Modules f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34992</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Help Desk - Customer Support Management System" (helpdesk) up to version 2.4.0 from FME Modules for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and cause other impacts via 'Tickets::getsearchedtickets()'</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34988 | SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Complete for Create a Quote in Frontend + Backend Pro" (askforaquotemodul) &lt;= 1.0.51 from Buy Add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34988</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Complete for Create a Quote in Frontend + Backend Pro" (askforaquotemodul) &lt;= 1.0.51 from Buy Addons for PrestaShop allows attackers to view sensitive information and cause other impacts via methods `AskforaquotemodulcustomernewquoteModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemoduladdproductnewquoteModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemodulCouponcodeModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemodulgetshippingcostModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemodulgetstateModuleFrontController::run().`</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36682 | In the module "Theme settings" (pk_themesettings) &lt;= 1.8.8 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can download all email collected while S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36682</link><description>In the module "Theme settings" (pk_themesettings) &lt;= 1.8.8 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can download all email collected while SHOP is in maintenance mode. Due to a lack of permissions control, a guest can access the txt file which collect email when maintenance is enable which can lead to leak of personal information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34991 | In the module "Axepta" (axepta) before 1.3.4 from Quadra Informatique for PrestaShop, a guest can download partial credit card information (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34991</link><description>In the module "Axepta" (axepta) before 1.3.4 from Quadra Informatique for PrestaShop, a guest can download partial credit card information (expiry date) / postal address / email / etc. without restriction due to a lack of permissions control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6290 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6290</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6291 | Use after free in Swiftshader in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6291</link><description>Use after free in Swiftshader in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6292 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6292</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6293 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6293</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33898 | Axiros AXESS Auto Configuration Server (ACS) 4.x and 5.0.0 has Incorrect Access Control. An authorization bypass allows remote attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33898</link><description>Axiros AXESS Auto Configuration Server (ACS) 4.x and 5.0.0 has Incorrect Access Control. An authorization bypass allows remote attackers to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45195 | Adminer and AdminerEvo SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45195</link><description>Adminer and AdminerEvo are vulnerable to SSRF via database connection fields. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to enumerate or access systems the attacker would not otherwise have access to. Adminer is no longer supported, but this issue was fixed in AdminerEvo version 4.8.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45196 | Adminer and AdminerEvo denial of service via HTTP redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45196</link><description>Adminer and AdminerEvo allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service by connecting to an attacker-controlled service that responds with HTTP redirects. The denial of service is subject to PHP configuration limits. Adminer is no longer supported, but this issue was fixed in AdminerEvo version 4.8.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38897 | WAVLINK WN551K1'live_check.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38897</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1'live_check.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38902 | H3C Magic R230 V100R002 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as roo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38902</link><description>H3C Magic R230 V100R002 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38903 | H3C Magic R230 V100R002's udpserver opens port 9034, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38903</link><description>H3C Magic R230 V100R002's udpserver opens port 9034, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38895 | WAVLINK WN551K1'live_mfg.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38895</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1'live_mfg.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38896 | WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the start_hour parameter of /cgi-bin/nightled.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38896</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the start_hour parameter of /cgi-bin/nightled.cgi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38894 | WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the IP parameter of /cgi-bin/touchlist_sync.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38894</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the IP parameter of /cgi-bin/touchlist_sync.cgi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37759 | DataGear v5.0.0 and earlier was discovered to contain a SpEL (Spring Expression Language) expression injection vulnerability via the Data Vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37759</link><description>DataGear v5.0.0 and earlier was discovered to contain a SpEL (Spring Expression Language) expression injection vulnerability via the Data Viewing interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38892 | An issue in Wavlink WN551K1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ExportAllSettings.sh component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38892</link><description>An issue in Wavlink WN551K1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ExportAllSettings.sh component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34312 | Virtual Programming Lab for Moodle up to v4.2.3 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component vplid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34312</link><description>Virtual Programming Lab for Moodle up to v4.2.3 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component vplide.js.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34313 | An issue in VPL Jail System up to v4.0.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via a crafted request to a public endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34313</link><description>An issue in VPL Jail System up to v4.0.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via a crafted request to a public endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37678 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. Finesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37678</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. Finesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37681 | An issue the background management system of Shanxi Internet Chuangxiang Technology Co., Ltd v1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to cause a deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37681</link><description>An issue the background management system of Shanxi Internet Chuangxiang Technology Co., Ltd v1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the index.html component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-45785 | TruDesk Help Desk/Ticketing Solution v1.1.11 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack which would allow an attacker to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45785</link><description>TruDesk Help Desk/Ticketing Solution v1.1.11 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack which would allow an attacker to restart the server, causing a DoS attack. The attacker must craft a webpage that would perform a GET request to the /api/v1/admin/restart endpoint, then the victim (who has sufficient privileges), would visit the page and the server restart would begin. The attacker must know the full URL that TruDesk is on in order to craft the webpage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37677 | An issue in Shenzhen Weitillage Industrial Co., Ltd the access management specialist V6.62.51215 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37677</link><description>An issue in Shenzhen Weitillage Industrial Co., Ltd the access management specialist V6.62.51215 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37679 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., LTd Finnesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37679</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., LTd Finnesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.jsp parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37680 | Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. FineSoft &lt;=8.0 is affected by Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows remote attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37680</link><description>Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. FineSoft &lt;=8.0 is affected by Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Enter any account and password, click Login, the page will report an error, and a controllable parameter will appear at the URL:weburl.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37732 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Anchor CMS v.0.12.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .pdf file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37732</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Anchor CMS v.0.12.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .pdf file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49793 | Path traversal in `CodeChecker server` in the endpoint of `CodeChecker store`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49793</link><description>CodeChecker is an analyzer tooling, defect database and viewer extension for the Clang Static Analyzer and Clang Tidy. Zip files uploaded to the server endpoint of `CodeChecker store` are not properly sanitized. An attacker, using a path traversal attack, can load and display files on the machine of `CodeChecker server`. The vulnerable endpoint is `/Default/v6.53/CodeCheckerService@massStoreRun`. The path traversal vulnerability allows reading data on the machine of the `CodeChecker server`, with the same permission level as the `CodeChecker server`.
The attack requires a user account on the `CodeChecker server`, with permission to store to a server, and view the stored report. This vulnerability has been patched in version 6.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6104 | go-retryablehttp can leak basic auth credentials to log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6104</link><description>go-retryablehttp prior to 0.7.7 did not sanitize urls when writing them to its log file. This could lead to go-retryablehttp writing sensitive HTTP basic auth credentials to its log file. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-6104, was fixed in go-retryablehttp 0.7.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38369 | XWiki programming rights may be inherited by inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38369</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. The content of a document included using `{{include reference="targetdocument"/}}` is executed with the right of the includer and not with the right of its author. This means that any user able to modify the target document can impersonate the author of the content which used the `include` macro. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.0 RC1 by making the default behavior safe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33879 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Downlo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33879</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Download.ashx isCompleted method allows arbitrary file download and deletion via absolute path traversal in the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33880 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. It discloses full pathnames via Virto.SharePoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33880</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. It discloses full pathnames via Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Download.ashx?action=archive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33881 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Downlo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33881</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Download.ashx isCompleted method allows an NTLMv2 hash leak via a UNC share pathname in the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38373 | FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP Buffer Over-Read in DNS Response Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38373</link><description>FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP is a lightweight TCP/IP stack for FreeRTOS. FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP versions 4.0.0 through 4.1.0 contain a buffer over-read issue in the DNS Response Parser when parsing domain names in a DNS response. A carefully crafted DNS response with domain name length value greater than the actual domain name length, could cause the parser to read beyond the DNS response buffer. This issue affects applications using DNS functionality of the FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP stack. Applications that do not use DNS functionality are not affected, even when the DNS functionality is enabled. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6285 | Integer Underflow in Memory Range Check in Renesas RCAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6285</link><description>Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability in Renesas arm-trusted-firmware.
An integer underflow in image range check calculations could lead to bypassing address restrictions and loading of images to unallowed addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6287 | Incorrect Address Range Calculations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6287</link><description>Incorrect Calculation vulnerability in Renesas arm-trusted-firmware allows Local Execution of Code.


When checking whether a new image invades/overlaps with a previously loaded image the code neglects to consider a few cases. that could An attacker to bypass memory range restriction and overwrite an already loaded image partly or completely, which could result in code execution and bypass of secure boot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33687 | Insufficient verification of data authenticity issue exists in NJ Series CPU Unit all versions and NX Series CPU Unit all versions. If a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33687</link><description>Insufficient verification of data authenticity issue exists in NJ Series CPU Unit all versions and NX Series CPU Unit all versions. If a user program in the affected product is altered, the product may not be able to detect the alteration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33278 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ASUS router RT-AX88U with firmware versions v3.0.0.4.388_24198 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33278</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ASUS router RT-AX88U with firmware versions v3.0.0.4.388_24198 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the connection_state_machine due to improper length validation for the cookie field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37825 | An issue in EnvisionWare Computer Access &amp; Reservation Control SelfCheck v1.0 (fixed in OneStop 3.2.0.27184 Hotfix May 2024) allows unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37825</link><description>An issue in EnvisionWare Computer Access &amp; Reservation Control SelfCheck v1.0 (fixed in OneStop 3.2.0.27184 Hotfix May 2024) allows unauthenticated attackers on the same network to perform a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32936 | media: ti: j721e-csi2rx: Fix races while restarting DMA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32936</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: ti: j721e-csi2rx: Fix races while restarting DMA

After the frame is submitted to DMA, it may happen that the submitted
list is not updated soon enough, and the DMA callback is triggered
before that.

This can lead to kernel crashes, so move everything in a single
lock/unlock section to prevent such races.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33847 | f2fs: compress: don&amp;#x27;t allow unaligned truncation on released compress inode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33847</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: compress: don't allow unaligned truncation on released compress inode

f2fs image may be corrupted after below testcase:
- mkfs.f2fs -O extra_attr,compression -f /dev/vdb
- mount /dev/vdb /mnt/f2fs
- touch /mnt/f2fs/file
- f2fs_io setflags compression /mnt/f2fs/file
- dd if=/dev/zero of=/mnt/f2fs/file bs=4k count=4
- f2fs_io release_cblocks /mnt/f2fs/file
- truncate -s 8192 /mnt/f2fs/file
- umount /mnt/f2fs
- fsck.f2fs /dev/vdb

[ASSERT] (fsck_chk_inode_blk:1256)  --&gt; ino: 0x5 has i_blocks: 0x00000002, but has 0x3 blocks
[FSCK] valid_block_count matching with CP             [Fail] [0x4, 0x5]
[FSCK] other corrupted bugs                           [Fail]

The reason is: partial truncation assume compressed inode has reserved
blocks, after partial truncation, valid block count may change w/o
.i_blocks and .total_valid_block_count update, result in corruption.

This patch only allow cluster size aligned truncation on released
compress inode for fixing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34027 | f2fs: compress: fix to cover {reserve,release}_compress_blocks() w/ cp_rwsem lock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34027</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: compress: fix to cover {reserve,release}_compress_blocks() w/ cp_rwsem lock

It needs to cover {reserve,release}_compress_blocks() w/ cp_rwsem lock
to avoid racing with checkpoint, otherwise, filesystem metadata including
blkaddr in dnode, inode fields and .total_valid_block_count may be
corrupted after SPO case.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34030 | PCI: of_property: Return error for int_map allocation failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34030</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: of_property: Return error for int_map allocation failure

Return -ENOMEM from of_pci_prop_intr_map() if kcalloc() fails to prevent a
NULL pointer dereference in this case.

[bhelgaas: commit log]</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35247 | fpga: region: add owner module and take its refcount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35247</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fpga: region: add owner module and take its refcount

The current implementation of the fpga region assumes that the low-level
module registers a driver for the parent device and uses its owner pointer
to take the module's refcount. This approach is problematic since it can
lead to a null pointer dereference while attempting to get the region
during programming if the parent device does not have a driver.

To address this problem, add a module owner pointer to the fpga_region
struct and use it to take the module's refcount. Modify the functions for
registering a region to take an additional owner module parameter and
rename them to avoid conflicts. Use the old function names for helper
macros that automatically set the module that registers the region as the
owner. This ensures compatibility with existing low-level control modules
and reduces the chances of registering a region without setting the owner.

Also, update the documentation to keep it consistent with the new interface
for registering an fpga region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36479 | fpga: bridge: add owner module and take its refcount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36479</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fpga: bridge: add owner module and take its refcount

The current implementation of the fpga bridge assumes that the low-level
module registers a driver for the parent device and uses its owner pointer
to take the module's refcount. This approach is problematic since it can
lead to a null pointer dereference while attempting to get the bridge if
the parent device does not have a driver.

To address this problem, add a module owner pointer to the fpga_bridge
struct and use it to take the module's refcount. Modify the function for
registering a bridge to take an additional owner module parameter and
rename it to avoid conflicts. Use the old function name for a helper macro
that automatically sets the module that registers the bridge as the owner.
This ensures compatibility with existing low-level control modules and
reduces the chances of registering a bridge without setting the owner.

Also, update the documentation to keep it consistent with the new interface
for registering an fpga bridge.

Other changes: opportunistically move put_device() from __fpga_bridge_get()
to fpga_bridge_get() and of_fpga_bridge_get() to improve code clarity since
the bridge device is taken in these functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37021 | fpga: manager: add owner module and take its refcount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37021</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fpga: manager: add owner module and take its refcount

The current implementation of the fpga manager assumes that the low-level
module registers a driver for the parent device and uses its owner pointer
to take the module's refcount. This approach is problematic since it can
lead to a null pointer dereference while attempting to get the manager if
the parent device does not have a driver.

To address this problem, add a module owner pointer to the fpga_manager
struct and use it to take the module's refcount. Modify the functions for
registering the manager to take an additional owner module parameter and
rename them to avoid conflicts. Use the old function names for helper
macros that automatically set the module that registers the manager as the
owner. This ensures compatibility with existing low-level control modules
and reduces the chances of registering a manager without setting the owner.

Also, update the documentation to keep it consistent with the new interface
for registering an fpga manager.

Other changes: opportunistically move put_device() from __fpga_mgr_get() to
fpga_mgr_get() and of_fpga_mgr_get() to improve code clarity since the
manager device is taken in these functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37026 | drm/xe: Only use reserved BCS instances for usm migrate exec queue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37026</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe: Only use reserved BCS instances for usm migrate exec queue

The GuC context scheduling queue is 2 entires deep, thus it is possible
for a migration job to be stuck behind a fault if migration exec queue
shares engines with user jobs. This can deadlock as the migrate exec
queue is required to service page faults. Avoid deadlock by only using
reserved BCS instances for usm migrate exec queue.

(cherry picked from commit 04f4a70a183a688a60fe3882d6e4236ea02cfc67)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38667 | riscv: prevent pt_regs corruption for secondary idle threads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38667</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: prevent pt_regs corruption for secondary idle threads

Top of the kernel thread stack should be reserved for pt_regs. However
this is not the case for the idle threads of the secondary boot harts.
Their stacks overlap with their pt_regs, so both may get corrupted.

Similar issue has been fixed for the primary hart, see c7cdd96eca28
("riscv: prevent stack corruption by reserving task_pt_regs(p) early").
However that fix was not propagated to the secondary harts. The problem
has been noticed in some CPU hotplug tests with V enabled. The function
smp_callin stored several registers on stack, corrupting top of pt_regs
structure including status field. As a result, kernel attempted to save
or restore inexistent V context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39291 | drm/amdgpu: Fix buffer size in gfx_v9_4_3_init_ cp_compute_microcode() and rlc_microcode()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39291</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Fix buffer size in gfx_v9_4_3_init_ cp_compute_microcode() and rlc_microcode()

The function gfx_v9_4_3_init_microcode in gfx_v9_4_3.c was generating
about potential truncation of output when using the snprintf function.
The issue was due to the size of the buffer 'ucode_prefix' being too
small to accommodate the maximum possible length of the string being
written into it.

The string being written is "amdgpu/%s_mec.bin" or "amdgpu/%s_rlc.bin",
where %s is replaced by the value of 'chip_name'. The length of this
string without the %s is 16 characters. The warning message indicated
that 'chip_name' could be up to 29 characters long, resulting in a total
of 45 characters, which exceeds the buffer size of 30 characters.

To resolve this issue, the size of the 'ucode_prefix' buffer has been
reduced from 30 to 15. This ensures that the maximum possible length of
the string being written into the buffer will not exceed its size, thus
preventing potential buffer overflow and truncation issues.

Fixes the below with gcc W=1:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c: In function ‘gfx_v9_4_3_early_init’:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:379:52: warning: ‘%s’ directive output may be truncated writing up to 29 bytes into a region of size 23 [-Wformat-truncation=]
  379 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_rlc.bin", chip_name);
      |                                                    ^~
......
  439 |         r = gfx_v9_4_3_init_rlc_microcode(adev, ucode_prefix);
      |                                                 ~~~~~~~~~~~~
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:379:9: note: ‘snprintf’ output between 16 and 45 bytes into a destination of size 30
  379 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_rlc.bin", chip_name);
      |         ^~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:413:52: warning: ‘%s’ directive output may be truncated writing up to 29 bytes into a region of size 23 [-Wformat-truncation=]
  413 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_mec.bin", chip_name);
      |                                                    ^~
......
  443 |         r = gfx_v9_4_3_init_cp_compute_microcode(adev, ucode_prefix);
      |                                                        ~~~~~~~~~~~~
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:413:9: note: ‘snprintf’ output between 16 and 45 bytes into a destination of size 30
  413 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_mec.bin", chip_name);
      |         ^~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39292 | um: Add winch to winch_handlers before registering winch IRQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39292</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

um: Add winch to winch_handlers before registering winch IRQ

Registering a winch IRQ is racy, an interrupt may occur before the winch is
added to the winch_handlers list.

If that happens, register_winch_irq() adds to that list a winch that is
scheduled to be (or has already been) freed, causing a panic later in
winch_cleanup().

Avoid the race by adding the winch to the winch_handlers list before
registering the IRQ, and rolling back if um_request_irq() fails.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4748 | RCE in Cruddiy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4748</link><description>The CRUDDIY project is vulnerable to shell command injection via sending a crafted POST request to the application server. 
The exploitation risk is limited since CRUDDIY is meant to be launched locally. Nevertheless, a user with the project running on their computer might visit a website which would send such a malicious request to the locally launched server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38384 | blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from reorder of WRITE -&amp;gt;lqueued</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38384</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from reorder of WRITE -&gt;lqueued

__blkcg_rstat_flush() can be run anytime, especially when blk_cgroup_bio_start
is being executed.

If WRITE of `-&gt;lqueued` is re-ordered with READ of 'bisc-&gt;lnode.next' in
the loop of __blkcg_rstat_flush(), `next_bisc` can be assigned with one
stat instance being added in blk_cgroup_bio_start(), then the local
list in __blkcg_rstat_flush() could be corrupted.

Fix the issue by adding one barrier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38663 | blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from resetting io stat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from resetting io stat

Since commit 3b8cc6298724 ("blk-cgroup: Optimize blkcg_rstat_flush()"),
each iostat instance is added to blkcg percpu list, so blkcg_reset_stats()
can't reset the stat instance by memset(), otherwise the llist may be
corrupted.

Fix the issue by only resetting the counter part.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38664 | drm: zynqmp_dpsub: Always register bridge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm: zynqmp_dpsub: Always register bridge

We must always register the DRM bridge, since zynqmp_dp_hpd_work_func
calls drm_bridge_hpd_notify, which in turn expects hpd_mutex to be
initialized. We do this before zynqmp_dpsub_drm_init since that calls
drm_bridge_attach. This fixes the following lockdep warning:

[   19.217084] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[   19.227530] DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
[   19.227768] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 140 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:582 __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.241696] Modules linked in:
[   19.244937] CPU: 0 PID: 140 Comm: kworker/0:4 Not tainted 6.6.20+ #96
[   19.252046] Hardware name: xlnx,zynqmp (DT)
[   19.256421] Workqueue: events zynqmp_dp_hpd_work_func
[   19.261795] pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[   19.269104] pc : __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.273364] lr : __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.277592] sp : ffffffc085c5bbe0
[   19.281066] x29: ffffffc085c5bbe0 x28: 0000000000000000 x27: ffffff88009417f8
[   19.288624] x26: ffffff8800941788 x25: ffffff8800020008 x24: ffffffc082aa3000
[   19.296227] x23: ffffffc080d90e3c x22: 0000000000000002 x21: 0000000000000000
[   19.303744] x20: 0000000000000000 x19: ffffff88002f5210 x18: 0000000000000000
[   19.311295] x17: 6c707369642e3030 x16: 3030613464662072 x15: 0720072007200720
[   19.318922] x14: 0000000000000000 x13: 284e4f5f4e524157 x12: 0000000000000001
[   19.326442] x11: 0001ffc085c5b940 x10: 0001ff88003f388b x9 : 0001ff88003f3888
[   19.334003] x8 : 0001ff88003f3888 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : 0000000000000000
[   19.341537] x5 : 0000000000000000 x4 : 0000000000001668 x3 : 0000000000000000
[   19.349054] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffffff88003f3880
[   19.356581] Call trace:
[   19.359160]  __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.363032]  mutex_lock_nested+0x24/0x30
[   19.367187]  drm_bridge_hpd_notify+0x2c/0x6c
[   19.371698]  zynqmp_dp_hpd_work_func+0x44/0x54
[   19.376364]  process_one_work+0x3ac/0x988
[   19.380660]  worker_thread+0x398/0x694
[   19.384736]  kthread+0x1bc/0x1c0
[   19.388241]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[   19.392031] irq event stamp: 183
[   19.395450] hardirqs last  enabled at (183): [] finish_task_switch.isra.0+0xa8/0x2d4
[   19.405140] hardirqs last disabled at (182): [] __schedule+0x714/0xd04
[   19.413612] softirqs last  enabled at (114): [] srcu_invoke_callbacks+0x158/0x23c
[   19.423128] softirqs last disabled at (110): [] srcu_invoke_callbacks+0x158/0x23c
[   19.432614] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

(cherry picked from commit 61ba791c4a7a09a370c45b70a81b8c7d4cf6b2ae)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37233 | WordPress Play.ht plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37233</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Play.Ht allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Play.Ht: from n/a through 3.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3264 | Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med Health Aplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3264</link><description>Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. Mia-Med Health Aplication allows Signature Spoofing by Improper Validation.This issue affects Mia-Med Health Aplication: before 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4839 | CSRF in Servers Configurations in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4839</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the 'Servers Configurations' function of the parisneo/lollms-webui, versions 9.6 to the latest. The affected functions include Elastic search Service (under construction), XTTS service, Petals service, vLLM service, and Motion Ctrl service, which lack CSRF protection. This vulnerability allows attackers to deceive users into unwittingly installing the XTTS service among other packages by submitting a malicious installation request. Successful exploitation results in attackers tricking users into performing actions without their consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37107 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Authenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37107</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37109 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Authenticated Arbitrary PHP Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37109</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X allows Code Injection.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37111 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Unauthenticated Denial of Service Attack vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37111</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37228 | WordPress InstaWP Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.38 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37228</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in InstaWP Team InstaWP Connect allows Code Injection.This issue affects InstaWP Connect: from n/a through 0.1.0.38.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37231 | WordPress Salon booking system plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37231</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Salon Booking System Salon booking system allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Salon booking system: from n/a through 9.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5862 | User Enumeration in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med Health Aplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5862</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. Mia-Med Health Aplication allows Interface Manipulation.This issue affects Mia-Med Health Aplication: before 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37092 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37092</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37089 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37089</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37091 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36038 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36038</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ITOM products versions from 128234 to 128248 are affected by the stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the proxy server option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29868 | Apache StreamPipes, Apache StreamPipes: Use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) in Recovery Token Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29868</link><description>Use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes user self-registration and password recovery mechanism.
This allows an attacker to guess the recovery token in a reasonable time and thereby to take over the attacked user's account.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: from 0.69.0 through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 10:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6160 | SQL Injection in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6160</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in MegaBIP software allows attacker to disclose the contents of the database, obtain session cookies or modify the content of pages. This issue affects MegaBIP software versions through 5.12.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36496 | Hardcoded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36496</link><description>The configuration file is encrypted with a static key derived from a 
static five-character password which allows an attacker to decrypt this 
file. The application hashes this five-character password with 
the outdated and broken MD5 algorithm (no salt) and uses the first five 
bytes as the key for RC4. The configuration file is then encrypted with 
these parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36497 | Unhashed Storage of Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36497</link><description>The decrypted configuration file contains the password in cleartext 
which is used to configure WINSelect. It can be used to remove the 
existing restrictions and disable WINSelect entirely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4754 | Stored XSS in Next4Biz&amp;#x27;s BPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4754</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Next4Biz CRM &amp; BPM Software Business Process Manangement (BPM) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Business Process Manangement (BPM): from 6.6.4.4 before 6.6.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5683 | Remote Code Execution in Next4Biz&amp;#x27;s BPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5683</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Next4Biz CRM &amp; BPM Software Business Process Manangement (BPM) allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects Business Process Manangement (BPM): from 6.6.4.4 before 6.6.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36495 | Read/Write Permissions for Everyone on Configuration File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36495</link><description>The application Faronics WINSelect (Standard + Enterprise) saves its configuration in an encrypted file on the file system which "Everyone" has read and write access to, path to file:



C:\ProgramData\WINSelect\WINSelect.wsd

The path for the affected WINSelect Enterprise configuration file is:

C:\ProgramData\Faronics\StorageSpace\WS\WINSelect.wsd</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27136 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-site scripting vulnerability on upload page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27136</link><description>XSS in Upload page in Apache JSPWiki 2.12.1 and priors allows the attacker to execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the victim.  Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.2 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24554 | Bludit - Insecure Token Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24554</link><description>Bludit uses predictable methods in combination with the MD5 hashing algorithm to generate sensitive tokens such as the API token and the user token. This allows attackers to authenticate against the Bludit API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24550 | Bludit - Remote Code Execution (RCE) through File API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24550</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in Bludit, allowing attackers with knowledge of the API token to upload arbitrary files through the File API which leads to arbitrary code execution on the server. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of file uploads, enabling malicious actors to upload and execute PHP files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24551 | Bludit - Remote Code Execution (RCE) through Image API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24551</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in Bludit, allowing authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code through the Image API. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of file uploads, enabling malicious actors to upload and execute PHP files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24552 | Bludit is Vulnerable to Session Fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24552</link><description>A session fixation vulnerability in Bludit allows an attacker to bypass the server's authentication if they can trick an administrator or any other user into authorizing a session ID of their choosing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24553 | Bludit uses SHA1 as Password Hashing Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24553</link><description>Bludit uses the SHA-1 hashing algorithm to compute password hashes. Thus, attackers could determine cleartext passwords with brute-force attacks due to the inherent speed of SHA-1. In addition, the salt that is computed by Bludit is generated with a non-cryptographically secure function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4460 | DoS Vulnerability in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4460</link><description>A denial of service (DoS) vulnerability exists in zenml-io/zenml version 0.56.3 due to improper handling of line feed (`\n`) characters in component names. When a low-privileged user adds a component through the API endpoint `api/v1/workspaces/default/components` with a name containing a `\n` character, it leads to uncontrolled resource consumption. This vulnerability results in the inability of users to add new components in certain categories (e.g., 'Image Builder') and to register new stacks through the UI, thereby degrading the user experience and potentially rendering the ZenML Dashboard unusable. The issue does not affect component addition through the Web UI, as `\n` characters are properly escaped in that context. The vulnerability was tested on ZenML running in Docker, and it was observed in both Firefox and Chrome browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4899 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4899</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its Post settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4900 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.8 - Contributor+ Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4900</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.8 does not validate and escape one of its Post settings, which could allow contributor and above role to perform Open redirect attacks against any user viewing a malicious post</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4499 | CSRF Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms XTTS Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4499</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of parisneo/lollms version 9.6 due to a lax CORS policy. The vulnerability allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions by tricking a user into visiting a malicious webpage, which can then trigger arbitrary LoLLMS-XTTS API requests. This issue can lead to the reading and writing of audio files and, when combined with other vulnerabilities, could allow for the reading of arbitrary files on the system and writing files outside the permitted audio file location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6280 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6280</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269493 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6278 | lahirudanushka School Management System Subject Page subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6278</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file subject.php of the component Subject Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6279 | lahirudanushka School Management System Exam Results Page examresults-par.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6279</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file examresults-par.php of the component Exam Results Page. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269492.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6277 | lahirudanushka School Management System Student Page student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6277</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file student.php of the component Student Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6276 | lahirudanushka School Management System Teacher Page teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6276</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file teacher.php of the component Teacher Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269489 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6274 | lahirudanushka School Management System Attendance Report Page attendancelist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6274</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /attendancelist.php of the component Attendance Report Page. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269487.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6275 | lahirudanushka School Management System Parent Page parent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6275</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file parent.php of the component Parent Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269488.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3121 | Remote Code Execution in create_conda_env function in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3121</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the create_conda_env function of the parisneo/lollms repository, version 5.9.0. The vulnerability arises from the use of shell=True in the subprocess.Popen function, which allows an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by manipulating the env_name and python_version parameters. This issue could lead to a serious security breach as demonstrated by the ability to execute the 'whoami' command among potentially other harmful commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 01:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>