<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-4796 | Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.34 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation via User Email Change/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4796</link><description>The Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.34. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity or capability prior to updating their details like email in the 'Eventin\Speaker\Api\SpeakerController::update_item' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8735 | GNU cflow Lexer c.c yylex null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8735</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in GNU cflow up to 1.8. Affected by this vulnerability is the function yylex of the file c.c of the component Lexer. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10013 | AjaXplorer &amp;lt; 2.6 checkInstall.php Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10013</link><description>An unauthenticated remote command execution vulnerability exists in AjaXplorer (now known as Pydio Cells) versions prior to 2.6. The flaw resides in the checkInstall.php script within the access.ssh plugin, which fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input to the destServer GET parameter. By injecting shell metacharacters, remote attackers can execute arbitrary system commands on the server with the privileges of the web server process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10036 | Project Pier &amp;lt;= 0.8.8 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10036</link><description>Project Pier 0.8.8 and earlier contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in tools/upload_file.php. The upload handler fails to validate the file type or enforce authentication, allowing remote attackers to upload malicious PHP files directly into a web-accessible directory. The uploaded file is stored with a predictable suffix and can be executed by requesting its URL, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10041 | WAN Emulator v2.3 Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10041</link><description>WAN Emulator v2.3 contains two unauthenticated command execution vulnerabilities. The result.php script calls shell_exec() with unsanitized input from the pc POST parameter, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands as the www-data user. The system also includes a SUID-root binary named dosu, which is vulnerable to command injection via its first argument. An attacker can exploit both flaws in sequence to achieve full remote code execution and escalate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10042 | Sflog! CMS 1.0 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10042</link><description>Sflog! CMS 1.0 contains an authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the blog management interface. The application ships with default credentials (admin:secret) and allows authenticated users to upload files via manage.php. The upload mechanism fails to validate file types, enabling attackers to upload a PHP backdoor into a web-accessible directory (blogs/download/uploads/). Once uploaded, the file can be executed remotely, resulting in full remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10043 | ActFax 4.32 Client Importer Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10043</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in ActFax Server version 4.32, specifically in the "Import Users from File" functionality of the client interface. The application fails to properly validate the length of tab-delimited fields in .exp files, leading to unsafe usage of strcpy() during CSV parsing. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious .exp file and importing it using the default character set "ECMA-94 / Latin 1 (ISO 8859)". Successful exploitation may result in arbitrary code execution, leading to full system compromise. User interaction is required to trigger the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10044 | MobileCartly 1.0 savepage.php Arbitrary File Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10044</link><description>MobileCartly version 1.0 contains an arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the savepage.php script. The application fails to perform authentication or authorization checks before invoking file_put_contents() on attacker-controlled input. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this flaw by sending crafted HTTP GET requests to savepage.php, specifying both the filename and content. This allows arbitrary file creation within the pages/ directory or any writable path on the server, allowing remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10045 | XODA 0.4.5 Arbitrary PHP File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10045</link><description>XODA version 0.4.5 contains an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server. The flaw resides in the upload functionality, which fails to properly validate or restrict uploaded file types. By crafting a multipart/form-data POST request, an attacker can upload a .php file directly into the web-accessible files/ directory and trigger its execution via a subsequent GET request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10046 | E-Mail Security Virtual Appliance learn-msg.cgi Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10046</link><description>The E-Mail Security Virtual Appliance (ESVA) (tested on version ESVA_2057) contains an unauthenticated command injection vulnerability in the learn-msg.cgi script. The CGI handler fails to sanitize user-supplied input passed via the id parameter, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary shell commands. Exploitation requires no authentication and results in full command execution on the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10047 | Cyclope Employee Surveillance Solution v6.x SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10047</link><description>Cyclope Employee Surveillance Solution versions 6.x is vulnerable to a SQL injection flaw in its login mechanism. The username parameter in the auth-login POST request is not properly sanitized, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL statements. This can be leveraged to write and execute a malicious PHP file on disk, resulting in remote code execution under the SYSTEM user context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10048 | Zenoss 3.x showDaemonXMLConfig Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10048</link><description>Zenoss Core 3.x contains a command injection vulnerability in the showDaemonXMLConfig endpoint. The daemon parameter is passed directly to a Popen() call in ZenossInfo.py without proper sanitation, allowing authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands on the server as the zenoss user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10049 | WebPageTest Arbitrary PHP File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10049</link><description>WebPageTest version 2.6 and earlier contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the resultimage.php script. The application fails to validate or sanitize user-supplied input before saving uploaded files to a publicly accessible directory. This flaw allows remote attackers to upload and execute arbitrary PHP code, resulting in full remote code execution under the web server context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10050 | CuteFlow &amp;lt;= 2.11.2 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10050</link><description>CuteFlow version 2.11.2 and earlier contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the restart_circulation_values_write.php script. The application fails to validate or restrict uploaded file types, allowing unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary PHP files to the upload/___1/ directory. These files are then accessible via the web server, enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10051 | Photodex ProShow Producer 5.0.3256 load File Handling Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10051</link><description>Photodex ProShow Producer version 5.0.3256 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the handling of plugin load list files. When a specially crafted load file is placed in the installation directory, the application fails to properly validate its contents, leading to a buffer overflow when the file is parsed during startup. Exploitation requires local access to place the file and user interaction to launch the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10052 | EGallery 1.2 Arbitrary PHP File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10052</link><description>EGallery version 1.2 contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uploadify.php script. The application fails to validate file types or enforce authentication, allowing remote attackers to upload malicious PHP files directly into the web-accessible egallery/ directory. This results in full remote code execution under the web server context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10053 | Simple Web Server Connection Header Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10053</link><description>Simple Web Server 2.2 rc2 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in its handling of the Connection HTTP header. When a remote attacker sends an overly long string in this header, the server uses vsprintf() without proper bounds checking, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. This flaw allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the web server process. The vulnerability is triggered before authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8734 | GNU Bison scan-code.c code_free double free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8734</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in GNU Bison up to 3.8.2. Affected is the function code_free of the file src/scan-code.c. The manipulation leads to double free. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52913 | A vulnerability in the NuPoint Unified Messaging (NPM) component of Mitel MiCollab through 9.8 SP2 (9.8.2.12) could allow an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52913</link><description>A vulnerability in the NuPoint Unified Messaging (NPM) component of Mitel MiCollab through 9.8 SP2 (9.8.2.12) could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a path traversal attack due to insufficient input validation. A successful exploit could allow unauthorized access, enabling the attacker to view, corrupt, or delete users' data and system configurations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52914 | A vulnerability in the Suite Applications Services component of Mitel MiCollab 10.0 through SP1 FP1 (10.0.1.101) could allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52914</link><description>A vulnerability in the Suite Applications Services component of Mitel MiCollab 10.0 through SP1 FP1 (10.0.1.101) could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct a SQL Injection attack due to insufficient validation of user input. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL database commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8733 | GNU Bison obprintf.c __obstack_vprintf_internal assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNU Bison up to 3.8.2. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function __obstack_vprintf_internal of the file obprintf.c. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50927 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the List All FTP User Function in EHCP v20.04.1.b allows authenticated attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50927</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the List All FTP User Function in EHCP v20.04.1.b allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript via injecting a crafted payload into the ftpusername parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5095 | Burk Technology ARC Solo Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5095</link><description>Burk Technology ARC Solo's password change mechanism can be utilized without proper 
authentication procedures, allowing an attacker to take over the device.
 A password change request can be sent directly to the device's HTTP 
endpoint without providing valid credentials. The system does not 
enforce proper authentication or session validation, allowing the 
password change to proceed without verifying the request's legitimacy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50928 | Easy Hosting Control Panel EHCP v20.04.1.b was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter in the Change Settin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50928</link><description>Easy Hosting Control Panel EHCP v20.04.1.b was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter in the Change Settings function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50465 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the Test...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50465</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the TestDefinitionDAO interface. The testPlatform parameter can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50466 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the Test...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50466</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the TestDefinitionDAO interface. The entityType parameter can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50467 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the Test...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50467</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the TestDefinitionDAO interface. The supportedDataTypeParam parameter can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50468 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the DocS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50468</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the DocStoreDAO interface. The entityType parameters can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8732 | libxml2 xmlcatalog xmlParseSGMLCatalog recursion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8732</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libxml2 up to 2.14.5. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function xmlParseSGMLCatalog of the component xmlcatalog. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled recursion. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The code maintainer explains, that "[t]he issue can only be triggered with untrusted SGML catalogs and it makes absolutely no sense to use untrusted catalogs. I also doubt that anyone is still using SGML catalogs at all."</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46414 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46414</link><description>The affected product does not limit the number of attempts for inputting
 the correct PIN for a registered product, which may allow an attacker 
to gain unauthorized access using brute-force methods if they possess a 
valid device serial number. The API provides clear feedback when the 
correct PIN is entered. This vulnerability was patched in a server-side 
update on April 6, 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8284 | Packet Power EMX and EG Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8284</link><description>By default, the Packet Power Monitoring and Control Web Interface do not
 enforce authentication mechanisms. This vulnerability could allow 
unauthorized users to access and manipulate monitoring and control 
functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8393 | Dreame Technology iOS and Android Mobile Applications Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8393</link><description>A TLS vulnerability exists in the phone application used to manage a 
connected device. The phone application accepts self-signed certificates
 when establishing TLS communication which may result in 
man-in-the-middle attacks on untrusted networks. Captured communications
 may include user credentials and sensitive session tokens.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47872 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Observable Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47872</link><description>The public-facing product registration endpoint server responds 
differently depending on whether the S/N is valid and unregistered, 
valid but already registered, or does not exist in the database. 
Combined with the fact that serial numbers are sequentially assigned, 
this allows an attacker to gain information on the product registration 
status of different S/Ns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53520 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Download of Code Without Integrity Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53520</link><description>The affected product allows firmware updates to be downloaded from EG4's
 website, transferred via USB dongles, or installed through EG4's 
Monitoring Center (remote, cloud-connected interface) or via a serial 
connection, and can install these files without integrity checks. The 
TTComp archive format used for the firmware is unencrypted and can be 
unpacked and altered without detection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52586 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52586</link><description>The MOD3 command traffic between the monitoring application and the 
inverter is transmitted in plaintext without encryption or obfuscation. 
This vulnerability may allow an attacker with access to a local network 
to intercept, manipulate, replay, or forge critical data, including 
read/write operations for voltage, current, and power configuration, 
operational status, alarms, telemetry, system reset, or inverter control
 commands, potentially disrupting power generation or reconfiguring 
inverter settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4576 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.133, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4576</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.133, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.4 ,2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.15, 7.4 GA through update 92 allows an remote non-authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript into the modules/apps/blogs/blogs-web/src/main/resources/META-INF/resources/blogs/entry_cover_image_caption.jsp</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8355 | XXE leading to SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8355</link><description>In Xerox FreeFlow Core version 8.0.4, improper handling of XML input allows injection of external entities. An attacker can craft malicious XML containing references to internal URLs, this results in a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8356 | Path Traversal leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8356</link><description>In Xerox FreeFlow Core version 8.0.4, an attacker can exploit a Path Traversal vulnerability to access unauthorized files on the server. This can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE), allowing the attacker to run arbitrary commands on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8731 | TRENDnet TI-G160i/TI-PG102i/TPL-430AP SSH Service default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8731</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TI-G160i, TI-PG102i and TPL-430AP up to 20250724. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component SSH Service. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36023 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36023</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 24.0.0 through 24.0.0 IF005 and 24.0.1 through 24.0.1 IF002 could allow an authenticated user to view sensitive user and system information due to an indirect object reference through a user-controlled key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8730 | Belkin F9K1009/F9K1010 Web Interface hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Belkin F9K1009 and F9K1010 2.00.04/2.00.09 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36119 | IBM i authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36119</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 is affected by an authenticated user obtaining elevated privileges with IBM Digital Certificate Manager for i (DCM) due to a web session hijacking vulnerability. An authenticated user without administrator privileges could exploit this vulnerability to perform actions in DCM as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-9322 | The /users endpoint in Statamic Core before 2.11.8 allows XSS to add an administrator user. This can be exploited via CSRF. Stored XSS can o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9322</link><description>The /users endpoint in Statamic Core before 2.11.8 allows XSS to add an administrator user. This can be exploited via CSRF. Stored XSS can occur via a JavaScript payload in a username during account registration. Reflected XSS can occur via the /users PATH_INFO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8729 | MigoXLab LMeterX upload_service.py process_cert_files path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8729</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MigoXLab LMeterX 1.2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function process_cert_files of the file backend/service/upload_service.py. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is f1b00597e293d09452aabd4fa57f3185207350e8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8749 | Path traversal vulnerability in MiR robot software via API requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8749</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in API Endpoint in Mobile Industrial Robots (MiR) Software Versions prior to 3.0.0 on MiR Robots allows authenticated users to extract files from the robot file system via a crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8088 | Path traversal vulnerability in WinRAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8088</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability affecting the Windows version of WinRAR allows the attackers to execute arbitrary code by crafting malicious archive files. This vulnerability was exploited in the wild and was discovered by Anton Cherepanov, Peter Košinár, and Peter Strýček
     from ESET.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8748 | OS command injection in MiR robots and MiR fleet via crafted HTTP requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8748</link><description>MiR software versions prior to version 3.0.0 are affected by a command injection vulnerability. A malicious 
HTTP request crafted by an authenticated user could allow the execution of arbitrary commands on the 
underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48913 | Apache CXF: Untrusted JMS configuration can lead to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48913</link><description>If untrusted users are allowed to configure JMS for Apache CXF, previously they could use RMI or LDAP URLs, potentially leading to code execution capabilities.  This interface is now restricted to reject those protocols, removing this possibility.

Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 3.6.8, 4.0.9 or 4.1.3, which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53606 | Apache Seata (incubating): Deserialization of untrusted Data in Apache Seata Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53606</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Seata (incubating).

This issue affects Apache Seata (incubating): 2.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.5.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6572 | OpenStreetMap for Gutenberg and WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6572</link><description>The OpenStreetMap for Gutenberg and WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) WordPress plugin through 1.2.0 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54958 | Powered BLUE 870 versions 0.20130927 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54958</link><description>Powered BLUE 870 versions 0.20130927 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary OS commands may be executed on the affected product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54959 | Powered BLUE Server versions 0.20130927 and prior contain a path traversal vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54959</link><description>Powered BLUE Server versions 0.20130927 and prior contain a path traversal vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary file in the affected product may be disclosed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:06:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54940 | An HTML injection vulnerability exists in WordPress plugin "Advanced Custom Fields" prior to 6.4.3. If this vulnerability is exploited, craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54940</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability exists in WordPress plugin "Advanced Custom Fields" prior to 6.4.3. If this vulnerability is exploited, crafted HTML code may be rendered and page display may be tampered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58255 | EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58255</link><description>EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58256 | EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58256</link><description>EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58257 | EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58257</link><description>EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8707 | Huuge Box App com.huuge.game.zjbox AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Huuge Box App 1.0.3 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.huuge.game.zjbox. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8708 | Antabot White-Jotter com.gm.wj.config.ShiroConfiguration ShiroConfiguration.java CookieRememberMeManager deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8708</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Antabot White-Jotter 0.22. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function CookieRememberMeManager of the file ShiroConfiguration.java of the component com.gm.wj.config.ShiroConfiguration. The manipulation with the input EVANNIGHTLY_WAOU leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8706 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Energy Overview Module CreateFunctionLog sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8706</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /CommonSolution/CreateFunctionLog of the component Energy Overview Module. The manipulation of the argument MM_MenID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8705 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Energy Overview Module GetTargetConfig sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8705</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /WEAS_HomePage/GetTargetConfig of the component Energy Overview Module. The manipulation of the argument BP_ProID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54793 | Astro: Duplicate trailing slash feature can lead to Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54793</link><description>Astro is a web framework for content-driven websites. In versions 5.2.0 through 5.12.7, there is an Open Redirect vulnerability in the trailing slash redirection logic when handling paths with double slashes. This allows an attacker to redirect users to arbitrary external domains by crafting URLs such as https://mydomain.com//malicious-site.com/. This increases the risk of phishing and other social engineering attacks. This affects sites that use on-demand rendering (SSR) with the Node or Cloudflare adapters. It does not affect static sites, or sites deployed to Netlify or Vercel. This issue is fixed in version 5.12.8. To work around this issue at the network level, block outgoing redirect responses with a Location header value that starts with `//`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54886 | skops: Card.get_model does not block arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54886</link><description>skops is a Python library which helps users share and ship their scikit-learn based models. In versions 0.12.0 and below, the Card.get_model does not contain any logic to prevent arbitrary code execution. The Card.get_model function supports both joblib and skops for model loading. When loading .skops models, it uses skops' secure loading with trusted type validation, raising errors for untrusted types unless explicitly allowed. However, when non-.zip file formats are provided, the function silently falls back to joblib without warning. Unlike skops, joblib allows arbitrary code execution during loading, bypassing security measures and potentially enabling malicious code execution. This issue is fixed in version 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54887 | jwe: Missing AES-GCM authentication tag validation in encrypted JWEs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54887</link><description>jwe is a Ruby implementation of the RFC 7516 JSON Web Encryption (JWE) standard. In versions 1.1.0 and below, authentication tags of encrypted JWEs can be brute forced, which may result in loss of confidentiality for those JWEs and provide ways to craft arbitrary JWEs. This puts users at risk because JWEs can be modified to decrypt to an arbitrary value, decrypted by observing parsing differences and the GCM internal GHASH key can be recovered. Users are affected by this vulnerability even if they do not use an AES-GCM encryption algorithm for their JWEs. As the GHASH key may have been leaked, users must rotate the encryption keys after upgrading. This issue is fixed in version 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8703 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Environmental Real-Time Data Module GetAreaTrendChartData sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8703</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /WEAS_HomePage/GetAreaTrendChartData of the component Environmental Real-Time Data Module. The manipulation of the argument energyId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8704 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Analysis Conclusion Query Module GetAlarmResultProcessList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8704</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /WEAS_AlarmResult/GetAlarmResultProcessList of the component Analysis Conclusion Query Module. The manipulation of the argument resultId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54368 | uv is vulnerable to ZIP payload obfuscation through parsing differentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54368</link><description>uv is a Python package and project manager written in Rust. In versions 0.8.5 and earlier, remote ZIP archives were handled in a streamwise fashion, and file entries were not reconciled against the archive's central directory. An attacker could contrive a ZIP archive that would extract with legitimate contents on some package installers, and malicious contents on others due to multiple local file entries. An attacker could  also contrive a "stacked" ZIP input with multiple internal ZIPs, which would be handled differently by different package installers. The attacker could choose which installer to target in both scenarios. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.6. To work around this issue, users may choose to set UV_INSECURE_NO_ZIP_VALIDATION=1 to revert to the previous behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8702 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Historical Data Query Module GetVariableByOneIDNew sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8702</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /CommonSolution/GetVariableByOneIDNew of the component Historical Data Query Module. The manipulation of the argument ObjectID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54952 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause smaller-than-expected memory regions to be allocated, potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54952</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause smaller-than-expected memory regions to be allocated, potentially resulting in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit 8f062d3f661e20bb19b24b767b9a9a46e8359f2b.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54950 | An out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result in code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54950</link><description>An out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit fb03b6f85596a8f954d97929075335255b6a58d4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54951 | A group of related buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54951</link><description>A group of related buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit cea9b23aa8ff78aff92829a466da97461cc7930c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30405 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause objects to be placed outside their allocated memory area, po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30405</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause objects to be placed outside their allocated memory area, potentially resulting in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit 0830af8207240df8d7f35b984cdf8bc35d74fa73.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54949 | A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54949</link><description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit ede82493dae6d2d43f8c424e7be4721abe5242be</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30404 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause overlapping allocations, potentially resulting in code execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30404</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause overlapping allocations, potentially resulting in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit d158236b1dc84539c1b16843bc74054c9dcba006.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54787 | SuiteCRM: Improper Authorization for attachment downloads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54787</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. There is a vulnerability in SuiteCRM version 7.14.6 which allows unauthenticated downloads of any file from the upload-directory, as long as it is named by an ID (e.g. attachments). An unauthenticated attacker could download internal files when he discovers a valid file-ID.
Valid IDs could be brute-forced, but this is quite time-consuming as the file-IDs are usually UUIDs. This issue is fixed in version 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45765 | ruby-jwt v3.0.0.beta1 was discovered to contain weak encryption. NOTE: the Supplier's perspective is "keysize is not something that is enfor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45765</link><description>ruby-jwt v3.0.0.beta1 was discovered to contain weak encryption. NOTE: the Supplier's perspective is "keysize is not something that is enforced by this library. Currently more recent versions of OpenSSL are enforcing some key sizes and those restrictions apply to the users of this gem also."</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53767 | Azure OpenAI Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53767</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53774 | Microsoft 365 Copilot BizChat Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53774</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53787 | Microsoft 365 Copilot BizChat Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53787</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53792 | Azure Portal Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53792</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8701 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System GetPageList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8701</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /OL_OprationLog/GetPageList. The manipulation of the argument optUser leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26513 | The installer for SAN Host Utilities for Windows versions prior to 8.0 is susceptible to a vulnerability which when successfully exploited c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26513</link><description>The installer for SAN Host Utilities for Windows versions prior to 8.0 is susceptible to a vulnerability which when successfully exploited could allow a local user to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8698 | Open5GS AMF Service nsmf-handler.c amf_nsmf_pdusession_handle_release_sm_context assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8698</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function amf_nsmf_pdusession_handle_release_sm_context of the file src/amf/nsmf-handler.c of the component AMF Service. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 66bc558e417e70ae216ec155e4e81c14ae0ecf30. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48709 | An issue was discovered in BMC Control-M 9.0.21.300. When Control-M Server has a database connection, it runs DBUStatus.exe frequently, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48709</link><description>An issue was discovered in BMC Control-M 9.0.21.300. When Control-M Server has a database connection, it runs DBUStatus.exe frequently, which then calls dbu_connection_details.vbs with the username, password, database hostname, and port written in cleartext, which can be seen in event and process logs in two separate locations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47183 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_tree function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47183</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_tree function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 file, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47219 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_trak function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47219</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_trak function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 file, possibly leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47806 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's parse_subrip_time function may write data past the bounds of a stack buffer, leading to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47806</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's parse_subrip_time function may write data past the bounds of a stack buffer, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47807 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's subrip_unescape_formatting function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47807</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's subrip_unescape_formatting function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtitle file, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47808 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's tmplayer_parse_line function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtitle file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47808</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's tmplayer_parse_line function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtitle file, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7195 | Operator-sdk: privilege escalation due to incorrect permissions of /etc/passwd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7195</link><description>Early versions of Operator-SDK provided an insecure method to allow operator containers to run in environments that used a random UID. Operator-SDK before 0.15.2 provided a script, user_setup, which modifies the permissions of the /etc/passwd file to 664 during build time. Developers who used Operator-SDK before 0.15.2 to scaffold their operator may still be impacted by this if the insecure user_setup script is still being used to build new container images. In affected images, the /etc/passwd file was created during build time with group-writable permissions and a group ownership of root (gid=0). An attacker who can execute commands within an affected container, even as a non-root user, may be able to leverage their membership in the root group to modify the /etc/passwd file. This could allow the attacker to add a new user with any arbitrary UID, including UID 0, leading to full root privileges within the container.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8697 | agentUniverse MCPSessionManager/MCPTool/MCPToolkit StdioServerParameters os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8697</link><description>A vulnerability was found in agentUniverse up to 0.0.18 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function StdioServerParameters of the component MCPSessionManager/MCPTool/MCPToolkit. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50675 | GPMAW 14, a bioinformatics software, has a critical vulnerability related to insecure file permissions in its installation directory. The di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50675</link><description>GPMAW 14, a bioinformatics software, has a critical vulnerability related to insecure file permissions in its installation directory. The directory is accessible with full read, write, and execute permissions for all users, allowing unprivileged users to manipulate files within the directory, including executable files like GPMAW3.exe, Fragment.exe, and the uninstaller GPsetup64_17028.exe. An attacker with user-level access can exploit this misconfiguration by replacing or modifying the uninstaller (GPsetup64_17028.exe) with a malicious version. While the application itself runs in the user's context, the uninstaller is typically executed with administrative privileges when an administrator attempts to uninstall the software. By exploiting this flaw, an attacker could gain administrative privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the admin, resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50692 | FoxCMS &lt;=v1.2.5 is vulnerable to Code Execution in admin/template_file/editFile.html.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50692</link><description>FoxCMS &lt;=v1.2.5 is vulnerable to Code Execution in admin/template_file/editFile.html.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55077 | Tyler Technologies ERP Pro 9 SaaS application escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55077</link><description>Tyler Technologies ERP Pro 9 SaaS allows an authenticated user to escape the application and execute limited operating system commands within the remote Microsoft Windows environment with the privileges of the authenticated user. Tyler Technologies deployed hardened remote Windows environment settings to all ERP Pro 9 SaaS customer environments as of 2025-08-01.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51533 | An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows unauthorized attackers to access internal forms via sending a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51533</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows unauthorized attackers to access internal forms via sending a crafted GET request. This is fixed in Halbjahresversion 2024_12_004.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41530 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the app_contact parameter in appsearch.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41530</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the app_contact parameter in appsearch.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41531 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func3.php via the username1 and password2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41531</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func3.php via the username1 and password2 parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41532 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the doctor_contact parameter in doctorsearch.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41532</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the doctor_contact parameter in doctorsearch.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41525 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the patient_contact parameter in patientsearch.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41525</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the patient_contact parameter in patientsearch.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41526 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func1.php via the username3 and password3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41526</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func1.php via the username3 and password3 parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41527 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the password2 parameter in func.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41527</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the password2 parameter in func.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41528 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in contact.php via the txtname, txtphone, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41528</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in contact.php via the txtname, txtphone, and txtmail parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41529 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in func2.php via the fname and l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41529</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in func2.php via the fname and lname parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41520 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createClassArms.php via the clas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41520</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createClassArms.php via the classId and classArmName parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41521 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createSessionTerm.php via the id...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41521</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createSessionTerm.php via the id, termId, and sessionName parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41522 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createStudents.php via the Id, f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41522</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createStudents.php via the Id, firstname, and admissionNumber parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41523 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the emailAddress parameter at createClas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41523</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the emailAddress parameter at createClassTeacher.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41524 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter at index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41524</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter at index.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51629 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PdfViewer component of Agenzia Impresa Eccobook 2.81.1 allows attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51629</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PdfViewer component of Agenzia Impresa Eccobook 2.81.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Temp parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40992 | Hospital Management System 4 is vulnerable to a SQL injection in /Hospital-Management-System-master/func.php via the password2 parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40992</link><description>Hospital Management System 4 is vulnerable to a SQL injection in /Hospital-Management-System-master/func.php via the password2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41519 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the sessionName parameter a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41519</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the sessionName parameter at createSessionTerm.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24000 | WordPress Post SMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Account Takeover Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24000</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in WPExperts Post SMTP allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Post SMTP: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42048 | OpenOrange Business Framework 1.15.5 provides unprivileged users with write access to the installation directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42048</link><description>OpenOrange Business Framework 1.15.5 provides unprivileged users with write access to the installation directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34148 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater OS Command Injection via WISP SSID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34148</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02). When configuring the device in WISP mode, the 'ssid' parameter is passed unsanitized to system-level scripts. This allows remote attackers within Wi-Fi range to inject arbitrary shell commands that execute as root, resulting in full device compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34149 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater OS Command Injection via WPA2 Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34149</link><description>A command injection vulnerability affects the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02) during WPA2 configuration. The 'key' parameter is interpreted directly by the system shell, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root. Exploitation requires no authentication and can be triggered during wireless setup.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34150 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater PPPoE Username Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34150</link><description>The PPPoE configuration interface of the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02) is vulnerable to command injection via the 'user' parameter. Input is processed unsafely during network setup, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34151 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater PPPoE Password Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34151</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the 'passwd' parameter of the PPPoE setup process on the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02). The input is passed directly to system-level commands without sanitation, enabling unauthenticated attackers to achieve root-level code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34152 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater OS Command Injection via Time Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34152</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02) via the 'time' parameter of the '/protocol.csp?' endpoint. The input is processed by the internal date '-s' command without rebooting or disrupting HTTP service. Unlike other injection points, this vector allows remote compromise without triggering visible configuration changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54392 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication error data, a different vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54392</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication error data, a different vulnerability than CVE-2025-47189.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54393 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows Static Code Injection. Authenticated users can obt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54393</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows Static Code Injection. Authenticated users can obtain administrative access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54394 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 has Insufficiently Protected Credentials for requests to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54394</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 has Insufficiently Protected Credentials for requests to remote Excel resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54395 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication configuration data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54395</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication configuration data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54396 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows SQL Injection. Authenticated users can exploit thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54396</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows SQL Injection. Authenticated users can exploit this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54397 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 inserts Sensitive Information Into Sent Data to authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54397</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 inserts Sensitive Information Into Sent Data to authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55137 | LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles lacks type checking in password reset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55137</link><description>LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles lacks type checking in password reset.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55138 | LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles token ownership in password reset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55138</link><description>LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles token ownership in password reset.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56339 | IBM WebSphere Application Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56339</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 9.0 and WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 25.0.0.7 could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions caused by a failure to honor security configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55133 | In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via topicName in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55133</link><description>In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via topicName in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55134 | In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via tag in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55134</link><description>In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via tag in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55135 | In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before 690ce56, there is XSS via a profile picture to server/controller/userController.js. Formats o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55135</link><description>In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before 690ce56, there is XSS via a profile picture to server/controller/userController.js. Formats other than PNG, JPEG, and WEBP are permitted by server/routes/userRoutes.js; this includes SVG.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55136 | ERC (aka Emotion Recognition in Conversation) through 0.3 has insecure deserialization via a serialized object because jsonpickle is used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55136</link><description>ERC (aka Emotion Recognition in Conversation) through 0.3 has insecure deserialization via a serialized object because jsonpickle is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47907 | Incorrect results returned from Rows.Scan in database/sql</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47907</link><description>Cancelling a query (e.g. by cancelling the context passed to one of the query methods) during a call to the Scan method of the returned Rows can result in unexpected results if other queries are being made in parallel. This can result in a race condition that may overwrite the expected results with those of another query, causing the call to Scan to return either unexpected results from the other query or an error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7054 | Infinite loop triggered by connection ID retirement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7054</link><description>Cloudflare quiche was discovered to be vulnerable to an infinite loop when sending packets containing RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID frames.

QUIC connections possess a set of connection identifiers (IDs); see  Section 5.1 of RFC 9000 https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc9000#section-5.1 . Once the QUIC handshake completes, a local endpoint is responsible for issuing and retiring Connection IDs that are used by the remote peer to populate the Destination Connection ID field in packets sent from remote to local. Each Connection ID has a sequence number to ensure synchronization between peers.

An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by first completing a handshake and then sending a specially-crafted set of frames that trigger a connection ID retirement in the victim. When the victim attempts to send a packet containing RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID frames,  Section 19.16 of RFC 9000 https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc9000#section-19.6  requires that the sequence number of the retired connection ID must not be the same as the sequence number of the connection ID used by the packet. In other words, a packet cannot contain a frame that retires itself. In scenarios such as path migration, it is possible for there to be multiple active paths with different active connection IDs that could be used to retire each other. The exploit triggered an unintentional behaviour of a quiche design feature that supports retirement across paths while maintaining full connection ID synchronization, leading to an infinite loop.This issue affects quiche: from 0.15.0 before 0.24.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44779 | An issue in Ollama v0.1.33 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via sending a crafted packet to the endpoint /api/pull.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44779</link><description>An issue in Ollama v0.1.33 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via sending a crafted packet to the endpoint /api/pull.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50952 | openjpeg v 2.5.0 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component /openjp2/dwt.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50952</link><description>openjpeg v 2.5.0 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component /openjp2/dwt.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47188 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47188</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a command injection attack due to insufficient parameter sanitization. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of the phone, leading to disclosure or modification of sensitive configuration data or affecting device availability and operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52680 | EyouCMS 1.6.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=System&amp;a=web&amp;lang=cn.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52680</link><description>EyouCMS 1.6.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php?m=admin&amp;amp;c=System&amp;amp;a=web&amp;lang;=cn.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 14:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55401 | An issue in 4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55401</link><description>An issue in 4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8533 | Incorrect Authorization of XPC Service in Fantastical.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8533</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the XPC services of Fantastical. The services failed to implement proper client authorization checks in its listener:shouldAcceptNewConnection method, unconditionally accepting requests from any local process. As a result, any local, unprivileged process could connect to the XPC service and access its methods.




This issue has been resolved in version 4.0.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35970 | On multiple products of SEIKO EPSON and FUJIFILM Corporation, the initial administrator password is easy to guess from the information avail...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35970</link><description>On multiple products of SEIKO EPSON and FUJIFILM Corporation, the initial administrator password is easy to guess from the information available via SNMP. If the administrator password is not changed from the initial one, a remote attacker with SNMP access can log in to the product with the administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29866 | : External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows : Parameter Injection.This issue affects X-Free ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29866</link><description>: External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows : Parameter Injection.This issue affects X-Free Uploader: from 1.0.1.0084 before 1.0.1.0085, from 2.0.1.0034 before 2.0.1.0035.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32094 | An issue was discovered in Akamai Ghost, as used for the Akamai CDN platform before 2025-03-26. Under certain circumstances, a client making...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32094</link><description>An issue was discovered in Akamai Ghost, as used for the Akamai CDN platform before 2025-03-26. Under certain circumstances, a client making an HTTP/1.x OPTIONS request with an "Expect: 100-continue" header, and using obsolete line folding, can lead to a discrepancy in how two in-path Akamai servers interpret the request, allowing an attacker to smuggle a second request in the original request body.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29865 | : Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows Path Tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29865</link><description>: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows Path Traversal.This issue affects X-Free Uploader: from 1.0.1.0084 before 1.0.1.0085, from 2.0.1.0034 before 2.0.1.0035.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8576 | Use after free in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8576</link><description>Use after free in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8577 | Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8577</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8578 | Use after free in Cast in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8578</link><description>Use after free in Cast in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8579 | Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8579</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8580 | Inappropriate implementation in Filesystems in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8580</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Filesystems in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8581 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8581</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8582 | Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Core in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8582</link><description>Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Core in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8583 | Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8583</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3770 | SMM IDT Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3770</link><description>EDK2 contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause “Protection Mechanism Failure” by local access. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will lead to arbitrary code execution and impact Confidentiality, Integrity, and Availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54783 | SuiteCRM: Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) through HTTP Referrer header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54783</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.6 and below have a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code by modifying the HTTP Referer header to include some arbitrary domain with malicious JavaScript code at the end. The server will attempt to block the arbitrary domain but allow the JavaScript code to execute. This is fixed in version 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54784 | SuiteCRM is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) through its email viewer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54784</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. There is a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the email viewer in versions 7.14.0 through 7.14.6. An external attacker could send a prepared message to the inbox of the SuiteCRM-instance. By simply viewing emails as the logged-in user, the payload can be triggered. With that, an attacker is able to run arbitrary actions as the logged-in user - like extracting data, or if it is an admin executing the payload, takeover the instance. This is fixed in versions 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54798 | tmp does not restrict arbitrary temporary file / directory write via symbolic link `dir` parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54798</link><description>tmp is a temporary file and directory creator for node.js. In versions 0.2.3 and below, tmp is vulnerable to an arbitrary temporary file / directory write via symbolic link dir parameter. This is fixed in version 0.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54799 | Lego does not enforce HTTPS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54799</link><description>Let's Encrypt client and ACME library written in Go (Lego). In versions 4.25.1 and below, the github.com/go-acme/lego/v4/acme/api package (thus the lego library and the lego cli as well) don't enforce HTTPS when talking to CAs as an ACME client. Unlike the http-01 challenge which solves an ACME challenge over unencrypted HTTP, the ACME protocol requires HTTPS when a client communicates with the CA to performs ACME functions. However, the library fails to enforce HTTPS both in the original discover URL (configured by the library user) and in the subsequent addresses returned by the CAs in the directory and order objects. If users input HTTP URLs or CAs misconfigure endpoints, protocol operations occur over HTTP instead of HTTPS. This compromises privacy by exposing request/response details like account and request identifiers to network attackers. This was fixed in version 4.25.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54882 | Himmelblau&amp;#x27;s Kerberos credential cache collection is world readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54882</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. In versions 0.8.0 through 0.9.21 and 1.0.0-beta through 1.1.0, Himmelblau stores the cloud TGT received during logon in the Kerberos credential cache. The created credential cache collection and received credentials are stored as world readable. This is fixed in versions 0.9.22 and 1.2.0. To work around this issue, remove all read access to Himmelblau caches for all users except for owners.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54885 | Thinbus generates insufficient entropy: 252 bits vs minimum 256 bits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54885</link><description>Thinbus Javascript Secure Remote Password is a browser SRP6a implementation for zero-knowledge password authentication. In versions 2.0.0 and below, a protocol compliance bug causes the client to generate a fixed 252 bits of entropy instead of the intended bit length of the safe prime (defaulted to 2048 bits). The client public value is being generated from a private value that is 4 bits below the specification. This reduces the protocol's designed security margin it is now practically exploitable. The servers full sized 2048 bit random number is used to create the shared session key and password proof. This is fixed in version 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54788 | SuiteCRM: Authenticated Blind SQL Injection in InboundEmail module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54788</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions and below, the InboundEmail module allows the arbitrary execution of queries in the backend database, leading to SQL injection. This can have wide-reaching implications on confidentiality, integrity, and availability, as database data can be retrieved, modified, or removed entirely. This issue is fixed in version 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54786 | SuiteCRM: Legacy iCal service allows unauthenticated access to meeting data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54786</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions 7.14.6 and 8.8.0, the broken authentication in the legacy iCal service allows unauthenticated access to meeting data. An unauthenticated actor can view any user's meeting (calendar event) data given their username, related functionality allows user enumeration. This is fixed in versions 7.14.7 and 8.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54785 | SuiteCRM is Vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in Reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54785</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions 7.14.6  and 8.8.0, user-supplied input is not validated/sanitized before it is passed to the unserialize function, which could lead to penetration, privilege escalation, sensitive data exposure, Denial of Service, cryptomining and ransomware. This issue is fixed in version 7.14.7 and 8.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7770 | Predictable Seed in Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) in Tigo Energy Cloud Connect Advanced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7770</link><description>Tigo Energy's CCA device is vulnerable to insecure session ID generation in their remote API. The session IDs are generated using a predictable method based on the current timestamp, allowing attackers to recreate valid session IDs. When combined with the ability to circumvent session ID requirements for certain commands, this enables unauthorized access to sensitive device functions on connected solar optimization systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47908 | Denial of service via malicious preflight requests in github.com/rs/cors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47908</link><description>Middleware causes a prohibitive amount of heap allocations when processing malicious preflight requests that include a Access-Control-Request-Headers (ACRH) header whose value contains many commas. This behavior can be abused by attackers to produce undue load on the middleware/server as an attempt to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51058 | Bottinelli Informatical Vedo Suite 2024.17 is vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the /api_vedo/video/preview endpoint, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51058</link><description>Bottinelli Informatical Vedo Suite 2024.17 is vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the /api_vedo/video/preview endpoint, which allows remote authenticated attackers to trigger HTTP requests towards arbitrary remote paths via the "file" URL parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6632 | PSD File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6632</link><description>A maliciously crafted PSD file, when linked or imported into Autodesk 3ds Max, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6633 | RBG File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6633</link><description>A maliciously crafted RBG file, when parsed through Autodesk 3ds Max, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6634 | TGA File Parsing Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6634</link><description>A maliciously crafted TGA file, when linked or imported into Autodesk 3ds Max, can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7769 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (&amp;#x27;Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in Tigo Energy Cloud Connect Advanced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7769</link><description>Tigo Energy's CCA is vulnerable to a command injection vulnerability in the /cgi-bin/mobile_api endpoint when the DEVICE_PING command is called, allowing remote code execution due to improper handling of user input. When used with default credentials, this enables attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the device that could cause potential unauthorized access, service disruption, and data exposure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50740 | AutoConnect 1.4.2, an Arduino library, is vulnerable to a cross site scripting (xss) vulnerability. The AutoConnect web interface /_ac/confi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50740</link><description>AutoConnect 1.4.2, an Arduino library, is vulnerable to a cross site scripting (xss) vulnerability. The AutoConnect web interface /_ac/config allows HTML/JS code to be executed via a crafted network SSID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51052 | A path traversal vulnerability in Vedo Suite 2024.17 allows remote authenticated attackers to read arbitrary filesystem files by exploiting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51052</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in Vedo Suite 2024.17 allows remote authenticated attackers to read arbitrary filesystem files by exploiting an unsanitized 'file_get_contents()' function call in '/api_vedo/template'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51053 | A Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /api_vedo/ in Vedo Suite version 2024.17 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary Javascrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51053</link><description>A Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /api_vedo/ in Vedo Suite version 2024.17 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary Javascript or HTML code and potentially trigger code execution in victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51054 | Vedo Suite 2024.17 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, which allows remote attackers to obtain a valid high privilege JWT token witho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51054</link><description>Vedo Suite 2024.17 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, which allows remote attackers to obtain a valid high privilege JWT token without prior authentication via sending an empty HTTP POST request to the /autologin/ API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51055 | Insecure Data Storage of credentials has been found in /api_vedo/configuration/config.yml file in Vedo Suite version 2024.17. This file cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51055</link><description>Insecure Data Storage of credentials has been found in /api_vedo/configuration/config.yml file in Vedo Suite version 2024.17. This file contains clear-text credentials, secret keys, and database information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51056 | An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Vedo Suite version 2024.17 allows remote authenticated attackers to write to arbitrary filesyst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51056</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Vedo Suite version 2024.17 allows remote authenticated attackers to write to arbitrary filesystem paths by exploiting the insecure 'uploadPreviews()' custom function in '/api_vedo/colorways_preview', ultimately resulting in remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51057 | A local file inclusion (LFI) vulnerability in Vedo Suite version 2024.17 allows remote authenticated attackers to read arbitrary filesystem ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51057</link><description>A local file inclusion (LFI) vulnerability in Vedo Suite version 2024.17 allows remote authenticated attackers to read arbitrary filesystem files by exploiting an unsanitized 'readfile()' function call in '/api_vedo/video/preview'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7768 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Tigo Energy Cloud Connect Advanced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7768</link><description>Tigo Energy's Cloud Connect Advanced (CCA) device contains hard-coded credentials that allow unauthorized users to gain administrative access. This vulnerability enables attackers to escalate privileges and take full control of the device, potentially modifying system settings, disrupting solar energy production, and interfering with safety mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55398 | 4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 was discovered to contain insecure permissions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55398</link><description>4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 was discovered to contain insecure permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55399 | 4C Strategies Exonaut before v21.6.2.1-1 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55399</link><description>4C Strategies Exonaut before v21.6.2.1-1 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55402 | 4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 was discovered to contain an access control issue.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55402</link><description>4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 was discovered to contain an access control issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46660 | An issue was discovered in 4C Strategies Exonaut 21.6. Passwords, stored in the database, are hashed without a salt.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46660</link><description>An issue was discovered in 4C Strategies Exonaut 21.6. Passwords, stored in the database, are hashed without a salt.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46659 | An issue was discovered in ExonautWeb in 4C Strategies Exonaut 21.6. Information disclosure can occur via an external HTTPS request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46659</link><description>An issue was discovered in ExonautWeb in 4C Strategies Exonaut 21.6. Information disclosure can occur via an external HTTPS request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38746 | Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery, versions prior to 5.5.14.0, contains an Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38746</link><description>Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery, versions prior to 5.5.14.0, contains an Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with physical access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38747 | Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery, versions prior to 5.5.14.0, contain a Creation of Temporary File With Insecure Permissions vulnerability. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38747</link><description>Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery, versions prior to 5.5.14.0, contain a Creation of Temporary File With Insecure Permissions vulnerability. A local authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45764 | jsrsasign v11.1.0 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45764</link><description>jsrsasign v11.1.0 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51624 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Zone Bitaqati thru 3.4.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51624</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Zone Bitaqati thru 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45766 | poco v1.14.1-release was discovered to contain weak encryption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45766</link><description>poco v1.14.1-release was discovered to contain weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8667 | SkyworkAI DeepResearchAgent tools.py from_mcp os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8667</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SkyworkAI DeepResearchAgent up to 08eb7f8eb9505d0094d75bb97ff7dacc3fa3bbf2. Affected is the function from_code/from_dict/from_mcp of the file src/tools/tools.py. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8419 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: keycloak smtp inject vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8419</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak-services. Special characters used during e-mail registration may perform SMTP Injection and unexpectedly send short unwanted e-mails. The email is limited to 64 characters (limited local part of the email), so the attack is limited to very shorts emails (subject and little data, the example is 60 chars). This flaw's only direct consequence is an unsolicited email being sent from the Keycloak server. However, this action could be a precursor for more sophisticated attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8665 | agno-agi agno Model Context Protocol mcp.py MultiMCPTools os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8665</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in agno-agi agno up to 1.7.5. This issue affects the function MCPTools/MultiMCPTools in the library libs/agno/agno/tools/mcp.py of the component Model Context Protocol Handler. The manipulation of the argument command leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30127 | An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. Once access is gained either by default, common, or cracked passwords, th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30127</link><description>An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. Once access is gained either by default, common, or cracked passwords, the video recordings (containing sensitive routes, conversations, and footage) are open for downloading by creating a socket to command port 7777, and then downloading video via port 7778 and audio via port 7779.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20215 | Cisco Webex Meeting Client Join Certificate Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20215</link><description>A vulnerability in the meeting-join functionality of Cisco Webex Meetings could have allowed an unauthenticated, network-proximate attacker to complete a meeting-join process in place of an intended targeted user, provided the requisite conditions were satisfied. Cisco has addressed this vulnerability in the Cisco Webex Meetings service, and no customer action is needed.

This vulnerability existed due to client certificate validation issues. Prior to this vulnerability being addressed, an attacker could have exploited this vulnerability by monitoring local wireless or adjacent networks for client-join requests and attempting to interrupt and complete the meeting-join flow as another user who was currently joining a meeting. To successfully exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would need the capability to position themselves in a local wireless or adjacent network, to monitor and intercept the targeted network traffic flows, and to satisfy timing requirements in order to interrupt the meeting-join flow and exploit the vulnerability. A successful exploit could have allowed the attacker to join the meeting as another user. However, the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any malicious use of the vulnerability that is described in this advisory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20331 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerabiliy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20331</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20332 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Authorization Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20332</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify parts of the configuration on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to the lack of server-side validation of Administrator permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted HTTP request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify descriptions of files on a specific page. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid read-only Administrator&amp;nbsp;credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53786 | Microsoft Exchange Server Hybrid Deployment Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53786</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51531 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the contex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51531</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a victim's browser via injcting a crafted payload into the tabfields parameter at /dpw/scripts/cgiip.exe/WService. This is fixed in Halbjahresversion 2024_12_004.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51532 | Incorrect access control in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows unauthorized attackers to access the built-in Database Monitor via a crafted reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51532</link><description>Incorrect access control in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows unauthorized attackers to access the built-in Database Monitor via a crafted request. This is fixed in Halbjahresversion 2024_12_004.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8244 | Walk/WalkDir in path/filepath susceptible to symlink race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8244</link><description>The filepath.Walk and filepath.WalkDir functions are documented as not following symbolic links, but both functions are susceptible to a TOCTOU (time of check/time of use) race condition where a portion of the path being walked is replaced with a symbolic link while the walk is in progress.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48393 | The server identity check mechanism for firmware upgrade performed via command shell is insecurely implemented potentially allowing an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48393</link><description>The server identity check mechanism for firmware upgrade performed via command shell is insecurely implemented potentially allowing an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-middle attack. This security issue has been fixed in the latest version which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48394 | An attacker with authenticated and privileged access could modify the contents of a non-sensitive file by traversing the path in the limited...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48394</link><description>An attacker with authenticated and privileged access could modify the contents of a non-sensitive file by traversing the path in the limited shell of the CLI. This security issue has been fixed in the latest version which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50234 | MCCMS v2.7.0 has an SSRF vulnerability located in the index() method of the sys\apps\controllers\api\Gf.php file, where the pic parameter is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50234</link><description>MCCMS v2.7.0 has an SSRF vulnerability located in the index() method of the sys\apps\controllers\api\Gf.php file, where the pic parameter is processed. The pic parameter is decrypted using the sys_auth($pic, 1) function, which utilizes a hard-coded key Mc_Encryption_Key (bD2voYwPpNuJ7B8), defined in the db.php file. The decrypted URL is passed to the geturl() method, which uses cURL to make a request to the URL without proper security checks. An attacker can craft a malicious encrypted pic parameter, which, when decrypted, points to internal addresses or local file paths (such as http://127.0.0.1 or file://). By using the file:// protocol, the attacker can access arbitrary files on the local file system (e.g., file:///etc/passwd, file:///C:/Windows/System32/drivers/etc/hosts), allowing them to read sensitive configuration files, log files, and more, leading to information leakage or system exposure. The danger of this SSRF vulnerability includes accessing internal services and local file systems through protocols like http://, ftp://, and file://, which can result in sensitive data leakage, remote code execution, privilege escalation, or full system compromise, severely affecting the system's security and stability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50233 | A vulnerability in QCMS version 6.0.5 allows authenticated users to read arbitrary files from the server due to insufficient validation of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50233</link><description>A vulnerability in QCMS version 6.0.5 allows authenticated users to read arbitrary files from the server due to insufficient validation of the "Name" parameter in the backend template editor. By manipulating the parameter, attackers can perform directory traversal and access sensitive files outside the intended template directory, potentially exposing system configuration, PHP source code, or other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51306 | In Gatling Enterprise versions below 1.25.0, a user logging-out can still use his session token to continue using the application without ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51306</link><description>In Gatling Enterprise versions below 1.25.0, a user logging-out can still use his session token to continue using the application without expiration, due to incorrect session management.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51308 | In Gatling Enterprise versions below 1.25.0, a low-privileged user that does not hold the role "admin" could perform a REST API call on read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51308</link><description>In Gatling Enterprise versions below 1.25.0, a low-privileged user that does not hold the role "admin" could perform a REST API call on read-only endpoints, allowing him to collect some information, due to missing authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52885 | Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52885</link><description>The Mobile Access Portal's File Share application is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack, allowing an authenticated, malicious end-user (authorized to at least one File Share application) to list the file names of 'nobody'-accessible directories on the Mobile Access gateway.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2028 | Lack of TLS validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2028</link><description>Lack of TLS validation when downloading a CSV file including mapping from IPs to countries used ONLY for displaying country flags in logs</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36020 | IBM Guardium Data Protection information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36020</link><description>IBM Guardium Data Protection could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information due to cleartext transmission of sensitive credential information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50286 | A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Grav CMS v1.7.48 allows an authenticated admin to upload a malicious plugin via the /admin/to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50286</link><description>A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Grav CMS v1.7.48 allows an authenticated admin to upload a malicious plugin via the /admin/tools/direct-install interface. Once uploaded, the plugin is automatically extracted and loaded, allowing arbitrary PHP code execution and reverse shell access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51040 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Web Management System Unauthorized access vulnerability via the /FrameSetCore.html endpoint in Electrolink...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51040</link><description>Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Web Management System Unauthorized access vulnerability via the /FrameSetCore.html endpoint in Electrolink 500W, 1kW, 2kW Medium DAB Transmitter Web v01.09, v01.08, v01.07, and Display v1.4, v1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8616 | Malicious browser plugins may cause Authentication replay attack vulnerability to bypass authentication in OpenText Advanced Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8616</link><description>A weakness identified in OpenText Advanced Authentication where a Malicious browser plugin can record and replay the user authentication process to bypass Authentication. This issue affects Advanced Authentication on or before 6.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3320 | IBM Tivoli Monitoring code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3320</link><description>IBM Tivoli Monitoring 6.3.0.7 through 6.3.0.7 Service Pack 20 is vulnerable to a heap-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A remote attacker could overflow a buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system or cause the server to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3354 | IBM Tivoli Monitoring code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3354</link><description>IBM Tivoli Monitoring 6.3.0.7 through 6.3.0.7 Service Pack 20 is vulnerable to a heap-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A remote attacker could overflow a buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system or cause the server to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23311 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a stack overflow through specially crafted HTTP reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23311</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a stack overflow through specially crafted HTTP requests. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to remote code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23317 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability in the HTTP server, where an attacker could start a reverse shell by sending a speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23317</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability in the HTTP server, where an attacker could start a reverse shell by sending a specially crafted HTTP request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to remote code execution, denial of service, data tampering, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23318 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23318</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, data tampering, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23319 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23319</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of-bounds write by sending a request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to remote code execution, denial of service, data tampering, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23320 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause the share...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23320</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause the shared memory limit to be exceeded by sending a very large request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23321 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a divide by zero issue by issuing an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23321</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a divide by zero issue by issuing an invalid request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23322 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where multiple requests could cause a double free when a strea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23322</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where multiple requests could cause a double free when a stream is cancelled before it is processed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23323 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an integer overflow or wraparound, le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23323</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an integer overflow or wraparound, leading to a segmentation fault, by providing an invalid request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23324 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an integer overflow or wraparound, le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23324</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an integer overflow or wraparound, leading to a segmentation fault,  by providing an invalid request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23325 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause uncontrolled recursion through a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23325</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause uncontrolled recursion through a specially crafted input. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23326 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an integer overflow through a sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23326</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an integer overflow through a specially crafted input. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23327 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an integer overflow through spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23327</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an integer overflow through specially crafted inputs. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23331 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a memory allocation with excessive si...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23331</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a memory allocation with excessive size value, leading to a segmentation fault, by providing an invalid request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23333 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23333</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of-bounds read by manipulating shared memory data. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23334 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23334</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the Python backend, where an attacker could cause an out-of-bounds read by sending a request. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23335 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux and the Tensor RT backend contain a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an unde...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23335</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux and the Tensor RT backend contain a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an underflow by a specific model configuration and a specific input. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23310 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause stack buffer overflow by special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23310</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause stack buffer overflow by specially crafted inputs. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to remote code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5197 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in huggingface/transformers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5197</link><description>A Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the Hugging Face Transformers library, specifically in the `convert_tf_weight_name_to_pt_weight_name()` function. This function, responsible for converting TensorFlow weight names to PyTorch format, uses a regex pattern `/[^/]*___([^/]*)/` that can be exploited to cause excessive CPU consumption through crafted input strings due to catastrophic backtracking. The vulnerability affects versions up to 4.51.3 and is fixed in version 4.53.0. This issue can lead to service disruption, resource exhaustion, and potential API service vulnerabilities, impacting model conversion processes between TensorFlow and PyTorch formats.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46391 | CWE-284: Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46391</link><description>CWE-284: Improper Access Control</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46388 | CWE-200 Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46388</link><description>CWE-200 Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46389 | CWE-620: Unverified Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46389</link><description>CWE-620: Unverified Password Change</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46390 | CWE-204: Observable Response Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46390</link><description>CWE-204: Observable Response Discrepancy</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46387 | CWE-639 Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46387</link><description>CWE-639 Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46386 | CWE-639 Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46386</link><description>CWE-639 Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6013 | Vault LDAP MFA Enforcement Bypass When Using Username As Alias</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6013</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise’s (“Vault”) ldap auth method may not have correctly enforced MFA if username_as_alias was set to true and a user had multiple CNs that are equal but with leading or trailing spaces. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.2 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.2, 1.19.8, 1.18.13, and 1.16.24.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22469 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in CL4/6NX Plus and CL4/6NX-J Plus (Japan model) with the firmware versions prior to 1.15.5-r1. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22469</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in CL4/6NX Plus and CL4/6NX-J Plus (Japan model) with the firmware versions prior to 1.15.5-r1. An arbitrary OS command may be executed on the system with a certain non-administrative user privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22470 | CL4/6NX Plus and CL4/6NX-J Plus (Japan model) with the firmware versions prior to 1.15.5-r1 allow crafted dangerous files to be uploaded. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22470</link><description>CL4/6NX Plus and CL4/6NX-J Plus (Japan model) with the firmware versions prior to 1.15.5-r1 allow crafted dangerous files to be uploaded. An arbitrary Lua script may be executed on the system with the root privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7771 | Code Execution / Escalation of Privileges in ThrottleStop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7771</link><description>ThrottleStop.sys, a legitimate driver, exposes two IOCTL interfaces that allow arbitrary read and write access to physical memory via the MmMapIoSpace function. This insecure implementation can be exploited by a malicious user-mode application to patch the running Windows kernel and invoke arbitrary kernel functions with ring-0 privileges. The vulnerability enables local attackers to execute arbitrary code in kernel context, resulting in privilege escalation and potential follow-on attacks, such as disabling security software or bypassing kernel-level protections. ThrottleStop.sys version 3.0.0.0 and possibly others are affected. Apply updates per vendor instructions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8620 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 4.6.0 - Unauthenticated Donor Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8620</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract donor names, emails, and donor id.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8556 | Github.com/cloudflare/circl: circl-fourq: missing and wrong validation can lead to incorrect results</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8556</link><description>A flaw was found in CIRCL's implementation of the FourQ elliptic curve. This vulnerability allows an attacker to compromise session security via low-order point injection and incorrect point validation during Diffie-Hellman key exchange.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7202 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) allowed remote control of Elgato Key Lights</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7202</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Elgato's Key Lights and related light products allows an attacker to host a malicious webpage that remotely controlles the victim's lights.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21452 | Reachable Assertion in Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21452</link><description>Transient DOS while processing a random-access response (RAR) with an invalid PDU length on LTE network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21455 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera_Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21455</link><description>Memory corruption while submitting blob data to kernel space though IOCTL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21456 | Use After Free in NPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21456</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL command when multiple threads are called to map/unmap buffer concurrently.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21457 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive OS Platform Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21457</link><description>Information disclosure while opening a fastrpc session when domain is not sanitized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21458 | Use After Free in NPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21458</link><description>Memory corruption when IOCTL interface is called to map and unmap buffers simultaneously.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21461 | Out-of-bounds Write in Camera_Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21461</link><description>Memory corruption when programming registers through virtual CDM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21464 | Out-of-bounds Read in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21464</link><description>Information disclosure while reading data from an image using specified offset and size parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21465 | Out-of-bounds Read in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21465</link><description>Information disclosure while processing the hash segment in an MBN file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21472 | Leftover Debug Code in Secure Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21472</link><description>Information disclosure while capturing logs as eSE debug messages are logged.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21473 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera_Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21473</link><description>Memory corruption when using Virtual cdm (Camera Data Mover) to write registers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21474 | Use After Free in BTHOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21474</link><description>Memory corruption while processing commands from A2dp sink command queue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21477 | Improper Input Validation in Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21477</link><description>Transient DOS while processing CCCH data when NW sends data with invalid length.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27062 | Improper Access Control in Automotive Multimedia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27062</link><description>Memory corruption while handling client exceptions, allowing unauthorized channel access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27065 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27065</link><description>Transient DOS while processing a frame with malformed shared-key descriptor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27066 | Reachable Assertion in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27066</link><description>Transient DOS while processing an ANQP message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27067 | Improper Validation of Array Index in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27067</link><description>Memory corruption while processing DDI call with invalid buffer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27068 | Buffer Over-read in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27068</link><description>Memory corruption while processing an IOCTL command with an arbitrary address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27069 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27069</link><description>Memory corruption while processing DDI command calls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27071 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Powerline Communication Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27071</link><description>Memory corruption while processing specific files in Powerline Communication Firmware.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27072 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Automotive Vehicle Networks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27072</link><description>Information disclosure while processing a packet at EAVB BE side with invalid header length.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27073 | Reachable Assertion in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27073</link><description>Transient DOS while creating NDP instance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27075 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Bluetooth HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27075</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL command with larger buffer in Bluetooth Host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27076 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27076</link><description>Memory corruption while processing simultaneous requests via escape path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47324 | Exposure of Sensitive Information Through Metadata in Powerline Communication Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47324</link><description>Information disclosure while accessing and modifying the PIB file of a remote device via powerline.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7954 | Race Condition in Shopware Voucher Submission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7954</link><description>A race condition vulnerability has been identified in Shopware's voucher system of Shopware v6.6.10.4 that allows attackers to bypass intended voucher restrictions and exceed usage limitations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7376 | Information Tampering Vulnerability in multiple processes of GENESIS64, MC Works64, and GENESIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7376</link><description>Windows Shortcut Following (.LNK) vulnerability in multiple processes of Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions GENESIS version 11.00, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions, and Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS version 11.00 allows a local authenticated attacker to make an unauthorized write to arbitrary files, by creating a symbolic link from a file used as a write destination by the processes of the affected products to a target file. This could allow the attacker to destroy the file on a PC with the affected products installed, resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the PC if the destroyed file is necessary for the operation of the PC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7727 | Gutenverse &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Animated Text and Fun Fact Blocks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7727</link><description>The Gutenverse plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Animated Text and Fun Fact blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20990 | Improper access control in accessing system device node prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access device identifier.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20990</link><description>Improper access control in accessing system device node prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access device identifier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21010 | Improper privilege management in SamsungAccount prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to deactivate Samsung acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21010</link><description>Improper privilege management in SamsungAccount prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to deactivate Samsung account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21011 | Improper access control in SemSensorService for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21011</link><description>Improper access control in SemSensorService for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information related to motion and body sensors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21012 | Improper access control in fall detection for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to modify fall detection c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21012</link><description>Improper access control in fall detection for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to modify fall detection configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21013 | Improper access control in SemSensorManager for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21013</link><description>Improper access control in SemSensorManager for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information related to outdoor exercise and sleep time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21014 | Improper export of android application component in Emergency SoS prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21014</link><description>Improper export of android application component in Emergency SoS prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21015 | Path Traversal in Document scanner prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to delete file with Document scanner's privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21015</link><description>Path Traversal in Document scanner prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to delete file with Document scanner's privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21016 | Improper access control in PkgPredictorService prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 in Chinese Android 13, 14, 15 and 16 allows local attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21016</link><description>Improper access control in PkgPredictorService prior to SMR Aug-2025 Release 1 in Chinese Android 13, 14, 15 and 16 allows local attackers to use the privileged APIs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21017 | Out-of-bounds write in detaching crypto box in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to write out-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21017</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in detaching crypto box in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21018 | Out-of-bounds read in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21018</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21019 | Improper authorization in Samsung Health prior to version 6.30.1.003 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Health. User interacti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21019</link><description>Improper authorization in Samsung Health prior to version 6.30.1.003 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Health. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21020 | Out-of-bounds write in creating bitmap images in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to write ou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21020</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in creating bitmap images in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21021 | Out-of-bounds write in drawing pinpad in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21021</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in drawing pinpad in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.17.2 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21022 | Improper access control in Galaxy Wearable prior to version 2.2.63.25042861 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21022</link><description>Improper access control in Galaxy Wearable prior to version 2.2.63.25042861 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21023 | Improper access control in WcsExtension for Galaxy Watch prior to Android Watch 16 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21023</link><description>Improper access control in WcsExtension for Galaxy Watch prior to Android Watch 16 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21024 | Use of Implicit Intent for Sensitive Communication in Smart View prior to Android 16 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21024</link><description>Use of Implicit Intent for Sensitive Communication in Smart View prior to Android 16 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6994 | Reveal Listing &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6994</link><description>The Reveal Listing plugin by smartdatasoft for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 3.3. This is due to the plugin allowing users who are registering new accounts to set their own role or by supplying 'listing_user_role' field. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain elevated privileges by creating an account with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7399 | Betheme &amp;lt;= 28.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7399</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via an Elementor display setting in all versions up to, and including, 28.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7498 | Exclusive Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.7.9.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7498</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8100 | Element Pack Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 8.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Open Street Map Widget Marker Content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8100</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'marker_content' parameter in versions up to, and including, 8.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54639 | ParcelMismatch vulnerability in attribute deserialization.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause playback control ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54639</link><description>ParcelMismatch vulnerability in attribute deserialization.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause playback control screen display exceptions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54640 | ParcelMismatch vulnerability in attribute deserialization.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause playback control ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54640</link><description>ParcelMismatch vulnerability in attribute deserialization.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause playback control screen display exceptions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54641 | Issue of buffer overflow caused by insufficient data verification in the kernel acceleration module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54641</link><description>Issue of buffer overflow caused by insufficient data verification in the kernel acceleration module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54642 | Issue of buffer overflow caused by insufficient data verification in the kernel gyroscope module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54642</link><description>Issue of buffer overflow caused by insufficient data verification in the kernel gyroscope module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54643 | Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the kernel ambient light module.
Impact: Successful exploitation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54643</link><description>Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the kernel ambient light module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54644 | Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the kernel ambient light module.
Impact: Successful exploitation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54644</link><description>Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the kernel ambient light module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54645 | Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the location service module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54645</link><description>Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the location service module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54646 | Vulnerability of inadequate packet length check in the BLE module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect performa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54646</link><description>Vulnerability of inadequate packet length check in the BLE module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54647 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the SSAP module of the NearLink protocol stack.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54647</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the SSAP module of the NearLink protocol stack.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54648 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the SSAP module of the NearLink protocol stack.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54648</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the SSAP module of the NearLink protocol stack.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54649 | Vulnerability of using incompatible types to access resources in the location service.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54649</link><description>Vulnerability of using incompatible types to access resources in the location service.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause some location information attributes to be incorrect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54650 | Improper array index verification vulnerability in the audio codec module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54650</link><description>Improper array index verification vulnerability in the audio codec module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the audio decoding function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54651 | Race condition vulnerability in the kernel hufs module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54651</link><description>Race condition vulnerability in the kernel hufs module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54624 | Unexpected injection event vulnerability in the multimodalinput module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ava...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54624</link><description>Unexpected injection event vulnerability in the multimodalinput module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54625 | Race condition vulnerability in the kernel file system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54625</link><description>Race condition vulnerability in the kernel file system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54626 | Pointer dangling vulnerability in the cjwindow module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect function stability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54626</link><description>Pointer dangling vulnerability in the cjwindow module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect function stability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54627 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the skia module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54627</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the skia module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54628 | Vulnerability of incomplete verification information in the communication module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54628</link><description>Vulnerability of incomplete verification information in the communication module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54629 | Race condition issue occurring in the physical page import process of the memory management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54629</link><description>Race condition issue occurring in the physical page import process of the memory management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54630 | :Vulnerability of insufficient data length verification in the DFA module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54630</link><description>:Vulnerability of insufficient data length verification in the DFA module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54631 | Vulnerability of insufficient data length verification in the partition module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54631</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient data length verification in the partition module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54632 | Vulnerability of insufficient data length verification in the HVB module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54632</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient data length verification in the HVB module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54633 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the register configuration of the DMA module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54633</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the register configuration of the DMA module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54634 | Vulnerability of improper processing of abnormal conditions in huge page separation.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54634</link><description>Vulnerability of improper processing of abnormal conditions in huge page separation.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54635 | Vulnerability of returning released pointers in the distributed notification service.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54635</link><description>Vulnerability of returning released pointers in the distributed notification service.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54636 | Issue of buffer overflow caused by insufficient data verification in the kernel drop detection module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54636</link><description>Issue of buffer overflow caused by insufficient data verification in the kernel drop detection module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54637 | Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the kernel ambient light module.
Impact: Successful exploitation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54637</link><description>Out-of-bounds array access issue due to insufficient data verification in the kernel ambient light module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54638 | Issue of inconsistent read/write serialization in the ad module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54638</link><description>Issue of inconsistent read/write serialization in the ad module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the availability of the ad service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8420 | Request a Quote Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Unauthenticated Limited Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8420</link><description>The Request a Quote Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in version less than, or equal to, 2.5.2 via the emd_form_builder_lite_pagenum function. This is due to the plugin not properly validating user input before using it as a function name. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server, however, parameters can not be passed to the functions called.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8595 | Zakra &amp;lt;= 4.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Subscriber+ Demo Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8595</link><description>The Zakra theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the welcome_notice_import_handler() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to import demo settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54606 | Status verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54606</link><description>Status verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54607 | Authentication management vulnerability in the ArkWeb module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54607</link><description>Authentication management vulnerability in the ArkWeb module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54608 | Vulnerability that allows setting screen rotation direction without permission verification in the screen management module.
Impact: Success...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54608</link><description>Vulnerability that allows setting screen rotation direction without permission verification in the screen management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause device screen orientation to be arbitrarily set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54609 | Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the audio codec module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54609</link><description>Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the audio codec module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54610 | Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the audio codec module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54610</link><description>Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the audio codec module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54611 | EXTRA_REFERRER resource read vulnerability in the Gallery module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54611</link><description>EXTRA_REFERRER resource read vulnerability in the Gallery module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54612 | Iterator failure vulnerability in the card management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect function stab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54612</link><description>Iterator failure vulnerability in the card management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect function stability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54613 | Iterator failure vulnerability in the card management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect function stab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54613</link><description>Iterator failure vulnerability in the card management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect function stability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54614 | Input verification vulnerability in the home screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54614</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the home screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54615 | Vulnerability of insufficient information protection in the media library module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54615</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient information protection in the media library module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54616 | Out-of-bounds array access vulnerability in the ArkUI framework.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54616</link><description>Out-of-bounds array access vulnerability in the ArkUI framework.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54617 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the dms_fwk module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can cause RCE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54617</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the dms_fwk module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can cause RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54618 | Permission control vulnerability in the distributed clipboard module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54618</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the distributed clipboard module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54619 | Iterator failure issue in the multi-mode input module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause iterator failures and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54619</link><description>Iterator failure issue in the multi-mode input module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause iterator failures and affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54620 | Deserialization vulnerability of untrusted data in the ability module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect avai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54620</link><description>Deserialization vulnerability of untrusted data in the ability module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54621 | Iterator failure issue in the WantAgent module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause memory release failures.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54621</link><description>Iterator failure issue in the WantAgent module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause memory release failures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54622 | Binding authentication bypass vulnerability in the devicemanager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54622</link><description>Binding authentication bypass vulnerability in the devicemanager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54623 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the devicemanager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54623</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the devicemanager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6256 | Flex Guten &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via thumbnailHoverEffect Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6256</link><description>The Flex Guten plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘thumbnailHoverEffect’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6259 | esri-map-view &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via esri-map-view Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6259</link><description>The esri-map-view plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's esri-map-view shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6690 | WP Tournament Registration &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via field Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6690</link><description>The WP Tournament Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘field’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6986 | FileBird – WordPress Media Library Folders &amp;amp; File Manager &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6986</link><description>The FileBird – WordPress Media Library Folders &amp; File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7036 | CleverReach WP &amp;lt;= 1.5.20 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7036</link><description>The CleverReach® WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.20 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7502 | WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 8.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7502</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8628 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8628</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26064.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8629 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8629</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26252.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8630 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8630</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26253.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8631 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8631</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26254.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8632 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8632</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26255.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8633 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8633</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26256.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8634 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8634</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26257.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8635 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8635</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26258.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8636 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8636</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26259.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8637 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8637</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26260.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8638 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8638</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26261.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8639 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8639</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26262.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8640 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8640</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26263.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8641 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8641</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26264.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8642 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8642</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26265.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8643 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8643</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26266.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8644 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8644</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26267.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8645 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8645</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26268.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8646 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8646</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26269.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8647 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8647</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26270.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8648 | Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8648</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26271.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8649 | Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8649</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JKWifiService. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26305.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8650 | Kenwood DMX958XR libSystemLib Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8650</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR libSystemLib Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26306.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8651 | Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8651</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JKWifiService. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26307.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8652 | Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8652</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JKWifiService. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26311.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8653 | Kenwood DMX958XR JKRadioService Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8653</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR JKRadioService Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JKRadioService. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26312.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8654 | Kenwood DMX958XR ReadMVGImage Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8654</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR ReadMVGImage Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ReadMVGImage function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26313.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8655 | Kenwood DMX958XR libSystemLib Command injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8655</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR libSystemLib Command injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware update process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26314.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8656 | Kenwood DMX958XR Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8656</link><description>Kenwood DMX958XR Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to downgrade software on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the libSystemLib library. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26355.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54652 | Path traversal vulnerability in the virtualization base module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54652</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the virtualization base module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the confidentiality of the virtualization module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54653 | Path traversal vulnerability in the virtualization file module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54653</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the virtualization file module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the confidentiality of the virtualization file module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54655 | Race condition vulnerability in the virtualization base module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54655</link><description>Race condition vulnerability in the virtualization base module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect the confidentiality and integrity of the virtualization graphics module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>