<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-10488 | Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings &amp;lt;= 8.4.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10488</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file move due to insufficient file path validation in the add_listing_action AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to move arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is moved (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10580 | Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp;amp; Block Control Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10580</link><description>The Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp; Block Control Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10637 | Social Feed Gallery &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10637</link><description>The Social Feed Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in versions less than, or equal to, 4.9.2. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to exfiltrate Instagram profile and media data from any account the site owner connected to their site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11255 | Password Policy Manager | Password Manager &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Configuration Log Out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11255</link><description>The Password Policy Manager | Password Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'moppm_ajax' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to log out the site's connection to miniorange.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11497 | Advanced Database Cleaner &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11497</link><description>The Advanced Database Cleaner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the aDBc_prepare_elements_to_clean() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to alter the keep last setting via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11875 | SpendeOnline.org &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11875</link><description>The SpendeOnline.org plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spendeonline' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11893 | Charitable – Donation Plugin for WordPress – Fundraising with Recurring Donations &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 1.8.8.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11893</link><description>The Charitable – Donation Plugin for WordPress – Fundraising with Recurring Donations &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the donation_ids parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.8.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. Exploitation of the vulnerability requires a paid donation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11976 | FuseWP – WordPress User Sync to Email List &amp;amp; Marketing Automation (Mailchimp, Constant Contact, ActiveCampaign etc.) &amp;lt;= 1.1.23.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Sync Rule Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11976</link><description>The FuseWP – WordPress User Sync to Email List &amp; Marketing Automation (Mailchimp, Constant Contact, ActiveCampaign etc.) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.23.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the save_changes function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add or edit sync rules via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12034 | Fast Velocity Minify &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12034</link><description>The Fast Velocity Minify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4203 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via get_members Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4203</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to error‐based or time-based SQL Injection via the get_members() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.8 due to missing integer validation on the 'offset' and 'row_count' parameters. The function blindly interpolates 'row_count' into a 'LIMIT offset,row_count' clause using esc_sql() rather than enforcing numeric values. MySQL 5.x’s grammar allows a 'PROCEDURE ANALYSE' clause immediately after a LIMIT clause. Unauthenticated attackers controlling 'row_count' can append a stored‐procedure call, enabling error‐based or time‐based blind SQL injection that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8416 | Product Filter by WBW &amp;lt;= 2.9.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8416</link><description>The Product Filter by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'filtersDataBackend' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.7. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8483 | Discussion Board – WordPress Forum Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8483</link><description>The The Discussion Board – WordPress Forum Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9322 | Stripe Payment Forms &amp;lt;= 8.3.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9322</link><description>The Stripe Payment Forms by WP Full Pay – Accept Credit Card Payments, Donations &amp; Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'wpfs-form-name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10694 | User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Missing Authorization to Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10694</link><description>The User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the `maybe_load_onboarding_wizard` function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access the onboarding wizard page and view configuration information including the administrator email address.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10737 | Open Source Genesis Framework &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10737</link><description>The Open Source Genesis Framework theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the theme's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11238 | Watu Quiz &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTTP Referer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11238</link><description>The Watu Quiz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP Referer header in versions less than, or equal to, 3.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when the "Save source URL" option is enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever an user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11244 | Password Protected &amp;lt;= 2.7.11 - Unauthenticated Authorization Bypass via IP Address Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11244</link><description>The Password Protected plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass via IP address spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.11. This is due to the plugin trusting client-controlled HTTP headers (such as X-Forwarded-For, HTTP_CLIENT_IP, and similar headers) to determine user IP addresses in the `pp_get_ip_address()` function when the "Use transients" feature is enabled. This makes it possible for attackers to bypass authorization by spoofing these headers with the IP address of a legitimately authenticated user, granted the "Use transients" option is enabled (non-default configuration) and the site is not behind a CDN or reverse proxy that overwrites these headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11269 | Product Filter by WBW &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11269</link><description>The Product Filter by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'approveNotice' action in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11564 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11564</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check while verifying webhook signatures on the "verifyAndCreateOrderData" function  
in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass payment verification and mark orders as paid by submitting forged webhook requests with `payment_type` set to 'recurring'.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11879 | GenerateBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11879</link><description>The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_option_rest' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to read arbitrary WordPress options, including sensitive information such as SMTP credentials, API keys, and other data stored by other plugins.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11888 | ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon – All in One WooCommerce Solution &amp;lt;= 4.8.4 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Editor+) License Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11888</link><description>The ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon – All in One WooCommerce Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an insufficient capability check on the post_deactive() function and post_activate() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to activate and deactivate licenses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12005 | WP VR – 360 Panorama and Free Virtual Tour Builder For WordPress &amp;lt;= 8.5.41 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12005</link><description>The WP VR – 360 Panorama and Free Virtual Tour Builder For WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.41. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to modify sensitive plugin options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12095 | Simple Registration for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Privilege Escalation via Role Request Approval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12095</link><description>The Simple Registration for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.8. This is due to missing nonce validation on the role requests admin page handler in the includes/display-role-admin.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve pending role requests and escalate user privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6639 | Tutor LMS Pro – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to View/Edit Other Assignments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6639</link><description>The Tutor LMS Pro – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to missing validation on a user controlled key when viewing and editing assignments through the tutor_assignment_submit() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view and edit assignment submissions of other students.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6680 | Tutor LMS &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6680</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with tutor-level access and above, to view assignments for courses they don't teach which may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8413 | Listeo &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via soundcloud Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8413</link><description>The Listeo theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `soundcloud` shortcode in version less than, or equal to, 2.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8588 | Gutenberg Blocks – PublishPress Blocks Controls, Visibility, Reusable Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8588</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks – PublishPress Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Marker Title' and 'Marker Description' parameters for the Maps block in versions up to, and including, 3.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level access and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8666 | Testimonial Carousel For Elementor &amp;lt;= 11.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8666</link><description>The Testimonial Carousel For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters in versions less than, or equal to, 11.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10579 | BackWPup &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10579</link><description>The BackWPup – WordPress Backup &amp; Restore Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'backwpup_working' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve access to a back-up's filename while a backup is running. This information has little value on it's own, but could be used to aid in a brute force attack to retrieve back-up contents in limited environments (i.e. NGINX).</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 04:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11823 | ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11823</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button_exist_text' parameter in the 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11760 | eRoom – Webinar &amp;amp; Meeting Plugin for Zoom, Google Meet, Microsoft Teams &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11760</link><description>The eRoom – Webinar &amp; Meeting Plugin for Zoom, Google Meet, Microsoft Teams plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to exposure of sensitive information in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This is due to the plugin exposing Zoom SDK secret keys in client-side JavaScript within the meeting view template. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract the sdk_secret value, which should remain server-side, compromising the security of the Zoom integration and allowing attackers to generate valid JWT signatures for unauthorized meeting access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 02:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34502 | Shuffle Master Deck Mate 2 Missing Secure Boot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34502</link><description>Deck Mate 2 lacks a verified secure-boot chain and runtime integrity validation for its controller and display modules. Without cryptographic boot verification, an attacker with physical access can modify or replace the bootloader, kernel, or filesystem and gain persistent code execution on reboot. This weakness allows long-term firmware tampering that survives power cycles. The vendor indicates that more recent firmware updates strengthen update-chain integrity and disable physical update ports to mitigate related attack avenues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 23:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34503 | Shuffle Master Deck Mate 1 Unauthenticated EEPROM Firmware Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34503</link><description>Deck Mate 1 executes firmware directly from an external EEPROM without verifying authenticity or integrity. An attacker with physical access can replace or reflash the EEPROM to run arbitrary code that persists across reboots. Because this design predates modern secure-boot or signed-update mechanisms, affected systems should be physically protected or retired from service. The vendor has not indicated that firmware updates are available for this legacy model.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 23:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34500 | Shuffle Master Deck Mate 2 Insecure Update Chain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34500</link><description>Deck Mate 2's firmware update mechanism accepts packages without cryptographic signature verification, encrypts them with a single hard-coded AES key shared across devices, and uses a truncated HMAC for integrity validation. Attackers with access to the update interface - typically via the unit's USB update port - can craft or modify firmware packages to execute arbitrary code as root, allowing persistent compromise of the device's integrity and deck randomization process. Physical or on-premises access remains the most likely attack path, though network-exposed or telemetry-enabled deployments could theoretically allow remote exploitation if misconfigured. The vendor confirmed that firmware updates have been issued to correct these update-chain weaknesses and that USB update access has been disabled on affected units.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 23:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12194 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Legion of the Bouncy Castle Inc. Bouncy Castle for Java FIPS bc-fips on All (API modules)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12194</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Legion of the Bouncy Castle Inc. Bouncy Castle for Java FIPS bc-fips on All (API modules), Legion of the Bouncy Castle Inc. Bouncy Castle for Java LTS bcprov-lts8on on All (API modules) allows Excessive Allocation. This vulnerability is associated with program files core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/fips/AESNativeCFB.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/fips/AESNativeGCM.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/fips/SHA256NativeDigest.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/fips/AESNativeEngine.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/fips/AESNativeCBC.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/fips/AESNativeCTR.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeCFB.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeGCM.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeEngine.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeCBC.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeGCMSIV.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeCCM.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/engines/AESNativeCTR.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/digests/SHA256NativeDigest.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/digests/SHA224NativeDigest.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/digests/SHA3NativeDigest.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/digests/SHAKENativeDigest.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/digests/SHA512NativeDigest.Java, core/src/main/jdk1.9/org/bouncycastle/crypto/digests/SHA384NativeDigest.Java.

This issue affects Bouncy Castle for Java FIPS: from 2.1.0 through 2.1.1; Bouncy Castle for Java LTS: from 2.73.0 through 2.73.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 23:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62711 | Wasmtime vulnerable to segfault when using component resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62711</link><description>Wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. In versions from 38.0.0 to before 38.0.3, the implementation of component-model related host-to-wasm trampolines in Wasmtime contained a bug where it's possible to carefully craft a component, which when called in a specific way, would crash the host with a segfault or assert failure. Wasmtime 38.0.3 has been released and is patched to fix this issue. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 22:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4106 | WatchGuard Firebox leftover debug code vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4106</link><description>An authenticated admin user with access to both the management WebUI and command line interface on a Firebox can enable a diagnostic debug shell by uploading a platform and version-specific diagnostic package and executing a leftover diagnostic command.



This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 before 12.11.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 21:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34293 | GN4 Publishing System Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34293</link><description>GN4 Publishing System versions prior to 2.6 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability via the API. Authenticated requests to the API's object endpoints allow an authenticated user to request arbitrary user IDs and receive sensitive account data for those users, including the stored password and the account's security question and answer. The exposed recovery data and encrypted password may be used to reset or take over the target account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 21:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52099 | Integer Overflow vulnerability in SQLite SQLite3 v.3.50.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the setupLookaside funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52099</link><description>Integer Overflow vulnerability in SQLite SQLite3 v.3.50.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the setupLookaside function</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60954 | Microweber CMS 2.0 has Weak Password Requirements. The application does not enforce minimum password length or complexity during password re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60954</link><description>Microweber CMS 2.0 has Weak Password Requirements. The application does not enforce minimum password length or complexity during password resets. Users can set extremely weak passwords, including single-character passwords, which can lead to account compromise, including administrative accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62717 | Emlog Pro session verification code error due to clearing logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62717</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. In version 2.5.23, Emlog Pro is vulnerable to a session verification code error due to a clearing logic error. This means the verification code could be reused anywhere an email verification code is required. This issue has been fixed in commit 1f726df.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62723 | FlashMQ does not release memory of queued QoS messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62723</link><description>FlashMQ is a MQTT broker/server, designed for multi-CPU environments. Prior to version 1.23.2, any authenticated user can create sessions and have them collect QoS messages. When not sent to a client, these are then not released upon (eventual) session expiration. Version 1.23.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62716 | Plane Vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting via Open Redirect in ?next_path Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62716</link><description>Plane is open-source project management software. Prior to version 1.1.0, an open redirect vulnerability in the ?next_path query parameter allows attackers to supply arbitrary schemes (e.g., javascript:) that are passed directly to router.push. This results in a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim’s browser. The issue can be exploited without authentication and has severe impact, including information disclosure, and privilege escalation and modifications of administrative settings. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60419 | An issue was discovered in the NDIS Usermode IO driver (RtkIOAC60.sys, version 6.0.5600.16348) allowing local authenticated attackers to sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60419</link><description>An issue was discovered in the NDIS Usermode IO driver (RtkIOAC60.sys, version 6.0.5600.16348) allowing local authenticated attackers to send a crafted IOCTL request to the driver to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 19:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60730 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in the unInstallTheme function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60730</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in the unInstallTheme function</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 18:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60729 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the validThemeFilePath function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60729</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the validThemeFilePath function</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60731 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a File Upload vulnerability in the installTheme function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60731</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a File Upload vulnerability in the installTheme function</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60735 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a File Upload vulnerability in the installPlugin function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60735</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a File Upload vulnerability in the installPlugin function</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12176 | Undocumented Administrative Accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12176</link><description>Undocumented administrative accounts were getting created to facilitate access for applications running on board.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60547 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWAN_Wizard7.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60547</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWAN_Wizard7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60548 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formLanSetupRouterSetting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60548</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formLanSetupRouterSettings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60553 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWAN_Wizard52.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60553</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWAN_Wizard52.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60549 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formAutoDetecWAN_wizard4.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60549</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formAutoDetecWAN_wizard4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60550 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formEasySetTimezone.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60550</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formEasySetTimezone.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60551 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the next_page parameter in the function formDeviceReboot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60551</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the next_page parameter in the function formDeviceReboot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60552 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formTcpipSetup.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60552</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formTcpipSetup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60803 | Antabot White-Jotter up to commit 9bcadc was discovered to contain an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60803</link><description>Antabot White-Jotter up to commit 9bcadc was discovered to contain an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /api/aaa;/../register.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60554 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetEnableWizard.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60554</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetEnableWizard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60555 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWizardSelectMode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60555</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWizardSelectMode.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60556 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWizard1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60556</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetWizard1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60557 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetEasy_Wizard.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60557</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetEasy_Wizard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60558 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formVirtualServ.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60558</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formVirtualServ.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62714 | Karmada Dashboard API Unauthorized Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62714</link><description>Karmada Dashboard is a general-purpose, web-based control panel for Karmada which is a multi-cluster management project. Prior to version 0.2.0, there is an authentication bypass vulnerability in the Karmada Dashboard API. The backend API endpoints (e.g., /api/v1/secret, /api/v1/service) did not enforce authentication, allowing unauthenticated users to access sensitive cluster information such as Secrets and Services directly. Although the web UI required a valid JWT for access, the API itself remained exposed to direct requests without any authentication checks. Any user or entity with network access to the Karmada Dashboard service could exploit this vulnerability to retrieve sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60559 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetDomainFilter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60559</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetDomainFilter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60561 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetEmail.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60561</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetEmail.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60562 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formWlSiteSurvey.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60562</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formWlSiteSurvey.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60563 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetPortTr.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60563</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetPortTr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60564 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetLog.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60564</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetLog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60565 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSchedule.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60565</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSchedule.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60566 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetMACFilter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60566</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetMACFilter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60801 | jshERP up to commit fbda24da was discovered to contain an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the jsh_erp function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60801</link><description>jshERP up to commit fbda24da was discovered to contain an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the jsh_erp function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56438 | An issue in the firmware update mechanism of Nous W3 Smart WiFi Camera v1.33.50.82 allows unauthenticated and physically proximate attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56438</link><description>An issue in the firmware update mechanism of Nous W3 Smart WiFi Camera v1.33.50.82 allows unauthenticated and physically proximate attackers to escalate privileges to root via supplying a crafted update.tar archive file stored on a FAT32-formatted SD card.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60568 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formAdvFirewall.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60568</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formAdvFirewall.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60569 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetRoute.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60569</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetRoute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60570 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formLogDnsquery.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60570</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formLogDnsquery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60571 | D-Link DIR600LAx FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetQoS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60571</link><description>D-Link DIR600LAx FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formSetQoS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60572 | D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formAdvNetwork.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60572</link><description>D-Link DIR600L Ax FW116WWb01 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the curTime parameter in the function formAdvNetwork.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11145 | User Enumeration in CBK Soft&amp;#x27;s enVision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11145</link><description>Observable Discrepancy, Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in CBK Soft Software Hardware Electronic Computer Systems Industry and Trade Inc. EnVision allows Account Footprinting.This issue affects enVision: before 250566.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61430 | Improper handling of DNS over TCP in Simple DNS Plus v9 allows a remote attacker with querying access to the DNS server to cause the server ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61430</link><description>Improper handling of DNS over TCP in Simple DNS Plus v9 allows a remote attacker with querying access to the DNS server to cause the server to return request payloads from other clients. This happens when the TCP length prefix is malformed (len differs from actual packet len), and due to a concurrency/buffering issue, even when the lengths match. A length prefix that is smaller than the actual packet size increases information leakage. In summary, this vulnerability allows an attacker to see DNS queries of other clients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43994 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) DSM 20.1.21, contain(s) a Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43994</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) DSM 20.1.21, contain(s) a Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43995 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.21, contain(s) an Improper Authentication vulnerability. An unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43995</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.21, contain(s) an Improper Authentication vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Protection mechanism bypass. Authentication Bypass in DSM Data Collector. An unauthenticated remote attacker can access APIs exposed by ApiProxy.war in DataCollectorEar.ear by using a special SessionKey and UserId. These userid are special users created in compellentservicesapi for special purposes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60936 | Emoncms 11.7.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site in the input handling mechanism. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers with API acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60936</link><description>Emoncms 11.7.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site in the input handling mechanism. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers with API access to inject malicious JavaScript code that executes when administrators view the application logs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60938 | Emoncms 11.7.3 has a remote code execution vulnerability in the firmware upload feature that allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60938</link><description>Emoncms 11.7.3 has a remote code execution vulnerability in the firmware upload feature that allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands on the target system. The vulnerability stems from insufficient input validation of user-controlled parameters including filename, port, baud_rate, core, and autoreset within the /admin/upload-custom-firmware endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8536 | SQL Injection in DobryCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8536</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in DobryCMS. Improper neutralization of input provided by user into language functionality allows for SQL Injection attacks.

This issue affects older branches of this software.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-43768 | In Malwarebytes For Teams v.1.0.990 and before and fixed in v.1.0.1003 and later a privilege escalation can occur via the COM interface runn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43768</link><description>In Malwarebytes For Teams v.1.0.990 and before and fixed in v.1.0.1003 and later a privilege escalation can occur via the COM interface running in mbamservice.exe.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46185 | An Insecure Permission vulnerability in pgcodekeeper 10.12.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the plaintext stora...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46185</link><description>An Insecure Permission vulnerability in pgcodekeeper 10.12.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the plaintext storage of passwords and usernames.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46425 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46425</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46183 | The Utils.deserialize function in pgCodeKeeper 10.12.0 processes serialized data from untrusted sources. If an attacker provides a specially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46183</link><description>The Utils.deserialize function in pgCodeKeeper 10.12.0 processes serialized data from untrusted sources. If an attacker provides a specially crafted .ser file, deserialization may result in unintended code execution or other malicious behavior on the target system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11576 | AI Chatbot Free Models – Customer Support, Live Chat, Virtual Assistant &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Unauthenticated CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11576</link><description>The AI Chatbot Free Models – Customer Support, Live Chat, Virtual Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSV Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.5. This is due to insufficient sanitization in the 'newcodebyte_chatbot_export_messages' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to embed untrusted input into exported CSV files, which can result in code execution when these files are downloaded and opened on a local system with a vulnerable configuration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40020 | can: peak_usb: fix shift-out-of-bounds issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40020</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: peak_usb: fix shift-out-of-bounds issue

Explicitly uses a 64-bit constant when the number of bits used for its
shifting is 32 (which is the case for PC CAN FD interfaces supported by
this driver).

[mkl: update subject, apply manually]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40021 | tracing: dynevent: Add a missing lockdown check on dynevent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40021</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tracing: dynevent: Add a missing lockdown check on dynevent

Since dynamic_events interface on tracefs is compatible with
kprobe_events and uprobe_events, it should also check the lockdown
status and reject if it is set.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40022 | crypto: af_alg - Fix incorrect boolean values in af_alg_ctx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40022</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: af_alg - Fix incorrect boolean values in af_alg_ctx

Commit 1b34cbbf4f01 ("crypto: af_alg - Disallow concurrent writes in
af_alg_sendmsg") changed some fields from bool to 1-bit bitfields of
type u32.

However, some assignments to these fields, specifically 'more' and
'merge', assign values greater than 1.  These relied on C's implicit
conversion to bool, such that zero becomes false and nonzero becomes
true.

With a 1-bit bitfields of type u32 instead, mod 2 of the value is taken
instead, resulting in 0 being assigned in some cases when 1 was intended.

Fix this by restoring the bool type.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40023 | drm/xe/vf: Don&amp;#x27;t expose sysfs attributes not applicable for VFs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40023</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/vf: Don't expose sysfs attributes not applicable for VFs

VFs can't read BMG_PCIE_CAP(0x138340) register nor access PCODE
(already guarded by the info.skip_pcode flag) so we shouldn't
expose attributes that require any of them to avoid errors like:

 [] xe 0000:03:00.1: [drm] Tile0: GT0: VF is trying to read an \
                     inaccessible register 0x138340+0x0
 [] RIP: 0010:xe_gt_sriov_vf_read32+0x6c2/0x9a0 [xe]
 [] Call Trace:
 []  xe_mmio_read32+0x110/0x280 [xe]
 []  auto_link_downgrade_capable_show+0x2e/0x70 [xe]
 []  dev_attr_show+0x1a/0x70
 []  sysfs_kf_seq_show+0xaa/0x120
 []  kernfs_seq_show+0x41/0x60

(cherry picked from commit a2d6223d224f333f705ed8495bf8bebfbc585c35)</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40024 | vhost: Take a reference on the task in struct vhost_task.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40024</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vhost: Take a reference on the task in struct vhost_task.

vhost_task_create() creates a task and keeps a reference to its
task_struct. That task may exit early via a signal and its task_struct
will be released.
A pending vhost_task_wake() will then attempt to wake the task and
access a task_struct which is no longer there.

Acquire a reference on the task_struct while creating the thread and
release the reference while the struct vhost_task itself is removed.
If the task exits early due to a signal, then the vhost_task_wake() will
still access a valid task_struct. The wake is safe and will be skipped
in this case.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53733 | net: sched: cls_u32: Undo tcf_bind_filter if u32_replace_hw_knode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53733</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: sched: cls_u32: Undo tcf_bind_filter if u32_replace_hw_knode

When u32_replace_hw_knode fails, we need to undo the tcf_bind_filter
operation done at u32_set_parms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40018 | ipvs: Defer ip_vs_ftp unregister during netns cleanup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40018</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipvs: Defer ip_vs_ftp unregister during netns cleanup

On the netns cleanup path, __ip_vs_ftp_exit() may unregister ip_vs_ftp
before connections with valid cp-&gt;app pointers are flushed, leading to a
use-after-free.

Fix this by introducing a global `exiting_module` flag, set to true in
ip_vs_ftp_exit() before unregistering the pernet subsystem. In
__ip_vs_ftp_exit(), skip ip_vs_ftp unregister if called during netns
cleanup (when exiting_module is false) and defer it to
__ip_vs_cleanup_batch(), which unregisters all apps after all connections
are flushed. If called during module exit, unregister ip_vs_ftp
immediately.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40019 | crypto: essiv - Check ssize for decryption and in-place encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40019</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: essiv - Check ssize for decryption and in-place encryption

Move the ssize check to the start in essiv_aead_crypt so that
it's also checked for decryption and in-place encryption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10861 | Popup builder with Gamification, Multi-Step Popups, Page-Level Targeting, and WooCommerce Triggers &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10861</link><description>The Popup builder with Gamification, Multi-Step Popups, Page-Level Targeting, and WooCommerce Triggers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to insufficient validation on the URLs supplied via the URL parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services, as well as conduct network reconnaissance. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10680 | OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_beta1 on POSIX based platforms allows a remote authenticated server to inject shell commands via DNS variable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10680</link><description>OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_beta1 on POSIX based platforms allows a remote authenticated server to inject shell commands via DNS variables when --dns-updown is in use</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5350 | SSRF and Reflected XSS Vulnerability in Deprecated Try-It Feature of Multiple WSO2 Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5350</link><description>SSRF and Reflected XSS Vulnerabilities exist in multiple WSO2 products within the deprecated Try-It feature, which was accessible only to administrative users. This feature accepted user-supplied URLs without proper validation, leading to server-side request forgery (SSRF). Additionally, the retrieved content was directly reflected in the HTTP response, enabling reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) in the admin user's browser context.

By tricking an administrator into accessing a crafted link, an attacker could force the server to fetch malicious content and reflect it into the admin’s browser, leading to arbitrary JavaScript execution for UI manipulation or data exfiltration. While session cookies are protected with the HttpOnly flag, the XSS still poses a significant security risk.

Furthermore, SSRF can be used by a privileged user to query internal services, potentially aiding in internal network enumeration if the target endpoints are reachable from the affected product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5605 | Authentication Bypass via URI Manipulation in Multiple WSO2 Products&amp;#x27; Management Console Leading to Partial Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5605</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the Management Console of multiple WSO2 products. A malicious actor with access to the console can manipulate the request URI to bypass authentication and access certain restricted resources, resulting in partial information disclosure.

The known exposure from this issue is limited to memory statistics. While the vulnerability does not allow full account compromise, it still enables unauthorized access to internal system details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36361 | IBM App Connect Enterprise runtime is vulnerable to a lack of authorization on windows environments using IWA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36361</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise 13.0.1.0 through 13.0.4.2, and 12.0.1.0 through 12.0.12.17 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions on customer defined resources due to missing authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 09:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12134 | ZoloBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Popup Enable/Disable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12134</link><description>The ZoloBlocks – Gutenberg Block Editor Plugin with Advanced Blocks, Dynamic Content, Templates &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update_popup_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable/disable popups.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 09:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12136 | Real Cookie Banner: GDPR &amp;amp; ePrivacy Cookie Consent &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery via scan-without-login Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12136</link><description>The Real Cookie Banner: GDPR &amp; ePrivacy Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.4. This is due to insufficient validation on the user-supplied URL in the '/scanner/scan-without-login' REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services via the `url` parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 09:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11253 | SQLi in Aksis Technologies&amp;#x27; Netty ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11253</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Aksis Technology Inc. Netty ERP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Netty ERP: before V.1.1000.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10701 | Time Clock – A WordPress Employee &amp;amp; Volunteer Time Clock Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Custom+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10701</link><description>The Time Clock – A WordPress Employee &amp; Volunteer Time Clock Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'data' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with Time Clock user credentials to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an affected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10740 | URL Shortener Plugin For WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Link Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10740</link><description>The URL Shortener Plugin For WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access to functionality provided by the API due to a missing capability check on the verifyRequest function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify links.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10748 | RapidResult &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10748</link><description>The RapidResult plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level permissions and above to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10749 | Microsoft Azure Storage for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.5.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Media Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10749</link><description>The Microsoft Azure Storage for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthorized Arbitrary Media Deletion in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.1. This is due to missing capability checks on the 'azure-storage-media-replace' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access and above to delete arbitrary media files from the WordPress Media Library via the replace_attachment parameter granted they can access the nonce which is exposed to all authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10901 | Originality.ai AI Checker &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Disclosure via &amp;#x27;ai_get_table&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10901</link><description>The Originality.ai AI Checker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ai_get_table' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read all data in the wp_originalityai_log database table, which can include post titles, scan scores, credits used, and other data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10902 | Originality.ai AI Checker &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Scan Log Deletion via &amp;#x27; ai_scan_result_remove&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10902</link><description>The Originality.ai AI Checker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ai_scan_result_remove' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete all data in the wp_originalityai_log database table, which can include post titles, scan scores, credits used, and other data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11172 | Check Plagiarism &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11172</link><description>The Check Plagiarism plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the chk_plag_mine_plugin_wpse10500_admin_action() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the API key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11257 | LLM Hubspot Blog Import &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Hubspot Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11257</link><description>The LLM Hubspot Blog Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'process_save_blogs' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to trigger an import of all Hubspot data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11504 | Quickcreator – AI Blog Writer 0.0.9 - 0.1.17 - Unauthenticated API Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11504</link><description>The Quickcreator – AI Blog Writer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions 0.0.9 to 0.1.17 through the /wp-content/plugins/quickcreator/dupasrala.txt file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the plugin's API key and subsequently use that to perform actions on the site like creating new posts and injecting XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11887 | Supervisor &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11887</link><description>The Supervisor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several AJAX functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update various plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11889 | AIO Forms &amp;lt;= 1.3.15 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload via Zip Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11889</link><description>The AIO Forms – Craft Complex Forms Easily plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the import functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11992 | Multi Item Responsive Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11992</link><description>The Multi Item Responsive Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'mioptions.php' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12014 | NGINX Cache Optimizer &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Dynamic Caching Exclusion Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12014</link><description>The NGINX Cache Optimizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'nginxcacheoptimizer-blacklist-update' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add URLs to the Exclude URLs From Dynamic Caching setting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12016 | qnotsquiz &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12016</link><description>The qnotsquiz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'qnotsquiz_custom_start_text' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12017 | VNPAY for Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12017</link><description>The VNPAY Payment gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'message' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12028 | IndieAuth &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Account Takeover via Stolen OAuth Tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12028</link><description>The IndieAuth plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This is due to missing nonce verification on the `login_form_indieauth()` function and the authorization endpoint at wp-login.php?action=indieauth. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to force authenticated users to approve OAuth authorization requests for attacker-controlled applications via a forged request granted they can trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link or visiting a malicious page while logged in. The attacker can then exchange the stolen authorization code for an access token, effectively taking over the victim's account with the granted scopes (create, update, delete).</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12072 | Disable Content Editor For Specific Template &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Template Configuration Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12072</link><description>The Disable Content Editor For Specific Template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on template configuration updates. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add or delete template configurations via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12096 | Simple Excel Pricelist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12096</link><description>The Simple Excel Pricelist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pricelist' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62868 | WordPress Edge CPT plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62868</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Edge-Themes Edge CPT allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Edge CPT: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6440 | WooCommerce Designer Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.26 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6440</link><description>The WooCommerce Designer Pro plugin for WordPress, used by the Pricom - Printing Company &amp; Design Services WordPress theme, is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'wcdp_save_canvas_design_ajax' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.26. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10723 | PixelYourSite &amp;lt; 11.1.2 - Admin+ LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10723</link><description>The PixelYourSite  WordPress plugin before 11.1.2 does not validate some URL parameters before using them to generate paths passed to function/s, allowing any admins to perform LFI attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10874 | Orbit Fox &amp;lt; 3.0.2 - Author+ Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10874</link><description>The Orbit Fox: Duplicate Page, Menu Icons, SVG Support, Cookie Notice, Custom Fonts &amp; More WordPress plugin before 3.0.2 does not limit URLs which may be used for the stock photo import feature, allowing the user to specify arbitrary URLs. This leads to a server-side request forgery as the user may force the server to access any URL of their choosing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9158 | Stored XSS in Request Tracker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9158</link><description>The Request Tracker software is vulnerable to a Stored XSS vulnerability in calendar invitation parsing feature, which displays invitation data without HTML sanitization. XSS vulnerability allows an attacker to send a specifically crafted e-mail enabling JavaScript code execution by displaying the ticket in the context of the logged-in user. 

This vulnerability affects versions from 5.0.4 through 5.0.8 and from 6.0.0 through 6.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9978 | Jeg Elementor Kit &amp;lt; 2.7.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9978</link><description>The Jeg Kit for Elementor  WordPress plugin before 2.7.0 does not sanitize SVG file contents when uploaded via xmlrpc.php, leading to a cross site scripting vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58070 | Pleasanter contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Preview for Attachments, which allows an attacker to execute an arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58070</link><description>Pleasanter contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Preview for Attachments, which allows an attacker to execute an arbitrary script in a logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 05:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61931 | Pleasanter contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Body, Description and Comments, which allows an attacker to execute an ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61931</link><description>Pleasanter contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Body, Description and Comments, which allows an attacker to execute an arbitrary script in a logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 05:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60023 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60023</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to interact with the ProductivityService PLC simulator and delete arbitrary directories on the target machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7730 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.4.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `percentage` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7730</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘percentage’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58429 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58429</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to interact with the ProductivityService PLC simulator and delete arbitrary files on the target machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59776 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59776</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to interact with the ProductivityService PLC simulator and create arbitrary directories on the target machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62254 | The ComboServlet in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.2, 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62254</link><description>The ComboServlet in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.2, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.5, 7.4 GA through update 92, 7.3 GA through update 35, and older unsupported versions  does not limit the number or size of the files it will combine, which allows remote attackers to create very large responses that lead to a denial of service attack via the URL query string.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58078 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite  Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58078</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 

4.4.1.19.


 The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to interact with the ProductivityService PLC simulator and write files with arbitrary data on the target machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58456 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58456</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 

4.4.1.19.

 The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to interact with the ProductivityService PLC simulator and read arbitrary files on the target machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61934 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Binding to an Unrestricted IP Address CWE-1327</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61934</link><description>A binding to an unrestricted IP address vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version v4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to interact with the ProductivityService PLC simulator and read, write, or delete arbitrary files and folders on the target machine</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62688 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62688</link><description>An incorrect permission assignment for a critical resource vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an attacker with low-privileged credentials to change their role, gaining full control access to the project.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61977 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61977</link><description>A weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten password vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version v4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an attacker to decrypt an encrypted project by answering just one recovery question.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62498 | AutomationDirect Productivity Suite Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62498</link><description>A relative path traversal (ZipSlip) vulnerability was discovered in Productivity Suite software version 

4.4.1.19. The vulnerability allows an attacker who can tamper with a productivity project to execute arbitrary code on the machine where the project is opened.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59273 | Azure Event Grid System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59273</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59503 | Azure Compute Resource Provider Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59503</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59500 | Azure Notification Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59500</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12100 | MongoDB BI Connector ODBC driver installation via MSI may leave ACLs unset on custom installation directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12100</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in MongoDB BI Connector ODBC driver allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects BI Connector ODBC driver: from 1.0.0 through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54963 | An issue was discovered in BAE SOCET GXP before 4.6.0.2. An attacker with the ability to interact with the GXP Job Service may submit a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54963</link><description>An issue was discovered in BAE SOCET GXP before 4.6.0.2. An attacker with the ability to interact with the GXP Job Service may submit a crafted job request that grants read access to files on the filesystem with the permissions of the GXP Job Service process. The path to a file is not sanitized for directory traversal, potentially allowing an attacker to read sensitive files in some configurations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57848 | Container-native-virtualization: privilege escalation via excessive /etc/passwd permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57848</link><description>A container privilege escalation flaw was found in certain Container-native Virtualization images. This issue stems from the /etc/passwd file being created with group-writable permissions during build time. In certain conditions, an attacker who can execute commands within an affected container, even as a non-root user, can leverage their membership in the root group to modify the /etc/passwd file. This could allow the attacker to add a new user with any arbitrary UID, including UID 0, leading to full root privileges within the container.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54964 | An issue was discovered in BAE SOCET GXP before 4.6.0.2. An attacker with the ability to interact with the GXP Job Service may inject arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54964</link><description>An issue was discovered in BAE SOCET GXP before 4.6.0.2. An attacker with the ability to interact with the GXP Job Service may inject arbitrary executables. If the Job Service is configured for local-only access, this may allow for privilege escalation in certain situations. If the Job Service is network accessible, this may allow remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54966 | An issue was discovered in BAE SOCET GXP before 4.6.0.2. Some endpoints on the SOCET GXP Job Status Service may return sensitive information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54966</link><description>An issue was discovered in BAE SOCET GXP before 4.6.0.2. Some endpoints on the SOCET GXP Job Status Service may return sensitive information in certain situations, including local file paths and SOCET GXP version information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62517 | Rollbar.js Prototype Pollution Vulnerability in merge()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62517</link><description>Rollbar.js offers error tracking and logging from Javascript to Rollbar. In versions before 2.26.5 and from 3.0.0-alpha1 to before 3.0.0-beta5, there is a prototype pollution vulnerability in merge(). If application code calls rollbar.configure() with untrusted input, prototype pollution is possible. This issue has been fixed in versions 2.26.5 and 3.0.0-beta5. A workaround involves ensuring that values passed to rollbar.configure() do not contain untrusted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58428 | Command Injection in Veeder-Root TLS4B Automatic Tank Gauge System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58428</link><description>The TLS4B ATG system's SOAP-based interface is vulnerable due to its accessibility through the web services handler. This vulnerability enables remote attackers with valid credentials to execute system-level commands on the underlying Linux system. This could allow the attacker to achieve remote command execution, full shell access, and potential lateral movement within the network.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55067 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Veeder-Root TLS4B Automatic Tank Gauge System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55067</link><description>The TLS4B ATG system is vulnerable to improper handling of Unix time values that exceed the 2038 epoch rollover. When the system clock reaches January 19, 2038, it resets to December 13, 1901, causing authentication failures and disrupting core system functionalities such as login access, history visibility, and leak detection termination. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to manipulate the system time to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition, leading to administrative lockout, operational timer failures, and corrupted log entries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62236 | Frontier Airlines publicly available email address validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62236</link><description>The Frontier Airlines website has a publicly available endpoint that validates if an email addresses is associated with an account. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could determine valid email addresses, possibly aiding in further attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12044 | Vault Vulnerable to Denial of Service Due to Rate Limit Regression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12044</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise (“Vault”) are vulnerable to an unauthenticated denial of service when processing JSON payloads. This occurs due to a regression from a previous fix for [+HCSEC-2025-24+|https://discuss.hashicorp.com/t/hcsec-2025-24-vault-denial-of-service-though-complex-json-payloads/76393]  which allowed for processing JSON payloads before applying rate limits. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-12044, is fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.21.0 and Vault Enterprise 1.16.27, 1.19.11, 1.20.5, and 1.21.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11621 | Vault AWS auth method bypass due to AWS client cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11621</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise’s (“Vault”) AWS Auth method may be susceptible to authentication bypass if the role of the configured bound_principal_iam is the same across AWS accounts, or uses a wildcard. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-11621, is fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.21.0 and Vault Enterprise 1.21.0, 1.20.5, 1.19.11, and 1.16.27</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62255 | Self Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the edit Knowledge Base article page in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.101, and older u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62255</link><description>Self Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the edit Knowledge Base article page in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.101, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.5, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions  allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into an attachment's filename.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6978 | Diagnostics command injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6978</link><description>Diagnostics command injection vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6979 | Captive Portal can allow authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6979</link><description>Captive Portal can allow authentication bypass</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6980 | Captive Portal can expose sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6980</link><description>Captive Portal can expose sensitive information</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23352 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause uninitialized pointer access. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23352</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause uninitialized pointer access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60837 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MCMS v6.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60837</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MCMS v6.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of a user's browser via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60859 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard 5.6.15 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted c_id parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60859</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard 5.6.15 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted c_id parameter in bbs/view_comment.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10937 | Oxford Nanopore Technologies MinKNOW  Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10937</link><description>Oxford Nanopore Technologies' MinKNOW software at or prior to version 24.11 creates a temporary file to store the local authentication token during startup, before copying it to its final location. This temporary file is created in a directory accessible to all users on the system. An unauthorized local user or process can exploit this behavior by placing a file lock on the temporary token file using the flock system call. This prevents MinKNOW from completing the token generation process. As a result, no valid local token is created, and the software is unable to execute commands on the sequencer. This leads to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, blocking sequencing operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23300 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel driver, where a user could cause a null pointer dereference by alloca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23300</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel driver, where a user could cause a null pointer dereference by allocating a specific memory resource. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23330 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker might be able to trigger a null pointer dereference. A successful...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23330</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker might be able to trigger a null pointer dereference. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23332 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability in a kernel module, where an attacker might be able to trigger a null pointer defer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23332</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability in a kernel module, where an attacker might be able to trigger a null pointer deference. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23345 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in a video decoder, where an attacker might cause an out-of-bounds read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23345</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in a video decoder, where an attacker might cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23347 | NVIDIA Project G-Assist contains a vulnerability where an attacker might be able to escalate permissions. A successful exploit of this vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23347</link><description>NVIDIA Project G-Assist contains a vulnerability where an attacker might be able to escalate permissions. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54808 | Oxford Nanopore Technologies MinKNOW Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54808</link><description>Oxford Nanopore Technologies' MinKNOW software at or prior to version 24.11 stores authentication tokens in a file located in the system's temporary directory (/tmp) on the host machine. This directory is typically world-readable, allowing any local user or application to access the token. If the token is leaked (e.g., via malware infection or other local exploit), and remote access is enabled, it can be used to establish unauthorized remote connections to the sequencer. Remote access must be enabled for remote exploitation to succeed. This may occur either because the user has enabled remote access for legitimate operational reasons or because malware with elevated privileges (e.g., sudo access) enables it without user consent. This vulnerability can be chained with remote access capabilities to generate a developer token from a remote device. Developer tokens can be created with arbitrary expiration dates, enabling persistent access to the sequencer and bypassing standard authentication mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61464 | gnuboard gnuboard4 v4.36.04 and before is vulnerable to Second-order SQL Injection via the search_table in bbs/search.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61464</link><description>gnuboard gnuboard4 v4.36.04 and before is vulnerable to Second-order SQL Injection via the search_table in bbs/search.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57240 | Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 17gz International Student service system 1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57240</link><description>Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 17gz International Student service system 1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the registration step.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61413 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /manager/pages component of Piranha CMS v12.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61413</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /manager/pages component of Piranha CMS v12.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via creating a page and injecting a crafted payload into the Markdown blocks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34155 | Tibbo AggreGate Network Manager &amp;lt; 6.40.05 Login Functionality User Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34155</link><description>Tibbo AggreGate Network Manager &lt; 6.40.05 contains an observable response discrepancy in its login functionality. Authentication failure messages differ based on whether a supplied username exists or not, allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to infer valid account identifiers. This can facilitate user enumeration and increase the likelihood of targeted brute-force or credential-stuffing attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34156 | Tibbo AggreGate Network Manager &amp;lt; 6.40.05 System Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34156</link><description>Tibbo AggreGate Network Manager &lt; 6.40.05 exposes sensitive system information through an unauthenticated endpoint at /cwmp/happyaxis.jsp. The page discloses Java system properties, server path details, and version information to unauthorized users, resulting in information disclosure that could aid further compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62713 | Kottster app reinitialization can be re-triggered allowing command injection in development mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62713</link><description>Kottster is a self hosted Node.js admin panel. From versions 3.2.0 to before 3.3.2, Kottster contains a pre-authentication remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability when running in development mode. This affects development mode only, production deployments were never affected. This issue has been fixed in version 3.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62169 | OctoPrint-SpoolManager Plugin APIs do not enforce authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62169</link><description>OctoPrint-SpoolManager is a plugin for managing spools and all their usage metadata. In versions 1.8.0a2 and older of the testing branch and versions 1.7.7 and older of the stable branch, the APIs of the OctoPrint-SpoolManager plugin do not correctly enforce authentication or authorization checks. This issue has been patched in versions 1.8.0a3 of the testing branch and 1.7.8 of the stable branch. The impact of this vulnerability is greatly reduced when using OctoPrint version 1.11.2 and newer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50951 | FontForge v20230101 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the utf7toutf8_copy function at /fontforge/sfd.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50951</link><description>FontForge v20230101 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the utf7toutf8_copy function at /fontforge/sfd.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12114 | Serial Console Enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12114</link><description>Enabled serial console could potentially leak information that might help attacker to find vulnerabilities.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50949 | FontForge v20230101 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the component DlgCreate8.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50949</link><description>FontForge v20230101 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the component DlgCreate8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50950 | Audiofile v0.3.7 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the ModuleState::setup function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50950</link><description>Audiofile v0.3.7 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the ModuleState::setup function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59048 | OpenBao AWS Plugin Vulnerable to Cross-Account IAM Role Impersonation in AWS Auth Method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59048</link><description>OpenBao's AWS Plugin generates AWS access credentials based on IAM policies. Prior to version 0.1.1, the AWS Plugin is vulnerable to cross-account IAM role Impersonation in the AWS auth method. The vulnerability allows an IAM role from an untrusted AWS account to authenticate by impersonating a role with the same name in a trusted account, leading to unauthorized access. This impacts all users of the auth-aws plugin who operate in a multi-account AWS environment where IAM role names may not be unique across accounts. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.1.1 of the auth-aws plugin. A workaround for this issue involves guaranteeing that IAM role names are unique across all AWS accounts that could potentially interact with your OpenBao environment, and to audit for any duplicate IAM roles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61132 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability in the password reset component in levlaz braindump v0.4.14 allows remote attackers to conduct passwor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61132</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability in the password reset component in levlaz braindump v0.4.14 allows remote attackers to conduct password reset poisoning and account takeover via manipulation of the Host header when Flask's url_for(_external=True) generates reset links without a fixed SERVER_NAME.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61136 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability in the password reset component in axewater sharewarez v2.4.3 allows remote attackers to conduct passw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61136</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability in the password reset component in axewater sharewarez v2.4.3 allows remote attackers to conduct password reset poisoning and account takeover via manipulation of the Host header when Flask's url_for(_external=True) generates reset links without a fixed SERVER_NAME.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56007 | CRLF-injection in KeeneticOS before 4.3 at "/auth" API endpoint allows attackers to take over the device via adding additional users with fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56007</link><description>CRLF-injection in KeeneticOS before 4.3 at "/auth" API endpoint allows attackers to take over the device via adding additional users with full permissions by managing the victim to open page with exploit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56008 | Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in KeeneticOS before 4.3 at "Wireless ISP" page allows attackers located near to the router to take...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56008</link><description>Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in KeeneticOS before 4.3 at "Wireless ISP" page allows attackers located near to the router to takeover the device via adding additional users with full permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56009 | Cross site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in KeeneticOS before 4.3 at "/rci" API endpoint allows attackers to take over the device via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56009</link><description>Cross site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in KeeneticOS before 4.3 at "/rci" API endpoint allows attackers to take over the device via adding additional users with full permissions by managing the victim to open page with exploit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12110 | Keycloak: org.keycloak:keycloak-services: user can refresh offline session even after client&amp;#x27;s offline_access scope was removed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12110</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. An offline session continues to be valid when the offline_access scope is removed from the client. The refresh token is accepted and you can continue to request new tokens for the session. As it can lead to a situation where an administrator removes the scope, and assumes that offline sessions are no longer available, but they are.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11429 | Keycloak-server: too long and not settings compliant session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11429</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. Keycloak does not immediately enforce the disabling of the "Remember Me" realm setting on existing user sessions. Sessions created while "Remember Me" was active retain their extended session lifetime until they expire, overriding the administrator's recent security configuration change. This is a logic flaw in session management increases the potential window for successful session hijacking or unauthorized long-term access persistence. The flaw lies in the session expiration logic relying on the session-local "remember-me" flag without validating the current realm-level configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1680 | An acceptance of extraneous untrusted data with trusted data vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s Ethernet switches, which allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1680</link><description>An acceptance of extraneous untrusted data with trusted data vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s Ethernet switches, which allows attackers with administrative privileges to manipulate HTTP Host headers by injecting a specially crafted Host header into HTTP requests sent to an affected device’s web service. This vulnerability is classified as Host Header Injection, where invalid Host headers can manipulate to redirect users, forge links, or phishing attacks. There is no impact to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device; no loss of confidentiality, integrity, and availability within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1679 | Cross-site Scripting has been identified in Moxa’s Ethernet switches, which allows an authenticated administrative attacker to inject malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1679</link><description>Cross-site Scripting has been identified in Moxa’s Ethernet switches, which allows an authenticated administrative attacker to inject malicious scripts to an affected device’s web service that could impact authenticated users interacting with the device’s web interface. This vulnerability is classified as stored cross-site scripting (XSS); attackers inject malicious scripts into the system, and the scripts persist across sessions. There is no impact to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device; no loss of availability within any subsequent systems but has some loss of confidentiality and integrity within the subsequent system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53701 | XSS vulnerability in Vilar VS-IPC1002 IP cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53701</link><description>Vilar VS-IPC1002 IP cameras are vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks, because parameters in GET requests sent to /cgi-bin/action endpoint are not sanitized properly, making it possible to target logged in admin users.
The vendor did not respond in any way. Only version 1.1.0.18 was tested, other versions might be vulnerable as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53702 | DoS vulnerability in Vilar VS-IPC1002 IP cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53702</link><description>Vilar VS-IPC1002 IP cameras are vulnerable to DoS (Denial-of-Service) attacks. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network might send a crafted request to /cgi-bin/action endpoint and render the device completely unresponsive. A manual restart of the device is required. 
The vendor did not respond in any way. Only version 1.1.0.18 was tested, other versions might be vulnerable as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60852 | A CSV Injection vulnerability existed in Instant Developer Foundation versions prior to 25.0.9600. Applications built with affected versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60852</link><description>A CSV Injection vulnerability existed in Instant Developer Foundation versions prior to 25.0.9600. Applications built with affected versions of the framework did not properly sanitize user-controlled input before including it in CSV exports. This issue could lead to code execution on the system where the exported CSV file is opened.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62256 | Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.109, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.7, 7.4 GA through update 92, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62256</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.109, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.7, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions does not properly restrict access to OpenAPI in certain circumstances, which allows remote attackers to access the OpenAPI YAML file via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10705 | MxChat – AI Chatbot for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Unauthenticated Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10705</link><description>The MxChat – AI Chatbot for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs in the PDF processing functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make the WordPress server perform HTTP requests to arbitrary destinations via the mxchat_handle_chat_request AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11023 | Local File Inclusion in ArkSigner&amp;#x27;s AcBakImzala</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11023</link><description>Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere, Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ArkSigner Software and Hardware Inc. AcBakImzala allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects AcBakImzala: before v5.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11128 | Feedzy RSS Feeds Lite &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11128</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.0 via the 'feedzy_sanitize_feeds' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8427 | Beaver Builder Plugin (Starter Version) &amp;lt;= 2.9.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;auto_play&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8427</link><description>The Beaver Builder Plugin (Starter Version) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘auto_play’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62393 | Moodle: course access permissions not properly checked in course_output_fragment_course_overview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62393</link><description>A flaw was found in the course overview output function where user access permissions were not fully enforced. This could allow unauthorized users to view information about courses they should not have access to, potentially exposing limited course details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62394 | Moodle: quiz notifications sent to suspended participants</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62394</link><description>Moodle failed to verify enrolment status correctly when sending quiz notifications. As a result, suspended or inactive users might receive quiz-related messages, leaking limited course information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62395 | Moodle: external cohort search service leaks system cohort data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62395</link><description>A flaw in the cohort search web service allowed users with permissions in lower contexts to access cohort information from the system context, revealing restricted administrative data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62396 | Moodle: router (r.php) could expose application directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62396</link><description>An error-handling issue in the Moodle router (r.php) could cause the application to display internal directory listings when specific HTTP headers were not properly configured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62397 | Moodle: router produces json instead of 404 error for invalid course id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62397</link><description>The router’s inconsistent response to invalid course IDs allowed attackers to infer which course IDs exist, potentially aiding reconnaissance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62398 | Moodle: possible to bypass mfa</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62398</link><description>A serious authentication flaw allowed attackers with valid credentials to bypass multi-factor authentication under certain conditions, potentially compromising user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62399 | Moodle: password brute force risk when mobile/web services enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62399</link><description>Moodle’s mobile and web service authentication endpoints did not sufficiently restrict repeated password attempts, making them susceptible to brute-force attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62400 | Moodle: hidden group names visible to event creators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62400</link><description>Moodle exposed the names of hidden groups to users who had permission to create calendar events but not to view hidden groups. This could reveal private or restricted group information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62401 | Moodle: possible to bypass timer in timed assignments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62401</link><description>An issue in Moodle’s timed assignment feature allowed students to bypass the time restriction, potentially giving them more time than allowed to complete an assessment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10355 | Open redirection vulnerability in MOLGENIS EMX2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10355</link><description>Open redirection vulnerability in MOLGENIS EMX2 v11.14.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to create a malicious URL using a manipulated redirection parameter, potentially leading users to phishing sites or other malicious destinations via “/%2f%2f”.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41073 | Path Traversal in Gandia Integra Total by TESI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41073</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in version 4.4.2236.1 of TESI Gandia Integra Total. This issue allows an authenticated attacker to download a ZIP file containing files from the server, including those located in parent directories (e.g., ..\..\..), by exploiting the “direstudio” parameter in “/encuestas/integraweb[_v4]/integra/html/view/comprimir.php”.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40643 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Energy CRM by Status Tracker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40643</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Energy CRM v2025 by Status Tracker Ltd, consisting of a stored XSS due to lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to “/crm/create_job_submit.php”, using the “JobCreatedBy” parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 10:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9980 | Multiple Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9980</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to multiple Stored XSS in page editor functionality (pages-form). Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting edited page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9981 | Multiple Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9981</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to multiple Stored XSS in slider editor functionality (sliders-form). Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed on every page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12105 | Libsoup: heap use-after-free in libsoup message queue handling during http/2 read completion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12105</link><description>A flaw was found in the asynchronous message queue handling of the libsoup library, widely used by GNOME and WebKit-based applications to manage HTTP/2 communications. When network operations are aborted at specific timing intervals, an internal message queue item may be freed twice due to missing state synchronization. This leads to a use-after-free memory access, potentially crashing the affected application. Attackers could exploit this behavior remotely by triggering specific HTTP/2 read and cancel sequences, resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10914 | Reflected XSS in Proliz&amp;#x27;s OBS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10914</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Proliz Software Ltd. Co. OBS (Student Affairs Information System) allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects OBS (Student Affairs Information System): before V26.0401.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10727 | Reflected XSS in ArkSigner&amp;#x27;s AcBakImzala</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10727</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ArkSigner Software and Hardware Inc. AcBakImzala allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AcBakImzala: before v5.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54806 | GROWI v4.2.7 and earlier contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability  in the page alert function. If a user accesses a crafted URL while l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54806</link><description>GROWI v4.2.7 and earlier contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability  in the page alert function. If a user accesses a crafted URL while logged in to the affected product, an arbitrary script may be executed on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54856 | Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Edit ContentData page. If crafted input is stored by an attacker with "...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54856</link><description>Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Edit ContentData page. If crafted input is stored by an attacker with "ContentType Management" privilege, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accesses Edit ContentData page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61865 | NarSuS App registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system driv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61865</link><description>NarSuS App registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 04:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62499 | Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Edit CategorySet of ContentType page. If crafted input is stored by an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62499</link><description>Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Edit CategorySet of ContentType page. If crafted input is stored by an attacker with "ContentType Management" privilege, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accesses Edit CategorySet of ContentType page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 04:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12104 | Incorrect Content-Type Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12104</link><description>Outdated and Vulnerable UI Dependencies might potentially lead to exploitation.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62820 | Slack Nebula before 1.9.7 mishandles CIDR in some configurations and thus accepts arbitrary source IP addresses within the Nebula network.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62820</link><description>Slack Nebula before 1.9.7 mishandles CIDR in some configurations and thus accepts arbitrary source IP addresses within the Nebula network.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35981 | Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor (CWE-359) in the Command Centre Server allows a privileged Operator to vie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35981</link><description>Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor (CWE-359) in the Command Centre Server allows a privileged Operator to view limited personal data about a Cardholder they would not normally have permissions to view. 

This issue affects Command Centre Server: 9.30.1874 (MR1), 9.20.2337 (MR3), 9.10.3194 (MR6).</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41402 | Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security (CWE-602) in the Command Centre Server allows a privileged operator to enter invalid compete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41402</link><description>Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security (CWE-602) in the Command Centre Server allows a privileged operator to enter invalid competency data, bypassing expiry checks. 

This issue affects Command Centre Server: 

 9.30 prior to vEL9.30.2482 (MR2), 9.20 prior to vEL9.20.2819 (MR4), 9.10 prior to vEL9.10.3672 (MR7), all versions of 9.00 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47699 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere (CWE-497) in the Gallagher Morpho integration could allow an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47699</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere (CWE-497) in the Gallagher Morpho integration could allow an authenticated operator with limited site permissions to make critical changes to local Morpho devices. 

This issue affects Command Centre Server:

9.30 prior to vEL9.30.2482 (MR2), 9.20 prior to vEL9.20.2819 (MR4), 9.10 prior to vEL9.10.3672 (MR7), 9.00 prior to vEL9.00.3831 (MR8), all versions of 8.90 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48428 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information (CWE-312) in the Gallagher Morpho integration could allow an authenticated user with access to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48428</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information (CWE-312) in the Gallagher Morpho integration could allow an authenticated user with access to the Command Centre Server to export a specific signing key while in use allowing them to deploy a compromised or counterfeit device on that site. 
This issue affects Command Centre Server: 9.20 prior to vEL9.20.2819 (MR4), 9.10 prior to vEL9.10.3672 (MR7), 9.00 prior to vEL9.00.3831 (MR8), all versions of 8.90 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48430 | Uncaught Exception (CWE-248) in the Command Centre Server allows an Authorized and Privileged Operator to crash the Command Centre Server at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48430</link><description>Uncaught Exception (CWE-248) in the Command Centre Server allows an Authorized and Privileged Operator to crash the Command Centre Server at will.

This issue affects Command Centre Server: 

9.30 prior to vEL9.30.2482 (MR2), 9.20 prior to vEL9.20.2819 (MR4), 9.10 prior to vEL9.10.3672 (MR7), 9.00 prior to vEL9.00.3831 (MR8), all versions of 8.90 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62813 | LZ4 through 1.10.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact when the appl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62813</link><description>LZ4 through 1.10.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact when the application processes untrusted LZ4 frames. For example, LZ4F_createCDict_advanced in lib/lz4frame.c mishandles NULL checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11575 | MongoDB Atlas SQL ODBC driver installation via MSI may leave ACLs unset on custom installation directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11575</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in MongoDB Atlas SQL ODBC driver on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects MongoDB Atlas SQL ODBC driver: from 1.0.0 through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 01:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>