<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:46:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-7760 | Reflected XSS in Ofisimo&amp;#x27;s Association Web Package Flora</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7760</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ofisimo Web-Based Software Technologies Association Web Package Flora allows XSS Through HTTP Headers.This issue affects Association Web Package Flora: from v3.0 through 03022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6397 | XSS in Ankara Hosting&amp;#x27;s web site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6397</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ankara Hosting Website Design Website Software allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Website Software: through 03022026. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1664 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) via Header-Based Email Routing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1664</link><description>Summary

An Insecure Direct Object Reference has been found to exist in `createHeaderBasedEmailResolver()` function within the Cloudflare Agents SDK. The issue occurs because the `Message-ID` and `References` headers are parsed to derive the target agentName and agentId without proper validation or origin checks, allowing an external attacker with control of these headers to route inbound mail to arbitrary Durable Object instances and namespaces .




Root cause

The `createHeaderBasedEmailResolver()` function lacks cryptographic verification or origin validation for the headers used in the routing logic, effectively allowing external input to dictate internal object routing.




Impact

Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in email routing lets an attacker steer inbound mail to arbitrary Agent instances via spoofed Message-ID.





Mitigation:

  *  PR:  https://github.com/cloudflare/agents/blob/main/docs/email.md ] provides the necessary architectural context for coding agents to mitigate the issue by refactoring the resolver to enforce strict identity boundaries.
  *  Agents-sdk users should  upgrade to agents@0.3.7</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11598 | Exposure of Confidential Information in mObywatel application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11598</link><description>In mObywatel iOS application an unauthorized user can use the App Switcher to view the account owner's personal information in the minimized app window, even after the login session has ended (reopening the app would require the user to log in). The data exposed depends on the last application view displayed before the application was minimized

This issue was fixed in version 4.71.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1432 | SQL injection (SQLi) on the Buroweb platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1432</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the Buroweb platform version 2505.0.12, specifically in the 'tablon' component. This vulnerability is present in several parameters that do not correctly sanitize user input in the endpoint '/sta/CarpetaPublic/doEvent?APP_CODE=STA&amp;amp;PAGE_CODE=TABLON'. Exploiting this vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute queries on the database and gain access to confidential information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67848 | Moodle: moodle: authentication bypass via lti provider allows suspended users to gain unauthorized access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67848</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. This authentication bypass vulnerability allows suspended users to authenticate through the Learning Tools Interoperability (LTI) Provider. The issue arises from the LTI authentication handlers failing to enforce the user's suspension status, enabling unauthorized access to the system. This can lead to information disclosure or other unauthorized actions by users who should be restricted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67849 | Moodle: moodle: cross-site scripting (xss) via improper sanitization of ai prompt responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67849</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. This cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability, caused by improper sanitization of AI prompt responses, allows attackers to inject malicious HTML or script into web pages. When other users view these compromised pages, their sessions could be stolen, or the user interface could be manipulated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67850 | Moodle: moodle: cross-site scripting vulnerability via inadequate input filtering in formula editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67850</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. This vulnerability, known as Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), occurs due to insufficient checks on user-provided data in the formula editor's arithmetic expression fields. A remote attacker could inject malicious code into these fields. When other users view these expressions, the malicious code would execute in their web browsers, potentially compromising their data or leading to unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67851 | Moodle: moodle: formula injection allows arbitrary formula execution via unescaped data export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67851</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. This formula injection vulnerability occurs when data fields are exported without proper escaping. A remote attacker could exploit this by providing malicious data that, when exported and opened in a spreadsheet, allows arbitrary formulas to execute. This can lead to compromised data integrity and unintended operations within the spreadsheet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67852 | Moodle: moodle: open redirect vulnerability in oauth login flow allows redirection to malicious sites.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67852</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. An open redirect vulnerability in the OAuth login flow allows a remote attacker to redirect users to attacker-controlled pages after they have successfully authenticated. This occurs due to insufficient validation of redirect parameters, which could lead to phishing attacks or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67853 | Moodle: moodle: brute-force facilitation due to missing rate limiting in confirmation email service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67853</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. A remote attacker could exploit a lack of proper rate limiting in the confirmation email service. This vulnerability allows attackers to more easily enumerate or guess user credentials, facilitating brute-force attacks against user accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67855 | Mooodle: mooodle: information disclosure and script execution via reflected cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67855</link><description>A flaw was found in mooodle. A remote attacker could exploit a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the policy tool return URL. This vulnerability arises from insufficient sanitization of URL parameters, allowing attackers to inject malicious scripts through specially crafted links. Successful exploitation could lead to information disclosure or arbitrary client-side script execution within the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67856 | Moodle: moodle: privilege escalation via incomplete role checks in badge awarding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67856</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. An authorization logic flaw, specifically due to incomplete role checks during the badge awarding process, allowed badges to be granted without proper verification. This could enable unauthorized users to obtain badges they are not entitled to, potentially leading to privilege escalation or unauthorized access to certain features.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67857 | Moodle: moodle: data exposure of user identifiers in urls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67857</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. During anonymous assignment submissions, user identifiers were inadvertently exposed in URLs. This data exposure allows unauthorized viewers to see internal user IDs, compromising the intended anonymity and potentially leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41065 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in LUNA from Luna Imaging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41065</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability type in LUNA software v7.5.5.6. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by inyecting a malicious payload through the 'Edit Batch Name' function. THe payload is stored by the application and subsequently displayed without proper sanitization when other users access it. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59902 | HTML injection in NICE Chat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59902</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in NICE Chat. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject and render arbitrary HTML content in email transcripts by modifying the 'firstName' and 'lastName' parameters during a chat session. The injected HTML is included in the body of the email sent by the system, which could enable phishing attacks, impersonation, or credential theft.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8461 | Reflected XSS in Seres Software&amp;#x27;s syWEB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8461</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Seres Software syWEB allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects syWEB: through 03022026. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8456 | Reflected XSS in Kod8 Software&amp;#x27;s Kod8 Individual and SME Website</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8456</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kod8 Software Technologies Trade Ltd. Co. Kod8 Individual and SME Website allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kod8 Individual and SME Website: through 03022026. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1591 | Stored XSS via Attachments Feature in https://pdfonline.foxit.com/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1591</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Cloud (pdfonline) contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the file upload feature. A malicious username is embedded into the upload file list without proper escaping, allowing arbitrary JavaScript execution when the list is displayed.

This issue affects pdfonline.foxit.com: before 2026‑02‑03.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1592 | Stored XSS via Create New Layer Field found in Foxit PDF Editor Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1592</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Cloud (pdfonline) contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Create New Layer feature. Unsanitized user input is embedded into the HTML output, allowing arbitrary JavaScript execution when the layer is referenced.

This issue affects pdfonline.foxit.com: before 2026‑02‑03.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1371 | Tutor LMS &amp;lt;= 3.9.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Disclosure in Coupon Details via &amp;#x27;tutor_coupon_details&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1371</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5. This is due to missing authorization checks in the `ajax_coupon_details()` function, which only validates nonces but does not verify user capabilities. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive coupon information including coupon codes, discount amounts, usage statistics, and course/bundle applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1375 | Tutor LMS &amp;lt;= 3.9.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Instructor+) Arbitrary Course Modification and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1375</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5. This is due to missing object-level authorization checks in the `course_list_bulk_action()`, `bulk_delete_course()`, and `update_course_status()` functions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Tutor Instructor-level access and above, to modify or delete arbitrary courses they do not own by manipulating course IDs in bulk action requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1730 | OS DataHub Maps &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1730</link><description>The OS DataHub Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to incorrect file type validation in the 'OS_DataHub_Maps_Admin::add_file_and_ext' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8589 | Reflected XSS in AKCE Software&amp;#x27;s SKSPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8589</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AKCE Software Technology R&amp;amp;D Industry and Trade Inc. SKSPro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SKSPro: through 07012026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8590 | Information Disclosure in AKCE Software&amp;#x27;s SKSPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8590</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in AKCE Software Technology R&amp;amp;D Industry and Trade Inc. SKSPro allows Directory Indexing.This issue affects SKSPro: through 07012026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20704 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in WRC-X1500GS-B and WRC-X1500GSA-B. If a user accesses a malicious page while logged-in to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20704</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in WRC-X1500GS-B and WRC-X1500GSA-B. If a user accesses a malicious page while logged-in to the affected product, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22550 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in WRC-X1500GS-B and WRC-X1500GSA-B. A crafted request from a logged-in user may lead to an arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22550</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in WRC-X1500GS-B and WRC-X1500GSA-B. A crafted request from a logged-in user may lead to an arbitrary OS command execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24449 | For WRC-X1500GS-B and WRC-X1500GSA-B, the initial passwords can be calculated easily from the system information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24449</link><description>For WRC-X1500GS-B and WRC-X1500GSA-B, the initial passwords can be calculated easily from the system information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24465 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN access point devices. A crafted packet may lead to arbitrary code ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24465</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN access point devices. A crafted packet may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0617 | LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events &amp;lt;= 5.2.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0617</link><description>The LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the customer profile fields in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever an administrator views the customer's activity history.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1058 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt;= 1.15.35 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Hidden Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1058</link><description>The Form Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via hidden field values in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.35. This is due to insufficient output escaping when displaying hidden field values in the admin submissions list. The plugin uses html_entity_decode() on user-supplied hidden field values without subsequent escaping before output, which converts HTML entity-encoded payloads back into executable JavaScript. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in the admin submissions view that will execute whenever an administrator accesses the submissions list.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1065 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt;= 1.15.35 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1065</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.35. This is due to the plugin's default file upload allowlist including SVG files combined with weak substring-based extension validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload malicious SVG files containing JavaScript code that will execute when viewed by administrators or site visitors via file upload fields in forms granted they can submit forms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1210 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.20.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;_elementor_data&amp;#x27; Meta Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1210</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the '_elementor_data' meta field in all versions up to, and including, 3.20.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1447 | Mail Mint &amp;lt;= 1.19.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1447</link><description>The Mail Mint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.19.2. This is due to missing nonce validation on the create_or_update_note function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create or update contact notes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Due to missing sanitization and escaping this can lead to stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58381 | Directory transversal vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1c2 and 9.2.2 through 9.2.2a using various shell commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58381</link><description>A
 vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1c2 could allow an 
authenticated attacker with admin privileges using the shell commands 
“source, ping6, sleep, disown, wait to modify the path variables and 
move upwards in the directory structure or to traverse to different 
directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14274 | Unlimited Elements for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Border Hero Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14274</link><description>The Unlimited Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Border Hero widget's Button Link field in versions up to 2.0.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9711 | Privilege escalation in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1c3, and 9.2.2 though 9.2.2b</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9711</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1c3 could allow elevating the privileges of the local authenticated user to “root” using the export option of seccertmgmt and seccryptocfg commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0950 | Spectra Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.19.17 - Unauthenticated Information Disclosure in Sensitive Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0950</link><description>The Spectra Gutenberg Blocks – Website Builder for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.17. This is due to the plugin failing to check `post_password_required()` before rendering post excerpts in the `render_excerpt()` function and the `uagb_get_excerpt()` helper function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read excerpts of password-protected posts by simply viewing any page that contains a Spectra Post Grid, Post Masonry, Post Carousel, or Post Timeline block.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24694 | The installer for Roland Cloud Manager ver.3.1.19 and prior insecurely loads Dynamic Link Libraries (DLLs), which could allow an attacker to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24694</link><description>The installer for Roland Cloud Manager ver.3.1.19 and prior insecurely loads Dynamic Link Libraries (DLLs), which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58380 | Directory transversal vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1 using grep command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58380</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1 could allow an authenticated attacker with admin privileges using the shell command “grep” to modify the path variables and move upwards in the directory structure or to traverse to different directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0383 | Information disclosure in Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1c2, 9.2.2 through 9.2.2a and 10.0.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0383</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to access insecurely stored file contents including the history command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0909 | WP ULike &amp;lt;= 4.8.3.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Log Deletion via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0909</link><description>The WP ULike plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.3.1. This is due to the `wp_ulike_delete_history_api` AJAX action not verifying that the log entry being deleted belongs to the current user. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above (granted the 'stats' capability is assigned to their role), to delete arbitrary log entries belonging to other users via the 'id' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1788 | Buffer Overflow in Xquic Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1788</link><description>: Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Xquic Project Xquic Server xquic on Linux (QUIC protocol implementation, packet processing module modules) allows : Buffer Manipulation.This issue affects Xquic Server: through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24936 | An improper input validation vulnerability was found in ADM while joining a AD Domain.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24936</link><description>When a specific function is enabled while joining a AD Domain from ADM, an improper input parameters validation vulnerability in a specific CGI program allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to write arbitrary data to any file on the system. By exploiting this vulnerability, attackers can overwrite critical system files, leading to a complete system compromise.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.1.RCI1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24932 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was found in ADM while updating the DDNS settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24932</link><description>The DDNS update function in ADM fails to properly validate the hostname of the DDNS server's TLS/SSL certificate. Although the connection uses HTTPS, an improper validated TLS/SSL certificates allows a remote attacker can intercept the communication to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack, which may obtain the sensitive information of DDNS updating process, including the user's account email, MD5 hashed password, and device serial number.This issue affects ADM: from 4.1.0 through 4.3.3.ROF1, from 5.0.0 through 5.1.1.RCI1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24933 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was found in ADM while sending HTTPS requests to the server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24933</link><description>The API communication component fails to validate the SSL/TLS certificate when sending HTTPS requests to the server. An improper certificates validation vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker can perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack to intercept the cleartext communication, potentially leading to the exposure of sensitive user information, including account emails, MD5 hashed passwords, and device serial numbers.


Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.1.RCI1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24934 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was found in ADM while querying an external server for the device&amp;#x27;s WAN IP address.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24934</link><description>The DDNS function uses an insecure HTTP connection or fails to validate the SSL/TLS certificate when querying an external server for the device's WAN IP address. An unauthenticated remote attacker can perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack to spoof the response, leading the device to update its DDNS record with an incorrect IP address.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.1.RCI1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24935 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was found in a third-party NAT traversal module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24935</link><description>A third-party NAT traversal module fails to validate SSL/TLS certificates when connecting to the signaling server. While subsequent access to device services requires additional authentication, a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attacker can intercept or redirect the NAT tunnel establishment. This could allow an attacker to disrupt service availability or facilitate further targeted attacks by acting as a proxy between the user and the device services.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.1.RCI1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12774 | SQL queries with sensitive information printed in logs with Brocade SANnav before 3.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12774</link><description>A vulnerability in the migration script for Brocade SANnav before 3.0 could allow the collection of database sql queries in the SANnav support save file. An attacker with access to Brocade SANnav supportsave file, could open the file and  then obtain sensitive information such as details of database tables and encrypted passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58379 | Password Exposure in Brocade Fabric OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58379</link><description>Brocade Fabric OS before 9.2.1 has a vulnerability that could allow a local authenticated attacker to reveal command line passwords using commands that may expose higher privilege sensitive information by a lower privileged user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58382 | Privilege escalation in Brocade Fabric before 9.2.1c2 and 9.2.2 through 9.2.2a</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58382</link><description>A vulnerability in the secure configuration of authentication and 
management services in Brocade Fabric OS before Fabric OS 9.2.1c2 could 
allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials 
to execute arbitrary commands as root using “supportsave”, 
“seccertmgmt”, “configupload” command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58383 | Privilege escalation via bind command in Brocade Fabric OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58383</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade Fabric OS versions before 9.2.1c2 could allow an administrator-level user to execute the bind command, to escalate privileges and bypass security controls allowing the execution of arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67481 | mw.message(…).parse() doesn&amp;#x27;t output safe HTML, but it&amp;#x27;s being used as if it does</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67481</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.JqueryMsg/mediawiki.JqueryMsg.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.16, 1.43.6, 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67482 | Lua segfault in unpack()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67482</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Scribunto, Wikimedia Foundation luasandbox. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Engines/LuaCommon/lualib/mwInit.Lua, library.C.

This issue affects Scribunto: from * before 1.39.16, 1.43.6, 1.44.3, 1.45.1; luasandbox: from * before fea2304f8f6ab30314369a612f4f5b165e68e95a.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67483 | Theoretical i18n XSS in mediawiki.page.preview.js when a page has multiple protection levels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67483</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Page.Preview.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.43.6, 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67484 | Action API xslt option allows JavaScript execution by administrators who are not interface administrators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67484</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Api/ApiFormatXml.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.16, 1.43.6, 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61651 | i18n XSS through Special:CheckUser CheckUser helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files modules/ext.CheckUser/checkuser/checkUserHelper/buildUserElement.Js.

This issue affects CheckUser: from * before 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61652 | Action API discussiontoolspageinfo does not check for authorizeRead for the page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61652</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation DiscussionTools.This issue affects DiscussionTools: from * before 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61653 | Extension:TextExtracts does not check for authorizeRead when returning extracts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61653</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation TextExtracts. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/ApiQueryExtracts.Php.

This issue affects TextExtracts: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61654 | UserInfoCard: Do permission checking when getting counts of global and local edits, new articles and thanks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61654</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Thanks. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/ThanksQueryHelper.Php.

This issue affects Thanks: from * before 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61655 | Stored XSS through system messages in VisualEditor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation VisualEditor. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/ApiVisualEditorEdit.Php, modules/ve-mw/init/targets/ve.Init.Mw.DesktopArticleTarget.Js, modules/ve-mw/ui/dialogs/ve.Ui.MWSaveDialog.Js.

This issue affects VisualEditor: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61656 | XSS when pasting into VE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation VisualEditor. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/ce/ve.Ce.ClipboardHandler.Js.

This issue affects VisualEditor: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61657 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Vector. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61657</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Vector. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/skins.Vector.Js/stickyHeader.Js.

This issue affects Vector: from * before 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61658 | Special:GlobalContributions shows edits on wikis the viewer doesn&amp;#x27;t have access to</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61658</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/GlobalContributions/GlobalContributionsPager.Php.

This issue affects CheckUser: from * before 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67475 | Stored XSS through edit summaries in MW Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67475</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/CommentFormatter/CommentParser.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.16, 1.43.6, 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67476 | Importing leaks IP address of importer via EventStreams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67476</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Import/ImportableOldRevisionImporter.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67477 | Stored XSS through a system message in Special:ApiSandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67477</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Special.Apisandbox/ApiSandboxLayout.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67478 | Wrong E-Mail address composition for usernames with a comma and Umlauts in it like &amp;quot;Döe, Jähn&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67478</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Mail/UserMailer.Php.

This issue affects CheckUser: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67479 | Magic word replacement in legacy parser allows using reserved data attributes through wikitext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67479</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki, Wikimedia Foundation Cite. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Parser/CoreParserFunctions.Php, includes/Parser/Sanitizer.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1; Cite: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67480 | list=allrevisions can be used to bypass Extension:Lockdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67480</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Api/ApiQueryRevisionsBase.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.16, 1.43.6, 1.44.3, 1.45.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11173 | Reauth for enabling 2FA can be bypassed by submitting a form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11173</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation OATHAuth. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/Special/OATHManage.Php.

This issue affects OATHAuth: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11261 | Stored i18n XSS exposed by security patch for T402077</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Language/mediawiki.Language.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.15, 1.43.5, 1.44.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12773 | Plain password is generated in the audit logs while executing update-reports-purge-settings.sh script with Brocade SANnav before 2.4.0a</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12773</link><description>A vulnerability in update-reports-purge-settings.sh script logging for Brocade SANnav before 2.4.0a could allow the collection of SANnav database password in the system audit logs. The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker with access to the audit logs to access the Brocade SANnav database password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15556 | Notepad++ &amp;lt; 8.8.9 WinGUp Updater Lacks Update Integrity Verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15556</link><description>Notepad++ versions prior to 8.8.9, when using the WinGUp updater, contain an update integrity verification vulnerability where downloaded update metadata and installers are not cryptographically verified. An attacker able to intercept or redirect update traffic can cause the updater to download and execute an attacker-controlled installer, resulting in arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61645 | CodexTablePager has i18n XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/pager/CodexTablePager.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61646 | Watchlist group mode reveals authors of edits with hidden authorship</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61646</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/RecentChanges/EnhancedChangesList.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61648 | Stored XSS through system messages in CheckUser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files modules/ext.CheckUser.TempAccounts/components/ShowIPButton.Vue, modules/ext.CheckUser.TempAccounts/SpecialBlock.Js.

This issue affects CheckUser: from * before 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61649 | UserInfoCard: Check that performing user has permission to view log entries for number of past blocks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61649</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/Services/CheckUserUserInfoCardService.Php.

This issue affects CheckUser: from 7cedd58781d261f110651b6af4f41d2d11ae7309.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61650 | UserInfoCard is vulnerable to message key stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61650</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/Services/CheckUserUserInfoCardService.Php.

This issue affects CheckUser: from * before 795bf333272206a0189050d975e94b70eb7dc507.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61644 | i18n XSS through Special:Watchlist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61644</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Rcfilters/ui/WatchlistTopSectionWidget.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before &gt; fb856ce9cf121e046305116852cca4899ecb48ca.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61647 | UserInfoCard: Don&amp;#x27;t allow access to information about users who are suppressed if you don&amp;#x27;t have suppressor rights</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61647</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation CheckUser. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/Api/Rest/Handler/UserInfoHandler.Php.

This issue affects CheckUser: from a3dc1bbcc33acbcca6831d6afaccbb1054c93a57, 0584eb2ad564648aa3ce9c555dd044dda02b55f4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61637 | Stored XSS through system messages in MW Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61637</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Action/mediawiki.Action.Edit.Preview.Js, resources/src/mediawiki.Page.Preview.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61638 | Sanitizer::validateAttributes data-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki, Wikimedia Foundation Parsoid. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/parser/Sanitizer.Php, src/Core/Sanitizer.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1; Parsoid: from * before 0.16.6, 0.20.4, 0.21.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61639 | Suppressed blocked IP is visible in Special:BlockList, RC, and other places</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61639</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/logging/ManualLogEntry.Php, includes/recentchanges/RecentChangeFactory.Php, includes/recentchanges/RecentChangeStore.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61634 | HTML rest endpoint needs PoolCounter and proper parser cache check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61634</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/Rest/Handler/PageHTMLHandler.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61640 | Stored XSS through system messages in Special:RecentChangesLinked (MW Core)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Rcfilters/ui/RclToOrFromWidget.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61641 | API list=allpages with maxsize is making really slow queries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61641</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/api/ApiQueryAllPages.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61642 | Stored XSS through system messages provided to CodexHtmlForms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/htmlform/CodexHTMLForm.Php, includes/htmlform/fields/HTMLButtonField.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61643 | EventStreams publishes suppressed recent change entries that are suppressed from their creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61643</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/recentchanges/RecentChangeRCFeedNotifier.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61635 | Add rate limiting to ApiFancyCaptchaReload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61635</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation ConfirmEdit. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/FancyCaptcha/ApiFancyCaptchaReload.Php.

This issue affects ConfirmEdit: *.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61636 | Codex Special:Block vulnerable to message key XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/htmlform/fields/HTMLButtonField.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.14, 1.43.4, 1.44.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12679 | Plain text pbe key visible in audit log during Brocade SANnav migration from 2.4.0a to 3.0.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12679</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav before 2.4.0b prints the 
Password-Based Encryption (PBE) key in plaintext in the system audit log
 file. The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker 
with access to the audit logs to access the pbe key.

Note: The vulnerability is only triggered during a migration and not 
in a new installation. The system audit logs are accessible only to a 
privileged user on the server.



These audit logs are the local server VM’s audit logs and are not 
controlled by SANnav. These logs are only visible to the server admin of
 the host server and are not visible to the SANnav admin or any SANnav 
user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12680 | Brocade SANnav DataBase plaintext password is logged in failover logs (CVE-2025-12680)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12680</link><description>Brocade SANnav before Brocade SANnav 2.4.0b logs database passwords in clear text in the standby SANnav server, after disaster recovery failover.  The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker with admin privilege able to access the SANnav logs or the supportsave to read the database password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12772 | Plaintext Switch admin login password is seen in Brocade SANnav support save</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12772</link><description>Brocade SANnav before 2.4.0b logs the Brocade Fabric OS Switch admin password on the SANnav support save logs.

When OOM occurs on a Brocade SANnav server, the call stack trace for the Brocade switch is also collected in the heap dump file which contains this switch password in clear text. The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker with admin privilege able to access the SANnav logs or the supportsave to read the switch admin password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13096 | XML eXternal Entity injection (XXE) vulnerability affect IBM Business Automation Workflow -</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13096</link><description>IBM Business Automation Workflow containers V25.0.0 through V25.0.0-IF007, V24.0.1 - V24.0.1-IF007, V24.0.0 - V24.0.0-IF007 and IBM Business Automation Workflow traditional V25.0.0, V24.0.1, V24.0.0 is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36194 | This Power System update is being released to address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36194</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW1110.00 through FW1110.03, FW1060.00 through FW1060.51, and FW950.00 through FW950.F0 may expose a limited amount of data to a peer partition in specific shared processor configurations during certain operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36238 | Power System Exposure of Sensitive System Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36238</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW1110.00 through FW1110.03, FW1060.00 through FW1060.51, and FW950.00 through FW950.F0 could allow a local user with administration privileges to obtain sensitive information from a Virtual TPM through a series of PowerVM service procedures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36253 | Multiple Vulnerabilities in IBM Concert Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36253</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.1.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36436 | Multiple security vulnerabilities are addressed with IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation iFixes for January 2026.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36436</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 25.0.0 through 25.0.0 Interim Fix 002, 24.0.1 through 24.0.1 Interim Fix 005, and 24.0.0 through 24.0.0 Interim Fix 007  is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66480 | Wildfire has Arbitrary File Upload via Directory Traversal in UploadFileAction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66480</link><description>Wildfire IM is an instant messaging and real-time audio/video solution. Prior to 1.4.3, a critical vulnerability exists in the im-server component related to the file upload functionality found in com.xiaoleilu.loServer.action.UploadFileAction. The application exposes an endpoint (/fs) that handles multipart file uploads but fails to properly sanitize the filename provided by the user. Specifically, the writeFileUploadData method directly concatenates the configured storage directory with the filename extracted from the upload request without stripping directory traversal sequences (e.g., ../../). This vulnerability allows an attacker to write arbitrary files to any location on the server's filesystem where the application process has write permissions. By uploading malicious files (such as scripts, executables, or overwriting configuration files like authorized_keys or cron jobs), an attacker can achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) and completely compromise the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69207 | Khoj has an IDOR in Notion OAuth Flow Enables Index Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69207</link><description>Khoj is a self-hostable artificial intelligence app. Prior to 2.0.0-beta.23, an IDOR in the Notion OAuth callback allows an attacker to hijack any user's Notion integration by manipulating the state parameter. The callback endpoint accepts any user UUID without verifying the OAuth flow was initiated by that user, allowing attackers to replace victims' Notion configurations with their own, resulting in data poisoning and unauthorized access to the victim's Khoj search index. This attack requires knowing the user's UUID which can be leaked through shared conversations where an AI generated image is present. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.0.0-beta.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6589 | With MultiBlocks enabled and a user who is suppressed via a MultiBlock, a user without &amp;#x27;hideuser&amp;#x27; can see the hidden username in the BlockList</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6589</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/specials/pagers/BlockListPager.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: &gt;= 1.42.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6590 | Complete content leak of private wikis due to PasswordReset Wikitext injection in error message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6590</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/htmlform/fields/HTMLUserTextField.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * through 1.39.12, 1.42.76 1.43.1, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6591 | HTML injection in API action=feedcontributions output from i18n message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6591</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/api/ApiFeedContributions.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.13, 1.42.7 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6592 | Creating a permanent account from a temporary account associates temp username and IP address with real username in AbuseLog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6592</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation AbuseFilter. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/auth/AuthManager.Php.

This issue affects AbuseFilter: from fe0b1cb9e9691faf4d8d9bd80646589f6ec37615 before 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6593 | &amp;quot;{{SITENAME}} registered email address has been changed&amp;quot; email sent to unverified email addresses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6593</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/user/User.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from 1.27.0 before 1.39.13, 1.42.7 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6594 | XSS in Special:ApiSandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6594</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/src/mediawiki.Special.Apisandbox/ApiSandbox.Js.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from 1.27.0 before 1.39.13, 1.42.7 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6595 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Multimedia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6595</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MultimediaViewer.This issue affects MultimediaViewer: from * before 1.39.13, 1.42.7, 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6596 | Vector inserts portlet labels as HTML, allowing for stored XSS through system messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6596</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Vector. This vulnerability is associated with program files resources/skins.Vector.Js/portlets.Js, resources/skins.Vector.Legacy.Js/portlets.Js.

This issue affects Vector: from &gt;= 1.40.0 before 1.42.7, 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6597 | MediaWiki should not consider autocreation as login for the purposes of security reauthentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6597</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/auth/AuthManager.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from * before 1.39.13, 1.42.7, 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6927 | Autoblocks from global account suppressions are publicly visible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6927</link><description>Vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki. This vulnerability is associated with program files includes/specials/pagers/BlockListPager.Php, includes/api/ApiQueryBlocks.Php.

This issue affects MediaWiki: from &gt;= 1.42.0 before 1.39.13, 1.42.7 1.43.2, 1.44.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70958 | Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the installation module of Subrion CMS v4.2.1 allows attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70958</link><description>Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the installation module of Subrion CMS v4.2.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of the user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the dbuser, dbpwd, and dbname parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70959 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Jobs module of Tendenci CMS v15.3.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70959</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Jobs module of Tendenci CMS v15.3.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70960 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Forums module of Tendenci CMS v15.3.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70960</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Forums module of Tendenci CMS v15.3.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0924 | BuhoCleaner 1.15.2 - Local Privilege Escalation via PID reuse attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0924</link><description>BuhoCleaner contains an insecure XPC service that allows local, unprivileged users to escalate their privileges to root via insecure functions.This issue affects BuhoCleaner: 1.15.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1777 | Cleartext transmission of sensitive materials in aws/sagemaker-python-sdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1777</link><description>The Amazon SageMaker Python SDK before v3.2.0 and v2.256.0 includes the ModelBuilder HMAC signing key in the cleartext response elements of the DescribeTrainingJob function. A third party with permissions to both call this API and permissions to modify objects in the Training Jobs S3 output location may have the ability to upload arbitrary artifacts which are executed the next time the Training Job is invoked.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1778 | TLS disabled by default in select aws/sagemaker-python-sdk configurations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1778</link><description>Amazon SageMaker Python SDK before v3.1.1 or v2.256.0 disables TLS certificate verification for HTTPS connections made by the service when a Triton Python model is imported, incorrectly allowing for requests with invalid and self-signed certificates to succeed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22778 | vLLM leaks a heap address when PIL throws an error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22778</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From 0.8.3 to before 0.14.1, when an invalid image is sent to vLLM's multimodal endpoint, PIL throws an error. vLLM returns this error to the client, leaking a heap address. With this leak, we reduce ASLR from 4 billion guesses to ~8 guesses. This vulnerability can be chained a heap overflow with JPEG2000 decoder in OpenCV/FFmpeg to achieve remote code execution. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22780 | Rizin has a heap overflow on mach0_chained_fixups.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22780</link><description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Prior to 0.8.2, a heap overflow can be exploited when a malicious mach0 file, having bogus entries for the dyld chained segments, is parsed by rizin. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23476 | FacturaScripts Affected by Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23476</link><description>FacturaScripts is open-source enterprise resource planning and accounting software. Prior to 2025.8, there a reflected XSS bug in FacturaScripts. The problem is in how error messages get displayed. Twig's | raw filter is used, which skips HTML escaping. When triggering a database error (like passing a string where an integer is expected), the error message includes the input and gets rendered without sanitization. This vulnerability is fixed in 2025.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23515 | RCE - Command Injection in Signal K set-system-time plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23515</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. Prior to 1.5.0, a command injection vulnerability allows authenticated users with write permissions to execute arbitrary shell commands on the Signal K server when the set-system-time plugin is enabled. Unauthenticated users can also exploit this vulnerability if security is disabled on the Signal K server. This occurs due to unsafe construction of shell commands when processing navigation.datetime values received via WebSocket delta messages. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23997 | FacturaScripts has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in &amp;quot;Observations&amp;quot; field via History View</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23997</link><description>FacturaScripts is open-source enterprise resource planning and accounting software. In 2025.71 and earlier, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the Observations field. The flaw occurs in the History view, where historical data is rendered without proper HTML entity encoding. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of viewing the history by administrators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24007 | Tuleap is missing CSRF protection in the Overview inconsistent items</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24007</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite for management of software development and collaboration. Tuleap is missing CSRF protection in the Overview inconsistent items. An attacker could use this vulnerability to trick victims into repairing inconsistent items (creating artifact links from the release). This vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 17.0.99.1768924735 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 17.2-5, 17.1-6, and 17.0-9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24040 | jsPDF has a Shared State Race Condition in addJS Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24040</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 4.1.0, the addJS method in the jspdf Node.js build utilizes a shared module-scoped variable (text) to store JavaScript content. When used in a concurrent environment (e.g., a Node.js web server), this variable is shared across all requests. If multiple requests generate PDFs simultaneously, the JavaScript content intended for one user may be overwritten by a subsequent request before the document is generated. This results in Cross-User Data Leakage, where the PDF generated for User A contains the JavaScript payload (and any embedded sensitive data) intended for User B. Typically, this only affects server-side environments, although the same race conditions might occur if jsPDF runs client-side. The vulnerability has been fixed in jsPDF@4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24043 | jsPDF Affected by Stored XMP Metadata Injection (Spoofing &amp;amp; Integrity Violation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24043</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 4.1.0, user control of the first argument of the addMetadata function allows users to inject arbitrary XML. If given the possibility to pass unsanitized input to the addMetadata method, a user can inject arbitrary XMP metadata into the generated PDF. If the generated PDF is signed, stored or otherwise processed after, the integrity of the PDF can no longer be guaranteed. The vulnerability has been fixed in jsPDF@4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24051 | OpenTelemetry-Go Affected by Arbitrary Code Execution via PATH Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24051</link><description>OpenTelemetry-Go is the Go implementation of OpenTelemetry. The OpenTelemetry Go SDK in version v1.20.0-1.39.0 is vulnerable to Path Hijacking (Untrusted Search Paths) on macOS/Darwin systems. The resource detection code in sdk/resource/host_id.go executes the ioreg system command using a search path. An attacker with the ability to locally modify the PATH environment variable can achieve Arbitrary Code Execution (ACE) within the context of the application. A fix was released with v1.40.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24133 | jsPDF Affected by Denial of Service (DoS) via Unvalidated BMP Dimensions in BMPDecoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24133</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 4.1.0, user control of the first argument of the addImage method results in denial of service. If given the possibility to pass unsanitized image data or URLs to the addImage method, a user can provide a harmful BMP file that results in out of memory errors and denial of service. Harmful BMP files have large width and/or height entries in their headers, which lead to excessive memory allocation. The html method is also affected. The vulnerability has been fixed in jsPDF@4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24471 | Improper Validation in Conduit-derived homeservers resulting in Unintended Proxy or Intermediary (&amp;#x27;Confused Deputy&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24471</link><description>continuwuity is a Matrix homeserver written in Rust. This vulnerability allows an attacker with a malicious remote server to cause the local server to sign an arbitrary event upon user interaction. Upon a user account leaving a room (rejecting an invite), joining a room or knocking on a room, the victim server may ask a remote server for assistance. If the victim asks the attacker server for assistance the attacker is able to provide an arbitrary event, which the victim will sign and return to the attacker. For the /leave endpoint, this works for any event with a supported room version, where the origin and origin_server_ts is set by the victim. For the /join endpoint, an additionally victim-set content field in the format of a join membership is needed. For the /knock endpoint, an additional victim-set content field in the format of a knock membership and a room version not between 1 and 6 is needed. This was exploited as a part of a larger chain against the continuwuity.org homeserver. This vulnerability affects all Conduit-derived servers. This vulnerability is fixed in Continuwuity 0.5.1, Conduit 0.10.11, Grapevine 0aae932b, and Tuwunel 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24737 | jsPDF has a PDF Injection in AcroFormChoiceField which allows Arbitrary JavaScript Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24737</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 4.1.0, user control of properties and methods of the Acroform module allows users to inject arbitrary PDF objects, such as JavaScript actions. If given the possibility to pass unsanitized input to one of the following methods or properties, a user can inject arbitrary PDF objects, such as JavaScript actions, which are executed when the victim opens the document. The vulnerable API members are AcroformChoiceField.addOption, AcroformChoiceField.setOptions, AcroFormCheckBox.appearanceState, and AcroFormRadioButton.appearanceState. The vulnerability has been fixed in jsPDF@4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24763 | Authenticated Command Injection in OpenClaw Docker Execution via PATH Environment Variable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24763</link><description>OpenClaw (formerly  Clawdbot) is a personal AI assistant you run on your own devices. Prior to 2026.1.29, a command injection vulnerability existed in OpenClaw’s Docker sandbox execution mechanism due to unsafe handling of the PATH environment variable when constructing shell commands. An authenticated user able to control environment variables could influence command execution within the container context. This vulnerability is fixed in 2026.1.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25059 | OpenList affected by Path Traversal in file copy and remove handlers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25059</link><description>OpenList Frontend is a UI component for OpenList. Prior to 4.1.10, the application contains path traversal vulnerability in multiple file operation handlers in server/handles/fsmanage.go. Filename components in req.Names are directly concatenated with validated directories using stdpath.Join. This allows ".." sequences to bypass path restrictions, enabling users to access other users' files within the same storage mount and perform unauthorized actions such as deletion, renaming, or copying of files. An authenticated attacker can bypass directory-level authorisation by injecting traversal sequences into filename components, enabling unauthorised file removal and copying across user boundaries within the same storage mount. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.1.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25060 | OpenList Insecure TLS Default Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25060</link><description>OpenList Frontend is a UI component for OpenList. Prior to 4.1.10, certificate verification is disabled by default for all storage driver communications. The TlsInsecureSkipVerify setting is default to true in the DefaultConfig() function in internal/conf/config.go. This vulnerability enables Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attacks by disabling TLS certificate verification, allowing attackers to intercept and manipulate all storage communications. Attackers can exploit this through network-level attacks like ARP spoofing, rogue Wi-Fi access points, or compromised internal network equipment to redirect traffic to malicious endpoints. Since certificate validation is skipped, the system will unknowingly establish encrypted connections with attacker-controlled servers, enabling full decryption, data theft, and manipulation of all storage operations without triggering any security warnings. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.1.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25134 | Group-Office Argument Injection in MaintenanceController::actionZipLanguage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25134</link><description>Group-Office is an enterprise customer relationship management and groupware tool. Prior to 6.8.150, 25.0.82, and 26.0.5, the MaintenanceController exposes an action zipLanguage which takes a lang parameter and passes it directly to a system zip command via exec(). This can be combined with uploading a crafted zip file to achieve remote code execution. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.8.150, 25.0.82, and 26.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25137 | NixOs Odoo database and filestore publicly accessible with default odoo configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25137</link><description>The NixOs Odoo package is an open source ERP and CRM system. From 21.11 to before 25.11 and 26.05, every NixOS based Odoo setup publicly exposes the database manager without any authentication. This allows unauthorized actors to delete and download the entire database, including Odoos file store. Unauthorized access is evident from http requests. If kept, searching access logs and/or Odoos log for requests to /web/database can give indicators, if this has been actively exploited. The database manager is a featured intended for development and not meant to be publicly reachable. On other setups, a master password acts as 2nd line of defence. However, due to the nature of NixOS, Odoo is not able to modify its own configuration file and thus unable to persist the auto-generated password. This also applies when manually setting a master password in the web-UI. This means, the password is lost when restarting Odoo. When no password is set, the user is prompted to set one directly via the database manager. This requires no authentication or action by any authorized user or the system administrator. Thus, the database is effectively world readable by anyone able to reach Odoo. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.11 and 26.05.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25142 | SandboxJS Prototype Pollution -&amp;gt; Sandbox Escape -&amp;gt; RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25142</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Prior to 0.8.27, SanboxJS does not properly restrict __lookupGetter__ which can be used to obtain prototypes, which can be used for escaping the sandbox / remote code execution. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25144 | Talishar has a Stored XSS which can lead to data exfiltration &amp;amp; user impersonation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25144</link><description>Talishar is a fan-made Flesh and Blood project. A Stored XSS exists in the chat in-game system. The playerID parameter in SubmitChat.php and is saved without sanitization and executed whenever a user view the current page game. This vulnerability is fixed by 09dd00e5452e3cd998eb1406a88e5b0fa868e6b4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25221 | PolarLearn has Multiple Login CSRFs via Missing OAuth state Parameter (GitHub &amp;amp; Google)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25221</link><description>PolarLearn is a free and open-source learning program. In 0-PRERELEASE-15 and earlier, the OAuth 2.0 implementation for GitHub and Google login providers is vulnerable to Login Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). The application fails to implement and verify the state parameter during the authentication flow. This allows an attacker to pre-authenticate a session and trick a victim into logging into the attacker's account. Any data the victim then enters or academic progress they make is stored on the attacker's account, leading to data loss for the victim and information disclosure to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25222 | PolarLearn Affected by User Enumeration via Argon2 Timing Attack on Sign-In Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25222</link><description>PolarLearn is a free and open-source learning program. In 0-PRERELEASE-15 and earlier, a timing attack vulnerability in the sign-in process allows unauthenticated attackers to determine if a specific email address is registered on the platform. By measuring the response time of the login endpoint, an attacker can distinguish between valid and invalid email addresses. This occurs because the server only performs the computationally expensive Argon2 password hashing if the user exists in the database. Requests for existing users take significantly longer (~650ms) than requests for non-existent users (~160ms).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25228 | SignalK Server has Path Traversal leading to information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25228</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. Prior to 2.20.3, a path traversal vulnerability in SignalK Server's applicationData API allows authenticated users on Windows systems to read, write, and list arbitrary files and directories on the filesystem. The validateAppId() function blocks forward slashes (/) but not backslashes (\), which are treated as directory separators by path.join() on Windows. This enables attackers to escape the intended applicationData directory. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22224 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22224</link><description>A command injection vulnerability may be exploited after the admin's authentication in the cloud communication interface on the TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.


This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.


This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22225 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22225</link><description>A command injection vulnerability may be exploited after the admin's authentication in the VPN Connection Service on the Archer BE230 v1.2. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.



This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.


This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22226 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22226</link><description>A command injection vulnerability may be exploited after the admin's authentication in the VPN server configuration module on the TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.


This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.


This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22227 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22227</link><description>A command injection vulnerability may be exploited after the admin's authentication via the configuration backup restoration function of the TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.


This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.


This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22229 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22229</link><description>A command injection vulnerability may be exploited after the admin's authentication via the import of a crafted VPN client configuration file on the TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.
This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID. 
This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0630 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0630</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2(web modules) allows adjacent 

authenticated 

attacker to execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.

This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0631 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0631</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2(vpn modules) allows an adjacent 

authenticated 

attacker to execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.

This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22221 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22221</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2(vpn modules) allows adjacent 

authenticated 

attacker 

execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.

This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22222 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22222</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2(web modules) allows adjacent 

authenticated 

attacker to execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.

This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22223 | Command Injection Vulnerability on TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22223</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in TP-Link Archer BE230 v1.2(vpn modules) allows adjacent 

authenticated 

attacker 

execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control of the device, resulting in severe compromise of configuration integrity, network security, and service availability.

This CVE covers one of multiple distinct OS command injection issues identified across separate code paths. Although similar in nature, each instance is tracked under a unique CVE ID.This issue affects Archer BE230 v1.2 &lt; 1.2.4 Build 20251218 rel.70420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1232 | Anti-Tamper Bypass in BeyondTrust Privilege Management for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1232</link><description>A medium-severity vulnerability has been identified in BeyondTrust Privilege Management for Windows versions &lt;=25.7. Under certain conditions, a local authenticated user with elevated privileges may be able to bypass the product’s anti-tamper protections, which could allow access to protected application components and the ability to modify product configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1770 | Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources in Crafter Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1770</link><description>Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources vulnerability in Crafter Studio of Crafter CMS allows authenticated developers to execute OS commands via Groovy Sandbox Bypass. By inserting malicious Groovy elements, an attacker may bypass sandbox restrictions and obtain RCE (Remote Code Execution).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14914 | IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14914</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 26.0.0.1 could allow a privileged user to upload a zip archive containing path traversal sequences resulting in an overwrite of files leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15395 | IBM Jazz Foundation access control violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15395</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.3 through 7.0.3 iFix019 and 7.1.0 through 7.1.0 iFix005 is vulnerable to access control violations that allows the users to view or access/perform actions beyond their expected capability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47358 | Use After Free in Secure Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47358</link><description>Memory Corruption when user space address is modified and passed to mem_free API, causing kernel memory to be freed inadvertently.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47359 | Use After Free in Secure Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47359</link><description>Memory Corruption when multiple threads simultaneously access a memory free API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47363 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Automotive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47363</link><description>Memory corruption when calculating oversized partition sizes without proper checks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47364 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Automotive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47364</link><description>Memory corruption while calculating offset from partition start point.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47366 | Exposed Dangerous Method or Function in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47366</link><description>Cryptographic issue when a Trusted Zone with outdated code is triggered by a HLOS providing incorrect input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47397 | Improper Release of Memory Before Removing Last Reference in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47397</link><description>Memory Corruption when initiating GPU memory mapping using scatter-gather lists due to unchecked IOMMU mapping errors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47398 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47398</link><description>Memory Corruption while deallocating graphics processing unit memory buffers due to improper handling of memory pointers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47399 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47399</link><description>Memory Corruption while processing IOCTL call to update sensor property settings with invalid input parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47402 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47402</link><description>Transient DOS when processing a received frame with an excessively large authentication information element.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1703 | Limited path traversal when installing wheel archives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1703</link><description>When pip is installing and extracting a maliciously crafted wheel archive, files may be extracted outside the installation directory. The path traversal is limited to prefixes of the installation directory, thus isn't able to inject or overwrite executable files in typical situations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50975 | Multiple Innomic VibroLine VLX and avibia AVLX allow unauthenticated access to device configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50975</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker is able to use an existing session id of a logged in user and gain full access to the device if configuration via ethernet is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50976 | Innomic VibroLine Configurator and avibia Configurator allow unintended device reset via USB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50976</link><description>A local attacker could cause a full device reset by resetting the device passwords using an invalid reset file via USB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50977 | Multiple Innomic VibroLine VLX and avibia AVLX allow unauthenticated configuration preset change via HTTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50977</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially disrupt operations by switching between multiple configuration presets via HTTP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50978 | Multiple Innomic VibroLine VLX and avibia AVLX allow unauthenticated configuration preset change via Modbus (TCP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50978</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially disrupt operations by switching between multiple configuration presets via Modbus (TCP).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50979 | Multiple Innomic VibroLine VLX and avibia AVLX allow unauthenticated configuration preset change via Modbus (RS485)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50979</link><description>An unauthenticated adjacent attacker could potentially disrupt operations by switching between multiple configuration presets via Modbus (RS485).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50980 | Multiple Innomic VibroLine VLX and avibia AVLX allow unauthenticated configuration preset change via CAN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50980</link><description>A unauthenticated adjacent attacker could potentially disrupt operations by switching between multiple configuration presets via CAN.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50981 | Multiple Innomic VibroLine VLX HD 5.0 and avibia AVLX weak password requirements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50981</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can gain full access on the affected devices as they are shipped without a password by default and setting one is not enforced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1186 | Path Traversal in EAP Legislator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1186</link><description>EAP Legislator is vulnerable to Path Traversal in file extraction functionality. Attacker can prepare zipx archive (default file type used by the Legislator application) and choose arbitrary path outside the intended directory (e.x. system startup) where files will be extracted by the victim upon opening the file.
This issue was fixed in version 2.25a.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1760 | Libsoup: soupserver: denial of service via http request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1760</link><description>A flaw was found in SoupServer. This HTTP request smuggling vulnerability occurs because SoupServer improperly handles requests that combine Transfer-Encoding: chunked and Connection: keep-alive headers. A remote, unauthenticated client can exploit this by sending specially crafted requests, causing SoupServer to fail to close the connection as required by RFC 9112. This allows the attacker to smuggle additional requests over the persistent connection, leading to unintended request processing and potential denial-of-service (DoS) conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1761 | Libsoup: stack-based buffer overflow in libsoup multipart response parsingmultipart http response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1761</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. This stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability occurs during the parsing of multipart HTTP responses due to an incorrect length calculation. A remote attacker can exploit this by sending a specially crafted multipart HTTP response, which can lead to memory corruption. This issue may result in application crashes or arbitrary code execution in applications that process untrusted server responses, and it does not require authentication or user interaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24070 | Local Privilege Escalation via DYLIB Injection in Native Instruments Native Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24070</link><description>During the installation of the Native Access application, a privileged helper `com.native-instruments.NativeAccess.Helper2`, which is used by Native Access to trigger functions via XPC communication like copy-file, remove or set-permissions, is deployed as well. The communication with the XPC service of the privileged helper is only allowed if the client process is signed with the corresponding certificate and fulfills the following code signing requirement:
"anchor trusted and certificate leaf[subject.CN] = \"Developer ID Application: Native Instruments GmbH (83K5EG6Z9V)\""

The Native Access application was found to be signed with the `com.apple.security.cs.allow-dyld-environment-variables` and `com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation` entitlements leading to DYLIB injection and therefore command execution in the context of this application. A low privileged user can exploit the DYLIB injection to trigger functions of the privileged helper XPC service resulting in privilege escalation by first deleting the /etc/sudoers file and then copying a malicious version of that file to /etc/sudoers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24071 | XPC Client Validation via PID leading to Local Privilege Escalation in Native Instruments Native Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24071</link><description>It was found that the XPC service offered by the privileged helper of Native Access  uses the PID of the connecting client to verify its code signature. This is considered insecure and can be exploited by PID reuse attacks. The connection handler function uses _xpc_connection_get_pid(arg2) as argument for the hasValidSignature function. This value can not be trusted since it is vulnerable to PID reuse attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8587 | Time-Based Blind SQLi in AKCE Software&amp;#x27;s SKSPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8587</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AKCE Software Technology R&amp;amp;D Industry and Trade Inc. SKSPro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SKSPro: through 07012026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1757 | Libxml2: memory leak leading to local denial of service in xmllint interactive shell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1757</link><description>A flaw was identified in the interactive shell of the xmllint utility, part of the libxml2 project, where memory allocated for user input is not properly released under certain conditions. When a user submits input consisting only of whitespace, the program skips command execution but fails to free the allocated buffer. Repeating this action causes memory to continuously accumulate. Over time, this can exhaust system memory and terminate the xmllint process, creating a denial-of-service condition on the local system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2356 | Remote Code Execution due to LFI in &amp;#x27;/reinstall_extension&amp;#x27; in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2356</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the '/reinstall_extension' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `name` parameter of the `@router.post("/reinstall_extension")` route. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject a malicious `name` parameter, leading to the server loading and executing arbitrary Python files from the upload directory for discussions. This issue arises due to the concatenation of `data.name` directly with `lollmsElfServer.lollms_paths.extensions_zoo_path` and its use as an argument for `ExtensionBuilder().build_extension()`. The server's handling of the `__init__.py` file in arbitrary locations, facilitated by `importlib.machinery.SourceFileLoader`, enables the execution of arbitrary code, such as command execution or creating a reverse-shell connection. This vulnerability affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui and can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) when the application is exposed to an external endpoint or the UI, especially when bound to `0.0.0.0` or in `headless mode`. No user interaction is required for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4147 | Insufficient Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4147</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.13, an insufficient granularity of access control vulnerability allows users to delete prompts created in other organizations through ID manipulation. The vulnerability stems from the application's failure to validate the ownership of the prompt before deletion, only checking if the user has permissions to delete such resources without verifying if it belongs to the user's project or organization. As a result, users can remove prompts not owned by their organization or project, leading to legitimate users being unable to access the removed prompts and causing information inconsistencies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5386 | Account Hijacking via Password Reset Token Leak in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5386</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.2, an account hijacking vulnerability exists due to a password reset token leak. A user with a 'viewer' role can exploit this vulnerability to hijack another user's account by obtaining the password reset token. The vulnerability is triggered when the 'viewer' role user sends a specific request to the server, which responds with a password reset token in the 'recoveryToken' parameter. This token can then be used to reset the password of another user's account without authorization. The issue results from an excessive attack surface, allowing lower-privileged users to escalate their privileges and take over accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5986 | Remote Arbitrary File Write with Arbitrary Data in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5986</link><description>A vulnerability in h2oai/h2o-3 version 3.46.0.1 allows remote attackers to write arbitrary data to any file on the server. This is achieved by exploiting the `/3/Parse` endpoint to inject attacker-controlled data as the header of an empty file, which is then exported using the `/3/Frames/framename/export` endpoint. The impact of this vulnerability includes the potential for remote code execution and complete access to the system running h2o-3, as attackers can overwrite critical files such as private SSH keys or script files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10279 | Privilege Escalation in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10279</link><description>In mlflow version 2.20.3, the temporary directory used for creating Python virtual environments is assigned insecure world-writable permissions (0o777). This vulnerability allows an attacker with write access to the `/tmp` directory to exploit a race condition and overwrite `.py` files in the virtual environment, leading to arbitrary code execution. The issue is resolved in version 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6208 | Uncontrolled Memory Consumption in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6208</link><description>The `SimpleDirectoryReader` component in `llama_index.core` version 0.12.23 suffers from uncontrolled memory consumption due to a resource management flaw. The vulnerability arises because the user-specified file limit (`num_files_limit`) is applied after all files in a directory are loaded into memory. This can lead to memory exhaustion and degraded performance, particularly in environments with limited resources. The issue is resolved in version 0.12.41.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7105 | Denial of Service via JavaScript Memory Overflow in danny-avila/librechat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7105</link><description>A vulnerability in danny-avila/librechat allows attackers to exploit the unrestricted Fork Function in `/api/convos/fork` to fork numerous contents rapidly. If the forked content includes a Mermaid graph with a large number of nodes, it can lead to a JavaScript heap out of memory error upon service restart, causing a denial of service. This issue affects the latest version of the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0599 | Unbounded External Image Fetch in Validation Leads to Resource-Exhaustion DoS in huggingface/text-generation-inference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0599</link><description>A vulnerability in huggingface/text-generation-inference version 3.3.6 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit unbounded external image fetching during input validation in VLM mode. The issue arises when the router scans inputs for Markdown image links and performs a blocking HTTP GET request, reading the entire response body into memory and cloning it before decoding. This behavior can lead to resource exhaustion, including network bandwidth saturation, memory inflation, and CPU overutilization. The vulnerability is triggered even if the request is later rejected for exceeding token limits. The default deployment configuration, which lacks memory usage limits and authentication, exacerbates the impact, potentially crashing the host machine. The issue is resolved in version 3.3.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1117 | Improper Access Control in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1117</link><description>A vulnerability in the `lollms_generation_events.py` component of parisneo/lollms version 5.9.0 allows unauthenticated access to sensitive Socket.IO events. The `add_events` function registers event handlers such as `generate_text`, `cancel_generation`, `generate_msg`, and `generate_msg_from` without implementing authentication or authorization checks. This allows unauthenticated clients to execute resource-intensive or state-altering operations, leading to potential denial of service, state corruption, and race conditions. Additionally, the use of global flags (`lollmsElfServer.busy`, `lollmsElfServer.cancel_gen`) for state management in a multi-client environment introduces further vulnerabilities, enabling one client's actions to affect the server's state and other clients' operations. The lack of proper access control and reliance on insecure global state management significantly impacts the availability and integrity of the service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54263 | WordPress Spirit Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54263</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Talemy Spirit Framework allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Spirit Framework: from n/a through 1.2.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1751 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1751</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting with 16.8 before 18.5.0 that could have allowed unauthorized edits to merge request approval rules under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9974 | Insufficient Input Validation on WEBUI in Nokia ONT/Beacon product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9974</link><description>The unified WEBUI application of the ONT/Beacon device contains an input handling flaw that allows authenticated users to trigger unintended system-level command execution. Due to insufficient validation of user-supplied data, a low-privileged authenticated attacker may be able to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying ONT/Beacon operating system, potentially impacting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20401 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20401</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01738310; Issue ID: MSV-5933.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20402 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20402</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00693083; Issue ID: MSV-5928.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20403 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20403</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01689254 (Note: For N15 and NR16) / MOLY01689259 (Note: For NR17 and NR17R); Issue ID: MSV-4843.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20404 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20404</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01689248; Issue ID: MSV-4837.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20405 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20405</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01688495; Issue ID: MSV-4818.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20406 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20406</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01726634; Issue ID: MSV-5728.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20407 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20407</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00464377; Issue ID: MSV-4905.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20408 | In wlan, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20408</link><description>In wlan, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00461651; Issue ID: MSV-4758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20409 | In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20409</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10363246; Issue ID: MSV-5779.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20410 | In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20410</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10362552; Issue ID: MSV-5760.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20411 | In cameraisp, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20411</link><description>In cameraisp, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10351676; Issue ID: MSV-5737.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20412 | In cameraisp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20412</link><description>In cameraisp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10351676; Issue ID: MSV-5733.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20413 | In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20413</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10362725; Issue ID: MSV-5694.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20414 | In imgsys, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20414</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10362999; Issue ID: MSV-5625.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20415 | In imgsys, there is a possible memory corruption due to improper locking. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious actor ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20415</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible memory corruption due to improper locking. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10363254; Issue ID: MSV-5617.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20417 | In pcie, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20417</link><description>In pcie, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10314946 / ALPS10340155; Issue ID: MSV-5154.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20418 | In Thread, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20418</link><description>In Thread, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00465153; Issue ID: MSV-4927.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20419 | In wlan AP/STA firmware, there is a possible system becoming irresponsive due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote (proximal/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20419</link><description>In wlan AP/STA firmware, there is a possible system becoming irresponsive due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00461663 /  WCNCR00463309; Issue ID: MSV-4852.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20420 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20420</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01738313; Issue ID: MSV-5935.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20421 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20421</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01738293; Issue ID: MSV-5922.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20422 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20422</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00827332; Issue ID: MSV-5919.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1518 | Keycloak: blind server-side request forgery (ssrf) via ciba backchannel notification endpoint in keycloak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1518</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak’s CIBA feature where insufficient validation of client-configured backchannel notification endpoints could allow blind server-side requests to internal services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 07:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20711 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in E-mail function of Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 6.0.3, which may allow an attacker to reset arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20711</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in E-mail function of Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 6.0.3, which may allow an attacker to reset arbitrary users’ passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22881 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Message function of Cybozu Garoon 5.15.0 to 6.0.3, which may allow an attacker to reset arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22881</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Message function of Cybozu Garoon 5.15.0 to 6.0.3, which may allow an attacker to reset arbitrary users’ passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22888 | Improper input verification issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 6.0.3, which may lead to unauthorized alteration of portal settings, pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22888</link><description>Improper input verification issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 6.0.3, which may lead to unauthorized alteration of portal settings, potentially blocking access to the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15030 | User Profile Builder &amp;lt; 3.15.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15030</link><description>The User Profile Builder  WordPress plugin before 3.15.2 does not have a proper password reset process, allowing a few unauthenticated requests to reset the password of any user by knowing their username, such as administrator ones, and therefore gain access to their account</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15396 | Library Viewer &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15396</link><description>The Library Viewer WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0658 | Five Star Restaurant Reservations &amp;lt; 2.7.9 - Arbitrary Bookings Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0658</link><description>The Five Star Restaurant Reservations  WordPress plugin before 2.7.9 does not have CSRF checks in some bulk actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins perform unwanted actions, such as deleting bookings via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13881 | Org.keycloak.services.resources.admin: keycloak: limited administrator can retrieve sensitive user attributes via admin api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13881</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak Admin API. This vulnerability allows an administrator with limited privileges to retrieve sensitive custom attributes via the /unmanagedAttributes endpoint, bypassing User Profile visibility settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1530 | Fog-kubevirt: fog-kubevirt: man-in-the-middle vulnerability due to disabled certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1530</link><description>A flaw was found in fog-kubevirt. This vulnerability allows a remote attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack due to disabled certificate validation. This enables the attacker to intercept and potentially alter sensitive communications between Satellite and OpenShift, resulting in information disclosure and data integrity compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1531 | Foreman-kubevirt: foreman_kubevirt: man-in-the-middle due to insecure default ssl verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1531</link><description>A flaw was found in foreman_kubevirt. When configuring the connection to OpenShift, the system disables SSL verification if a Certificate Authority (CA) certificate is not explicitly set. This insecure default allows a remote attacker, capable of intercepting network traffic between Satellite and OpenShift, to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack. Such an attack could lead to the disclosure or alteration of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1746 | JeecgBoot Online Report API loadDictItemByKeyword sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1746</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in JeecgBoot 3.9.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /JeecgBoot/sys/api/loadDictItemByKeyword of the component Online Report API. Such manipulation of the argument keyword leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1745 | SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1745</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0. This affects an unknown part. This manipulation causes cross-site request forgery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1744 | D-Link DSL-6641K sp_pppoe_user.js doSubmitPPP cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1744</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DSL-6641K N8.TR069.20131126. Affected by this issue is the function doSubmitPPP of the file sp_pppoe_user.js. The manipulation of the argument Username results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24788 | RaspAP raspap-webgui versions prior to 3.3.6 contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24788</link><description>RaspAP raspap-webgui versions prior to 3.3.6 contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a user who can log in to the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25200 | A vulnerability in MagicInfo9 Server allows authorized users to upload HTML files without authentication, leading to Stored XSS, which can r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25200</link><description>A vulnerability in MagicInfo9 Server allows authorized users to upload HTML files without authentication, leading to Stored XSS, which can result in account takeover


This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1090.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25201 | An unauthenticated user can upload arbitrary files to execute remote code, leading to privilege escalation in MagicInfo9 Server.
This issue ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25201</link><description>An unauthenticated user can upload arbitrary files to execute remote code, leading to privilege escalation in MagicInfo9 Server.
This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1090.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25202 | The database account and password are hardcoded, allowing login with the account to manipulate the database in MagicInfo9 Server.This issue ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25202</link><description>The database account and password are hardcoded, allowing login with the account to manipulate the database in MagicInfo9 Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1090.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1742 | EFM ipTIME A8004T VPN Service timepro.cgi commit_vpncli_file_upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1742</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in EFM ipTIME A8004T 14.18.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function commit_vpncli_file_upload of the file /cgi/timepro.cgi of the component VPN Service. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1743 | DJI Mavic Mini/Spark/Mini SE Enhanced Wi-Fi Pairing authentication replay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1743</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DJI Mavic Mini, Spark and Mini SE up to 01.00.0500. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Enhanced Wi-Fi Pairing. The manipulation leads to authentication bypass by capture-replay. The attack must be carried out from within the local network. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1740 | EFM ipTIME A8004T Hidden Hiddenloginsetup timepro.cgi httpcon_check_session_url improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1740</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EFM ipTIME A8004T 14.18.2. This impacts the function httpcon_check_session_url of the file /cgi/timepro.cgi of the component Hidden Hiddenloginsetup Interface. The manipulation results in improper authentication. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1741 | EFM ipTIME A8004T Debug d.cgi httpcon_check_session_url backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1741</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in EFM ipTIME A8004T 14.18.2. Affected is the function httpcon_check_session_url of the file /sess-bin/d.cgi of the component Debug Interface. This manipulation of the argument cmd causes backdoor. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13348 | An improper access control vulnerability exists in ASUS Secure Delete Driver of ASUS Business Manager. This vulnerability can be triggered b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13348</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in ASUS Secure Delete Driver of ASUS Business Manager. This vulnerability can be triggered by a local user sending a specially crafted request, potentially leading to the creation of arbitrary files in a specified path. Refer to the "Security Update for ASUS Business Manager" section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1738 | Open5GS SGWC context.c sgwc_tunnel_add assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1738</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. The impacted element is the function sgwc_tunnel_add of the file /src/sgwc/context.c of the component SGWC. Executing a manipulation of the argument pdr can lead to reachable assertion. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1739 | Free5GC pcf smpolicy.go HandleCreateSmPolicyRequest null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1739</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Free5GC pcf up to 1.4.1. This affects the function HandleCreateSmPolicyRequest of the file internal/sbi/processor/smpolicy.go. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is df535f5524314620715e842baf9723efbeb481a7. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1737 | Open5GS CreateBearerRequest s5c-handler.c sgwc_s5c_handle_create_bearer_request assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1737</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. The affected element is the function sgwc_s5c_handle_create_bearer_request of the file /src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c of the component CreateBearerRequest Handler. Performing a manipulation results in reachable assertion. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 02:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1735 | Yealink MeetingBar A30 Diagnostic command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1735</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Yealink MeetingBar A30 133.321.0.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Diagnostic Handler. This manipulation causes command injection. It is feasible to perform the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1736 | Open5GS SGWC s11-handler.c assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1736</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Impacted is the function sgwc_s11_handle_create_indirect_data_forwarding_tunnel_request of the file /src/sgwc/s11-handler.c of the component SGWC. Such manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1734 | Zhong Bang CRMEB crontab Endpoint CrontabController.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1734</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Zhong Bang CRMEB up to 5.6.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file crmeb/app/api/controller/v1/CrontabController.php of the component crontab Endpoint. The manipulation results in missing authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1733 | Zhong Bang CRMEB :uni tidyOrder improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1733</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Zhong Bang CRMEB up to 5.6.3. This affects the function detail/tidyOrder of the file /api/store_integral/order/detail/:uni. The manipulation of the argument order_id leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25253 | OpenClaw (aka clawdbot or Moltbot) before 2026.1.29 obtains a gatewayUrl value from a query string and automatically makes a WebSocket conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25253</link><description>OpenClaw (aka clawdbot or Moltbot) before 2026.1.29 obtains a gatewayUrl value from a query string and automatically makes a WebSocket connection without prompting, sending a token value.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 22:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37037 | AVAST SecureLine 5.5.522.0 - &amp;#x27;SecureLine&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37037</link><description>Avast SecureLine 5.5.522.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem account permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37045 | NetBackup 7.0 - &amp;#x27;NetBackup INET Daemon&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37045</link><description>Veritas NetBackup 7.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the NetBackup INET Daemon service that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files\Veritas\NetBackup\bin\bpinetd.exe to inject malicious code that would execute with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37047 | Deep Instinct Windows Agent 1.2.29.0 - &amp;#x27;DeepMgmtService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37047</link><description>Deep Instinct Windows Agent 1.2.29.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the DeepMgmtService that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files\HP Sure Sense\DeepMgmtService.exe to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37048 | Iskysoft Application Framework Service 2.4.3.241 - &amp;#x27;IsAppService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37048</link><description>Iskysoft Application Framework Service 2.4.3.241 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious executables that would be run with the service's high-level system permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37055 | SpyHunter 4 - &amp;#x27;SpyHunter 4 Service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37055</link><description>SpyHunter 4 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path by placing malicious executables in specific file system locations to gain elevated access during service startup.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37061 | BOOTP Turbo 2.0.1214 - &amp;#x27;BOOTP Turbo&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37061</link><description>BOOTP Turbo 2.0.1214 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted executable path to inject malicious code that will be executed when the service starts with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37062 | DHCP Turbo 4.6.1298- &amp;#x27;DHCP Turbo 4&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37062</link><description>DHCP Turbo 4.61298 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code by exploiting the service binary path. Attackers can place malicious executables in the service path to gain elevated privileges when the service starts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37063 | TFTP Turbo 4.6.1273 - &amp;#x27;TFTP Turbo 4&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37063</link><description>TFTP Turbo 4.6.1273 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious executables that will be launched with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37064 | EPSON EasyMP Network Projection 2.81 - &amp;#x27;EMP_NSWLSV&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37064</link><description>EPSON EasyMP Network Projection 2.81 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the EMP_NSWLSV service that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\EPSON Projector\EasyMP Network Projection V2\ to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47921 | Free Photo &amp;amp; Video Vault 0.0.2 Directory Traversal Vulnerability via Web Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47921</link><description>Free Photo &amp; Video Vault 0.0.2 contains a directory traversal web vulnerability that allows remote attackers to manipulate application path requests and access sensitive system files. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability without privileges to retrieve environment variables and access unauthorized system paths.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50950 | Webile 1.0.1 Directory Traversal Vulnerability via Web Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50950</link><description>Webile 1.0.1 contains a directory traversal vulnerability that allows remote attackers to manipulate file system paths without authentication. Attackers can exploit path manipulation to access sensitive system directories and potentially compromise the mobile device's local file system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50951 | WiFi File Transfer 1.0.8 Persistent XSS via Web Server Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50951</link><description>WiFi File Transfer 1.0.8 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows remote attackers to inject malicious script codes through file and folder names. Attackers can exploit the web server's input validation weakness to execute arbitrary JavaScript when users preview infected file paths, potentially compromising user browser sessions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50952 | Banco Guayaquil 8.0.0 Mobile iOS Cross-Site Scripting via Profile Name Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50952</link><description>Banco Guayaquil 8.0.0 mobile iOS application contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the TextBox Name Profile input. Attackers can inject malicious script code through a POST request that executes on application review without user interaction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-54343 | QWE DL 2.0.1 Persistent XSS Vulnerability via Path Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-54343</link><description>QWE DL 2.0.1 mobile web application contains a persistent input validation vulnerability allowing remote attackers to inject malicious script code through path parameter manipulation. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability to execute persistent cross-site scripting attacks, potentially leading to session hijacking and application module manipulation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47856 | Easy Cart Shopping Cart 2021 Cross-Site Scripting via Search Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47856</link><description>Easy Cart Shopping Cart 2021 contains a non-persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the search module's keyword parameter. Remote attackers can inject malicious script code through the search input to compromise user sessions and manipulate application content.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47885 | Payment Terminal Multiple Versions Non-Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47885</link><description>Multiple payment terminal versions contain non-persistent cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in billing and payment information input fields. Attackers can inject malicious script code through vulnerable parameters to manipulate client-side requests and potentially execute session hijacking or phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47908 | Ultimate POS 4.4 Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Product Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47908</link><description>Ultimate POS 4.4 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the product name parameter that allows remote attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability through product add or edit functions to execute arbitrary JavaScript and potentially hijack user sessions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47909 | Mult-E-Cart Ultimate 2.4 SQL Injection via Vulnerable ID Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47909</link><description>Mult-E-Cart Ultimate 2.4 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in inventory, customer, vendor, and order modules. Remote attackers with privileged vendor or admin roles can exploit the 'id' parameter to execute malicious SQL commands and compromise the database management system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47911 | Affiliate Pro 1.7 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Index Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47911</link><description>Affiliate Pro 1.7 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the index module's input fields. Attackers can inject malicious scripts through fullname, username, and email parameters to execute client-side attacks and manipulate browser requests.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47912 | PHP Melody 3.0 Non-Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47912</link><description>PHP Melody version 3.0 contains multiple non-persistent cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in categories, import, and user import files. Attackers can inject malicious scripts through unvalidated parameters to execute client-side attacks and potentially hijack user sessions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47913 | PHP Melody 3.0 Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Video Editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47913</link><description>PHP Melody 3.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the video editor that allows privileged users to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can exploit the WYSIWYG editor to execute persistent scripts, potentially leading to session hijacking and application manipulation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47914 | PHP Melody 3.0 Persistent XSS Vulnerability via Edit Video Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47914</link><description>PHP Melody version 3.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the edit-video.php submitted parameter that allows remote attackers to inject malicious script code. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary JavaScript, potentially leading to session hijacking, persistent phishing, and manipulation of application modules.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47915 | PHP Melody 3.0 SQL Injection Vulnerability via Edit Video Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47915</link><description>PHP Melody version 3.0 contains a remote SQL injection vulnerability in the video edit module that allows authenticated attackers to inject malicious SQL commands. Attackers can exploit the unvalidated 'vid' parameter to execute arbitrary database queries and potentially compromise the web application and database management system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47916 | Simple CMS 2.1 SQL Injection Vulnerability via Users Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47916</link><description>Simple CMS 2.1 contains a remote SQL injection vulnerability that allows privileged attackers to inject unfiltered SQL commands in the users module. Attackers can exploit unvalidated input parameters in the admin.php file to compromise the database management system and web application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47917 | Simple CMS 2.1 Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via User Input Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47917</link><description>Simple CMS 2.1 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in user input parameters that allows remote attackers to inject malicious script code. Attackers can exploit the newUser and editUser modules to inject persistent scripts that execute on user list preview, potentially leading to session hijacking and application manipulation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47918 | Simple CMS 2.1 SQL Injection Vulnerability via Users Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47918</link><description>Simple CMS 2.1 contains a remote SQL injection vulnerability that allows privileged attackers to inject unfiltered SQL commands in the users module. Attackers can exploit unvalidated input parameters in the admin.php file to compromise the database management system and web application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47919 | Simple CMS 2.1 Non-Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Preview Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47919</link><description>Simple CMS 2.1 contains a non-persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the preview.php file's id parameter. Attackers can inject malicious script code through a GET request to execute arbitrary scripts and potentially hijack user sessions or perform phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47920 | WebMO Job Manager 20.0 Cross-Site Scripting via Search Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47920</link><description>WebMO Job Manager 20.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in search parameters that allows remote attackers to inject malicious script code. Attackers can exploit the filterSearch and filterSearchType parameters to perform non-persistent attacks including session hijacking and external redirects.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50797 | Stripe Green Downloads Wordpress Plugin 2.03 Persistent XSS via Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50797</link><description>Stripe Green Downloads Wordpress Plugin 2.03 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability allowing remote attackers to inject malicious scripts in button label fields. Attackers can exploit input parameters to execute arbitrary scripts, potentially leading to session hijacking and application module manipulation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50940 | Knap Advanced PHP Login 3.1.3 Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50940</link><description>Knap Advanced PHP Login 3.1.3 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows remote attackers to inject malicious script code in the name parameter. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary scripts in users and activity log backend modules, potentially leading to session hijacking and persistent phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50941 | BootCommerce 3.2.1 Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Order Checkout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50941</link><description>BootCommerce 3.2.1 contains persistent input validation vulnerabilities that allow remote attackers to inject malicious script code through guest order checkout input fields. Attackers can exploit unvalidated input parameters to execute arbitrary scripts, potentially leading to session hijacking, phishing attacks, and application module manipulation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50942 | Inciga Web 2.8.2 Client-Side Cross-Site Scripting via EventListener</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50942</link><description>Inciga Web 2.8.2 contains a client-side cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows remote attackers to inject malicious script codes through the icinga.min.js file. Attackers can exploit the EventListener.handleEvent method to execute arbitrary scripts, potentially leading to session hijacking and non-persistent phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>