<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:58:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-49394 | Mutt: neomutt: in-reply-to email header field it not protected by cryptograpic signing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49394</link><description>In mutt and neomutt the In-Reply-To email header field is not protected by cryptographic signing which allows an attacker to reuse an unencrypted but signed email message to impersonate the original sender.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49395 | Mutt: neomutt: bcc email header field is indirectly leaked by cryptographic info block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49395</link><description>In mutt and neomutt, PGP encryption does not use the --hidden-recipient mode which may leak the Bcc email header field by inferring from the recipients info.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11097 | SourceCodester Student Record Management System Main Menu infinite loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11097</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Record Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Main Menu. The manipulation leads to infinite loop. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11099 | code-projects Job Recruitment login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11099</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49393 | Mutt: neomutt: to and cc email header fields are not protected by cryptographic signing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49393</link><description>In neomutt and mutt, the To and Cc email headers are not validated by cryptographic signing which allows an attacker that intercepts a message to change their value and include himself as a one of the recipients to compromise message confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8881 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CGI program in the Zyxel GS1900-48 switch firmware version V2.80(AAHN.1)C0 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8881</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CGI program in the Zyxel GS1900-48 switch firmware version V2.80(AAHN.1)C0 and earlier could allow an authenticated, LAN-based attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8882 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program in the Zyxel GS1900-48 switch firmware version V2.80(AAHN.1)C0 and earlier could allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8882</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program in the Zyxel GS1900-48 switch firmware version V2.80(AAHN.1)C0 and earlier could allow an authenticated, LAN-based attacker with administrator privileges to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11096 | code-projects Task Manager newProject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11096</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Task Manager 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /newProject.php. The manipulation of the argument projectName leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42372 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (System Landscape Directory)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42372</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (System Landscape Directory) an unauthorized user can read and modify some restricted global SLD configurations causing low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47586 | NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47586</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to send a maliciously crafted http request which could cause a null pointer dereference in the kernel. This dereference will result in the system crashing and rebooting, causing the system to be temporarily unavailable. There is no impact on Confidentiality or Integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47587 | Missing authorization check in SAP Cash Management (Cash Operations)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47587</link><description>Cash Operations does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges causing low impact to confidentiality to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47588 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Java (Software Update Manager)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47588</link><description>In SAP NetWeaver Java (Software Update Manager 1.1), under certain conditions when a software upgrade encounters errors, credentials are written in plaintext to a log file. An attacker with local access to the server, authenticated as a non-administrative user, can acquire the credentials from the logs. This leads to a high impact on confidentiality, with no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47590 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Web Dispatcher</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47590</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can create a malicious link which they can make publicly available. When an authenticated victim clicks on this malicious link, input data will be used by the web site page generation to create content which when executed in the victim's browser (XXS) or transmitted to another server (SSRF) gives the attacker the ability to execute arbitrary code on the server fully compromising confidentiality, integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47592 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java (Logon Application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47592</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java allows an unauthenticated attacker to brute force the login functionality in order to identify the legitimate user IDs. This has an impact on confidentiality but not on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47593 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47593</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to read files from the server, which otherwise would be restricted.This attack is possible only if a Web Dispatcher or some sort of Proxy Server is in use and the file in question was previously opened or downloaded in an application based on SAP GUI for HTML Technology. This will not compromise the application's integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47595 | Local Privilege Escalation in SAP Host Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47595</link><description>An attacker who gains local membership to sapsys group could replace local files usually protected by privileged access. On successful exploitation the attacker could cause high impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 01:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11079 | Ansible-core: unsafe tagging bypass via hostvars object in ansible-core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11079</link><description>A flaw was found in Ansible-Core. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass unsafe content protections using the hostvars object to reference and execute templated content. This issue can lead to arbitrary code execution if remote data or module outputs are improperly templated within playbooks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23983 | Access rules for PingAccess may be circumvented with URL-encoded characters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23983</link><description>Improper handling of canonical URL-encoding may lead to bypass not properly constrained by request rules.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25253 | Driver Booster v10.6 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the Host parameter under the Customize proxy module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25253</link><description>Driver Booster v10.6 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the Host parameter under the Customize proxy module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25255 | Sublime Text 4 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the New Build System module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25255</link><description>Sublime Text 4 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the New Build System module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50601 | Persistent and reflected XSS vulnerabilities in the themeMode cookie and _h URL parameter of Axigen Mail Server up to version 10.5.28 allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50601</link><description>Persistent and reflected XSS vulnerabilities in the themeMode cookie and _h URL parameter of Axigen Mail Server up to version 10.5.28 allow attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript. Exploitation could lead to session hijacking, data leakage, and further exploitation via a multi-stage attack. Fixed in versions 10.3.3.67, 10.4.42, and 10.5.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52533 | gio/gsocks4aproxy.c in GNOME GLib before 2.82.1 has an off-by-one error and resultant buffer overflow because SOCKS4_CONN_MSG_LEN is not suf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52533</link><description>gio/gsocks4aproxy.c in GNOME GLib before 2.82.1 has an off-by-one error and resultant buffer overflow because SOCKS4_CONN_MSG_LEN is not sufficient for a trailing '\0' character.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 23:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25254 | SuperScan v4.1 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the Hostname/IP parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25254</link><description>SuperScan v4.1 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the Hostname/IP parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 22:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50636 | PyMOL 2.5.0 contains a vulnerability in its "Run Script" function, which allows the execution of arbitrary Python code embedded within .PYM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50636</link><description>PyMOL 2.5.0 contains a vulnerability in its "Run Script" function, which allows the execution of arbitrary Python code embedded within .PYM files. Attackers can craft a malicious .PYM file containing a Python reverse shell payload and exploit the function to achieve Remote Command Execution (RCE). This vulnerability arises because PyMOL treats .PYM files as Python scripts without properly validating or restricting the commands within the script, enabling attackers to run unauthorized commands in the context of the user running the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 22:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51213 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Online Shop Store v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php component...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51213</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Online Shop Store v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 22:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51026 | The NetAdmin IAM system (version 4.0.30319) has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /BalloonSave.ashx endpoint, where it is po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51026</link><description>The NetAdmin IAM system (version 4.0.30319) has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /BalloonSave.ashx endpoint, where it is possible to inject a malicious payload into the Content= field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44546 | Powerjob &gt;= 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL injection via the version parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44546</link><description>Powerjob &gt;= 3.20 is vulnerable to SQL injection via the version parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46962 | The SYQ com.downloader.video.fast (aka Master Video Downloader) application through 2.0 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46962</link><description>The SYQ com.downloader.video.fast (aka Master Video Downloader) application through 2.0 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the com.downloader.video.fast.SpeedMainAct component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46963 | The com.superfast.video.downloader (aka Super Unlimited Video Downloader - All in One) application through 5.1.9 for Android allows an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46963</link><description>The com.superfast.video.downloader (aka Super Unlimited Video Downloader - All in One) application through 5.1.9 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the com.bluesky.browser.ui.BrowserMainActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46964 | The com.video.downloader.all (aka All Video Downloader) application through 11.28 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46964</link><description>The com.video.downloader.all (aka All Video Downloader) application through 11.28 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the com.video.downloader.all.StartActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46966 | The Ikhgur mn.ikhgur.khotoch (aka Video Downloader Pro &amp; Browser) application through 1.0.42 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46966</link><description>The Ikhgur mn.ikhgur.khotoch (aka Video Downloader Pro &amp; Browser) application through 1.0.42 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the mn.ikhgur.khotoch.MainActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46965 | The DS allvideo.downloader.browser (aka Fast Video Downloader: Browser) application through 1.6-RC1 for Android allows an attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46965</link><description>The DS allvideo.downloader.browser (aka Fast Video Downloader: Browser) application through 1.6-RC1 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the allvideo.downloader.browser.DefaultBrowserActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51188 | TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51188</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the vsRule_VirtualServerName_1.1.10.0.0 parameter on the /virtual_server.htm page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51189 | TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51189</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the macList_Name_1.1.1.0.0 parameter on the /filters.htm page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51190 | TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51190</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the ptRule_ApplicationName_1.1.6.0.0 parameter on the /special_ap.htm page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51187 | TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51187</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-651BR 2.04B1, TEW-652BRP 3.04b01, and TEW-652BRU 1.00b12 devices contain a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the firewallRule_Name_1.1.1.0.0 parameter on the /firewall_setting.htm page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51484 | Insufficient Validation in Controllers (Activation/Deactivation) in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51484</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. The current implementation of token parsing fails to properly validate CSRF tokens when activating or deactivating controllers. This vulnerability allows an attacker to exploit CSRF attacks, potentially enabling them to change website features that should only be managed by administrators through malicious requests. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51485 | Insufficient Validation in Plugins (Activation/Deactivation) in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51485</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. The current implementation of token parsing fails to properly validate CSRF tokens when activating or deactivating plugins. This vulnerability allows an attacker to exploit CSRF attacks, potentially enabling them to change website features that should only be managed by administrators through malicious requests. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51486 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51486</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. The vulnerability exists in the interface section of the Ampache menu, where users can change the "Custom URL - Favicon". This section is not properly sanitized, allowing for the input of strings that can execute JavaScript. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36061 | EnGenius EWS356-FIT devices through 1.1.30 allow blind OS command injection. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands via sh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36061</link><description>EnGenius EWS356-FIT devices through 1.1.30 allow blind OS command injection. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands via shell metacharacters to the Ping and Speed Test utilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51487 | Insufficient Validation in Catalog (Activation/Deactivation) in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51487</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. The current implementation of token parsing fails to properly validate CSRF tokens when activating or deactivating catalog. This vulnerability allows an attacker to exploit CSRF attacks, potentially enabling them to change website features that should only be managed by administrators through malicious requests. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51488 | Insufficient Validation in Delete Message in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51488</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. The current implementation of token parsing does not adequately validate CSRF tokens when users delete messages. This vulnerability could be exploited to forge CSRF attacks, allowing an attacker to delete messages to any user, including administrators, if they interact with a malicious request. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51489 | Insufficient Message Token Validation in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51489</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. The current implementation of token parsing does not adequately validate CSRF tokens when users send messages to one another. This vulnerability could be exploited to forge CSRF attacks, allowing an attacker to send messages to any user, including administrators, if they interact with a malicious request. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52530 | GNOME libsoup before 3.6.0 allows HTTP request smuggling in some configurations because '\0' characters at the end of header names are ignor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52530</link><description>GNOME libsoup before 3.6.0 allows HTTP request smuggling in some configurations because '\0' characters at the end of header names are ignored, i.e., a "Transfer-Encoding\0: chunked" header is treated the same as a "Transfer-Encoding: chunked" header.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52531 | GNOME libsoup before 3.6.1 allows a buffer overflow in applications that perform conversion to UTF-8 in soup_header_parse_param_list_strict....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52531</link><description>GNOME libsoup before 3.6.1 allows a buffer overflow in applications that perform conversion to UTF-8 in soup_header_parse_param_list_strict. Input received over the network cannot trigger this.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52532 | GNOME libsoup before 3.6.1 has an infinite loop, and memory consumption. during the reading of certain patterns of WebSocket data from clien...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52532</link><description>GNOME libsoup before 3.6.1 has an infinite loop, and memory consumption. during the reading of certain patterns of WebSocket data from clients.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11078 | code-projects Job Recruitment register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11078</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument e leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48322 | An issue in the component UsersController.php of ICMC - University of So Paulo Run.Codes v1.5.2 allows attackers to bypass authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48322</link><description>An issue in the component UsersController.php of ICMC - University of So Paulo Run.Codes v1.5.2 allows attackers to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51490 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51490</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. This vulnerability exists in the interface section of the Ampache menu, where users can change "Custom URL - Logo". This section is not properly sanitized, allowing for the input of strings that can execute JavaScript. This issue has been addressed in version 7.0.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51186 | D-Link DIR-820L 1.05b03 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the ping_addr parameter in the ping_v4 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51186</link><description>D-Link DIR-820L 1.05b03 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the ping_addr parameter in the ping_v4 and ping_v6 functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51747 | Arbitrary File Read and Delete in kanboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51747</link><description>Kanboard is project management software that focuses on the Kanban methodology. An authenticated Kanboard admin can read and delete arbitrary files from the server. File attachments, that are viewable or downloadable in Kanboard are resolved through its `path` entry in the `project_has_files`  SQLite db. Thus, an attacker who can upload a modified sqlite.db through the dedicated feature, can set arbitrary file links, by abusing path traversals. Once the modified db is uploaded and the project page is accessed, a file download can be triggered and all files, readable in the context of the Kanboard application permissions, can be downloaded. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.42 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51748 | Remote code execution through language setting in kanboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51748</link><description>Kanboard is project management software that focuses on the Kanban methodology. An authenticated Kanboard admin can run arbitrary php code on the server in combination with a file write possibility. The user interface language is determined and loaded by the setting `application_language` in the `settings` table. Thus, an attacker who can upload a modified sqlite.db through the dedicated feature, has control over the filepath, which is loaded. Exploiting this vulnerability has one constraint: the attacker must be able to place a file (called translations.php) on the system. However, this is not impossible, think of anonymous FTP server or another application that allows uploading files. Once the attacker has placed its file with the actual php code as the payload, the attacker can craft a sqlite db settings, which uses path traversal to point to the directory, where the `translations.php` file is stored. Then gaining code execution after importing the crafted sqlite.db. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.42 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10315 | Insecure Configuration in Gliffy Online</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10315</link><description>In Gliffy Online an insecure configuration was discovered in versions before 4.14.0-6</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51992 | Method Exposure Vulnerability in Modals in orchid/platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51992</link><description>Orchid is a @laravel package that allows for rapid application development of back-office applications, admin/user panels, and dashboards. This vulnerability is a method exposure issue (CWE-749: Exposed Dangerous Method or Function) in the Orchid Platform’s asynchronous modal functionality, affecting users of Orchid Platform version 8 through 14.42.x. Attackers could exploit this vulnerability to call arbitrary methods within the `Screen` class, leading to potential brute force of database tables, validation checks against user credentials, and disclosure of the server’s real IP address. The issue has been patched in the latest release, version 14.43.0, released on November 6, 2024. Users should upgrade to version 14.43.0 or later to address this vulnerability. If upgrading to version 14.43.0 is not immediately possible, users can mitigate the vulnerability by implementing middleware to intercept and validate requests to asynchronous modal endpoints, allowing only approved methods and parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52286 | Self Cross Site Scripting (XSS) In Merge Functionality in  Stirling-PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52286</link><description>Stirling-PDF is a locally hosted web application that allows you to perform various operations on PDF files. In affected versions the Merge functionality takes untrusted user input (file name) and uses it directly in the creation of HTML pages allowing any unauthenticated to execute JavaScript code in the context of the user. The issue stems to the code starting at `Line 24` in `src/main/resources/static/js/merge.js`. The file name is directly being input into InnerHTML with no sanitization on the file name, allowing a malicious user to be able to upload files with names containing HTML tags. As HTML tags can include JavaScript code, this can be used to execute JavaScript code in the context of the user. This is a self-injection style attack and relies on a user uploading the malicious file themselves and it impact only them, not other users. A user might be social engineered into running this to launch a phishing attack. Nevertheless, this breaks the expected security restrictions in place by the application. This issue has been addressed in version 0.32.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52288 | RMAC revert to the beginning of the session in libosdp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52288</link><description>libosdp is an implementation of IEC 60839-11-5 OSDP (Open Supervised Device Protocol) and provides a C library with support for C++, Rust and Python3. In affected versions an unexpected `REPLY_CCRYPT` or `REPLY_RMAC_I` may be introduced into an active stream when they should not be. Once RMAC_I message can be sent during a session, attacker with MITM access to the communication may intercept the original RMAC_I reply and save it. While the session continues, the attacker will record all of the replies and save them, till capturing the message to be replied (can be detected by ID, length or time based on inspection of visual activity next to the reader) Once attacker captures a session with the message to be replayed, he stops resetting the connection and waits for signal to perform the replay to of the PD to CP message (ex: by signaling remotely to the MIMT device or setting a specific timing). In order to replay, the attacker will craft a specific RMAC_I message in the proper seq of the execution, which will result in reverting the RMAC to the beginning of the session. At that phase - attacker can replay all the messages from the beginning of the session. This issue has been addressed in commit `298576d9` which is included in release version 3.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50667 | The boa httpd of Trendnet TEW-820AP 1.01.B01 has a stack overflow vulnerability in /boafrm/formIPv6Addr, /boafrm/formIpv6Setup, /boafrm/form...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50667</link><description>The boa httpd of Trendnet TEW-820AP 1.01.B01 has a stack overflow vulnerability in /boafrm/formIPv6Addr, /boafrm/formIpv6Setup, /boafrm/formDnsv6. The reason is that the check of ipv6 address is not sufficient, which allows attackers to construct payloads for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51135 | An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the component DocumentBuilderFactory of powertac-server v1.9.0 allows attackers to access sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51135</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the component DocumentBuilderFactory of powertac-server v1.9.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information or execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted request containing malicious XML entities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 18:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11077 | code-projects Job Recruitment index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11077</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 18:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11076 | code-projects Job Recruitment activation.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11076</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /activation.php. The manipulation of the argument e_hash leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 18:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11074 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System incadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11074</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /incadd.php. The manipulation of the argument inccat/desc/date/amount leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "inccat" to be affected. But it must be assumed "desc", "date", and "amount" are affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11073 | SourceCodester Hospital Management System delete-account.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11073</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /vm/patient/delete-account.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45087 | IBM WebSphere Application Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45087</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10917 | Eclipse OpenJ9 might return an incorrect value in JNI function GetStringUTFLength</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10917</link><description>In Eclipse OpenJ9 versions up to 0.47, the JNI function GetStringUTFLength may return an incorrect value which has wrapped around. From 0.48 the value is correct but may be truncated to include a smaller number of characters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43439 | Moodle: reflected xss via h5p error message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43439</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. H5P error messages require additional sanitizing to prevent a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45088 | IBM Maximo Asset Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45088</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39354 | Delta Electronics DIAScreen Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39354</link><description>If an attacker tricks a valid user into running Delta Electronics DIAScreen with a file containing malicious code, a stack-based buffer overflow in CEtherIPTagItem can be exploited, allowing the attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39605 | Delta Electronics DIAScreen Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39605</link><description>If an attacker tricks a valid user into running Delta Electronics DIAScreen with a file containing malicious code, a stack-based buffer overflow in BACnetParameter can be exploited, allowing the attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47131 | Delta Electronics DIAScreen Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47131</link><description>If an attacker tricks a valid user into running Delta Electronics DIAScreen with a file containing malicious code, a stack-based buffer overflow in BACnetObjectInfo can be exploited, allowing the attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50989 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /omrs/admin/search.php in PHPGurukul Online Marriage Registration System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50989</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /omrs/admin/search.php in PHPGurukul Online Marriage Registration System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "searchdata " parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50991 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ums-sp/admin/registered-users.php in PHPGurukul User Management System v1.0, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50991</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ums-sp/admin/registered-users.php in PHPGurukul User Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "fname" POST request parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50990 | A Reflected Cross Site Scriptng (XSS) vulnerability was found in /omrs/user/search.php in PHPGurukul Online Marriage Registration System v1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50990</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scriptng (XSS) vulnerability was found in /omrs/user/search.php in PHPGurukul Online Marriage Registration System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchdata" POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11070 | Sanluan PublicCMS Tag Type save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11070</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Sanluan PublicCMS 5.202406.d. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/cmsTagType/save of the component Tag Type Handler. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51054 | A Cross Site Scriptng (XSS) vulnerability was found in /omrs/admin/search.php in PHPGurukul Online Marriage Registration System 1.0, which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51054</link><description>A Cross Site Scriptng (XSS) vulnerability was found in /omrs/admin/search.php in PHPGurukul Online Marriage Registration System 1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchdata" POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10314 | Unauthenticated Denial of Service via Auto Generation Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10314</link><description>In Helix Core versions prior to 2024.2, an unauthenticated remote Denial of Service (DoS) via the auto-generation function was identified.  Reported by Karol Więsek.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10344 | Unauthenticated Denial of Service via Refuse Function in Helix Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10344</link><description>In Helix Core versions prior to 2024.2, an unauthenticated remote Denial of Service (DoS) via the refuse function was identified.  Reported by Karol Więsek.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50263 | fork: only invoke khugepaged, ksm hooks if no error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50263</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fork: only invoke khugepaged, ksm hooks if no error

There is no reason to invoke these hooks early against an mm that is in an
incomplete state.

The change in commit d24062914837 ("fork: use __mt_dup() to duplicate
maple tree in dup_mmap()") makes this more pertinent as we may be in a
state where entries in the maple tree are not yet consistent.

Their placement early in dup_mmap() only appears to have been meaningful
for early error checking, and since functionally it'd require a very small
allocation to fail (in practice 'too small to fail') that'd only occur in
the most dire circumstances, meaning the fork would fail or be OOM'd in
any case.

Since both khugepaged and KSM tracking are there to provide optimisations
to memory performance rather than critical functionality, it doesn't
really matter all that much if, under such dire memory pressure, we fail
to register an mm with these.

As a result, we follow the example of commit d2081b2bf819 ("mm:
khugepaged: make khugepaged_enter() void function") and make ksm_fork() a
void function also.

We only expose the mm to these functions once we are done with them and
only if no error occurred in the fork operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10345 | Unauthenticated Denial of Service via Shutdown Function in Helix Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10345</link><description>In Helix Core versions prior to 2024.2, an unauthenticated remote Denial of Service (DoS) via the shutdown function was identified.  Reported by Karol Więsek.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 13:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34014 | Arbitrary file overwrite during recovery due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Backup plugin for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34014</link><description>Arbitrary file overwrite during recovery due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Backup plugin for cPanel &amp; WHM (Linux) before build 818, Acronis Backup extension for Plesk (Linux) before build 599, Acronis Backup plugin for DirectAdmin (Linux) before build 181.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 13:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34015 | Sensitive information disclosure during file browsing due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Backu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34015</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure during file browsing due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Backup plugin for cPanel &amp; WHM (Linux) before build 818.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 13:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43427 | Moodle: admin presets export tool includes some secrets that should not be exported</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43427</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. When creating an export of site administration presets, some sensitive secrets and keys are not being excluded from the export, which could result in them unintentionally being leaked if the presets are shared with a third party.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43429 | Moodle: user information visibility control issues in gradebook reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43429</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. Some hidden user profile fields are visible in gradebook reports, which could result in users without the "view hidden user fields" capability having access to the information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43430 | Moodle: lack of access control when using external methods for quiz overrides</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43430</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. External API access to Quiz can override contained insufficient access control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43432 | Moodle: authorization headers preserved between &amp;quot;emulated redirects&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43432</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. The cURL wrapper in Moodle strips HTTPAUTH and USERPWD headers during emulated redirects, but retains other original request headers, so HTTP authorization header information could be unintentionally sent in requests to redirect URLs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43433 | Moodle: matrix user/power level management not always working as expected with suspended users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43433</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. Matrix room membership and power levels are incorrectly applied and revoked for suspended Moodle users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43435 | Moodle: can create global glossary without being admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43435</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. Insufficient capability checks make it possible for users with access to restore glossaries in courses to restore them into the global site glossary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43437 | Moodle: xss risk when restoring malicious course backup file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43437</link><description>A flaw was found in moodle. Insufficient sanitizing of data when performing a restore could result in a cross-site scripting (XSS) risk from malicious backup files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11067 | D-Link DSL6740C - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11067</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has a Path Traversal Vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files. Additionally, since the device's default password is a combination of the MAC address, attackers can obtain the MAC address through this vulnerability and attempt to log in to the device using the default password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 08:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11068 | D-Link DSL6740C - Incorrect Use of Privileged APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11068</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has an Incorrect Use of Privileged APIs vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to modify any user’s password by leveraging the API, thereby granting access to Web, SSH, and Telnet services using that user’s account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 08:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11065 | D-Link DSL6740C - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11065</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to inject and execute arbitrary system commands through a specific functionality provided by SSH and Telnet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11066 | D-Link DSL6740C - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11066</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to inject and execute arbitrary system commands through the specific web page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11064 | D-Link DSL6740C - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11064</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to inject and execute arbitrary system commands through a specific functionality provided by SSH and Telnet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11062 | D-Link DSL6740C - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11062</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to inject and execute arbitrary system commands through a specific functionality provided by SSH and Telnet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11063 | D-Link DSL6740C - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11063</link><description>The D-Link DSL6740C modem has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to inject and execute arbitrary system commands through a specific functionality provided by SSH and Telnet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11020 | Grand Vice info Webopac7 - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11020</link><description>Webopac from Grand Vice info has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attacks to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11021 | Grand Vice info Webopac - Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11021</link><description>Webopac from Grand Vice info has Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability. Remote attackers with regular privileges can inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the server. When users visit the compromised page, the code is automatically executed in their browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11019 | Grand Vice info Webopac7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11019</link><description>Webopac from Grand Vice info has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user's browser through phishing techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11018 | Grand Vice info Webopac - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11018</link><description>Webopac from Grand Vice info does not properly validate uploaded file types, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute webshells, which could lead to arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11016 | Grand Vice info Webopac - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11016</link><description>Webopac from Grand Vice info has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attacks to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11017 | Grand Vice info Webopac - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11017</link><description>Webopac from Grand Vice info does not properly validate uploaded file types, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to upload and execute webshells, which could lead to arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52350 | WordPress CRM 2go plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52350</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CRM 2go allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects CRM 2go: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52351 | WordPress BU Slideshow plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52351</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Boston University (IS&amp;amp;T) BU Slideshow allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BU Slideshow: from n/a through 2.3.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52352 | WordPress Postcasa Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52352</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Andrew Milo Postcasa Shortcode allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Postcasa Shortcode: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52353 | WordPress Christian Science Bible Lesson Subjects plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52353</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gabriel Serafini Christian Science Bible Lesson Subjects allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Christian Science Bible Lesson Subjects: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52354 | WordPress Web Stories Widgets For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52354</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cool Plugins Web Stories Widgets For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Web Stories Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52355 | WordPress OSM – OpenStreetMap plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52355</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hyumika OSM – OpenStreetMap allows Stored XSS.This issue affects OSM – OpenStreetMap: from n/a through 6.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51788 | WordPress The Novel Design Store Directory plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51788</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Joshua Wolfe The Novel Design Store Directory allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects The Novel Design Store Directory: from n/a through 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51820 | WordPress L Squared Hub WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51820</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in L Squared Support L Squared Hub WP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects L Squared Hub WP: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51837 | WordPress WP Contest plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51837</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SONS Creative Development WP Contest allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Contest: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51843 | WordPress Horsemanager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51843</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Olland.Biz Horsemanager allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Horsemanager: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51845 | WordPress Share Buttons – Social Media plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51845</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Richteam Share Buttons – Social Media allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Share Buttons – Social Media: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51882 | WordPress Gboy Custom Google Map plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51882</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ehues Gboy Custom Google Map allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Gboy Custom Google Map: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52356 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52356</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52357 | WordPress LIQUID BLOCKS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52357</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LIQUID DESIGN Ltd. LIQUID BLOCKS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LIQUID BLOCKS: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52358 | WordPress Responsive Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52358</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cyberchimps Responsive Addons for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Responsive Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51789 | WordPress Image Classify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51789</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in UjW0L Image Classify allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Image Classify: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51790 | WordPress HB AUDIO GALLERY plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51790</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Team HB WEBSOL HB AUDIO GALLERY allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects HB AUDIO GALLERY: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51791 | WordPress Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51791</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Made I.T. Forms allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Forms: from n/a through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51792 | WordPress Audio Record plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51792</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Dang Ngoc Binh Audio Record allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Audio Record: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51793 | WordPress RepairBuddy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8115 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51793</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Webful Creations Computer Repair Shop allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Computer Repair Shop: from n/a through 3.8115.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51571 | WordPress MasterBip para Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MasterBip MasterBip para Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects MasterBip para Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51572 | WordPress LH QR Codes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.06 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51572</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Peter Shaw LH QR Codes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LH QR Codes: from n/a through 1.06.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51573 | WordPress ML Responsive Audio plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2 -  Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matthew Lillistone ML Responsive Audio player with playlist Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ML Responsive Audio player with playlist Shortcode: from n/a through 0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51574 | WordPress Simple Goods plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Simple Goods allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Goods: from n/a through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51575 | WordPress Extender All In One For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Abdullah Extender All In One For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Extender All In One For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38826 | CVE-2024-38826 Cloud Controller Denial of Service Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38826</link><description>Authenticated users can upload specifically crafted files to leak server resources. This behavior can potentially be used to run a denial of service attack against Cloud Controller.

The Cloud Foundry project recommends upgrading the following releases:

  *  Upgrade capi release version to 1.194.0 or greater
  *  Upgrade cf-deployment version to v44.1.0 or greater. This includes a patched capi release</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11061 | Tenda AC10 fast_setting_wifi_set FUN_0044db3c stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11061</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13. Affected by this vulnerability is the function FUN_0044db3c of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. The manipulation of the argument timeZone leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48939 | Insufficient validation performed on the REST API License file in Paxton Net2 before 6.07.14023.5015 (SR4) enables use of the REST API with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48939</link><description>Insufficient validation performed on the REST API License file in Paxton Net2 before 6.07.14023.5015 (SR4) enables use of the REST API with an invalid License File. Attackers may be able to retrieve access-log data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11060 | Jinher Network Collaborative Management Platform 金和数字化智能办公平台 AcceptShow.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11060</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Jinher Network Collaborative Management Platform 金和数字化智能办公平台 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /C6/JHSoft.Web.AcceptAip/AcceptShow.aspx/. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41992 | Wi-Fi Alliance wfa_dut (in Wi-Fi Test Suite) through 9.0.0 allows OS command injection via 802.11x frames because the system() library funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41992</link><description>Wi-Fi Alliance wfa_dut (in Wi-Fi Test Suite) through 9.0.0 allows OS command injection via 802.11x frames because the system() library function is used. For example, on Arcadyan FMIMG51AX000J devices, this leads to wfaTGSendPing remote code execution as root via traffic to TCP port 8000 or 8080 on a LAN interface. On other devices, this may be exploitable over a WAN interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40457 | The BGP daemon in Extreme Networks ExtremeXOS (aka EXOS) 30.7.1.1 allows an attacker (who is not on a directly connected network) to cause a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40457</link><description>The BGP daemon in Extreme Networks ExtremeXOS (aka EXOS) 30.7.1.1 allows an attacker (who is not on a directly connected network) to cause a denial of service (BGP session reset) because of BGP attribute error mishandling (for attribute 21 and 25). NOTE: the vendor disputes this because it is "evaluating support for RFC 7606 as a future feature" and believes that "customers that have chosen to not require or implement RFC 7606 have done so willingly and with knowledge of what is needed to defend against these types of attacks."</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11059 | Project Worlds Free Download Online Shopping System success.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11059</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Free Download Online Shopping System up to 192.168.1.88. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /online-shopping-webvsite-in-php-master/success.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-10370 | Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips such as CYW43455, when a 2021-01-26 Bluetooth firmware update is not present, allow a Bl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10370</link><description>Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips such as CYW43455, when a 2021-01-26 Bluetooth firmware update is not present, allow a Bluetooth outage via a "Spectra" attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-10367 | Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips, when a January 2021 firmware update is not present, allow memory access via a "Spectra"...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10367</link><description>Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips, when a January 2021 firmware update is not present, allow memory access via a "Spectra" attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-10368 | Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips, when a January 2021 firmware update is not present, allow memory read access via a "Spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10368</link><description>Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips, when a January 2021 firmware update is not present, allow memory read access via a "Spectra" attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-10369 | Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips, when a January 2021 firmware update is not present, allow inferences about memory conte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10369</link><description>Certain Cypress (and Broadcom) Wireless Combo chips, when a January 2021 firmware update is not present, allow inferences about memory content via a "Spectra" attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11058 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System About Us Page aboutedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11058</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /aboutedit.php of the component About Us Page. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35473 | An issue was discovered in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.0.12. There is a missing expiration check in the OAuth2.0 handler, i.e., it does not verif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35473</link><description>An issue was discovered in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.0.12. There is a missing expiration check in the OAuth2.0 handler, i.e., it does not verify access token validity. An attacker can use a expired access token from an OIDC client to access the OAuth2 handler The earliest affected version is 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-41737 | In Faust 2.23.1, an input file with the lines "// r visualisation tCst" and "//process = +: L: abM-^Q;" and "process = route(333333333333333...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41737</link><description>In Faust 2.23.1, an input file with the lines "// r visualisation tCst" and "//process = +: L: abM-^Q;" and "process = route(3333333333333333333,2,1,2,3,1) : *;" leads to stack consumption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46956 | An issue was discovered in psi/zfile.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. Out-of-bounds data access in filenameforall can lead to arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46956</link><description>An issue was discovered in psi/zfile.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. Out-of-bounds data access in filenameforall can lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46952 | An issue was discovered in pdf/pdf_xref.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. There is a buffer overflow during handling of a PDF XRef st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46952</link><description>An issue was discovered in pdf/pdf_xref.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. There is a buffer overflow during handling of a PDF XRef stream (related to W array values).</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46953 | An issue was discovered in base/gsdevice.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. An integer overflow when parsing the filename format strin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46953</link><description>An issue was discovered in base/gsdevice.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. An integer overflow when parsing the filename format string (for the output filename) results in path truncation, and possible path traversal and code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46954 | An issue was discovered in decode_utf8 in base/gp_utf8.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. Overlong UTF-8 encoding leads to possible .....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46954</link><description>An issue was discovered in decode_utf8 in base/gp_utf8.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. Overlong UTF-8 encoding leads to possible ../ directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46955 | An issue was discovered in psi/zcolor.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. There is an out-of-bounds read when reading color in Indexed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46955</link><description>An issue was discovered in psi/zcolor.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. There is an out-of-bounds read when reading color in Indexed color space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46951 | An issue was discovered in psi/zcolor.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. An unchecked Implementation pointer in Pattern color space co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46951</link><description>An issue was discovered in psi/zcolor.c in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.04.0. An unchecked Implementation pointer in Pattern color space could lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46613 | WeeChat before 4.4.2 has an integer overflow and resultant buffer overflow at core/core-string.c when there are more than two billion items ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46613</link><description>WeeChat before 4.4.2 has an integer overflow and resultant buffer overflow at core/core-string.c when there are more than two billion items in a list. This affects string_free_split_shared , string_free_split, string_free_split_command, and string_free_split_tags.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11057 | Codezips Hospital Appointment System removeBranchResult.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11057</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Codezips Hospital Appointment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /removeBranchResult.php. The manipulation of the argument ID/Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11056 | Tenda AC10 WifiExtraSet FUN_0046AC38 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11056</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13. Affected is the function FUN_0046AC38 of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11055 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11055</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument adminname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10265 | Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.15.30 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via add_query_arg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10265</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.30. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10958 | WP Photo Album Plus &amp;lt;= 8.8.08.007 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via getshortcodedrenderedfenodelay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10958</link><description>The The WP Photo Album Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via getshortcodedrenderedfenodelay AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.08.007 . This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51576 | WordPress AMP Img Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51576</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPZA AMP Img Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AMP Img Shortcode: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11054 | SourceCodester Simple Music Cloud Community System ajax.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11054</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple Music Cloud Community System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /music/ajax.php?action=signup. The manipulation of the argument pp leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51577 | WordPress bpmn.io plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51577</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Camunda Services GmbH bpmn.Io allows Stored XSS.This issue affects bpmn.Io: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51578 | WordPress 3D Presentation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51578</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Luca Paggetti 3D Presentation allows Stored XSS.This issue affects 3D Presentation: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51580 | WordPress Clever Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51580</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CleverSoft Clever Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Clever Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51581 | WordPress Restaurant &amp;amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51581</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Restaurant &amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Restaurant &amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51583 | WordPress Kento Ads Rotator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51583</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in KentoThemes Kento Ads Rotator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kento Ads Rotator: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51584 | WordPress Marquee Elementor with Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51584</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Anas Edreesi Marquee Elementor with Posts allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Marquee Elementor with Posts: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11051 | AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System online_status.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11051</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System up to 3.0.3.151204. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manager/frontdesk/online_status.php. The manipulation of the argument AccountID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11050 | AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System language.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11050</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System up to 3.0.3.151204 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /language.php. The manipulation of the argument LangID/LangName/LangEName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11049 | ZKTeco ZKBio Time Image File photo direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11049</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ZKTeco ZKBio Time 9.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /auth_files/photo/ of the component Image File Handler. The manipulation leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11048 | D-Link DI-8003 dbsrv.asp dbsrv_asp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11048</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8003 16.07.16A1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function dbsrv_asp of the file /dbsrv.asp. The manipulation of the argument str leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11047 | D-Link DI-8003 upgrade_filter.asp upgrade_filter_asp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11047</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8003 16.07.16A1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upgrade_filter_asp of the file /upgrade_filter.asp. The manipulation of the argument path leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11046 | D-Link DI-8003 upgrade_filter.asp upgrade_filter_asp os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11046</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8003 16.07.16A1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function upgrade_filter_asp of the file /upgrade_filter.asp. The manipulation of the argument path leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>