<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 04:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-13262 | lsfusion platform UploadFileRequestHandler.java UploadFileRequestHandler path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13262</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in lsfusion platform up to 6.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function UploadFileRequestHandler of the file platform/web-client/src/main/java/lsfusion/http/controller/file/UploadFileRequestHandler.java. Executing manipulation of the argument sid can lead to path traversal. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 04:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13261 | lsfusion platform DownloadFileRequestHandler.java DownloadFileRequestHandler path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13261</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lsfusion platform up to 6.1. Affected is the function DownloadFileRequestHandler of the file web-client/src/main/java/lsfusion/http/controller/file/DownloadFileRequestHandler.java. Performing manipulation of the argument Version results in path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13283 | Chunghwa Telecom｜TenderDocTransfer - Arbitrary File Copy and Paste</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13283</link><description>TenderDocTransfer developed by Chunghwa Telecom has a Arbitrary File Copy and Paste vulnerability.  The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection in the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability. Attackers can copy arbitrary files on the user's system and paste them into any path, which poses a potential risk of information leakage or could consume hard drive space by copying files in large volumes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13284 | ThinPLUS｜ThinPLUS - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13284</link><description>ThinPLUS developed by ThinPLUS has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13260 | Campcodes Supplier Management System edit_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13260</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /manufacturer/edit_product.php. Such manipulation of the argument cmbProductUnit leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13282 | Chunghwa Telecom｜TenderDocTransfer - Arbitrary File Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13282</link><description>TenderDocTransfer developed by Chunghwa Telecom has a Arbitrary File Delete vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection in the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to delete arbitrary files on the user's system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10460 | Unsanitized parameter input leading to SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10460</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability on an endpoint in BEIMS Contractor Web, a legacy product that is no longer maintained or patched by the vendor, allows an unauthorised user to retrieve sensitive database contents via unsanitized parameter input. This vulnerability occurs due to improper input validation on /BEIMSWeb/contractor.asp endpoint and successful exploitation requires a contractor.asp endpoint open to the internet. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands, compromising the confidentiality, integrity and potentially the availability of the database. 





Version 5.7.139

 has been confirmed as vulnerable. Other versions have not been confirmed by the vendor and users should assume that all versions of BEIMS Contractor Web may be impacted until further guidance is provided by the vendor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13259 | Campcodes Supplier Management System edit_unit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13259</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /manufacturer/edit_unit.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13258 | Tenda AC20 WifiExtraSet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13258</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC20 up to 16.03.08.12. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13257 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13257</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/user/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:04:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13256 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System borrow.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13256</link><description>A weakness has been identified in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /borrow.php. Executing manipulation of the argument roll_number can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13254 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System add_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13254</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add_member.php. Such manipulation of the argument roll_number leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13255 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System book_search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13255</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /book_search.php. Performing manipulation of the argument book_pub/book_title results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13253 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System add_librarian.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13253</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add_librarian.php. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13252 | shsuishang ShopSuite ModulithShop RSA/OAuth2/Database hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13252</link><description>A vulnerability was found in shsuishang ShopSuite ModulithShop up to 45a99398cec3b7ad7ff9383694f0b53339f2d35a. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component RSA/OAuth2/Database. The manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13251 | WeiYe-Jing datax-web sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13251</link><description>A flaw has been found in WeiYe-Jing datax-web up to 2.1.2. Affected is an unknown function. Executing manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13250 | WeiYe-Jing datax-web Job triggerJob access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13250</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in WeiYe-Jing datax-web up to 2.1.2. This impacts the function remove/update/pause/start/triggerJob of the component Job Handler. Performing manipulation results in improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13249 | Jiusi OA OfficeServer unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13249</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Jiusi OA up to 20251102. This affects an unknown function of the file /OfficeServer?isAjaxDownloadTemplate=false of the component OfficeServer Interface. Such manipulation of the argument FileData leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13248 | SourceCodester Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System api_patient_schedule.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13248</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /php/api_patient_schedule.php. This manipulation of the argument appointmentID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13247 | PHPGurukul Tourism Management System user-bookings.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13247</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Tourism Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/user-bookings.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13246 | shsuishang ShopSuite ModulithShop JwtAuthenticationFilter.java JwtAuthenticationFilter path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13246</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in shsuishang ShopSuite ModulithShop up to 45a99398cec3b7ad7ff9383694f0b53339f2d35a. Impacted is the function JwtAuthenticationFilter of the file src/main/java/com/suisung/shopsuite/common/security/JwtAuthenticationFilter.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13245 | code-projects Student Information System editprofile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13245</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Student Information System 2.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /editprofile.php. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 09:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13244 | code-projects Student Information System register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13244</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Student Information System 2.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /register.php. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13243 | code-projects Student Information System editprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13243</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Information System 2.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /editprofile.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13242 | code-projects Student Information System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13242</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Student Information System 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /register.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13241 | code-projects Student Information System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13241</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Student Information System 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 07:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13240 | code-projects Student Information System searchquery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13240</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Student Information System 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /searchquery.php. Performing manipulation of the argument s results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 06:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13239 | Bdtask/CodeCanyon Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution submit_checkout behavioral workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13239</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Bdtask/CodeCanyon Isshue Multi Store eCommerce Shopping Cart Solution 5. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /submit_checkout. Such manipulation of the argument order_total_amount/cart_total_amount leads to enforcement of behavioral workflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 06:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13238 | Bdtask Flight Booking Software Edit Profile edit unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13238</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Bdtask Flight Booking Software 4. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /agent/profile/edit of the component Edit Profile Page. This manipulation causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13237 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System LogSignModal.PHP sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13237</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /LogSignModal.PHP. The manipulation of the argument U_USERNAME results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 05:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12482 | Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia &amp;lt;= 1.2.35 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12482</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘search’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.35 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 04:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13236 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13236</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/products/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 04:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13235 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13235</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/login.php. Executing manipulation of the argument user_email can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13233 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13233</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /index.php?q=single-item. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13234 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13234</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /index.php?q=product. Performing manipulation of the argument PROID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13232 | projectsend File Editor/Custom Download Aliases cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13232</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectsend up to r1720. Impacted is an unknown function of the component File Editor/Custom Download Aliases. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version r1945 is recommended to address this issue. Patch name: 334da1ea39cb12f6b6e98dd2f80bb033e0c7b845. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 02:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13221 | Intelbras UnniTI usuarios.xml credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13221</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Intelbras UnniTI 24.07.11. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /xml/sistema/usuarios.xml. Executing manipulation of the argument Usuario/Senha can lead to unprotected storage of credentials. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13210 | itsourcecode Inventory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13210</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Inventory Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/products/index.php?view=add. Such manipulation of the argument PROMODEL leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13209 | bestfeng oa_git_free WorkflowPredefineController.java updateWriteBack xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13209</link><description>A weakness has been identified in bestfeng oa_git_free up to 9.5. This affects the function updateWriteBack of the file yimioa-oa9.5\server\c-flow\src\main\java\com\cloudweb\oa\controller\WorkflowPredefineController.java. This manipulation of the argument writeProp causes xml external entity reference. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13208 | FantasticLBP Hotels Server hotelList.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13208</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FantasticLBP Hotels Server up to 67b44df162fab26df209bd5d5d542875fcbec1d0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file controller/api/hotelList.php. The manipulation of the argument subjectId/cityName results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13203 | code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System addmem.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13203</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /addmem.php. Executing manipulation of the argument studentnum can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13202 | code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System add_to_cart cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13202</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add_to_cart. Performing manipulation of the argument product_name results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13201 | code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13201</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Cafe Ordering System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13200 | SourceCodester Farm Management System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13200</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. This manipulation causes exposure of information through directory listing. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13199 | code-projects Email Logging Interface signup.cpp path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13199</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Email Logging Interface 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file signup.cpp. The manipulation of the argument Username results in path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 10:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13198 | DouPHP file.class.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13198</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DouPHP up to 1.8 Release 20251022. This impacts an unknown function of the file upload/include/file.class.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 09:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12983 | Memory Allocation with Excessive Size Value in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12983</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.9 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition by submitting specially crafted markdown content with nested formatting patterns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11865 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11865</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.1 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that, under certain circumstances, could have allowed an attacker to remove Duo flows of another user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11990 | Improper Handling of URL Encoding (Hex Encoding) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11990</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated user to gain CSRF tokens by exploiting improper input validation in repository references combined with redirect handling weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2615 | Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2615</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.7  before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2, that could have allowed a blocked user to access sensitive information by establishing GraphQL subscriptions through WebSocket connections.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6171 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6171</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker with reporter access to view branch names and pipeline details by accessing the packages API endpoint even when repository access was disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6945 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (&amp;#x27;Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6945</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.8 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to leak sensitive information from confidential issues by injecting hidden prompts into merge request comments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7000 | Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7000</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions  from 17.6  before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2, that, under specific conditions, could have allowed unauthorized users to view confidential branch names by accessing project issues with related merge requests.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7736 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7736</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.9 before 18.3.6, 18.4 before 18.4.4, and 18.5 before 18.5.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to bypass access control restrictions and view GitLab Pages content intended only for project members by authenticating through OAuth providers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13191 | D-Link DIR-816L soap.cgi soapcgi_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13191</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. This issue affects the function soapcgi_main of the file /soap.cgi. This manipulation causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 07:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12849 | Contest Gallery &amp;lt;= 28.0.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12849</link><description>The Contest Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 28.0.2. This is due to the plugin registering the `cg_check_wp_admin_upload_v10` AJAX action for both authenticated and unauthenticated users without implementing capability checks or nonce verification. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary WordPress media attachments into galleries and manipulate gallery metadata via the `cg_check_wp_admin_upload_v10` action. It does not enable an attacker to move or upload files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13190 | D-Link DIR-816L __ajax_exporer.sgi scandir_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13190</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. This vulnerability affects the function scandir_main of the file /portal/__ajax_exporer.sgi. The manipulation of the argument en results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13189 | D-Link DIR-816L gena.cgi genacgi_main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13189</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-816L 2_06_b09_beta. This affects the function genacgi_main of the file gena.cgi. The manipulation of the argument SERVER_ID/HTTP_SID leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12494 | Image Gallery – Photo Grid &amp;amp; Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.12.28 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Image File Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12494</link><description>The Image Gallery – Photo Grid &amp; Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the ajax_import_file function in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.28. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to move arbitrary image files on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12847 | All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp;amp; Increase Traffic &amp;lt;= 4.8.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Media Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12847</link><description>The All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp; Increase Traffic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary media attachment deletion due to a missing authorization check in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.9. This is due to the REST API endpoint `/wp-json/aioseo/v1/ai/image-generator` only verifying that users have the `edit_posts` capability (Contributors and above) without checking if they own or have permission to delete the specific media attachments. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to permanently delete arbitrary media attachments by ID via the REST API, granted they can determine valid attachment IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8994 | WP Project Manager &amp;lt;= 2.6.26 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;completed_at_operator&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8994</link><description>The Project Management, Team Collaboration, Kanban Board, Gantt Charts, Task Manager and More – WP Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘completed_at_operator’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.26 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12182 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Attachment Resize</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12182</link><description>The Qi Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the `resize_image_callback()` function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user has permission to resize a specific attachment. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to resize arbitrary media library images belonging to other users, which can result in unintended file writes, disk consumption, and server resource abuse through processing of large images.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 03:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8386 | AVEVA Application Server IDE Basic Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8386</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(with privilege of "aaConfigTools") to tamper with App Objects' help 
files and persist a cross-site scripting (XSS) injection that when 
executed by a victim user, can result in horizontal or vertical 
escalation of privileges. The vulnerability can only be exploited during
 config-time operations within the IDE component of Application Server. 
Run-time components and operations are not affected.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>