<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10247 | YouTube Gallery and Vimeo Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10247</link><description>The Video Gallery – Best WordPress YouTube Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the orderby parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10836 | Flixita &amp;lt;= 1.0.82 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10836</link><description>The Flixita theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.82 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9769 | Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9769</link><description>The Video Gallery – Best WordPress YouTube Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11149 | OpenBSD vmm GDTR limits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11149</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.4 before errata 014, vmm(4) did not restore GDTR limits properly on Intel (VMX) CPUs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49041 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49041</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6156 | Mark Laing discovered that LXD's PKI mode, until version 5.21.2, could be bypassed if the client's certificate was present in the trust stor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6156</link><description>Mark Laing discovered that LXD's PKI mode, until version 5.21.2, could be bypassed if the client's certificate was present in the trust store.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6219 | Mark Laing discovered in LXD's PKI mode, until version 5.21.1, that a restricted certificate could be added to the trust store with its rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6219</link><description>Mark Laing discovered in LXD's PKI mode, until version 5.21.1, that a restricted certificate could be added to the trust store with its restrictions not honoured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37861 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the nav2_amcl proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37861</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via sending a crafted .yaml file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37862 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotic Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2- ROS2-humble&amp;&amp; navigation2-humble allows a local a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37862</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotic Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2- ROS2-humble&amp;&amp; navigation2-humble allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .yaml file to the nav2_planner process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37863 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the nav2_amcl proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37863</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via sending a crafted .yaml file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38910 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble version was discovered to contain a use-after-free in the nav2_amcl process....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38910</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble version was discovered to contain a use-after-free in the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via sending a request to change dynamic parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38920 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38920</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggerd via remotely sending a request for change the value of dynamic-parameter`/amcl max_beams` .</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30962 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allows a l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30962</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the nav2_amcl process</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30963 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allows a l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30963</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30964 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30964</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the initial_pose_sub thread created by nav2_bt_navigator</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37860 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2- ROS2-humble&amp;&amp; navigation2-humble allows a local attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37860</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Open Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2- ROS2-humble&amp;&amp; navigation2-humble allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .yaml file to the nav2_amcl process</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30961 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30961</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) navigation2- ROS2-humble and navigation 2-humble allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the error-thrown mechanism in nav2_bt_navigator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52798 | path-to-regexp Unpatched `path-to-regexp` ReDoS in 0.1.x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52798</link><description>path-to-regexp turns path strings into a regular expressions. In certain cases, path-to-regexp will output a regular expression that can be exploited to cause poor performance. The regular expression that is vulnerable to backtracking can be generated in the 0.1.x release of path-to-regexp. Upgrade to 0.1.12. This vulnerability exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-45296.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9386 | In reboot_block_command of htc reboot_block driver, there is a possible
    stack buffer overflow due to a missing bounds check. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9386</link><description>In reboot_block_command of htc reboot_block driver, there is a possible
    stack buffer overflow due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to
    local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User
    interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9388 | In store_upgrade and store_cmd of drivers/input/touchscreen/stm/ftm4_pdc.c, there are out of bound writes due to missing bounds checks or in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9388</link><description>In store_upgrade and store_cmd of drivers/input/touchscreen/stm/ftm4_pdc.c, there are out of bound writes due to missing bounds checks or integer underflows. These could lead to escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9390 | In procfile_write of gl_proc.c, there is a possible out of  bounds read of a
    function pointer due to an incorrect bounds check. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9390</link><description>In procfile_write of gl_proc.c, there is a possible out of  bounds read of a
    function pointer due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local
    escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User
    interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9391 | In update_gps_sv and output_vzw_debug of
    vendor/mediatek/proprietary/hardware/connectivity/gps/gps_hal/src/gpshal_wor
    ker.c, there i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9391</link><description>In update_gps_sv and output_vzw_debug of
    vendor/mediatek/proprietary/hardware/connectivity/gps/gps_hal/src/gpshal_wor
    ker.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds
    check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System
    execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for
    exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13308 | In tscpu_write_GPIO_out and mtkts_Abts_write of mtk_ts_Abts.c, there is a possible buffer overflow in an sscanf due to improper input valida...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13308</link><description>In tscpu_write_GPIO_out and mtkts_Abts_write of mtk_ts_Abts.c, there is a possible buffer overflow in an sscanf due to improper input validation. This could lead to a local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54140 | sigstore-java has a vulnerability with bundle verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54140</link><description>sigstore-java is a sigstore java client for interacting with sigstore infrastructure. sigstore-java has insufficient verification for a situation where a bundle provides a invalid signature for a checkpoint. This bug impacts clients using any variation of KeylessVerifier.verify(). Currently checkpoints are only used to ensure the root hash of an inclusion proof was provided by the log in question. Failing to validate that means a bundle may provide an inclusion proof that doesn't actually correspond to the log in question. This may eventually lead a monitor/witness being unable to detect when a compromised logs are providing different views of themselves to different clients. There are other mechanisms right now that mitigate this, such as the signed entry timestamp. Sigstore-java currently requires a valid signed entry timestamp. By correctly verifying the signed entry timestamp we can make certain assertions about the log signing the log entry (like the log was aware of the artifact signing event and signed it). Therefore the impact on clients that are not monitors/witnesses is very low. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53457 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Device Settings section of LibreNMS v24.9.0 to v24.10.0 allows attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53457</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Device Settings section of LibreNMS v24.9.0 to v24.10.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Display Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53523 | JSFinder commit d70ab9bc5221e016c08cffaf0d9ac79646c90645 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in the find_by_file function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53523</link><description>JSFinder commit d70ab9bc5221e016c08cffaf0d9ac79646c90645 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in the find_by_file function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 20:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10933 | OpenBSD readdir directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10933</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.5 before errata 009 and OpenBSD 7.4 before errata 022, exclude any '/' in readdir name validation to avoid unexpected directory traversal on untrusted file systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53589 | GNU objdump 2.43 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the BFD (Binary File Descriptor) library's handling of tekhex format files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53589</link><description>GNU objdump 2.43 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the BFD (Binary File Descriptor) library's handling of tekhex format files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53442 | whapa v1.59 is vulnerable to Command Injection via a crafted filename to the HTML reports component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53442</link><description>whapa v1.59 is vulnerable to Command Injection via a crafted filename to the HTML reports component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48010 | STMicroelectronics SPC58 is vulnerable to Missing Protection Mechanism for Alternate Hardware Interface. Code running as Supervisor on the S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48010</link><description>STMicroelectronics SPC58 is vulnerable to Missing Protection Mechanism for Alternate Hardware Interface. Code running as Supervisor on the SPC58 PowerPC microcontrollers may disable the System Memory Protection Unit and gain unabridged read/write access to protected assets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11148 | OpenBSD httpd(8) null dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11148</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.4 before errata 006 and OpenBSD 7.3 before errata 020, httpd(8) is vulnerable to a NULL dereference when handling a malformed fastcgi request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50913 | Oxide control plane software before 5 allows SSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50913</link><description>Oxide control plane software before 5 allows SSRF.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41579 | DTStack Taier 1.4.0 allows remote attackers to specify the jobName parameter in the console listNames function to cause a SQL injection vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41579</link><description>DTStack Taier 1.4.0 allows remote attackers to specify the jobName parameter in the console listNames function to cause a SQL injection vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12130 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Out of Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12130</link><description>An “out of bounds read” code execution vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Arena®

 that could allow a threat actor to craft a DOE file and force the software to read beyond the boundaries of an allocated memory. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11158 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Uninitialized Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11158</link><description>An “uninitialized variable” code execution vulnerability exists in the 

Rockwell Automation Arena®

 that could allow a threat actor to craft a DOE file and force the software to access a variable before it being initialized. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11155 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Code Execution Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11155</link><description>A “use after free”  code execution vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Arena® that could allow a threat actor to craft a DOE file and force the software to use a resource that was already used. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11156 | Rockwell Automation Arena® Out of Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11156</link><description>An “out of bounds write”  code execution vulnerability exists in the

Rockwell Automation Arena®

 that could allow a threat actor to write beyond the boundaries of allocated memory in a DOE file. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12235 | Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM AuthorizationTokenCheckFilter.java doFilter access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12235</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM up to 1.0.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function doFilter of the file \agile-bpm-basic-master\ab-auth\ab-auth-spring-security-oauth2\src\main\java\com\dstz\auth\filter\AuthorizationTokenCheckFilter.java. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12234 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System edit-customer-detailed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12234</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-customer-detailed.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53846 | ssl fails to validate incorrect extened key usage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53846</link><description>OTP is a set of Erlang libraries, which consists of the Erlang runtime system, a number of ready-to-use components mainly written in Erlang, and a set of design principles for Erlang programs. A regression was introduced into the ssl application of OTP starting at OTP-25.3.2.8, OTP-26.2, and OTP-27.0, resulting in a server or client verifying the peer when incorrect extended key usage is presented (i.e., a server will verify a client if they have server auth ext key usage and vice versa).</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54128 | Directus has an HTML Injection in Comment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54128</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. The Comment feature has implemented a filter to prevent users from adding restricted characters, such as HTML tags. However, this filter operates on the client-side, which can be bypassed, making the application vulnerable to HTML Injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53490 | Favorites-web 1.3.0 favorites-web has a directory traversal vulnerability in SecurityFilter.java.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53490</link><description>Favorites-web 1.3.0 favorites-web has a directory traversal vulnerability in SecurityFilter.java.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12233 | code-projects Online Notice Board Profile Picture registration.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12233</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Notice Board up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /registration.php of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12231 | CodeZips Project Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12231</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeZips Project Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12232 | code-projects Simple CRUD Functionality index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12232</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple CRUD Functionality 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument newtitle/newdescr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53470 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /configuracao/gateway_pagamento.php of WeGIA v3.2.0 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53470</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /configuracao/gateway_pagamento.php of WeGIA v3.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the id or name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53471 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /configuracao/meio_pagamento.php of WeGIA v3.2.0 allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53471</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /configuracao/meio_pagamento.php of WeGIA v3.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the id or name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10716 | Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.2.1 are affected by an XSS issue with search.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10716</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.2.1 are affected by an XSS issue with search.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12247 | Improper propagation of permission scheme updates across cluster nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12247</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.2 and 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.2 fail to properly propagate permission scheme updates across cluster nodes which allows a user to keep old permissions, even if the permission scheme has been updated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53472 | WeGIA v3.2.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53472</link><description>WeGIA v3.2.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53856 | rPGP Panics on Malformed Untrusted Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53856</link><description>rPGP is a pure Rust implementation of OpenPGP. Prior to 0.14.1, rPGP allows an attacker to trigger rpgp crashes by providing crafted data. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53857 | rPGP Potential Resource Exhaustion when handling Untrusted Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53857</link><description>rPGP is a pure Rust implementation of OpenPGP. Prior to 0.14.1, rPGP allows attackers to trigger resource exhaustion vulnerabilities in rpgp by providing crafted messages. This affects general message parsing and decryption with symmetric keys.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54001 | Kanboard allows a persistent HTML injection site scripting in settings page date format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54001</link><description>Kanboard is project management software that focuses on the Kanban methodology. HTML can be injected and stored into the application settings section. The fields application_language, application_date_format,application_timezone and application_time_format allow arbirary user input which is reflected. The vulnerability can become xss if the user input is javascript code that bypass CSP. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.41.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54129 | Improper Initialization of `imc` Scheme Leading to `SIGABRT` in ION-DTN BPv7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54129</link><description>The NASA’s Interplanetary Overlay Network (ION) is an implementation of Delay/Disruption Tolerant Networking (DTN). A vulnerability exists in the version ION-DTN BPv7 implementation version 4.1.3 when receiving a bundle with an improper reference to the imc scheme with valid Service-Specific Part (SSP) in their Previous Node Block. The vulnerability can cause ION to become unresponsive. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.1.3s.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54130 | Segmentation Fault in `forwardBundle` Function of ION-DTN BPv7 When Destination EID is `dtn:none` (public)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54130</link><description>The NASA’s Interplanetary Overlay Network (ION) is an implementation of Delay/Disruption Tolerant Networking (DTN). A segmentation fault occurs with ION-DTN BPv7 software version 4.1.3 when a bundle with a Destination Endpoint ID (EID) set to dtn:none is received. This causes the node to become unresponsive to incoming bundles, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.1.3s.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11941 | Drupal core - Moderately critical - Denial of Service - SA-CORE-2024-001</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11941</link><description>A vulnerability in Drupal Core allows Excessive Allocation.This issue affects Drupal Core: from 10.2.0 before 10.2.2, from 10.1.0 before 10.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11942 | Drupal core - Moderately critical - Improper error handling - SA-CORE-2024-002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11942</link><description>A vulnerability in Drupal Core allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Drupal Core: from 10.0.0 before 10.2.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12229 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System complaint-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12229</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/complaint-search.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12230 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System subcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12230</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54679 | CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 6778ad1 does not require the FilemanagerAdmin capability for restartMySQL actions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54679</link><description>CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 6778ad1 does not require the FilemanagerAdmin capability for restartMySQL actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53703 | A vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN firmware 10.2.1.13-72sv and earlier versions mod_httprp library loaded by the Apache web serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53703</link><description>A vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN firmware 10.2.1.13-72sv and earlier versions mod_httprp library loaded by the Apache web server allows remote attackers to cause Stack-based buffer overflow and potentially lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45319 | A vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN 

firmware 10.2.1.13-72sv and earlier versions allows a remote authenticated attacker can cir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45319</link><description>A vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN 

firmware 10.2.1.13-72sv and earlier versions allows a remote authenticated attacker can circumvent the certificate requirement during authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52271 | PDF Document Spoofing in Documenso</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52271</link><description>User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in Documenso allows Content Spoofing.Displayed version does not show the layer flattened version, once download, If printed (e.g. via Google Chrome -&gt; Examine the print preview): Will render the vulnerability only, not all layers are flattened.


This issue affects Documenso: through 1.8.0, &gt;1.8.0 and Documenso SaaS (Hosted) as of 2024-12-05.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53702 | Use of cryptographically weak pseudo-random number generator (PRNG) vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN backup code generator that,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53702</link><description>Use of cryptographically weak pseudo-random number generator (PRNG) vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN backup code generator that, in certain cases, can be predicted by an attacker, potentially exposing the generated secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45318 | A vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN web management interface allows remote attackers to cause Stack-based buffer overflow and pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45318</link><description>A vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN web management interface allows remote attackers to cause Stack-based buffer overflow and potentially lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40763 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN due to the use of strcpy. This allows remote authenticated attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40763</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicWall SMA100 SSLVPN due to the use of strcpy. This allows remote authenticated attackers to cause Heap-based buffer overflow and potentially lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12227 | MSI Dragon Center IOCTL NTIOLib_X64.sys MmUnMapIoSpace null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12227</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MSI Dragon Center up to 2.0.146.0. This affects the function MmUnMapIoSpace in the library NTIOLib_X64.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Upgrading to version 2.0.148.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12228 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System user-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12228</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/user-search.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51548 | Dangerous File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51548</link><description>Dangerous File Upload vulnerabilities allow upload of malicious scripts. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51549 | Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51549</link><description>Absolute File Traversal  vulnerabilities allows access and modification of un-intended resources. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51550 | Data Validation / Sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51550</link><description>Data Validation / Data Sanitization  vulnerabilities in Linux allows unvalidated and unsanitized data to be injected in an Aspect device. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51551 | Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51551</link><description>Default Credentail vulnerabilities in ASPECT on Linux allows access to the product using publicly available default credentials. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.07.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.07.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.07.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51554 | off-by-one-error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51554</link><description>Default Credentail vulnerabilities in ASPECT on Linux allows access to the product using publicly available default credentials. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51555 | Force Change of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51555</link><description>Default Credentail vulnerabilities allows access to an Aspect device using publicly available default credentials since the system does not require the installer to change default credentials. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.07.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.07.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.07.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11317 | PHP Session Fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11317</link><description>Session Fixation vulnerabilities allow an attacker to fix a users session identifier before login providing an opportunity for session takeover on a product. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48839 | Remote Code Execution, RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48839</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability allows Remote Code Execution. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48840 | Unauthorized Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48840</link><description>Unauthorized Access vulnerabilities allow Remote Code Execution. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48843 | Denial of Service, DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48843</link><description>Denial of Service vulnerabilities where found providing a potiential for device service disruptions. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48844 | Denial of Service, DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48844</link><description>Denial of Service vulnerabilities where found providing a potiential for device service disruptions. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48845 | Weak Password Rules/Strength</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48845</link><description>Weak Password  Reset Rules vulnerabilities where found providing a potiential for the storage of weak passwords that could  facilitate unauthorized admin/application access. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.07.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.07.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.07.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48846 | Cross Side Request Forgery, CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48846</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerabilities where found providing a potiential for exposing sensitive information or changing system settings. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48847 | MD5 bypass operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48847</link><description>MD5 Checksum Bypass vulnerabilities where found exploiting a weakness in the way an application dependency calculates or validates MD5 checksum hashes. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.01; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.01; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.01</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51541 | Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51541</link><description>Local File Inclusion vulnerabilities allow access to sensitive system information. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51542 | Configuration Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51542</link><description>Configuration Download vulnerabilities allow access to dependency configuration information. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51543 | Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51543</link><description>Information Disclosure vulnerabilities allow access to application configuration information. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51544 | Service Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51544</link><description>Service Control vulnerabilities allow access to service restart requests and vm configuration settings. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51545 | Username Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51545</link><description>Username Enumeration vulnerabilities allow access to application level username add, delete, modify and list functions. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51546 | Credentails Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51546</link><description>Credentials Disclosure vulnerabilities allow access to on board project back-up bundles. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11316 | Filesize Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11316</link><description>Fileszie Check vulnerabilities allow a malicious user to bypass size limits or overload to the product. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12094 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Tinxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12094</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Tinxy mobile app due to storage of logged-in user information in plaintext on the device database. An attacker with physical access to the rooted device could exploit this vulnerability by accessing its database leading to unauthorized access of user information such as username, email address and mobile number.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54127 | Exposure of Wi-Fi Credentials in Plaintext in TP-Link Archer C50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54127</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the TP-Link Archer C50 due to presence of terminal access on a serial interface without proper access control. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by accessing the UART shell on the vulnerable device. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to obtain Wi-Fi credentials of the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6515 | unauthorized file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6515</link><description>Web browser interface may manipulate application username/password in clear text or Base64 encoding providing a higher probability of  unintended credentails exposure. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6516 | Cross Site Scripting XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6516</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities where found providing a potential for malicious scripts to be injected into a client browser. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6784 | SSRF Server Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6784</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerabilities were found providing a potential for access to unauthorized resources and unintended information disclosure. 
Affected products:


ABB ASPECT - Enterprise v3.08.02; 
NEXUS Series v3.08.02; 
MATRIX Series v3.08.02</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54126 | Insufficient Integrity Verification Vulnerability in TP-Link Archer C50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54126</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the TP-Link Archer C50 due to improper signature verification mechanism in the firmware upgrade process at its web interface. An attacker with administrative privileges within the router’s Wi-Fi range could exploit this vulnerability by uploading and executing malicious firmware which could lead to complete compromise of the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52270 | PDF Document Spoofing in DropBox Sign(HelloSign)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52270</link><description>User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in DropBox Sign(HelloSign) allows Content Spoofing.
Displayed version does not show the layer flattened version, once download, If printed (e.g. via Google Chrome -&gt; Examine the print preview): Will render the vulnerability only, not all layers are flattened.
This issue affects DropBox Sign(HelloSign): through 2024-12-04.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 11:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41137 | Apache Hive: Deserialization of untrusted data when fetching partitions from the Metastore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41137</link><description>Apache Hive Metastore (HMS) uses SerializationUtilities#deserializeObjectWithTypeInformation method when filtering and fetching partitions that is unsafe and can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) since it allows the deserialization of arbitrary data.

In real deployments, the vulnerability can be exploited only by authenticated users/clients that were able to successfully establish a connection to the Metastore. From an API perspective any code that calls the unsafe method may be vulnerable unless it performs additional prerechecks on the input arguments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 10:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45841 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in UD-LT1 firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier and UD-LT1/EX firmware Ver.2.1.8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45841</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in UD-LT1 firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier and UD-LT1/EX firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier. If an attacker with the guest account of the affected products accesses a specific file, the information containing credentials may be obtained.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47133 | UD-LT1 firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier and UD-LT1/EX firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier allow a remote authenticated attacker with an administrat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47133</link><description>UD-LT1 firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier and UD-LT1/EX firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier allow a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative account to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52564 | Inclusion of undocumented features or chicken bits issue exists in UD-LT1 firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier and UD-LT1/EX firmware Ver.2.1.8 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52564</link><description>Inclusion of undocumented features or chicken bits issue exists in UD-LT1 firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier and UD-LT1/EX firmware Ver.2.1.8 and earlier. A remote attacker may disable the firewall function of the affected products. As a result, an arbitrary OS command may be executed and/or configuration settings of the device may be altered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10056 | Contact Form Builder &amp;lt;= 4.10.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via livesite-pay Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10056</link><description>The Contact Form Builder by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's livesite-pay shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10777 | AnyWhere Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10777</link><description>The AnyWhere Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.11 via the 'INSERT_ELEMENTOR' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10848 | NewsMunch &amp;lt;= 1.0.35 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10848</link><description>The NewsMunch theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a malicious display name in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11324 | Accounting for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11324</link><description>The Accounting for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11341 | Simple Redirection &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Site Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11341</link><description>The Simple Redirection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and redirect all site visitors via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11420 | Blocksy &amp;lt;= 2.0.77 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11420</link><description>The Blocksy theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Contact Info Block link parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.77 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11779 | WIP WooCarousel Lite &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11779</link><description>The WIP WooCarousel Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wip_woocarousel_products_carousel' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10937 | Related Posts, Inline Related Posts, Contextual Related Posts, Related Content By PickPlugins &amp;lt;= 2.0.58 - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10937</link><description>The Related Posts, Inline Related Posts, Contextual Related Posts, Related Content By PickPlugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.58 via the wp_ajax_nopriv_related_post_ajax_get_post_ids AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including titles of posts in draft status.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 08:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11429 | Free Responsive Testimonials, Social Proof Reviews, and Customer Reviews – Stars Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11429</link><description>The Free Responsive Testimonials, Social Proof Reviews, and Customer Reviews – Stars Testimonials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.3 via the 'stars-testimonials-with-slider-and-masonry-grid' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 05:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42195 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is vulnerable to HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42195</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is vulnerable to HTML injection. This vulnerability may allow a user to embed arbitrary HTML tags in the Web UI potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 04:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10178 | Gutentor – Gutenberg Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp;lt;= 3.3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10178</link><description>The Gutentor – Gutenberg Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 04:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10881 | LUNA RADIO PLAYER &amp;lt;= 6.24.11.07 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10881</link><description>The LUNA RADIO PLAYER plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'lunaradio' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 6.24.11.07 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54014 | Improper authorization in handler for custom URL scheme issue in 'Skylark' App for Android 6.2.13 and earlier and 'Skylark' App for iOS 6.2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54014</link><description>Improper authorization in handler for custom URL scheme issue in 'Skylark' App for Android 6.2.13 and earlier and 'Skylark' App for iOS 6.2.13 and earlier allows an attacker to lead the application to access an arbitrary web site via another application installed on the user's device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12187 | 1000 Projects Library Management System showbook.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Library Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /showbook.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 01:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12188 | 1000 Projects Library Management System stu.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12188</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Library Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /brains/stu.php. The manipulation of the argument useri leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 01:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9408 | In m3326_gps_write and m3326_gps_read of gps.s, there is a possible Out Of
    Bounds Read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9408</link><description>In m3326_gps_write and m3326_gps_read of gps.s, there is a possible Out Of
    Bounds Read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to a local
    information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User
    interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9416 | In sg_remove_scat of scsi/sg.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to
    an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9416</link><description>In sg_remove_scat of scsi/sg.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to
    an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with
    System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for
    exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9439 | In __unregister_prot_hook and packet_release of af_packet.c, there is a
    possible use-after-free due to improper locking. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9439</link><description>In __unregister_prot_hook and packet_release of af_packet.c, there is a
    possible use-after-free due to improper locking. This could lead to local
    escalation of privilege in the kernel with System execution privileges
    needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9462 | In store_cmd of ftm4_pdc.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to
    an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9462</link><description>In store_cmd of ftm4_pdc.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to
    an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege
    with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for
    exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9463 | In sw49408_irq_runtime_engine_debug of touch_sw49408.c, there is a possible
    out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9463</link><description>In sw49408_irq_runtime_engine_debug of touch_sw49408.c, there is a possible
    out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to
    local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User
    interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9402 | In multiple functions of gl_proc.c, there is a buffer overwrite due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to escalation of privileges i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9402</link><description>In multiple functions of gl_proc.c, there is a buffer overwrite due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to escalation of privileges in the kernel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9403 | In the MTK_FLP_MSG_HAL_DIAG_REPORT_DATA_NTF handler of flp2hal_-
    interface.c, there is a possible stack buffer overflow due to a missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9403</link><description>In the MTK_FLP_MSG_HAL_DIAG_REPORT_DATA_NTF handler of flp2hal_-
    interface.c, there is a possible stack buffer overflow due to a missing
    bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in a
    privileged process with System execution privileges needed. User interaction
    is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9404 | In oemCallback of ril.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an
    integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9404</link><description>In oemCallback of ril.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an
    integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with
    System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for
    exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9407 | In emmc_rpmb_ioctl of emmc_rpmb.c, there is an Information Disclosure due to a Missing Bounds Check. This could lead to  Information Disclos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9407</link><description>In emmc_rpmb_ioctl of emmc_rpmb.c, there is an Information Disclosure due to a Missing Bounds Check. This could lead to  Information Disclosure of kernel data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12185 | code-projects Hotel Management System Administrator Login Password stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12185</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Hotel Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Administrator Login Password Handler. The manipulation of the argument Str2 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12186 | code-projects Hotel Management System Available Room hotelnew.c stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hotel Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file hotelnew.c of the component Available Room Handler. The manipulation of the argument admin_entry leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54221 | WordPress FAT Services Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54221</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Roninwp FAT Services Booking.This issue affects FAT Services Booking: from n/a through 5.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9397 | In WMT_unlocked_ioctl of MTK WMT device driver, there is a possible OOB
    write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9397</link><description>In WMT_unlocked_ioctl of MTK WMT device driver, there is a possible OOB
    write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of
    privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not
    needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9398 | In fm_set_stat of mediatek FM radio driver, there is a possible OOB write
    due to improper input validation. This could lead to local esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9398</link><description>In fm_set_stat of mediatek FM radio driver, there is a possible OOB write
    due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of
    privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not
    needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9399 | In /proc/driver/wmt_dbg driver, there are several possible out of bounds
    writes. These could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9399</link><description>In /proc/driver/wmt_dbg driver, there are several possible out of bounds
    writes. These could lead to local escalation of privilege with System
    execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for
    exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9400 | In gt1x_debug_write_proc and gt1x_tool_write of
    drivers/input/touchscreen/mediatek/GT1151/gt1x_generic.c and gt1x_tools.c,
    there is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9400</link><description>In gt1x_debug_write_proc and gt1x_tool_write of
    drivers/input/touchscreen/mediatek/GT1151/gt1x_generic.c and gt1x_tools.c,
    there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This
    could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges
    needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12183 | DedeCMS HTTP POST Request carbuyaction.php RemoveXSS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12183</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DedeCMS 5.7.116. This affects the function RemoveXSS of the file /plus/carbuyaction.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12182 | DedeCMS soft_add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12182</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in DedeCMS 5.7.116. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /member/soft_add.php. The manipulation of the argument body leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 22:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53982 | Arbitrary file download in Zoo-Project Echo Example</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53982</link><description>ZOO-Project is a C-based WPS (Web Processing Service) implementation. A path traversal vulnerability was discovered in Zoo-Project Echo example. The Echo example available by default in Zoo installs implements file caching, which can be controlled by user-given parameters. No input validation is performed in this parameter, which allows an attacker to fully control the file which is returned in the response. Patch was committed in November 22nd, 2024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 22:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9396 | In rpc_msg_handler and related handlers of drivers/misc/mediatek/eccci/port_rpc.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9396</link><description>In rpc_msg_handler and related handlers of drivers/misc/mediatek/eccci/port_rpc.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 22:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12180 | DedeCMS article_add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12180</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DedeCMS 5.7.116. Affected is an unknown function of the file /member/article_add.php. The manipulation of the argument body leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 22:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12181 | DedeCMS SWF File uploads_add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12181</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in DedeCMS 5.7.116. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /member/uploads_add.php of the component SWF File Handler. The manipulation of the argument mediatype leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 22:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38829 | Spring LDAP sensitive data exposure for case-sensitive comparisons</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38829</link><description>A vulnerability in VMware Tanzu Spring LDAP allows data exposure for case sensitive comparisons.This issue affects Spring LDAP: from 2.4.0 through 2.4.3, from 3.0.0 through 3.0.9, from 3.1.0 through 3.1.7, from 3.2.0 through 3.2.7, AND all versions prior to 2.4.0.

The usage of String.toLowerCase() and String.toUpperCase() has some Locale dependent exceptions that could potentially result in unintended columns from being queried
Related to  CVE-2024-38820 https://spring.io/security/cve-2024-38820</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 21:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39219 | An issue in Aginode GigaSwitch V5 before version 7.06G allows authenticated attackers with Administrator privileges to upload an earlier fir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39219</link><description>An issue in Aginode GigaSwitch V5 before version 7.06G allows authenticated attackers with Administrator privileges to upload an earlier firmware version, exposing the device to previously patched vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50947 | An issue in kmqtt v0.2.7 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50947</link><description>An issue in kmqtt v0.2.7 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51210 | Firepad through 1.5.11 allows remote attackers, who have knowledge of a pad ID, to retrieve both the current text of a document and all cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51210</link><description>Firepad through 1.5.11 allows remote attackers, who have knowledge of a pad ID, to retrieve both the current text of a document and all content that has previously been pasted into the document. NOTE: in several similar products, this is the intentional behavior for anyone who knows the full document ID and corresponding URL. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54674 | app/View/GalaxyClusters/cluster_export_misp_galaxy.ctp in MISP through 2.5.2 has stored XSS when exporting custom clusters into the misp-gal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54674</link><description>app/View/GalaxyClusters/cluster_export_misp_galaxy.ctp in MISP through 2.5.2 has stored XSS when exporting custom clusters into the misp-galaxy format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54675 | app/webroot/js/workflows-editor/workflows-editor.js in MISP through 2.5.2 has stored XSS in the editor interface for an ad-hoc workflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54675</link><description>app/webroot/js/workflows-editor/workflows-editor.js in MISP through 2.5.2 has stored XSS in the editor interface for an ad-hoc workflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48453 | An issue in INOVANCE AM401_CPU1608TPTN allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ExecuteUserProgramUpgrade function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48453</link><description>An issue in INOVANCE AM401_CPU1608TPTN allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ExecuteUserProgramUpgrade function</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12147 | Netgear R6900 HTTP Header upgrade_check.cgi buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R6900 1.0.1.26_1.0.20. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file upgrade_check.cgi of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9392 | In get_binary of vendor/mediatek/proprietary/hardware/connectivity/gps/gps_hal/src/data_coder.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9392</link><description>In get_binary of vendor/mediatek/proprietary/hardware/connectivity/gps/gps_hal/src/data_coder.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9393 | In procfile_write of drivers/misc/mediatek/connectivity/wlan/gen2/os/linux/gl_proc.c, there is a possible OOB write due to a missing bounds ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9393</link><description>In procfile_write of drivers/misc/mediatek/connectivity/wlan/gen2/os/linux/gl_proc.c, there is a possible OOB write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9394 | In mtk_p2p_wext_set_key of drivers/misc/mediatek/connectivity/wlan/gen2/os/linux/gl_p2p.c, there is a possible OOB write due to improper inp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9394</link><description>In mtk_p2p_wext_set_key of drivers/misc/mediatek/connectivity/wlan/gen2/os/linux/gl_p2p.c, there is a possible OOB write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9395 | In mtk_cfg80211_vendor_packet_keep_alive_start and mtk_cfg80211_vendor_set_config of drivers/misc/mediatek/connectivity/wlan/gen2/os/linux/g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9395</link><description>In mtk_cfg80211_vendor_packet_keep_alive_start and mtk_cfg80211_vendor_set_config of drivers/misc/mediatek/connectivity/wlan/gen2/os/linux/gl_vendor.c, there is a possible OOB write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12148 | Incorrect authorization in permission validation component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.6.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12148</link><description>Incorrect authorization in permission validation component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.6.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to access some reporting endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12149 | Incorrect permission assignment in temporary access requests component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.19.0 and earlier on Wind...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12149</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment in temporary access requests component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.19.0 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user that request temporary permissions on an entry to obtain more privileges than requested.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12151 | Incorrect permission assignment in the user migration feature in Devolutions Server 2024.3.8.0 and earlier allows users to retain their old ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12151</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment in the user migration feature in Devolutions Server 2024.3.8.0 and earlier allows users to retain their old permission sets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12196 | Incorrect authorization in the permission component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.7.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to view the pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12196</link><description>Incorrect authorization in the permission component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.7.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to view the password history of an entry without the view password permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39163 | binux pyspider up to v0.3.10 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the Flask endpoints.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39163</link><description>binux pyspider up to v0.3.10 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the Flask endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52676 | Itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum Project v.1.0.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /bcc_forum/members/home.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52676</link><description>Itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum Project v.1.0.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /bcc_forum/members/home.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20397 | Cisco NX-OS Software Image Verification Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20397</link><description>A vulnerability in the bootloader of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to an affected device, or an authenticated, local attacker with administrative credentials, to bypass NX-OS image signature verification.

This vulnerability is due to insecure bootloader settings. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing a series of bootloader commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass NX-OS image signature verification and load unverified software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53614 | A hardcoded decryption key in Thinkware Cloud APK v4.3.46 allows attackers to access sensitive data and execute arbitrary commands with elev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53614</link><description>A hardcoded decryption key in Thinkware Cloud APK v4.3.46 allows attackers to access sensitive data and execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37574 | The GriceMobile com.grice.call application 4.5.2 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone calls wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37574</link><description>The GriceMobile com.grice.call application 4.5.2 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone calls without user interaction by sending a crafted intent via the com.iui.mobile.presentation.MobileActivity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37575 | The Mister org.mistergroup.shouldianswer application 1.4.264 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37575</link><description>The Mister org.mistergroup.shouldianswer application 1.4.264 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone calls without user interaction by sending a crafted intent via the org.mistergroup.shouldianswer.ui.default_dialer.DefaultDialerActivity component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54002 | Dependency-Track allows enumeration of managed users via /api/v1/user/login endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54002</link><description>Dependency-Track is a Component Analysis platform that allows organizations to identify and reduce risk in the software supply chain. Performing a login request against the /api/v1/user/login endpoint with a username that exist in the system takes significantly longer than performing the same action with a username that is not known by the system. The observable difference in request duration can be leveraged by actors to enumerate valid names of managed users. LDAP and OpenID Connect users are not affected. The issue has been fixed in Dependency-Track 4.12.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11643 | Accessibility by AllAccessible &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11643</link><description>The Accessibility by AllAccessible plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'AllAccessible_save_settings' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54132 | GitHub CLI allows downloading malicious GitHub Actions workflow artifact to result in path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54132</link><description>The GitHub CLI is GitHub’s official command line tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in GitHub CLI that could create or overwrite files in unintended directories when users download a malicious GitHub Actions workflow artifact through gh run download. This vulnerability stems from a GitHub Actions workflow artifact named .. when downloaded using gh run download. The artifact name and --dir flag are used to determine the artifact’s download path. When the artifact is named .., the resulting files within the artifact are extracted exactly 1 directory higher than the specified --dir flag value. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.63.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54134 | @solana/web3.js modified package published to npm, containing malware that exfiltrates private key material</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54134</link><description>A publish-access account was compromised for `@solana/web3.js`, a JavaScript library that is commonly used by Solana dapps. This allowed an attacker to publish unauthorized and malicious packages that were modified, allowing them to steal private key material and drain funds from dapps, like bots, that handle private keys directly. This issue should not affect non-custodial wallets, as they generally do not expose private keys during transactions. This is not an issue with the Solana protocol itself, but with a specific JavaScript client library and only appears to affect projects that directly handle private keys and that updated within the window of 3:20pm UTC and 8:25pm UTC on Tuesday, December 3, 2024. These two unauthorized versions (1.95.6 and 1.95.7) were caught within hours and have since been unpublished. All Solana app developers should upgrade to version 1.95.8. Developers that suspect they might be compromised should rotate any suspect authority keys, including multisigs, program authorities, server keypairs, and so on.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40744 | Extension - tassos.gr - Unrestricted file upload in Convert Forms component for Joomla &amp;lt; 4.4.6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40744</link><description>Unrestricted file upload via security bypass in Convert Forms component for Joomla in versions before 4.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40745 | Extension - tassos.gr - Reflected Cross site scripting vulnerability in Convert Forms component for Joomla &amp;lt; 4.4.6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40745</link><description>Reflected Cross site scripting vulnerability in Convert Forms component for Joomla in versions before 4.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12056 | Client Secret not checked with OAuth Password grant type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12056</link><description>The Client secret is not checked when using the OAuth Password grant type.

By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker could connect to a web server using a client application not explicitly authorized as part of the OAuth deployment.
Exploitation requires valid credentials and does not permit the attacker to bypass user privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53126 | vdpa: solidrun: Fix UB bug with devres</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53126</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vdpa: solidrun: Fix UB bug with devres

In psnet_open_pf_bar() and snet_open_vf_bar() a string later passed to
pcim_iomap_regions() is placed on the stack. Neither
pcim_iomap_regions() nor the functions it calls copy that string.

Should the string later ever be used, this, consequently, causes
undefined behavior since the stack frame will by then have disappeared.

Fix the bug by allocating the strings on the heap through
devm_kasprintf().</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53127 | Revert &amp;quot;mmc: dw_mmc: Fix IDMAC operation with pages bigger than 4K&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53127</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "mmc: dw_mmc: Fix IDMAC operation with pages bigger than 4K"

The commit 8396c793ffdf ("mmc: dw_mmc: Fix IDMAC operation with pages
bigger than 4K") increased the max_req_size, even for 4K pages, causing
various issues:
- Panic booting the kernel/rootfs from an SD card on Rockchip RK3566
- Panic booting the kernel/rootfs from an SD card on StarFive JH7100
- "swiotlb buffer is full" and data corruption on StarFive JH7110

At this stage no fix have been found, so it's probably better to just
revert the change.

This reverts commit 8396c793ffdf28bb8aee7cfe0891080f8cab7890.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53128 | sched/task_stack: fix object_is_on_stack() for KASAN tagged pointers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53128</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sched/task_stack: fix object_is_on_stack() for KASAN tagged pointers

When CONFIG_KASAN_SW_TAGS and CONFIG_KASAN_STACK are enabled, the
object_is_on_stack() function may produce incorrect results due to the
presence of tags in the obj pointer, while the stack pointer does not have
tags.  This discrepancy can lead to incorrect stack object detection and
subsequently trigger warnings if CONFIG_DEBUG_OBJECTS is also enabled.

Example of the warning:

ODEBUG: object 3eff800082ea7bb0 is NOT on stack ffff800082ea0000, but annotated.
------------[ cut here ]------------
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 1 at lib/debugobjects.c:557 __debug_object_init+0x330/0x364
Modules linked in:
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 1 Comm: swapper/0 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc5 #4
Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
pstate: 600000c5 (nZCv daIF -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : __debug_object_init+0x330/0x364
lr : __debug_object_init+0x330/0x364
sp : ffff800082ea7b40
x29: ffff800082ea7b40 x28: 98ff0000c0164518 x27: 98ff0000c0164534
x26: ffff800082d93ec8 x25: 0000000000000001 x24: 1cff0000c00172a0
x23: 0000000000000000 x22: ffff800082d93ed0 x21: ffff800081a24418
x20: 3eff800082ea7bb0 x19: efff800000000000 x18: 0000000000000000
x17: 00000000000000ff x16: 0000000000000047 x15: 206b63617473206e
x14: 0000000000000018 x13: ffff800082ea7780 x12: 0ffff800082ea78e
x11: 0ffff800082ea790 x10: 0ffff800082ea79d x9 : 34d77febe173e800
x8 : 34d77febe173e800 x7 : 0000000000000001 x6 : 0000000000000001
x5 : feff800082ea74b8 x4 : ffff800082870a90 x3 : ffff80008018d3c4
x2 : 0000000000000001 x1 : ffff800082858810 x0 : 0000000000000050
Call trace:
 __debug_object_init+0x330/0x364
 debug_object_init_on_stack+0x30/0x3c
 schedule_hrtimeout_range_clock+0xac/0x26c
 schedule_hrtimeout+0x1c/0x30
 wait_task_inactive+0x1d4/0x25c
 kthread_bind_mask+0x28/0x98
 init_rescuer+0x1e8/0x280
 workqueue_init+0x1a0/0x3cc
 kernel_init_freeable+0x118/0x200
 kernel_init+0x28/0x1f0
 ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
ODEBUG: object 3eff800082ea7bb0 is NOT on stack ffff800082ea0000, but annotated.
------------[ cut here ]------------</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53129 | drm/rockchip: vop: Fix a dereferenced before check warning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53129</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/rockchip: vop: Fix a dereferenced before check warning

The 'state' can't be NULL, we should check crtc_state.

Fix warning:
drivers/gpu/drm/rockchip/rockchip_drm_vop.c:1096
vop_plane_atomic_async_check() warn: variable dereferenced before check
'state' (see line 1077)</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53130 | nilfs2: fix null-ptr-deref in block_dirty_buffer tracepoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53130</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix null-ptr-deref in block_dirty_buffer tracepoint

When using the "block:block_dirty_buffer" tracepoint, mark_buffer_dirty()
may cause a NULL pointer dereference, or a general protection fault when
KASAN is enabled.

This happens because, since the tracepoint was added in
mark_buffer_dirty(), it references the dev_t member bh-&gt;b_bdev-&gt;bd_dev
regardless of whether the buffer head has a pointer to a block_device
structure.

In the current implementation, nilfs_grab_buffer(), which grabs a buffer
to read (or create) a block of metadata, including b-tree node blocks,
does not set the block device, but instead does so only if the buffer is
not in the "uptodate" state for each of its caller block reading
functions.  However, if the uptodate flag is set on a folio/page, and the
buffer heads are detached from it by try_to_free_buffers(), and new buffer
heads are then attached by create_empty_buffers(), the uptodate flag may
be restored to each buffer without the block device being set to
bh-&gt;b_bdev, and mark_buffer_dirty() may be called later in that state,
resulting in the bug mentioned above.

Fix this issue by making nilfs_grab_buffer() always set the block device
of the super block structure to the buffer head, regardless of the state
of the buffer's uptodate flag.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53131 | nilfs2: fix null-ptr-deref in block_touch_buffer tracepoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53131</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix null-ptr-deref in block_touch_buffer tracepoint

Patch series "nilfs2: fix null-ptr-deref bugs on block tracepoints".

This series fixes null pointer dereference bugs that occur when using
nilfs2 and two block-related tracepoints.


This patch (of 2):

It has been reported that when using "block:block_touch_buffer"
tracepoint, touch_buffer() called from __nilfs_get_folio_block() causes a
NULL pointer dereference, or a general protection fault when KASAN is
enabled.

This happens because since the tracepoint was added in touch_buffer(), it
references the dev_t member bh-&gt;b_bdev-&gt;bd_dev regardless of whether the
buffer head has a pointer to a block_device structure.  In the current
implementation, the block_device structure is set after the function
returns to the caller.

Here, touch_buffer() is used to mark the folio/page that owns the buffer
head as accessed, but the common search helper for folio/page used by the
caller function was optimized to mark the folio/page as accessed when it
was reimplemented a long time ago, eliminating the need to call
touch_buffer() here in the first place.

So this solves the issue by eliminating the touch_buffer() call itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53132 | drm/xe/oa: Fix &amp;quot;Missing outer runtime PM protection&amp;quot; warning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53132</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/oa: Fix "Missing outer runtime PM protection" warning

Fix the following drm_WARN:

[953.586396] xe 0000:00:02.0: [drm] Missing outer runtime PM protection
...
&lt;4&gt; [953.587090]  ? xe_pm_runtime_get_noresume+0x8d/0xa0 [xe]
&lt;4&gt; [953.587208]  guc_exec_queue_add_msg+0x28/0x130 [xe]
&lt;4&gt; [953.587319]  guc_exec_queue_fini+0x3a/0x40 [xe]
&lt;4&gt; [953.587425]  xe_exec_queue_destroy+0xb3/0xf0 [xe]
&lt;4&gt; [953.587515]  xe_oa_release+0x9c/0xc0 [xe]

(cherry picked from commit b107c63d2953907908fd0cafb0e543b3c3167b75)</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53133 | drm/amd/display: Handle dml allocation failure to avoid crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53133</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Handle dml allocation failure to avoid crash

[Why]
In the case where a dml allocation fails for any reason, the
current state's dml contexts would no longer be valid. Then
subsequent calls dc_state_copy_internal would shallow copy
invalid memory and if the new state was released, a double
free would occur.

[How]
Reset dml pointers in new_state to NULL and avoid invalid
pointer

(cherry picked from commit bcafdc61529a48f6f06355d78eb41b3aeda5296c)</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53134 | pmdomain: imx93-blk-ctrl: correct remove path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53134</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pmdomain: imx93-blk-ctrl: correct remove path

The check condition should be 'i &lt; bc-&gt;onecell_data.num_domains', not
'bc-&gt;onecell_data.num_domains' which will make the look never finish
and cause kernel panic.

Also disable runtime to address
"imx93-blk-ctrl 4ac10000.system-controller: Unbalanced pm_runtime_enable!"</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53135 | KVM: VMX: Bury Intel PT virtualization (guest/host mode) behind CONFIG_BROKEN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53135</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: VMX: Bury Intel PT virtualization (guest/host mode) behind CONFIG_BROKEN

Hide KVM's pt_mode module param behind CONFIG_BROKEN, i.e. disable support
for virtualizing Intel PT via guest/host mode unless BROKEN=y.  There are
myriad bugs in the implementation, some of which are fatal to the guest,
and others which put the stability and health of the host at risk.

For guest fatalities, the most glaring issue is that KVM fails to ensure
tracing is disabled, and *stays* disabled prior to VM-Enter, which is
necessary as hardware disallows loading (the guest's) RTIT_CTL if tracing
is enabled (enforced via a VMX consistency check).  Per the SDM:

  If the logical processor is operating with Intel PT enabled (if
  IA32_RTIT_CTL.TraceEn = 1) at the time of VM entry, the "load
  IA32_RTIT_CTL" VM-entry control must be 0.

On the host side, KVM doesn't validate the guest CPUID configuration
provided by userspace, and even worse, uses the guest configuration to
decide what MSRs to save/load at VM-Enter and VM-Exit.  E.g. configuring
guest CPUID to enumerate more address ranges than are supported in hardware
will result in KVM trying to passthrough, save, and load non-existent MSRs,
which generates a variety of WARNs, ToPA ERRORs in the host, a potential
deadlock, etc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53136 | mm: revert &amp;quot;mm: shmem: fix data-race in shmem_getattr()&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53136</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: revert "mm: shmem: fix data-race in shmem_getattr()"

Revert d949d1d14fa2 ("mm: shmem: fix data-race in shmem_getattr()") as
suggested by Chuck [1].  It is causing deadlocks when accessing tmpfs over
NFS.

As Hugh commented, "added just to silence a syzbot sanitizer splat: added
where there has never been any practical problem".</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53137 | ARM: fix cacheflush with PAN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53137</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ARM: fix cacheflush with PAN

It seems that the cacheflush syscall got broken when PAN for LPAE was
implemented. User access was not enabled around the cache maintenance
instructions, causing them to fault.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53138 | net/mlx5e: kTLS, Fix incorrect page refcounting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53138</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5e: kTLS, Fix incorrect page refcounting

The kTLS tx handling code is using a mix of get_page() and
page_ref_inc() APIs to increment the page reference. But on the release
path (mlx5e_ktls_tx_handle_resync_dump_comp()), only put_page() is used.

This is an issue when using pages from large folios: the get_page()
references are stored on the folio page while the page_ref_inc()
references are stored directly in the given page. On release the folio
page will be dereferenced too many times.

This was found while doing kTLS testing with sendfile() + ZC when the
served file was read from NFS on a kernel with NFS large folios support
(commit 49b29a573da8 ("nfs: add support for large folios")).</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53139 | sctp: fix possible UAF in sctp_v6_available()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53139</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sctp: fix possible UAF in sctp_v6_available()

A lockdep report [1] with CONFIG_PROVE_RCU_LIST=y hints
that sctp_v6_available() is calling dev_get_by_index_rcu()
and ipv6_chk_addr() without holding rcu.

[1]
 =============================
 WARNING: suspicious RCU usage
 6.12.0-rc5-virtme #1216 Tainted: G        W
 -----------------------------
 net/core/dev.c:876 RCU-list traversed in non-reader section!!

other info that might help us debug this:

rcu_scheduler_active = 2, debug_locks = 1
 1 lock held by sctp_hello/31495:
 #0: ffff9f1ebbdb7418 (sk_lock-AF_INET6){+.+.}-{0:0}, at: sctp_bind (./arch/x86/include/asm/jump_label.h:27 net/sctp/socket.c:315) sctp

stack backtrace:
 CPU: 7 UID: 0 PID: 31495 Comm: sctp_hello Tainted: G        W          6.12.0-rc5-virtme #1216
 Tainted: [W]=WARN
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
 Call Trace:
  
 dump_stack_lvl (lib/dump_stack.c:123)
 lockdep_rcu_suspicious (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:6822)
 dev_get_by_index_rcu (net/core/dev.c:876 (discriminator 7))
 sctp_v6_available (net/sctp/ipv6.c:701) sctp
 sctp_do_bind (net/sctp/socket.c:400 (discriminator 1)) sctp
 sctp_bind (net/sctp/socket.c:320) sctp
 inet6_bind_sk (net/ipv6/af_inet6.c:465)
 ? security_socket_bind (security/security.c:4581 (discriminator 1))
 __sys_bind (net/socket.c:1848 net/socket.c:1869)
 ? do_user_addr_fault (./include/linux/rcupdate.h:347 ./include/linux/rcupdate.h:880 ./include/linux/mm.h:729 arch/x86/mm/fault.c:1340)
 ? do_user_addr_fault (./arch/x86/include/asm/preempt.h:84 (discriminator 13) ./include/linux/rcupdate.h:98 (discriminator 13) ./include/linux/rcupdate.h:882 (discriminator 13) ./include/linux/mm.h:729 (discriminator 13) arch/x86/mm/fault.c:1340 (discriminator 13))
 __x64_sys_bind (net/socket.c:1877 (discriminator 1) net/socket.c:1875 (discriminator 1) net/socket.c:1875 (discriminator 1))
 do_syscall_64 (arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 (discriminator 1) arch/x86/entry/common.c:83 (discriminator 1))
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe (arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:130)
 RIP: 0033:0x7f59b934a1e7
 Code: 44 00 00 48 8b 15 39 8c 0c 00 f7 d8 64 89 02 b8 ff ff ff ff eb bd 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 00 b8 31 00 00 00 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 8b 0d 09 8c 0c 00 f7 d8 64 89 01 48
All code
========
   0:	44 00 00             	add    %r8b,(%rax)
   3:	48 8b 15 39 8c 0c 00 	mov    0xc8c39(%rip),%rdx        # 0xc8c43
   a:	f7 d8                	neg    %eax
   c:	64 89 02             	mov    %eax,%fs:(%rdx)
   f:	b8 ff ff ff ff       	mov    $0xffffffff,%eax
  14:	eb bd                	jmp    0xffffffffffffffd3
  16:	66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 	cs nopw 0x0(%rax,%rax,1)
  1d:	00 00 00
  20:	0f 1f 00             	nopl   (%rax)
  23:	b8 31 00 00 00       	mov    $0x31,%eax
  28:	0f 05                	syscall
  2a:*	48 3d 01 f0 ff ff    	cmp    $0xfffffffffffff001,%rax		&lt;-- trapping instruction
  30:	73 01                	jae    0x33
  32:	c3                   	ret
  33:	48 8b 0d 09 8c 0c 00 	mov    0xc8c09(%rip),%rcx        # 0xc8c43
  3a:	f7 d8                	neg    %eax
  3c:	64 89 01             	mov    %eax,%fs:(%rcx)
  3f:	48                   	rex.W

Code starting with the faulting instruction
===========================================
   0:	48 3d 01 f0 ff ff    	cmp    $0xfffffffffffff001,%rax
   6:	73 01                	jae    0x9
   8:	c3                   	ret
   9:	48 8b 0d 09 8c 0c 00 	mov    0xc8c09(%rip),%rcx        # 0xc8c19
  10:	f7 d8                	neg    %eax
  12:	64 89 01             	mov    %eax,%fs:(%rcx)
  15:	48                   	rex.W
 RSP: 002b:00007ffe2d0ad398 EFLAGS: 00000202 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000031
 RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007ffe2d0ad3d0 RCX: 00007f59b934a1e7
 RDX: 000000000000001c RSI: 00007ffe2d0ad3d0 RDI: 0000000000000005
 RBP: 0000000000000005 R08: 1999999999999999 R09: 0000000000000000
 R10: 00007f59b9253298 R11: 000000000000
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53140 | netlink: terminate outstanding dump on socket close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53140</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netlink: terminate outstanding dump on socket close

Netlink supports iterative dumping of data. It provides the families
the following ops:
 - start - (optional) kicks off the dumping process
 - dump  - actual dump helper, keeps getting called until it returns 0
 - done  - (optional) pairs with .start, can be used for cleanup
The whole process is asynchronous and the repeated calls to .dump
don't actually happen in a tight loop, but rather are triggered
in response to recvmsg() on the socket.

This gives the user full control over the dump, but also means that
the user can close the socket without getting to the end of the dump.
To make sure .start is always paired with .done we check if there
is an ongoing dump before freeing the socket, and if so call .done.

The complication is that sockets can get freed from BH and .done
is allowed to sleep. So we use a workqueue to defer the call, when
needed.

Unfortunately this does not work correctly. What we defer is not
the cleanup but rather releasing a reference on the socket.
We have no guarantee that we own the last reference, if someone
else holds the socket they may release it in BH and we're back
to square one.

The whole dance, however, appears to be unnecessary. Only the user
can interact with dumps, so we can clean up when socket is closed.
And close always happens in process context. Some async code may
still access the socket after close, queue notification skbs to it etc.
but no dumps can start, end or otherwise make progress.

Delete the workqueue and flush the dump state directly from the release
handler. Note that further cleanup is possible in -next, for instance
we now always call .done before releasing the main module reference,
so dump doesn't have to take a reference of its own.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51465 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51465</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container 11.4, 11.5, 11.6, 12.0, 12.1, 12.2, and 12.3 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53125 | bpf: sync_linked_regs() must preserve subreg_def</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53125</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: sync_linked_regs() must preserve subreg_def

Range propagation must not affect subreg_def marks, otherwise the
following example is rewritten by verifier incorrectly when
BPF_F_TEST_RND_HI32 flag is set:

  0: call bpf_ktime_get_ns                   call bpf_ktime_get_ns
  1: r0 &amp;= 0x7fffffff       after verifier   r0 &amp;= 0x7fffffff
  2: w1 = w0                rewrites         w1 = w0
  3: if w0 &lt; 10 goto +0     --------------&gt;  r11 = 0x2f5674a6     (r)
  4: r1 &gt;&gt;= 32                               r11 &lt;&lt;= 32           (r)
  5: r0 = r1                                 r1 |= r11            (r)
  6: exit;                                   if w0 &lt; 0xa goto pc+0
                                             r1 &gt;&gt;= 32
                                             r0 = r1
                                             exit

(or zero extension of w1 at (2) is missing for architectures that
 require zero extension for upper register half).

The following happens w/o this patch:
- r0 is marked as not a subreg at (0);
- w1 is marked as subreg at (2);
- w1 subreg_def is overridden at (3) by copy_register_state();
- w1 is read at (5) but mark_insn_zext() does not mark (2)
  for zero extension, because w1 subreg_def is not set;
- because of BPF_F_TEST_RND_HI32 flag verifier inserts random
  value for hi32 bits of (2) (marked (r));
- this random value is read at (5).</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7488 | Business Logic Error in RestApp Inc.&amp;#x27;s Online Ordering System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7488</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in RestApp Inc. Online Ordering System allows Integer Attacks.This issue affects Online Ordering System: through 04.12.2024.


NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12138 | horilla create_skills deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12138</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in horilla up to 1.2.1. This vulnerability affects the function request_new/get_employee_shift/create_reimbursement/key_result_current_value_update/create_meetings/create_skills. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11935 | Email Address Obfuscation &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via class Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11935</link><description>The Email Address Obfuscation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘class’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 13:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10576 | Unauthorized factory reset of Infinix devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10576</link><description>Infinix devices contain a pre-loaded "com.transsion.agingfunction" application, that exposes an unsecured broadcast receiver. An attacker can communicate with the receiver and force the device to perform a factory reset without any Android system permissions. 

After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer. We suppose this issue affects all Infinix Mobile devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 12:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8894 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in ODA SDK versions &amp;lt; 2025.10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8894</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability was discovered in Open Design Alliance Drawings SDK before 2025.10. Reading crafted DWF file and missing proper checks on received SectionIterator data can trigger an unhandled exception. This can allow attackers to cause a crash, potentially enabling a denial-of-service attack (Crash, Exit, or Restart) or possible code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52269 | AI Assistant PDF Document Spoofing in [WITHHELD]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52269</link><description>** INITIAL LIMITED RELEASE **

User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in [WITHHELD] allows Content Spoofing.
The SaaS AI assistant ignores hidden content that is rendered after signing, misleading the user.
This issue affects [WITHHELD]: through 2024-12-04.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11854 | Listdom – Business Directory and Classified Ads Listings WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcode Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11854</link><description>The Listdom – Business Directory and Classified Ads Listings WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘shortcode’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52278 | Merged Downloaded PDF Document Spoofing in [WITHHELD]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52278</link><description>** INITIAL LIMITED RELEASE **
User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in [WITHHELD] allows Content Spoofing.
Downloading the merged document [WITHHELD], showing the spoofed content as signed by [WITHHELD] and the persons that signed using the product/service.
This issue affects [WITHHELD]: through [WITHHELD].</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54153 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.51866 unauthenticated database backup download was possible via vulnerable query parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54153</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.51866 unauthenticated database backup download was possible via vulnerable query parameter</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54154 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.51866 system takeover was possible through path traversal in plugin sandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54154</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.51866 system takeover was possible through path traversal in plugin sandbox</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54155 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.51866 improper access control allowed listing of project names during app import without authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54155</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.51866 improper access control allowed listing of project names during app import without authentication</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54156 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.52635 multiple merge functions were vulnerable to prototype pollution attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54156</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.52635 multiple merge functions were vulnerable to prototype pollution attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54157 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.52635 potential ReDoS was possible due to vulnerable RegExp in Ruby syntax detector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54157</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.52635 potential ReDoS was possible due to vulnerable RegExp in Ruby syntax detector</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54158 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.52635 potential spoofing attack was possible via lack of Punycode encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54158</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.52635 potential spoofing attack was possible via lack of Punycode encoding</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8962 | WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8962</link><description>The WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12107 | Double Free in µD3TN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12107</link><description>Double-Free Vulnerability in uD3TN BPv7 Caused by Malformed Endpoint Identifier allows remote attacker to reliably cause DoS</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 11:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52272 | Denial of Service on Tenda AC6V2 Due To Stack Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52272</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co Tenda AC6V2 (fromAdvSetLanip(overflow arg:lanMask) modules) allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Tenda AC6V2: through 15.03.06.50</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 10:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52273 | Denial of Service on Tenda AC6V2 Due To Stack Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52273</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co Tenda AC6V2 (setDoublePppoeConfig-&gt;guest_ip_check(overflow arg: mask) modules) allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Tenda AC6V2: through 15.03.06.50</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 10:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52274 | Denial of Service on Tenda AC6V2 Due To Stack Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52274</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co Tenda AC6V2 (setDoubleL2tpConfig-&gt;guest_ip_check(overflow arg: mask) modules) allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Tenda AC6V2: through 15.03.06.50</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52275 | Denial of Service on Tenda AC6V2 Due To Stack Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52275</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co Tenda AC6V2 (fromWizardHandle modules) allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Tenda AC6V2: through 15.03.06.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52277 | PDF Document Spoofing in [WITHHELD]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52277</link><description>** INITIAL LIMITED RELEASE **
User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in [WITHHELD] allows Content Spoofing.This issue affects [WITHHELD]: through [WITHHELD].</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52276 | PDF Document Spoofing in [WITHHELD]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52276</link><description>** INITIAL LIMITED RELEASE **

User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in [WITHHELD] allows Content Spoofing.This issue affects [WITHHELD]: through 2024-12-04.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 10:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11814 | Additional Custom Order Status for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11814</link><description>The Additional Custom Order Status for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the wfwp_wcos_delete_finished, wfwp_wcos_delete_fallback_finished, wfwp_wcos_delete_fallback_orders_updated, and wfwp_wcos_delete_fallback_status parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10567 | TI WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Plugin Setup Wizard Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10567</link><description>The TI WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wizard' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new pages, modify plugin settings, and perform limited options updates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 08:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10787 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10787</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private and draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 08:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11880 | B Testimonial – testimonial plugin for WP &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11880</link><description>The B Testimonial – testimonial plugin for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'b_testimonial' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 08:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11952 | Classic Addons – WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Limited Local PHP File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11952</link><description>The Classic Addons – WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Limited Local PHP File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.0 via the 'style' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, and permissions granted by an Administrator, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. The vulnerability is limited to PHP files in a Windows environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 08:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5020 | Multiple Plugins &amp;lt;= (Various Versions) - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via FancyBox JavaScript Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5020</link><description>Multiple plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bundled FancyBox JavaScript library (versions 1.3.4 to 3.5.7) in various versions due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 08:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6978 | WP Job Manager – Company Profiles &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6978</link><description>The WP Job Manager – Company Profiles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'company' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10664 | Knowledge Base documentation &amp;amp; wiki plugin – BasePress Docs &amp;lt;= 2.16.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Database Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10664</link><description>The Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress Docs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the basepress_db_posts_update() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11293 | Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp;amp; Content Restriction Social Sites Login &amp;lt;= 1.7.9 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11293</link><description>The  Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp; Content Restriction Social Sites Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.9. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11466 | Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11466</link><description>The Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11769 | Flower Delivery by Florist One &amp;lt;= 3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11769</link><description>The Flower Delivery by Florist One plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'flower-delivery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11903 | WP eCards &amp;lt;= 1.3.904 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11903</link><description>The WP eCards plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ecard' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.904 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52943 | Incorrect authorization vulnerability in Alert.Setting webapi component in Synology Surveillance Station before 9.2.0-11289 and 9.2.0-9289 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52943</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in Alert.Setting webapi component in Synology Surveillance Station before 9.2.0-11289 and 9.2.0-9289 allows remote authenticated users to to perform limited actions on the alerting function via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52944 | Incorrect authorization vulnerability in ActionRule webapi component in Synology Surveillance Station before 9.2.0-11289 and 9.2.0-9289 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52944</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in ActionRule webapi component in Synology Surveillance Station before 9.2.0-11289 and 9.2.0-9289 allows remote authenticated users to perform limited actions on the set action rules function via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11398 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in OTP reset functionality in Synology Router M...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11398</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in OTP reset functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-9 allows remote authenticated users to delete arbitrary files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45717 | SolarWinds Platform Cross- Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45717</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was susceptible to a XSS vulnerability that affects the search and node information section of the user interface. This vulnerability requires authentication and requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54664 | An issue was discovered in Veritas NetBackup before 10.5. This only applies to NetBackup components running on a Windows Operating System. I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54664</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas NetBackup before 10.5. This only applies to NetBackup components running on a Windows Operating System. If a user executes specific NetBackup commands or an attacker uses social engineering techniques to impel the user to execute the commands, a malicious DLL could be loaded, resulting in execution of the attacker's code in the user's security context, a different vulnerability than CVE-2024-52945.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 06:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54661 | readline.sh in socat through 1.8.0.1 relies on the /tmp/$USER/stderr2 file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54661</link><description>readline.sh in socat through 1.8.0.1 relies on the /tmp/$USER/stderr2 file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9404 | Denial-of-Service Vulnerability Identified in the VPort 07-3 Series</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9404</link><description>Moxa’s IP Cameras are affected by a medium-severity vulnerability, CVE-2024-9404, which could lead to a denial-of-service condition or cause a service crash. This vulnerability allows attackers to exploit the Moxa service, commonly referred to as moxa_cmd, originally designed for deployment. Because of insufficient input validation, this service may be manipulated to trigger a denial-of-service.

This vulnerability poses a significant remote threat if the affected products are exposed to publicly accessible networks. Attackers could potentially disrupt operations by shutting down the affected systems. Due to the critical nature of this security risk, we strongly recommend taking immediate action to prevent potential exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10885 | SearchIQ – The Search Solution &amp;lt;= 4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10885</link><description>The SearchIQ – The Search Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'siq_searchbox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12099 | Dollie Hub – Build Your Own WordPress Cloud Platform &amp;lt;= 6.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12099</link><description>The Dollie Hub – Build Your Own WordPress Cloud Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.0 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12123 | Unauthorized Modification of Ticket Requester</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12123</link><description>A hidden field manipulation vulnerability was identified in Issuetrak version 17.1 that could be triggered by an authenticated user. 

When an authenticated user submits a ticket, the request can be intercepted and subsequently modified by using a proxy.  The ticket requester can be changed from the original requester to another user in the same application, 
which the application then accepts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10587 | Funnelforms Free &amp;lt;= 3.7.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10587</link><description>The Interactive Contact Form and Multi Step Form Builder with Drag &amp; Drop Editor – Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.4.1 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10663 | Eleblog – Elementor Blog And Magazine Addons &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Deactivation Submission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10663</link><description>The Eleblog – Elementor Blog And Magazine Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the goodbye_form_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to submit a deactivation reason.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10832 | Posti Shipping &amp;lt;= 3.10.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via generate_notices_html Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10832</link><description>The Posti Shipping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the generate_notices_html() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10952 | Authors List &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via update_authors_list_ajax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10952</link><description>The The Authors List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via update_authors_list_ajax AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11093 | SG Helper &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11093</link><description>The SG Helper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in version 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11747 | Responsive Videos &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11747</link><description>The Responsive Videos plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'somryv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11807 | NPS computy &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11807</link><description>The NPS computy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'data1' and 'data2' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11813 | Pulsating Chat Button &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11813</link><description>The Pulsating Chat Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the amin_chat_button_settings_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11897 | Contact Form, Survey &amp;amp; Form Builder – MightyForms &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11897</link><description>The Contact Form, Survey &amp; Form Builder – MightyForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mightyforms' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 03:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11985 | An improper input validation vulnerability leads to device crashes in certain ASUS router models. 
Refer to the '12/03/2024 ASUS Router Impr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11985</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability leads to device crashes in certain ASUS router models. 
Refer to the '12/03/2024 ASUS Router Improper Input Validation' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40717 | A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows a low-privileged user with certain roles to perform remote code execution (RCE) by upda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40717</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows a low-privileged user with certain roles to perform remote code execution (RCE) by updating existing jobs. These jobs can be configured to run pre- and post-scripts, which can be located on a network share and are executed with elevated privileges by default. The user can update a job and schedule it to run almost immediately, allowing arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42449 | From the VSPC management agent machine, under condition that the management agent is authorized on the server, it is possible to remove arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42449</link><description>From the VSPC management agent machine, under condition that the management agent is authorized on the server, it is possible to remove arbitrary files on the VSPC server machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42451 | A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows low-privileged users to leak all saved credentials in plaintext. This is achieved by ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42451</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows low-privileged users to leak all saved credentials in plaintext. This is achieved by calling a series of methods over an external protocol, ultimately retrieving the credentials using a malicious setup on the attacker's side. This exposes sensitive data, which could be used for further attacks, including unauthorized access to systems managed by the platform.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42452 | A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows a low-privileged user to start an agent remotely in server mode and obtain credentials,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42452</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows a low-privileged user to start an agent remotely in server mode and obtain credentials, effectively escalating privileges to system-level access. This allows the attacker to upload files to the server with elevated privileges. The vulnerability exists because remote calls bypass permission checks, leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42453 | A vulnerability Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows low-privileged users to control and modify configurations on connected virtual infrastruct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42453</link><description>A vulnerability Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows low-privileged users to control and modify configurations on connected virtual infrastructure hosts. This includes the ability to power off virtual machines, delete files in storage, and make configuration changes, potentially leading to Denial of Service (DoS) and data integrity issues. The vulnerability is caused by improper permission checks in methods accessed via management services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42455 | A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows a low-privileged user to connect to remoting services and exploit insecure deserializat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42455</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows a low-privileged user to connect to remoting services and exploit insecure deserialization by sending a serialized temporary file collection. This exploit allows the attacker to delete any file on the system with service account privileges. The vulnerability is caused by an insufficient blacklist during the deserialization process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42456 | A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication platform allows a low-privileged user with a specific role to exploit a method that updates cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42456</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication platform allows a low-privileged user with a specific role to exploit a method that updates critical configuration settings, such as modifying the trusted client certificate used for authentication on a specific port. This can result in unauthorized access, enabling the user to call privileged methods and initiate critical services. The issue arises due to insufficient permission requirements on the method, allowing users with low privileges to perform actions that should require higher-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42457 | A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows users with certain operator roles to expose saved credentials by leveraging a combinati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42457</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication allows users with certain operator roles to expose saved credentials by leveraging a combination of methods in a remote management interface. This can be achieved using a session object that allows for credential enumeration and exploitation, leading to the leak of plaintext credentials to a malicious host. The attack is facilitated by improper usage of a method that allows operators to add a new host with an attacker-controlled IP, enabling them to retrieve sensitive credentials in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45204 | A vulnerability exists where a low-privileged user can exploit insufficient permissions in credential handling to leak NTLM hashes of saved ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45204</link><description>A vulnerability exists where a low-privileged user can exploit insufficient permissions in credential handling to leak NTLM hashes of saved credentials. The exploitation involves using retrieved credentials to expose sensitive NTLM hashes, impacting systems beyond the initial target and potentially leading to broader security vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45205 | An Improper Certificate Validation on the UniFi iOS App managing a standalone UniFi Access Point (not using UniFi Network Application) could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45205</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation on the UniFi iOS App managing a standalone UniFi Access Point (not using UniFi Network Application) could allow a malicious actor with access to an adjacent network to take control of this UniFi Access Point.


Affected Products:
UniFi iOS App (Version 10.17.7 and earlier) 
 
Mitigation:
UniFi iOS App (Version 10.18.0 or later).</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45206 | A vulnerability in Veeam Service Provider Console has been identified, which allows to perform arbitrary HTTP requests to arbitrary hosts of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45206</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Service Provider Console has been identified, which allows to perform arbitrary HTTP requests to arbitrary hosts of the network and get information about internal resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45207 | DLL injection in Veeam Agent for Windows can occur if the system's PATH variable includes insecure locations. When the agent runs, it search...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45207</link><description>DLL injection in Veeam Agent for Windows can occur if the system's PATH variable includes insecure locations. When the agent runs, it searches these directories for necessary DLLs. If an attacker places a malicious DLL in one of these directories, the Veeam Agent might load it inadvertently, allowing the attacker to execute harmful code. This could lead to unauthorized access, data theft, or disruption of services</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11479 | Authenticated HTML Injection in Issuetrak Ticket Comment Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11479</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was identified in Issuetrak version 17.1 that could be triggered by an authenticated user. HTML markup could be added to comments of tickets, which when submitted will render in the 
emails sent to all users on that ticket.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>