<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:35:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-40691 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40691</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2, 19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3, 20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1, and 22.0.2 may reveal sensitive information contained in application configuration to developer and administrator users.  IBM X-Force ID:  264805.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4311 | Vrm 360 3D Model Viewer &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Contributor+ Arbitrary File Upload Leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4311</link><description>The Vrm 360 3D Model Viewer WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload due to insufficient checks in a plugin shortcode.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4724 | WP All Export (Free &amp;lt; 1.4.0, Pro &amp;lt; 1.8.6) - Admin+ RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4724</link><description>The Export any WordPress data to XML/CSV WordPress plugin before 1.4.0, WP All Export Pro WordPress plugin before 1.8.6 does not validate and sanitise the `wp_query` parameter which allows an attacker to run arbitrary command on the remote server</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5005 | Autocomplete Location field Contact Form 7 &amp;lt; 3.0 - Admin+ Store Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5005</link><description>The Autocomplete Location field Contact Form 7 WordPress plugin before 3.0, autocomplete-location-field-contact-form-7-pro WordPress plugin before 2.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5348 | Product Catalog Enquiry for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 5.0.3 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS via Arbitrary Setting Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5348</link><description>The Product Catalog Mode For WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 5.0.3 does not properly authorize settings updates or escape settings values, leading to stored XSS by unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5882 | WP All Export (Free &amp;lt; 1.4.1, Pro &amp;lt; 1.8.6) - Remote Code Execution via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5882</link><description>The Export any WordPress data to XML/CSV WordPress plugin before 1.4.0, WP All Export Pro WordPress plugin before 1.8.6 does not check nonce tokens early enough in the request lifecycle, allowing attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5886 | WP All Export (Free &amp;lt; 1.4.1, Pro &amp;lt; 1.8.6) - Author+ PHAR Deserialization via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5886</link><description>The Export any WordPress data to XML/CSV WordPress plugin before 1.4.0, WP All Export Pro WordPress plugin before 1.8.6 does not check nonce tokens early enough in the request lifecycle, allowing attackers with the ability to upload files to make logged in users perform unwanted actions leading to PHAR deserialization, which may lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5949 | SmartCrawl WordPress SEO checker &amp;lt; 3.8.3 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5949</link><description>The SmartCrawl WordPress plugin before 3.8.3 does not prevent unauthorised users from accessing password-protected posts' content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6065 | Quttera Web Malware Scanner &amp;lt; 3.4.2.1 - Directory Listing to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6065</link><description>The Quttera Web Malware Scanner WordPress plugin before 3.4.2.1 doesn't restrict access to detailed scan logs, which allows a malicious actor to discover local paths and portions of the site's code</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6077 | Slider - Ultimate Responsive Image Slider &amp;lt; 3.5.12 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Post Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6077</link><description>The Slider WordPress plugin before 3.5.12 does not ensure that posts to be accessed via an AJAX action are slides and can be viewed by the user making the request, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to access the content arbitrary post such as private, draft and password protected</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6203 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 6.2.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Protected Post Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6203</link><description>The Events Calendar WordPress plugin before 6.2.8.1 discloses the content of password protected posts to unauthenticated users via a crafted request</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6222 | Quttera Web Malware Scanner &amp;lt; 3.4.2.1 - Admin+ Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6222</link><description>IThe Quttera Web Malware Scanner WordPress plugin before 3.4.2.1 does not validate user input used in a path, which could allow users with an admin role to perform path traversal attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6272 | Theme My Login 2FA &amp;lt; 1.2 -  Lack of Rate Limiting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6272</link><description>The Theme My Login 2FA WordPress plugin before 1.2 does not rate limit 2FA validation attempts, which may allow an attacker to brute-force all possibilities, which shouldn't be too long, as the 2FA codes are 6 digits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6289 | Swift Performance Lite &amp;lt;= 2.3.6.14 - Unauthenticated Configuration Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6289</link><description>The Swift Performance Lite WordPress plugin before 2.3.6.15 does not prevent users from exporting the plugin's settings, which may include sensitive information such as Cloudflare API tokens.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6295 | so-widgets-bundle &amp;lt; 1.51.0 - Admin+ Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6295</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle WordPress plugin before 1.51.0 does not validate user input before using it to generate paths passed to include function/s, allowing users with the administrator role to perform LFI attacks in the context of Multisite WordPress sites.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47741 | IBM i information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47741</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, IBM i Db2 Mirror for i 7.4 and 7.5 web browser clients may leave clear-text passwords in browser memory that can be viewed using common browser tools before the memory is garbage collected. A malicious actor with access to the victim's PC could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to the IBM i operating system. IBM X-Force ID: 272532.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51384 | In ssh-agent in OpenSSH before 9.6, certain destination constraints can be incompletely applied. When destination constraints are specified ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51384</link><description>In ssh-agent in OpenSSH before 9.6, certain destination constraints can be incompletely applied. When destination constraints are specified during addition of PKCS#11-hosted private keys, these constraints are only applied to the first key, even if a PKCS#11 token returns multiple keys.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51385 | In ssh in OpenSSH before 9.6, OS command injection might occur if a user name or host name has shell metacharacters, and this name is refere...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51385</link><description>In ssh in OpenSSH before 9.6, OS command injection might occur if a user name or host name has shell metacharacters, and this name is referenced by an expansion token in certain situations. For example, an untrusted Git repository can have a submodule with shell metacharacters in a user name or host name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6691 | Code Injection vulnerability in Cambium ePMP Force 300-25</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6691</link><description>Cambium ePMP Force 300-25 version 4.7.0.1 is vulnerable to a code injection vulnerability that could allow an attacker to perform remote code execution and gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 17:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46617 | WordPress AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp;amp; Ads.txt Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46617</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AdFoxly AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp; Ads.Txt.This issue affects AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp; Ads.Txt: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48766 | WordPress SVGator – Add Animated SVG Easily Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48766</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SVGator SVGator – Add Animated SVG Easily.This issue affects SVGator – Add Animated SVG Easily: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48762 | WordPress JetElements For Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48762</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Crocoblock JetElements For Elementor.This issue affects JetElements For Elementor: from n/a through 2.6.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48755 | WordPress teachPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48755</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Winkler teachPress.This issue affects teachPress: from n/a through 9.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48795 | The SSH transport protocol with certain OpenSSH extensions, found in OpenSSH before 9.6 and other products, allows remote attackers to bypas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48795</link><description>The SSH transport protocol with certain OpenSSH extensions, found in OpenSSH before 9.6 and other products, allows remote attackers to bypass integrity checks such that some packets are omitted (from the extension negotiation message), and a client and server may consequently end up with a connection for which some security features have been downgraded or disabled, aka a Terrapin attack. This occurs because the SSH Binary Packet Protocol (BPP), implemented by these extensions, mishandles the handshake phase and mishandles use of sequence numbers. For example, there is an effective attack against SSH's use of ChaCha20-Poly1305 (and CBC with Encrypt-then-MAC). The bypass occurs in chacha20-poly1305@openssh.com and (if CBC is used) the -etm@openssh.com MAC algorithms. This also affects Maverick Synergy Java SSH API before 3.1.0-SNAPSHOT, Dropbear through 2022.83, Ssh before 5.1.1 in Erlang/OTP, PuTTY before 0.80, AsyncSSH before 2.14.2, golang.org/x/crypto before 0.17.0, and libssh before 0.10.6; and there could be effects on Bitvise SSH through 9.31.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33214 | WordPress Taggbox Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33214</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tagbox Tagbox – UGC Galleries, Social Media Widgets, User Reviews &amp; Analytics.This issue affects Tagbox – UGC Galleries, Social Media Widgets, User Reviews &amp; Analytics: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47806 | WordPress Disable User Login Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47806</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saint Systems Disable User Login.This issue affects Disable User Login: from n/a through 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47789 | WordPress WooCommerce Canada Post Shipping Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47789</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WooCommerce Canada Post Shipping Method.This issue affects Canada Post Shipping Method: from n/a through 2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47787 | WordPress WooCommerce Bookings Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47787</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WooCommerce WooCommerce Bookings.This issue affects WooCommerce Bookings: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40312 | WordPress GiveWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.25.1 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40312</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in GiveWP GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform.This issue affects GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform: from n/a through 2.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6778 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in allegroai/clearml-server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6778</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository allegroai/clearml-server prior to 1.13.0. This vulnerability affects the ClearML Open Source Server which is not designed to be used as a publicly available service. Security recommendations stress it should be placed behind a company firewall or VPN. This vulnerability only affects users within the same organisation (I.e when a malicious party already has access to the internal network and to a user's ClearML login credentials).</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49840 | WordPress Multi Currency For WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49840</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Palscode Multi Currency For WooCommerce.This issue affects Multi Currency For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49843 | WordPress First Order Discount Woocommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.21 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49843</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in QuanticEdge First Order Discount Woocommerce.This issue affects First Order Discount Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.21.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49844 | WordPress WPPerformanceTester Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49844</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kevin Ohashi WPPerformanceTester.This issue affects WPPerformanceTester: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49853 | WordPress PayTR Taksit Tablosu Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49853</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PayTR Ödeme ve Elektronik Para Kuruluşu A.Ş. PayTR Taksit Tablosu – WooCommerce.This issue affects PayTR Taksit Tablosu – WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6817 | Use-after-free in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s netfilter: nf_tables component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6817</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability in the Linux kernel's netfilter: nf_tables component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

The function nft_pipapo_walk did not skip inactive elements during set walk which could lead double deactivations of PIPAPO (Pile Packet Policies) elements, leading to use-after-free.

We recommend upgrading past commit 317eb9685095678f2c9f5a8189de698c5354316a.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46177 | IBM MQ Appliance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46177</link><description>IBM MQ Appliance 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system.  An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  269536.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3628 | Rest bulk ops don&amp;#x27;t check permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3628</link><description>A flaw was found in Infinispan's REST. Bulk read endpoints do not properly evaluate user permissions for the operation. This issue could allow an authenticated user to access information outside of their intended permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3629 | Non-admins should not be able to get cache config via rest api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3629</link><description>A flaw was found in Infinispan's REST, Cache retrieval endpoints do not properly evaluate the necessary admin permissions for the operation. This issue could allow an authenticated user to access information outside of their intended permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47038 | Perl: write past buffer end via illegal user-defined unicode property</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47038</link><description>A vulnerability was found in perl. This issue occurs when a crafted regular expression is compiled by perl, which can allow an attacker controlled byte buffer overflow in a heap allocated buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4320 | Arithmetic overflow in satellite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4320</link><description>An arithmetic overflow flaw was found in Satellite when creating a new personal access token. This flaw allows an attacker who uses this arithmetic overflow to create personal access tokens that are valid indefinitely, resulting in damage to the system's integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5056 | Privelege escalation via config map</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5056</link><description>A flaw was found in the Skupper operator, which may permit a certain configuration to create a service account that would allow an authenticated attacker in the adjacent cluster to view deployments in all namespaces in the cluster. This issue permits unauthorized viewing of information outside of the user's purview.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5115 | Malicious role archive can cause ansible-galaxy to overwrite arbitrary files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5115</link><description>An absolute path traversal attack exists in the Ansible automation platform. This flaw allows an attacker to craft a malicious Ansible role and make the victim execute the role. A symlink can be used to overwrite a file outside of the extraction path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5236 | Circular reference on marshalling leads to dos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5236</link><description>A flaw was found in Infinispan, which does not detect circular object references when unmarshalling. An authenticated attacker with sufficient permissions could insert a maliciously constructed object into the cache and use it to cause out of memory errors and achieve a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5384 | Infinispan: credentials returned from configuration as clear text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5384</link><description>A flaw was found in Infinispan. When serializing the configuration for a cache to XML/JSON/YAML, which contains credentials (JDBC store with connection pooling, remote store), the credentials are returned in clear text as part of the configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6228 | Libtiff: heap-based buffer overflow in cpstriptotile() in tools/tiffcp.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6228</link><description>An issue was found in the tiffcp utility distributed by the libtiff package where a crafted TIFF file on processing may cause a heap-based buffer overflow leads to an application crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3430 | Openimageio: heap-buffer-overflow in file src/gif.imageio/gifinput.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3430</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenImageIO, where a heap buffer overflow exists in the src/gif.imageio/gifinput.cpp file. This flaw allows a remote attacker to pass a specially crafted file to the application, which triggers a heap-based buffer overflow and could cause a crash, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41677 | An information disclosure vulnerability was discovered in Bosch IP camera devices allowing an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41677</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability was discovered in Bosch IP camera devices allowing an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve information (like capabilities) about the device itself and network settings of the device, disclosing possibly internal network settings if the device is connected to the internet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32230 | An improper handling of a malformed API request to an API server in Bosch BT software products can allow an unauthenticated attacker to caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32230</link><description>An improper handling of a malformed API request to an API server in Bosch BT software products can allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) situation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35867 | An improper handling of a malformed API answer packets to API clients in Bosch BT software products can allow an unauthenticated attacker to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35867</link><description>An improper handling of a malformed API answer packets to API clients in Bosch BT software products can allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) situation. To exploit this vulnerability an attacker has to replace an existing API server e.g. through Man-in-the-Middle attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39509 | A command injection vulnerability exists in Bosch IP cameras that allows an authenticated user with administrative rights to run arbitrary c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39509</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in Bosch IP cameras that allows an authenticated user with administrative rights to run arbitrary commands on the OS of the camera.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28053 | Dell NetWorker Virtual Edition versions 19.8 and below contain the use of deprecated cryptographic algorithms in the SSH component. A remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28053</link><description>Dell NetWorker Virtual Edition versions 19.8 and below contain the use of deprecated cryptographic algorithms in the SSH component. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to some information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49854 | WordPress Caddy Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49854</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tribe Interactive Caddy – Smart Side Cart for WooCommerce.This issue affects Caddy – Smart Side Cart for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49855 | WordPress BC Menu Bar Cart Icon For WooCommerce By Binary Carpenter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.49.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49855</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BinaryCarpenter Menu Bar Cart Icon For WooCommerce By Binary Carpenter.This issue affects Menu Bar Cart Icon For WooCommerce By Binary Carpenter: from n/a through 1.49.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50372 | WordPress Custom Post Type Page Template Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50372</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hiroaki Miyashita Custom Post Type Page Template.This issue affects Custom Post Type Page Template: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32726 | Possible buffer overread from reading DNS responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32726</link><description>The vulnerability is caused by improper check for check if RDLENGTH does not overflow the buffer in response from DNS server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32727 | Code execution vulnerability in icmpping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32727</link><description>An attacker who has the privilege to configure Zabbix items can use function icmpping() with additional malicious command inside it to execute arbitrary code on the current Zabbix server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32728 | Code injection in zabbix_agent2 smart.disk.get caused by smartctl plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32728</link><description>The Zabbix Agent 2 item key smart.disk.get does not sanitize its parameters before passing them to a shell command resulting possible vulnerability for remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32725 | Leak of zbx_session cookie when using a scheduled report that includes a dashboard with a URL widget.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32725</link><description>The website configured in the URL widget will receive a session cookie when testing or executing scheduled reports. The received session cookie can then be used to access the frontend as the particular user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6911 | Multiple WSO2 products have been identified as vulnerable due to improper output encoding, a Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack can be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6911</link><description>Multiple WSO2 products have been identified as vulnerable due to improper output encoding, a Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack can be carried out by an attacker injecting a malicious payload into the Registry feature of the Management Console.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41314 | Apache Doris: Missing API authentication allowed DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41314</link><description>The api /api/snapshot and /api/get_log_file would allow unauthenticated access.
It could allow a DoS attack or get arbitrary files from FE node.
Please upgrade to 2.0.3 to fix these issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6483 | Improper Authentication Vulnerability in ADiTaaS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6483</link><description>The vulnerability exists in ADiTaaS (Allied Digital Integrated Tool-as-a-Service) version 5.1 due to an improper authentication vulnerability in the ADiTaaS backend API. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted HTTP requests to the vulnerable platform.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to gain full access to the customers’ data and completely compromise the targeted platform.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50979 | Crypto++ (aka cryptopp) through 8.9.0 has a Marvin side channel during decryption with PKCS#1 v1.5 padding.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50979</link><description>Crypto++ (aka cryptopp) through 8.9.0 has a Marvin side channel during decryption with PKCS#1 v1.5 padding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50980 | gf2n.cpp in Crypto++ (aka cryptopp) through 8.9.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via DER public-key data ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50980</link><description>gf2n.cpp in Crypto++ (aka cryptopp) through 8.9.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via DER public-key data for an F(2^m) curve, if the degree of each term in the polynomial is not strictly decreasing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50981 | ModularSquareRoot in Crypto++ (aka cryptopp) through 8.9.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (infinite loop) via crafted DER pub...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50981</link><description>ModularSquareRoot in Crypto++ (aka cryptopp) through 8.9.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (infinite loop) via crafted DER public-key data associated with squared odd numbers, such as the square of 268995137513890432434389773128616504853.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6908 | DFIRKuiper TAR Archive case_management.py unzip_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6908</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DFIRKuiper Kuiper 2.3.4. This affects the function unzip_file of the file kuiper/app/controllers/case_management.py of the component TAR Archive Handler. The manipulation of the argument dst_path leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. Upgrading to version 2.3.5 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 94fa135153002f651f5526c55a7240e083db8d73. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248277 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6907 | codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS Deletion Interface delete.php improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6907</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS up to 1.2.4 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /file-manager/delete.php of the component Deletion Interface. The manipulation of the argument file leads to improper authentication. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248269 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6906 | Totolink A7100RU HTTP POST Request main buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6906</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink A7100RU 7.4cu.2313_B20191024. Affected is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument flag with the input ie8 leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248268. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6909 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;\..\filename&amp;#x27; in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6909</link><description>Path Traversal: '\..\filename' in GitHub repository mlflow/mlflow prior to 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6905 | Jahastech NxFilter Bind Request ldap injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6905</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Jahastech NxFilter 4.3.2.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file user,adap.jsp?actionFlag=test&amp;id=1 of the component Bind Request Handler. The manipulation leads to ldap injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248267. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50976 | Redpanda before 23.1.21 and 23.2.x before 23.2.18 has missing authorization checks in the Transactions API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50976</link><description>Redpanda before 23.1.21 and 23.2.x before 23.2.18 has missing authorization checks in the Transactions API.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3907 | Improper Privilege Management in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3907</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.0 prior to 16.4.4, 16.5 prior to 16.5.4, and 16.6 prior to 16.6.2 allows a project Maintainer to use a Project Access Token to escalate their role to Owner</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6903 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6903</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/singlelogin.php?submit=1. The manipulation of the argument loginId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248265 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6904 | Jahastech NxFilter config,admin.jsp cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6904</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Jahastech NxFilter 4.3.2.5. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /config,admin.jsp. The manipulation of the argument admin_name leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-248266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6902 | codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6902</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS up to 1.2.4 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /file-manager/upload.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248260.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 15:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50271 | HP-UX System Management Homepage, Disclosure of Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50271</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified with HP-UX System Management Homepage (SMH). This vulnerability could be exploited locally or remotely to disclose information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6901 | codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS HTTP POST Request handle-command.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6901</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS up to 1.2.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /terminal/handle-command.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument command with the input whoami leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248259.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6900 | rmountjoy92 DashMachine delete_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6900</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in rmountjoy92 DashMachine 0.5-4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /settings/delete_file. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 13:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6899 | rmountjoy92 DashMachine Config save_config code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6899</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in rmountjoy92 DashMachine 0.5-4. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /settings/save_config of the component Config Handler. The manipulation of the argument value_template leads to code injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248257 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 12:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49834 | WordPress WOOCS – WooCommerce Currency Switcher Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49834</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in realmag777 FOX – Currency Switcher Professional for WooCommerce.This issue affects FOX – Currency Switcher Professional for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.1.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49824 | WordPress Product Catalog Feed by PixelYourSite Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49824</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PixelYourSite Product Catalog Feed by PixelYourSite.This issue affects Product Catalog Feed by PixelYourSite: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49816 | WordPress Fix My Feed RSS Repair Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49816</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Innovative Solutions Fix My Feed RSS Repair.This issue affects Fix My Feed RSS Repair: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6898 | SourceCodester Best Courier Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6898</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248256.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49775 | WordPress CSV Importer Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49775</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Denis Kobozev CSV Importer.This issue affects CSV Importer: from n/a through 0.3.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6896 | SourceCodester Simple Image Stack Website cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6896</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Image Stack Website 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument search with the input sy2ap%22%3e%3cscript%3ealert(1)%3c%2fscript%3etkxh1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248255.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49769 | WordPress Integrate Google Drive Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49769</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SoftLab Integrate Google Drive.This issue affects Integrate Google Drive: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49751 | WordPress Block for Font Awesome Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49751</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ciprian Popescu Block for Font Awesome.This issue affects Block for Font Awesome: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 09:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24380 | WordPress Simple Wp Sitemap Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24380</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Webbjocke Simple Wp Sitemap.This issue affects Simple Wp Sitemap: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 09:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6895 | Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System ping.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6895</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /php/ping.php. The manipulation of the argument jsondata[ip] with the input netstat -ano leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6894 | Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System Log File system.html information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6894</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK). It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file access/html/system.html of the component Log File Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248253 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6893 | Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System exportrecord.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6893</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK) and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /php/exportrecord.php. The manipulation of the argument downname with the input C:\ICPAS\Wnmp\WWW\php\conversion.php leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248252.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 06:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6891 | PeaZip Library dragdropfilesdll.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6891</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PeaZip 9.4.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library dragdropfilesdll.dll of the component Library Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. An attack has to be approached locally. Upgrading to version 9.6.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248251. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early, confirmed the existence of the flaw and immediately worked on a patched release.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 03:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50965 | In MicroHttpServer (aka Micro HTTP Server) through 4398570, _ReadStaticFiles in lib/middleware.c allows a stack-based buffer overflow and po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50965</link><description>In MicroHttpServer (aka Micro HTTP Server) through 4398570, _ReadStaticFiles in lib/middleware.c allows a stack-based buffer overflow and potentially remote code execution via a long URI.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 02:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6888 | PHZ76 RtspServer RtspMesaage.cpp ParseRequestLine stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6888</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHZ76 RtspServer 1.0.0. This vulnerability affects the function ParseRequestLine of the file RtspMesaage.cpp. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248248. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 01:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6887 | saysky ForestBlog Image Upload img unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6887</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in saysky ForestBlog up to 20220630. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/upload/img of the component Image Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248247.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 01:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6886 | xnx3 wangmarket Role Management Page code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6886</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xnx3 wangmarket 6.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Role Management Page. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248246 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 01:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6885 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6885</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/vote/manage/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248245 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 22:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50784 | A buffer overflow in websockets in UnrealIRCd 6.1.0 through 6.1.3 before 6.1.4 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to crash the server...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50784</link><description>A buffer overflow in websockets in UnrealIRCd 6.1.0 through 6.1.3 before 6.1.4 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to crash the server by sending an oversized packet (if a websocket port is open). Remote code execution might be possible on some uncommon, older platforms.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 22:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6559 | The MW WP Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.3. This is due to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6559</link><description>The MW WP Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.3. This is due to the plugin not properly validating the path of an uploaded file prior to deleting it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, including the wp-config.php file, which can make site takeover and remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6853 | kalcaddle KodExplorer app.php index server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6853</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. Affected by this vulnerability is the function index of the file plugins/officeLive/app.php. The manipulation of the argument path leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248221 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6852 | kalcaddle KodExplorer app.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6852</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. Affected is an unknown function of the file plugins/webodf/app.php. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248220.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6851 | kalcaddle KodExplorer ZIP Archive app.php unzipList code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6851</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function unzipList of the file plugins/zipView/app.php of the component ZIP Archive Handler. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248219.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6889 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6889</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.1.17.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6890 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6890</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.1.17.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6850 | kalcaddle KodExplorer API Endpoint unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6850</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php?pluginApp/to/yzOffice/getFile of the component API Endpoint Handler. The manipulation of the argument path/file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248218 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6849 | kalcaddle kodbox app.php cover server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6849</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.48. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cover of the file plugins/fileThumb/app.php. The manipulation of the argument path leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.48.04 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 63a4d5708d210f119c24afd941d01a943e25334c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248210 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6848 | kalcaddle kodbox index.class.php check command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6848</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.48. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function check of the file plugins/officeViewer/controller/libreOffice/index.class.php. The manipulation of the argument soffice leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.48.04 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 63a4d5708d210f119c24afd941d01a943e25334c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248209 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 06:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39340 | A vulnerability exists on all versions of Ivanti Connect Secure below 22.6R2 where an attacker can send a specific request which may lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39340</link><description>A vulnerability exists on all versions of Ivanti Connect Secure below 22.6R2 where an attacker can send a specific request which may lead to Denial of Service (DoS) of the appliance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 02:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-24351 | TOCTOU race-condition vulnerability in Insyde InsydeH2O with Kernel 5.2 before version 05.27.29, Kernel 5.3 before version 05.36.29, Kernel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24351</link><description>TOCTOU race-condition vulnerability in Insyde InsydeH2O with Kernel 5.2 before version 05.27.29, Kernel 5.3 before version 05.36.29, Kernel 5.4 version before 05.44.13, and Kernel 5.5 before version 05.52.13 allows an attacker to alter data and code used by the remainder of the boot process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-24351 | TOCTOU race-condition vulnerability in Insyde InsydeH2O with Kernel 5.2 before version 05.27.29, Kernel 5.3 before version 05.36.29, Kernel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24351</link><description>TOCTOU race-condition vulnerability in Insyde InsydeH2O with Kernel 5.2 before version 05.27.29, Kernel 5.3 before version 05.36.29, Kernel 5.4 version before 05.44.13, and Kernel 5.5 before version 05.52.13 allows an attacker to alter data and code used by the remainder of the boot process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-17483 | An improper access control vulnerability exists in Uffizio's GPS Tracker all versions that lead to sensitive information disclosure of all t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17483</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in Uffizio's GPS Tracker all versions that lead to sensitive information disclosure of all the connected devices. By visiting the vulnerable host at port 9000, we see it responds with a JSON body that has all the details about the devices which have been deployed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-17484 | An Open Redirection vulnerability exists in Uffizio's GPS Tracker all versions allows an attacker to construct a URL within the application ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17484</link><description>An Open Redirection vulnerability exists in Uffizio's GPS Tracker all versions allows an attacker to construct a URL within the application that causes a redirection to an arbitrary external domain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-17485 | A Remote Code Execution vulnerability exist in Uffizio's GPS Tracker all versions. The web server can be compromised by uploading and execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17485</link><description>A Remote Code Execution vulnerability exist in Uffizio's GPS Tracker all versions. The web server can be compromised by uploading and executing a web/reverse shell. An attacker could then run commands, browse system files, and browse local resources</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42794 | An issue was discovered in AVEVA Edge (formerly InduSoft Web Studio) versions R2020 and prior. The application allows a client to provide a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42794</link><description>An issue was discovered in AVEVA Edge (formerly InduSoft Web Studio) versions R2020 and prior. The application allows a client to provide a malicious connection string that could allow an adversary to port scan the LAN, depending on the hosts' responses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42796 | An issue was discovered in ExecuteCommand() in AVEVA Edge (formerly InduSoft Web Studio) versions R2020 and prior that allows unauthenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42796</link><description>An issue was discovered in ExecuteCommand() in AVEVA Edge (formerly InduSoft Web Studio) versions R2020 and prior that allows unauthenticated arbitrary commands to be executed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42797 | Path traversal vulnerability in AVEVA Edge (formerly InduSoft Web Studio) versions R2020 and prior allows an unauthenticated user to steal t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42797</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in AVEVA Edge (formerly InduSoft Web Studio) versions R2020 and prior allows an unauthenticated user to steal the Windows access token of the user account configured for accessing external DB resources.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>