<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 14:25:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-24862 | NULL-pointer dereference in Linux kernel spi driver in function pci1xxxx_spi_probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24862</link><description>In function pci1xxxx_spi_probe, there is a potential null pointer that
may be caused by a failed memory allocation by the function devm_kzalloc.
Hence, a null pointer check needs to be added to prevent null pointer
dereferencing later in the code.

To fix this issue, spi_bus-&gt;spi_int[iter] should be checked. The memory
allocated by devm_kzalloc will be automatically released, so just directly
return -ENOMEM without worrying about memory leaks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24863 | NULL pointer deference in __drm_atomic_helper_connector_destroy_state in drm/arm/malidp of Linux kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24863</link><description>In malidp_mw_connector_reset, new memory is allocated with kzalloc, but 
no check is performed. In order to prevent null pointer dereferencing, 
ensure that mw_state is checked before calling 
__drm_atomic_helper_connector_reset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3740 | cym1102 nginxWebUI reload exec deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3740</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. This issue affects the function exec of the file /adminPage/conf/reload. The manipulation of the argument nginxExe leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260579.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 20:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3739 | cym1102 nginxWebUI upload os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3739</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /adminPage/main/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 18:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3738 | cym1102 nginxWebUI saveCmd handlePath certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3738</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. This affects the function handlePath of the file /adminPage/conf/saveCmd. The manipulation of the argument nginxPath leads to improper certificate validation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260577 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3737 | cym1102 nginxWebUI addOver findCountByQuery path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3737</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function findCountByQuery of the file /adminPage/www/addOver. The manipulation of the argument dir leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260576.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32487 | less through 653 allows OS command execution via a newline character in the name of a file, because quoting is mishandled in filename.c. Exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32487</link><description>less through 653 allows OS command execution via a newline character in the name of a file, because quoting is mishandled in filename.c. Exploitation typically requires use with attacker-controlled file names, such as the files extracted from an untrusted archive. Exploitation also requires the LESSOPEN environment variable, but this is set by default in many common cases.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 14:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3736 | cym1102 nginxWebUI upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /adminPage/main/upload. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260575.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 14:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3735 | Smart Office Main.aspx weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smart Office up to 20240405. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file Main.aspx. The manipulation of the argument New Password/Confirm Password with the input 1 leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 13:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3721 | TBK DVR-4104/DVR-4216 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3721</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TBK DVR-4104 and DVR-4216 up to 20240412 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /device.rsp?opt=sys&amp;amp;cmd=___S_O_S_T_R_E_A_MAX___. The manipulation of the argument mdb/mdc leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260573 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 12:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3720 | Tianwell Fire Intelligent Command Platform API Interface page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3720</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tianwell Fire Intelligent Command Platform 1.1.1.1 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /mfsNotice/page of the component API Interface. The manipulation of the argument gsdwid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260572.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26817 | amdkfd: use calloc instead of kzalloc to avoid integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26817</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

amdkfd: use calloc instead of kzalloc to avoid integer overflow

This uses calloc instead of doing the multiplication which might
overflow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3719 | Campcodes House Rental Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3719</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260571.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6494 | The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6494</link><description>The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 08:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3662 | The WPZOOM Social Feed Widget &amp; Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3662</link><description>The WPZOOM Social Feed Widget &amp; Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpzoom_instagram_clear_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete all Instagram images installed on the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 08:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2583 | Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt; 7.0.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2583</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate WordPress plugin before 7.0.5 does not properly escape some of its shortcodes attributes before they are echoed back to users, making it possible for users with the contributor role to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 05:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1957 | The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1957</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'give_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 02:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3027 | The Smart Slider 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the upload f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3027</link><description>The Smart Slider 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the upload function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1.22. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to upload files, including SVG files, which can be used to conduct stored cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 02:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32028 | Sensitive query parameters logged by default in OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation http and AspNetCore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32028</link><description>OpenTelemetry dotnet is a dotnet telemetry framework. In affected versions of `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.Http` and `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.AspNetCore` the `url.full` writes attribute/tag on spans (`Activity`) when tracing is enabled for outgoing http requests and `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.AspNetCore` writes the `url.query` attribute/tag on spans (`Activity`) when tracing is enabled for incoming http requests. These attributes are defined by the Semantic Conventions for HTTP Spans. Up until version `1.8.1` the values written by `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.Http` &amp; `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.AspNetCore` will pass-through the raw query string as was sent or received (respectively). This may lead to sensitive information (e.g. EUII - End User Identifiable Information, credentials, etc.) being leaked into telemetry backends (depending on the application(s) being instrumented) which could cause privacy and/or security incidents. Note: Older versions of `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.Http` &amp; `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.AspNetCore` may use different tag names but have the same vulnerability. The `1.8.1` versions of `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.Http` &amp; `OpenTelemetry.Instrumentation.AspNetCore` will now redact by default all values detected on transmitted or received query strings. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 23:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31462 | Limited file write in Stable-diffusion-webui - GHSL-2024-010</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31462</link><description>stable-diffusion-webui is a web interface for Stable Diffusion, implemented using Gradio library. Stable-diffusion-webui 1.7.0 is vulnerable to a limited file write affecting Windows systems. The create_ui method (Backup/Restore tab) in modules/ui_extensions.py takes user input into the config_save_name variable on line 653. This user input is later used in the save_config_state method and used to create a file path on line 65, which is afterwards opened for writing on line 67, which leads to a limited file write exploitable on Windows systems. This issue may lead to limited file write. It allows for writing json files anywhere on the server where the web server has access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28869 | Possible denial of service vulnerability with Content-length header in Traefik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28869</link><description>Traefik is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. In affected versions sending a GET request to any Traefik endpoint with the "Content-length" request header results in an indefinite hang with the default configuration. This vulnerability can be exploited by attackers to induce a denial of service. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 2.11.2 and 3.0.0-rc5. Users are advised to upgrade. For affected versions, this vulnerability can be mitigated by configuring the readTimeout option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29022 | Session Hijacking via XSS attack in header and session grid in Xibo CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29022</link><description>Xibo is an Open Source Digital Signage platform with a web content management system and Windows display player software. In affected versions some request headers are not correctly sanitised when stored in the session and display tables. These headers can be used to inject a malicious script into the session page to exfiltrate session IDs and User Agents. These session IDs / User Agents can subsequently be used to hijack active sessions. A malicious script can be injected into the display grid to exfiltrate information related to displays. Users should upgrade to version 3.3.10 or 4.0.9 which fix this issue. Customers who host their CMS with the Xibo Signage service have already received an upgrade or patch to resolve this issue regardless of the CMS version that they are running. Upgrading to a fixed version is necessary to remediate. Patches are available for earlier versions of Xibo CMS that are out of security support: 2.3 patch ebeccd000b51f00b9a25f56a2f252d6812ebf850.diff. 1.8 patch a81044e6ccdd92cc967e34c125bd8162432e51bc.diff. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29023 | Session Hijacking via token exposure on the session page in Xibo CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29023</link><description>Xibo is an Open Source Digital Signage platform with a web content management system and Windows display player software. Session tokens are exposed in the return of session search API call on the sessions page. Subsequently they can be exfiltrated and used to hijack a session. Users must be granted access to the session page, or be a super admin. Users should upgrade to version 3.3.10 or 4.0.9 which fix this issue. Customers who host their CMS with the Xibo Signage service have already received an upgrade or patch to resolve this issue regardless of the CMS version that they are running. Patches are available for earlier versions of Xibo CMS that are out of security support: 2.3 patch ebeccd000b51f00b9a25f56a2f252d6812ebf850.diff. 1.8 patch a81044e6ccdd92cc967e34c125bd8162432e51bc.diff. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32005 | Local File Inclusion in NiceGUI leaflet component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32005</link><description>NiceGUI is an easy-to-use, Python-based UI framework. A local file inclusion is present in the NiceUI leaflet component when requesting resource files under the `/_nicegui/{__version__}/resources/{key}/{path:path}` route. As a result any file on the backend filesystem which the web server has access to can be read by an attacker with access to the NiceUI leaflet website. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 1.4.21. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32019 | ndsudo: local privilege escalation via untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32019</link><description>Netdata is an open source observability tool. In affected versions the `ndsudo` tool shipped with affected versions of the Netdata Agent allows an attacker to run arbitrary programs with root permissions. The `ndsudo` tool is packaged as a `root`-owned executable with the SUID bit set. It only runs a restricted set of external commands, but its search paths are supplied by the `PATH` environment variable. This allows an attacker to control where `ndsudo` looks for these commands, which may be a path the attacker has write access to. This may lead to local privilege escalation. This vulnerability has been addressed in versions 1.45.3 and 1.45.2-169. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32003 | Dusk plugin may allow unfettered user authentication in misconfigured installs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32003</link><description>wn-dusk-plugin (Dusk plugin) is a plugin which integrates Laravel Dusk browser testing into Winter CMS. The Dusk plugin provides some special routes as part of its testing framework to allow a browser environment (such as headless Chrome) to act as a user in the Backend or User plugin without having to go through authentication. This route is `[[URL]]/_dusk/login/[[USER ID]]/[[MANAGER]]` - where `[[URL]]` is the base URL of the site, `[[USER ID]]` is the ID of the user account and `[[MANAGER]]` is the authentication manager (either `backend` for Backend, or `user` for the User plugin). If a configuration of a site using the Dusk plugin is set up in such a way that the Dusk plugin is available publicly and the test cases in Dusk are run with live data, this route may potentially be used to gain access to any user account in either the Backend or User plugin without authentication. As indicated in the `README`, this plugin should only be used in development and should *NOT* be used in a production instance. It is specifically recommended that the plugin be installed as a development dependency only in Composer. In order to remediate this issue, the special routes used above will now no longer be registered unless the `APP_ENV` environment variable is specifically set to `dusk`. Since Winter by default does not use this environment variable and it is not populated by default, it will only exist if Dusk's automatic configuration is used (which won't exhibit this vulnerability) or if a developer manually specifies it in their configuration. The automatic configuration performed by the Dusk plugin has also been hardened by default to use sane defaults and not allow external environment variables to leak into this configuration. This will only affect users in which the Winter CMS installation meets ALL the following criteria: 1. The Dusk plugin is installed in the Winter CMS instance. 2. The application is in production mode (ie. the `debug` config value is set to `true` in `config/app.php`). 3. The Dusk plugin's automatic configuration has been overridden, either by providing a custom `.env.dusk` file or by providing custom configuration in the `config/dusk` folder, or by providing configuration environment variables externally. 4. The environment has been configured to use production data in the database for testing, and not the temporary SQLite database that Dusk uses by default. 5. The application is connectable via the web. This issue has been fixed in version 2.1.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32000 | Truncated content of messages can be leaked from matrix-appservice-irc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32000</link><description>matrix-appservice-irc is a Node.js IRC bridge for the Matrix messaging protocol. matrix-appservice-irc before version 2.0.0 can be exploited to leak the truncated body of a message if a malicious user sends a Matrix reply to an event ID they don't have access to. As a precondition to the attack, the malicious user needs to know the event ID of the message they want to leak, as well as to be joined to both the Matrix room and the IRC channel it is bridged to. The message reply containing the leaked message content is visible to IRC channel members when this happens. matrix-appservice-irc 2.0.0 checks whether the user has permission to view an event before constructing a reply. Administrators should upgrade to this version. It's possible to limit the amount of information leaked by setting a reply template that doesn't contain the original message. See these lines `601-604` in the configuration file linked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0157 | Dell Storage Resource Manager, 4.9.0.0 and below, contain(s) a Session Fixation Vulnerability in SRM Windows Host Agent. An adjacent network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0157</link><description>Dell Storage Resource Manager, 4.9.0.0 and below, contain(s) a Session Fixation Vulnerability in SRM Windows Host Agent. An adjacent network unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the hijack of a targeted user's application session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3698 | Campcodes House Rental Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3698</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260485 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22339 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22339</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.0 through 7.0.5.20, 7.1 through 7.1.2.16, 7.2 through 7.2.3.9, 7.3 through 7.3.2.4 and IBM DevOps Deploy  8.0 through 8.0.0.1 is vulnerable to a sensitive information due to insufficient obfuscation of sensitive values from some log files.  IBM X-Force ID:  279979.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22358 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22358</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.0 through 7.0.5.20, 7.1 through 7.1.2.16, 7.2 through 7.2.3.9, 7.3 through 7.3.2.4 and IBM DevOps Deploy  8.0 through 8.0.0.1 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  280896.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22334 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy improper privilege control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22334</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.0 through 7.0.5.20, 7.1 through 7.1.2.16, 7.2 through 7.2.3.9, 7.3 through 7.3.2.4 and IBM DevOps Deploy  8.0 through 8.0.0.1 could be vulnerable to incomplete revocation of permissions when deleting a custom security resource type. When deleting a custom security type, associated permissions of objects using that type may not be fully revoked. This could lead to incorrect reporting of permission configuration and unexpected privileges being retained.  IBM X-Force ID:  279974.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3697 | Campcodes House Rental Management System manage_tenant.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3697</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file manage_tenant.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260484.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22359 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22359</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.0 through 7.0.5.20, 7.1 through 7.1.2.16, 7.2 through 7.2.3.9, 7.3 through 7.3.2.4 and IBM DevOps Deploy  8.0 through 8.0.0.1 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  280897.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3696 | Campcodes House Rental Management System view_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3696</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file view_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260483.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3691 | PHPGurukul Small CRM Registration Page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3691</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 3.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Registration Page. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260480.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3695 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System Users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3695</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260482 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30389 | Junos OS: EX4300 Series: Firewall filter not blocking egress traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30389</link><description>An Incorrect Behavior Order vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on EX4300 Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause an integrity impact to networks downstream of the vulnerable device.

When an output firewall filter is applied to an interface it doesn't recognize matching packets but permits any traffic.
This issue affects Junos OS 21.4 releases from 21.4R1 earlier than 21.4R3-S6.
This issue does not affect Junos OS releases earlier than 21.4R1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30390 | Junos OS Evolved: Connection limits is not being enforced while the resp. rate limit is being enforced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30390</link><description>An Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a limited Denial of Service (DoS) to the management plane.

When an incoming connection was blocked because it exceeded the connections-per-second rate-limit, the system doesn't consider existing connections anymore for subsequent connection attempts so that the connection limit can be exceeded.
This issue affects Junos OS Evolved:

All versions before 21.4R3-S4-EVO,

22.1-EVO versions before 22.1R3-S3-EVO,

22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-S2-EVO, 

22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R2-S1-EVO, 22.3R3-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30391 | Junos OS: MX Series with SPC3, and SRX Series: When IPsec authentication is configured with &amp;quot;hmac-sha-384&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;hmac-sha-512&amp;quot; no authentication of traffic is performed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30391</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (pfe) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series with SPC3, and SRX Series allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker to cause limited impact to the integrity or availability of the device.

If a device is configured with IPsec authentication algorithm hmac-sha-384 or hmac-sha-512, tunnels are established normally but for traffic traversing the tunnel no authentication information is sent with the encrypted data on egress, and no authentication information is expected on ingress. So if the peer is an unaffected device transit traffic is going to fail in both directions. If the peer is an also affected device transit traffic works, but without authentication, and configuration and CLI operational commands indicate authentication is performed.
This issue affects Junos OS:

All versions before 20.4R3-S7,

21.1 versions before 21.1R3, 

21.2 versions before 21.2R2-S1, 21.2R3, 

21.3 versions before 21.3R1-S2, 21.3R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30397 | Junos OS: An invalid certificate causes a Denial of Service in the Internet Key Exchange (IKE) process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30397</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the the Public Key Infrastructure daemon (pkid) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated networked attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).

The pkid is responsible for the certificate verification. Upon a failed verification, the pkid uses all CPU resources and becomes unresponsive to future verification attempts. This means that all subsequent VPN negotiations depending on certificate verification will fail.

This CPU utilization of pkid can be checked using this command: 
  root@srx&gt; show system processes extensive | match pkid
  xxxxx  root  103  0  846M  136M  CPU1  1 569:00 100.00% pkid

This issue affects:
Juniper Networks Junos OS
All versions prior to 20.4R3-S10;
21.2 versions prior to 21.2R3-S7;
21.4 versions prior to 21.4R3-S5;
22.1 versions prior to 22.1R3-S4;
22.2 versions prior to 22.2R3-S3;
22.3 versions prior to 22.3R3-S1;
22.4 versions prior to 22.4R3;
23.2 versions prior to 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30398 | Junos OS: SRX4600 Series - A high amount of specific traffic causes packet drops and an eventual PFE crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30398</link><description>An Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When a high amount of specific traffic is received on a SRX4600 device, due to an error in internal packet handling, a consistent rise in CPU memory utilization occurs. This results in packet drops in the traffic and eventually the PFE crashes. A manual reboot of the PFE will be required to restore the device to original state.

This issue affects Junos OS:  
21.2 before 21.2R3-S7,
21.4 before 21.4R3-S6, 
22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 
22.2 before 22.2R3-S3,
22.3 before 22.3R3-S2,
22.4 before 22.4R3,
23.2 before 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30401 | Junos OS: MX Series and EX9200-15C: Stack-based buffer overflow in aftman</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30401</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in the advanced forwarding management process aftman of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series with MPC10E, MPC11, MX10K-LC9600 line cards, MX304, and EX9200-15C, may allow an attacker to exploit a stack-based buffer overflow, leading to a reboot of the FPC.

Through code review, it was determined that the interface definition code for aftman could read beyond a buffer boundary, leading to a stack-based buffer overflow.
This issue affects Junos OS on MX Series and EX9200-15C:


  *  from 21.2 before 21.2R3-S1, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R2, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R2; 




This issue does not affect:



  *  versions of Junos OS prior to 20.3R1;
  *  any version of Junos OS 20.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30402 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: The l2ald crashes on receiving telemetry messages from a specific subscription</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30402</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Layer 2 Address Learning Daemon (l2ald) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When telemetry requests are sent to the device, and the Dynamic Rendering Daemon (drend) is suspended, the l2ald crashes and restarts due to factors outside the attackers control. Repeated occurrences of these events causes a sustained DoS condition.


This issue affects:
Junos OS:
All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S10;
21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;
22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3;
23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.

Junos OS Evolved:

All versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5-EVO;
22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4-EVO;
22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3-EVO;
22.3-EVO versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1-EVO;
22.4-EVO versions earlier than 22.4R3-EVO;
23.2-EVO versions earlier than 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30403 | Junos OS Evolved: When MAC learning happens, and an interface gets flapped, the PFE crashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30403</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When Layer 2 traffic is sent through a logical interface, MAC learning happens. If during this process, the interface flaps, an Advanced Forwarding Toolkit manager (evo-aftmand-bt) core is observed. This leads to a PFE restart. The crash reoccurs if the same sequence of events happens, which will lead to a sustained DoS condition.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved:
23.2-EVO versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28878 | IOSIX IO-1020 Micro ELD Download of Code Without Integrity Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28878</link><description>IO-1020 Micro ELD downloads source code or an executable from an 
adjacent location and executes the code without sufficiently verifying 
the origin or integrity of the code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30210 | IOSIX IO-1020 Micro ELD Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30210</link><description>IO-1020 Micro ELD uses a default WIFI password that could allow an adjacent attacker to connect to the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30382 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: RPD crash when CoS-based forwarding (CBF) policy is configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30382</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a network-based, unauthenticated attacker to send a specific routing update, causing an rpd core due to memory corruption, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

This issue can only be triggered when the system is configured for CoS-based forwarding (CBF) with a policy map containing a cos-next-hop-map action (see below).
This issue affects:
Junos OS: 


  *  all versions before 20.4R3-S10, 
  *  from 21.2 before 21.2R3-S8,
  *  from 21.3 before 21.3R3, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R2;




Junos OS Evolved: 


  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  from 21.3 before 21.3R3-EVO, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30384 | Junos OS: EX4300 Series: If a specific CLI command is issued PFE crashes will occur</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30384</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on EX4300 Series allows a locally authenticated attacker with low privileges to cause a Denial-of-Service (Dos).

If a specific CLI command is issued, a PFE crash will occur. This will cause traffic forwarding to be interrupted until the system self-recovers. 

This issue affects Junos OS: 

All versions before 20.4R3-S10,

21.2 versions before 21.2R3-S7,

21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30386 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: In a EVPN-VXLAN scenario state changes on adjacent systems can cause an l2ald process crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30386</link><description>A Use-After-Free vulnerability in the Layer 2 Address Learning Daemon (l2ald)

 of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause l2ald to crash leading to a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

In an EVPN-VXLAN scenario, when 

state updates are received and processed by the affected system, the correct order of some processing steps is not ensured, which can lead to an l2ald crash and restart. Whether the crash occurs depends on system internal timing which is outside the attackers control.
This issue affects:

Junos OS: 



  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S8,
  *  21.2 versions before 21.2R3-S6,
  *  21.3 versions before 21.3R3-S5,
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S4,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S3,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S1,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3,,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R2;




Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  21.2-EVO versions before 21.2R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  21.3-EVO

 versions before 21.3R3-S5-EVO,
  *  21.4-EVO

 versions before 21.4R3-S4-EVO,
  *  22.1-EVO

 versions before 22.1R3-S3-EVO,
  *  22.2-EVO

 versions before 22.2R3-S1-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO

 versions before 22.3R3-EVO,
  *  22.4-EVO

 versions before 22.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30387 | Junos OS: ACX5448 &amp;amp; ACX710: Due to interface flaps the PFE process can crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30387</link><description>A Missing Synchronization vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on ACX5448 and ACX710 allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

If an interface flaps while the system gathers statistics on that interface, two processes simultaneously access a shared resource which leads to a PFE crash and restart.

This issue affects Junos OS:

All versions before 20.4R3-S9,

21.2 versions before 21.2R3-S5, 

21.3 versions before 21.3R3-S5, 

21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S4,

22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S2,

22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S2,

22.3 versions before 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3,

22.4 versions before 22.4R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31069 | IOSIX IO-1020 Micro ELD Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31069</link><description>IO-1020 Micro ELD web server uses a default password for authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30388 | Junos OS: QFX5000 Series and EX Series: Specific malformed LACP packets will cause flaps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30388</link><description>An Improper Isolation or Compartmentalization vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (pfe) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on QFX5000 Series and EX Series allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If a specific malformed LACP packet is received by a QFX5000 Series, or an EX4400, EX4100 or EX4650 Series device, an LACP flap will occur resulting in traffic loss.
This issue affects Junos OS on QFX5000 Series, and on EX4400, EX4100 or EX4650 Series:



  *  20.4 versions from 

20.4R3-S4

before 20.4R3-S8,
  *  21.2 versions from 

21.2R3-S2

before 21.2R3-S6,
  *  21.4 versions from 

21.4R2

before 21.4R3-S4,

  *  22.1 versions from

22.1R2

 before 22.1R3-S3,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S1,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R2-S1, 22.4R3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30392 | Junos OS: MX Series with SPC3 and MS-MPC/-MIC: When URL filtering is enabled and a specific URL request is received a flowd crash occurs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30392</link><description>A Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Flow Processing Daemon (flowd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS MX Series platforms with SPC3 and MS-MPC/-MIC, when URL filtering is enabled and a specific URL request is received and processed, flowd will crash and restart. Continuous reception of the specific URL request will lead to a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue affects:
Junos OS:



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S6,

  *  from 21.3 before 21.3R3-S5,

  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S5,

  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S3,

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S1,

  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3,

  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R2-S1, 22.4R3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30394 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A specific EVPN type-5 route causes rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30394</link><description>A Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (RPD) component of Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause an rpd crash, leading to Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved platforms, when EVPN is configured, and a specific EVPN type-5 route is received via BGP, rpd crashes and restarts. Continuous receipt of this specific route will lead to a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue affects:
Junos OS:



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S7,

  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S5,

  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S4,

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S2,

  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S1,

  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3,

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2.





Junos OS Evolved:



  *  all versions before 21.4R3-S5-EVO,

  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S4-EVO,

  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S2-EVO,

  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S1-EVO,

  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO,

  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30395 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A malformed BGP tunnel encapsulation attribute will lead to an rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30395</link><description>An Improper Validation of Specified Type of Input vulnerability in Routing Protocol Daemon (RPD) of Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).

If a BGP update is received over an established BGP session which contains a tunnel encapsulation attribute with a specifically malformed TLV, rpd will crash and restart.
This issue affects:

Junos OS:



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S7, 

  *  from 21.3 before 21.3R3-S5, 

  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S5, 

  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 

  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2, 

  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3, 

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.





Junos OS Evolved:



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S7-EVO, 

  *  from 21.3-EVO before 21.3R3-S5-EVO, 

  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 

  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S2-EVO, 

  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO, 

  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R1-S2-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO.



This is a related but separate issue than the one described in JSA75739</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30405 | Junos OS: SRX 5000 Series with SPC2: Processing of specific crafted packets when ALG is enabled causes a transit traffic Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30405</link><description>An Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS SRX 5000 Series devices using SPC2 line cards while ALGs are enabled allows an attacker sending specific crafted packets to cause a transit traffic Denial of Service (DoS).

Continued receipt and processing of these specific packets will sustain the Denial of Service condition.

This issue affects:
Juniper Networks Junos OS SRX 5000 Series with SPC2 with ALGs enabled.
  *  All versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S6;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S5;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30406 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX Series with Paragon Active Assurance Test Agent: A local high privileged attacker can recover other administrators credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30406</link><description>A Cleartext Storage in a File on Disk vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved ACX Series devices using the Paragon Active Assurance Test Agent software installed on network devices allows a local, authenticated attacker with high privileges to read all other users login credentials.

This issue affects only Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved ACX Series devices using the Paragon Active Assurance Test Agent software installed on these devices from 23.1R1-EVO through 23.2R2-EVO. 

This issue does not affect releases before 23.1R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30407 | [Child CVE] JCNR and cRPD: Hard-coded SSH host keys in cRPD may allow Person-in-the-Middle (PitM) attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30407</link><description>The Use of a Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability in Juniper Networks Juniper Cloud Native Router (JCNR) and containerized routing Protocol Deamon (cRPD) products allows an attacker to perform Person-in-the-Middle (PitM) attacks which results in complete compromise of the container. 

Due to hardcoded SSH host keys being present on the container, a PitM attacker can intercept SSH traffic without being detected. 

This issue affects Juniper Networks JCNR:
  *  All versions before 23.4.


This issue affects Juniper Networks cRPD:
  *  All versions before 23.4R1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30409 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Higher CPU consumption on routing engine leads to Denial of Service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30409</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in telemetry processing of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a network-based authenticated attacker to cause the forwarding information base telemetry daemon (fibtd) to crash, leading to a limited Denial of Service. 

This issue affects Juniper Networks

 Junos OS:
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R1-S2, 22.1R2.


Junos OS Evolved: 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R1-S2-EVO, 22.1R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30410 | Junos OS: EX4300 Series: Loopback filter not blocking traffic despite having discard term.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30410</link><description>An Incorrect Behavior Order in the routing engine (RE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on EX4300 Series allows traffic intended to the device to reach the RE instead of being discarded when the discard term is set in loopback (lo0) interface. The intended function is that the lo0 firewall filter takes precedence over the revenue interface firewall filter. 

This issue affects only IPv6 firewall filter.

This issue only affects the EX4300 switch.  No other products or platforms are affected by this vulnerability. 

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:

  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S10,
  *  from 21.2 before 21.2R3-S7,
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31391 | Apache Solr Operator: Solr-Operator liveness and readiness probes may leak basic auth credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31391</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in the Apache Solr Operator.

This issue affects all versions of the Apache Solr Operator from 0.3.0 through 0.8.0.

When asked to bootstrap Solr security, the operator will enable basic authentication and create several accounts for accessing Solr: including the "solr" and "admin" accounts for use by end-users, and a "k8s-oper" account which the operator uses for its own requests to Solr.
One common source of these operator requests is healthchecks: liveness, readiness, and startup probes are all used to determine Solr's health and ability to receive traffic.
By default, the operator configures the Solr APIs used for these probes to be exempt from authentication, but users may specifically request that authentication be required on probe endpoints as well.
Whenever one of these probes would fail, if authentication was in use, the Solr Operator would create a Kubernetes "event" containing the username and password of the "k8s-oper" account.

Within the affected version range, this vulnerability affects any solrcloud resource which (1) bootstrapped security through use of the `.solrOptions.security.authenticationType=basic` option, and (2) required authentication be used on probes by setting `.solrOptions.security.probesRequireAuth=true`.

Users are recommended to upgrade to Solr Operator version 0.8.1, which fixes this issue by ensuring that probes no longer print the credentials used for Solr requests.  Users may also mitigate the vulnerability by disabling authentication on their healthcheck probes using the setting `.solrOptions.security.probesRequireAuth=false`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21598 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A malformed BGP tunnel encapsulation attribute will lead to an rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21598</link><description>An Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a network-based, unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If a BGP update is received over an established BGP session which contains a tunnel encapsulation attribute with a specifically malformed TLV, rpd will crash and restart.

This issue affects Juniper Networks
Junos OS:
  *  20.4 versions 20.4R1 and later versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2;



Junos OS Evolved:
  *  20.4-EVO versions 20.4R1-EVO and later versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9-EVO;
  *  21.2-EVO versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7-EVO;
  *  21.3-EVO versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5-EVO;
  *  21.4-EVO versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5-EVO;
  *  22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4-EVO;
  *  22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3-EVO;
  *  22.3-EVO versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1-EVO;
  *  22.4-EVO versions earlier than 22.4R3-EVO;
  *  23.2-EVO versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO;



This issue does not affect Juniper Networks
  *  Junos OS versions earlier than 20.4R1;
  *  Junos OS Evolved versions earlier than 20.4R1-EVO.



This is a related but separate issue than the one described in JSA79095.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21605 | Junos OS: SRX 300 Series: Specific link local traffic causes a control plane overload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21605</link><description>An Exposure of Resource to Wrong Sphere vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX 300 Series allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).



Specific valid link-local traffic is not blocked on ports in STP blocked state but is instead sent to the control plane of the device. This leads to excessive resource consumption and in turn severe impact on all control and management protocols of the device.



This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:
  *  21.2 version 21.2R3-S3 and later versions earlier than 21.2R3-S6;
  *  22.1 version 22.1R3 and later versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 version 

22.2R2

and later versions earlier than 22.2R3-S2;
  *  22.3 version 

22.3R2 

and later versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;

  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1, 23.2R2.




This issue does not affect Juniper Networks Junos OS 21.4R1 and later versions of 21.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21609 | Junos OS: MX Series with SPC3, and SRX Series: If specific IPsec parameters are negotiated iked will crash due to a memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21609</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the IKE daemon (iked) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series with SPC3, and SRX Series allows an administratively adjacent attacker which is able to successfully establish IPsec tunnels to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If specific values for the IPsec parameters local-ip, remote-ip, remote ike-id, and traffic selectors are sent from the peer, a memory leak occurs during every IPsec SA rekey which is carried out with a specific message sequence. This will eventually result in an iked process crash and restart.

The iked process memory consumption can be checked using the below command:
  user@host&gt; show system processes extensive | grep iked
           PID   USERNAME     PRI  NICE    SIZE    RES    STATE    C   TIME  WCPU COMMAND
           56903 root         31    0      4016M  2543M   CPU0     0   2:10  10.50% iked

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:
  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S4;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S2;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21610 | Junos OS: MX Series: In a scaled subscriber scenario if CoS information is gathered mgd processes gets stuck</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21610</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Class of Service daemon (cosd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series allows an authenticated, network-based attacker with low privileges to cause a limited Denial of Service (DoS).

In a scaled subscriber scenario when specific low privileged commands, received over NETCONF, SSH or telnet, are handled by cosd on behalf of mgd, the respective child management daemon (mgd) processes will get stuck. In case of (Netconf over) SSH this leads to stuck SSH sessions, so that when the connection-limit for SSH is reached new sessions can't be established anymore. A similar behavior will be seen for telnet etc.

Stuck mgd processes can be monitored by executing the following command:

  user@host&gt; show system processes extensive | match mgd | match sbwait

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series:
All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3;
23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21615 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A low-privileged user can access confidential information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21615</link><description>An Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a local, low-privileged attacker to access confidential information on the system.

On all Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved platforms, when NETCONF traceoptions are configured, and a super-user performs specific actions via NETCONF, then a low-privileged user can access sensitive information compromising the confidentiality of the system.
This issue affects:

Junos OS:



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S7, 

  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S5, 

  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 

  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2, 

  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3, 

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R1-S2.





Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S7-EVO, 

  *  from 21.3 before 21.3R3-S5-EVO, 

  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S5-EVO, 

  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5-EVO, 

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 

  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2-EVO,

  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-EVO, 

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R1-S2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21618 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: When LLDP is enabled and a malformed LLDP packet is received, l2cpd crashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21618</link><description>An Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability in the Layer-2 Control Protocols Daemon (l2cpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an adjacent, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved platforms, when LLDP is enabled on a specific interface, and a malformed LLDP packet is received, l2cpd crashes and restarts. The impact of the l2cpd crash is reinitialization of STP protocols (RSTP, MSTP or VSTP), and MVRP and ERP. Also, if any services depend on LLDP state (like PoE or VoIP device recognition), then these will also be affected.

This issue affects:

Junos OS:
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S4, 

  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S4, 

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S2, 

  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3-S1, 

  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3, 

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2.




 Junos OS Evolved:
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S5-EVO, 

  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S4-EVO, 

  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S2-EVO, 

  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R2-S2-EVO, 22.3R3-S1-EVO, 

  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO, 

  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.




This issue does not affect:
  *  Junos OS versions prior to 21.4R1;

  *  Junos OS Evolved versions prior to 21.4R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30381 | Paragon Active Assurance: probe_serviced exposes internal objects to local users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30381</link><description>An Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Juniper Networks Paragon Active Assurance Control Center allows a network-adjacent attacker with root access to a Test Agent Appliance the ability to access sensitive information about downstream devices.

The "netrounds-probe-login" daemon (also called probe_serviced) exposes functions where the Test Agent (TA) Appliance pushes interface state/config, unregister itself, etc.  The remote service accidentally exposes an internal database object that can be used for direct database access on the Paragon Active Assurance Control Center.




This issue affects Paragon Active Assurance: 4.1.0, 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3690 | PHPGurukul Small CRM Change Password sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3690</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 3.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Change Password Handler. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260479.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21590 | Junos OS Evolved: Packets which are not destined to the device can reach the RE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21590</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Juniper Tunnel Driver (jtd) and ICMP module of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated attacker within the MPLS administrative domain to send specifically crafted packets to the Routing Engine (RE) to cause a Denial of Service (DoS). 

When specifically crafted transit MPLS IPv4 packets are received by the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE), these packets are internally forwarded to the RE. Continued receipt of these packets may create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:

  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO;
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S6-EVO;
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S4-EVO;
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S3-EVO;
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO;
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.
  *  from 23.4-EVO before 23.4R1-S1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21593 | Junos OS: MX Series with MPC10, MPC11, LC9600, and MX304: A specific MPLS packet will cause a PFE crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21593</link><description>An Improper Check or Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If an attacker sends a specific MPLS packet, which upon processing, causes an internal loop, that leads to a PFE crash and restart. Continued receipt of these packets leads to a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.
 
Circuit cross-connect (CCC) needs to be configured on the device for it to be affected by this issue.

This issue only affects MX Series with MPC10, MPC11, LC9600, and MX304.

This issue affects:
Juniper Networks Junos OS
21.4 versions from 21.4R3 earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
22.2 versions from 22.2R2 earlier than 22.2R3-S2;
22.3 versions from 22.3R1 earlier than 22.3R2-S2;
22.3 versions from 22.3R3 earlier than 22.3R3-S1
22.4 versions from 22.4R1 earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51515 | WordPress Uncode Core plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51515</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Undsgn Uncode Core allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Uncode Core: from n/a through 2.8.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51499 | WordPress WooCommerce Shipping Per Product plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51499</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WooCommerce WooCommerce Shipping Per Product.This issue affects WooCommerce Shipping Per Product: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52211 | WordPress WP Job Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52211</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic WP Job Manager.This issue affects WP Job Manager: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3689 | Zhejiang Land Zongheng Network Technology O2OA information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3689</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Zhejiang Land Zongheng Network Technology O2OA up to 20240403. Affected is an unknown function of the file /x_portal_assemble_surface/jaxrs/portal/list?v=8.2.3-4-43f4fe3. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260478 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29461 | An issue in Floodlight SDN OpenFlow Controller v.1.2 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the datapath id component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29461</link><description>An issue in Floodlight SDN OpenFlow Controller v.1.2 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the datapath id component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3687 | bihell Dice Comment cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3687</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bihell Dice 3.1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Comment Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260474 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3688 | Xiamen Four-Faith RMP Router Management Platform sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3688</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Xiamen Four-Faith RMP Router Management Platform 5.2.2. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Device/Device/GetDeviceInfoList?deviceCode=&amp;amp;searchField=&amp;amp;deviceState=. The manipulation of the argument groupId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260476. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3705 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in OpenGnsys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3705</link><description>Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in OpenGnsys affecting version 1.1.1d (Espeto). This vulnerability allows an attacker to send a POST request to the endpoint '/opengnsys/images/M_Icons.php' modifying the file extension, due to lack of file extension verification, resulting in a webshell injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3706 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in OpenGnsys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3706</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in OpenGnsys affecting version 1.1.1d (Espeto). This vulnerability allows an attacker to view a php backup file (controlaccess.php-LAST) where database credentials are stored.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3707 | Exposure of Information Through Directory Listing vulnerability in OpenGnsys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3707</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in OpenGnsys affecting version 1.1.1d (Espeto). This vulnerability allows an attacker to enumerate all files in the web tree by accessing a php file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3704 | SQL Injection vulnerability in OpenGnsys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3704</link><description>SQL Injection Vulnerability has been found on OpenGnsys product affecting version 1.1.1d (Espeto). This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into login page to bypass it or even retrieve all the information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31839 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in tiagorlampert CHAOS v.5.0.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sendCommandHandler...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31839</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in tiagorlampert CHAOS v.5.0.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sendCommandHandler function in the handler.go component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3686 | DedeCMS update_guide.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3686</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DedeCMS 5.7.112-UTF8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file update_guide.php. The manipulation of the argument files leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260473 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2397 | infinite loop in the PPP printer of tcpdump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2397</link><description>Due to a bug in packet data buffers management, the PPP printer in tcpdump can enter an infinite loop when reading a crafted DLT_PPP_SERIAL .pcap savefile.  This problem does not affect any tcpdump release, but it affected the git master branch from 2023-06-05 to 2024-03-21.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51409 | WordPress AI Engine plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.98 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51409</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Jordy Meow AI Engine: ChatGPT Chatbot.This issue affects AI Engine: ChatGPT Chatbot: from n/a through 1.9.98.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30845 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Rainbow external link network disk v.5.5 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30845</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Rainbow external link network disk v.5.5 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation component of the input parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40211 | WordPress GiveWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.25.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via render_dropdown vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40211</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GiveWP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GiveWP: from n/a through 2.25.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25545 | An issue in Weave Weave Desktop v.7.78.10 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nwjs framework compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25545</link><description>An issue in Weave Weave Desktop v.7.78.10 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nwjs framework component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31818 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in DerbyNet v.9.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the page parameter of the kiosk.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31818</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in DerbyNet v.9.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the page parameter of the kiosk.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31235 | WordPress Comments Import &amp;amp; Export plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31235</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WebToffee WordPress Comments Import &amp; Export.This issue affects WordPress Comments Import &amp; Export: from n/a through 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31238 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31238</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover.This issue affects Smart Online Order for Clover: from n/a through 1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31239 | WordPress Nudgify Social Proof, Sales Popup &amp;amp; FOMO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31239</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Nudgify Nudgify Social Proof, Sales Popup &amp; FOMO.This issue affects Nudgify Social Proof, Sales Popup &amp; FOMO: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3685 | DedeCMS stepselect_main.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3685</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in DedeCMS 5.7.112-UTF8. Affected is an unknown function of the file stepselect_main.php. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260472. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31250 | WordPress WP Server Health Stats plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31250</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saumya Majumder WP Server Health Stats.This issue affects WP Server Health Stats: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31251 | WordPress Community by PeepSo plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31251</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PeepSo Community by PeepSo.This issue affects Community by PeepSo: from n/a through 6.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31262 | WordPress WooCommerce Checkout Field Editor (Checkout Manager) plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31262</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jcodex WooCommerce Checkout Field Editor (Checkout Manager).This issue affects WooCommerce Checkout Field Editor (Checkout Manager): from n/a through 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31263 | WordPress Loan Repayment Calculator and Application Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31263</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in aerin Loan Repayment Calculator and Application Form.This issue affects Loan Repayment Calculator and Application Form: from n/a through 2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31264 | WordPress Post Views Counter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31264</link><description>Unauthenticated Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Post Views Counter &lt;= 1.4.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31265 | WordPress Sumo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.34 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31265</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SumoMe Sumo.This issue affects Sumo: from n/a through 1.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31268 | WordPress AppPresser plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31268</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AppPresser Team AppPresser.This issue affects AppPresser: from n/a through 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28718 | An issue in OpenStack magnum yoga-eom version allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the cert_manager.py. component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28718</link><description>An issue in OpenStack magnum yoga-eom version allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the cert_manager.py. component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31269 | WordPress Easy Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31269</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Supsystic Easy Google Maps.This issue affects Easy Google Maps: from n/a through 1.11.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31271 | WordPress Ultimate Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.16 - Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31271</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Supsystic Ultimate Maps by Supsystic.This issue affects Ultimate Maps by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.2.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31272 | WordPress ARForms Form Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31272</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Repute InfoSystems ARForms Form Builder.This issue affects ARForms Form Builder: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31279 | WordPress Generate Child Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31279</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Catch Plugins Generate Child Theme.This issue affects Generate Child Theme: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31289 | WordPress Hello Elementor theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31289</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Elementor Hello Elementor.This issue affects Hello Elementor: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31293 | WordPress Easy Digital Downloads plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31293</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Easy Digital Downloads.This issue affects Easy Digital Downloads: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31301 | WordPress Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31301</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Themeisle Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG.This issue affects Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG: from n/a through 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31303 | WordPress Sign-up Sheets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.11.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31303</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Fetch Designs Sign-up Sheets.This issue affects Sign-up Sheets: from n/a through 2.2.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47714 | IBM Sterling File Gateway cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47714</link><description>IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.9, 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3, and 6.2.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  271531.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31305 | WordPress Transcoder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31305</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in rtCamp Transcoder.This issue affects Transcoder: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31354 | WordPress Slideshow Gallery LITE plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31354</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tribulant Slideshow Gallery.This issue affects Slideshow Gallery: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31360 | WordPress Benchmark Email Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31360</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Coded Commerce, LLC Benchmark Email Lite.This issue affects Benchmark Email Lite: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31362 | WordPress ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Memberships, Groups and Communities plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31362</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31363 | WordPress LifterLMS plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31363</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in LifterLMS.This issue affects LifterLMS: from n/a through 7.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31364 | WordPress ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31364</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ELEXtensions ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts.This issue affects ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27261 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27261</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.2 could allow a privileged user to install a potentially dangerous tar file, which could give them access to subsequent systems where the package was installed.  IBM X-Force ID:  283986.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-8006 | The server in Circontrol Raption through 5.11.2 has a pre-authentication stack-based buffer overflow that can be exploited to gain run-time ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8006</link><description>The server in Circontrol Raption through 5.11.2 has a pre-authentication stack-based buffer overflow that can be exploited to gain run-time control of the device as root. The ocpp1.5 and pwrstudio binaries on the charging station do not use a number of common exploitation mitigations. In particular, there are no stack canaries and they do not use the Position Independent Executable (PIE) format.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31371 | WordPress WP Event Aggregator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31371</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Xylus Themes WP Event Aggregator.This issue affects WP Event Aggregator: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31372 | WordPress No-Bot Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31372</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Arnan de Gans No-Bot Registration.This issue affects No-Bot Registration: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3054 | WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHAR Deserialization in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.99 via deser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3054</link><description>WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHAR Deserialization in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.99 via deserialization of untrusted input at the wpvividstg_get_custom_exclude_path_free action. This is due to the plugin not providing sufficient path validation on the tree_node[node][id] parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with admin-level access and above, to call files using a PHAR wrapper that will deserialize the data and call arbitrary PHP Objects. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3211 | The Shopping Cart &amp; eCommerce Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'productid' attribute of the ec_addtocart sh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3211</link><description>The Shopping Cart &amp; eCommerce Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'productid' attribute of the ec_addtocart shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3400 | PAN-OS: OS Command Injection Vulnerability in GlobalProtect Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3400</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Fixes for PAN-OS 10.2, PAN-OS 11.0, and PAN-OS 11.1 are in development and are expected to be released by April 14, 2024. Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability. All other versions of PAN-OS are also not impacted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27309 | Apache Kafka: Potential incorrect access control during migration from ZK mode to KRaft mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27309</link><description>While an Apache Kafka cluster is being migrated from ZooKeeper mode to KRaft mode, in some cases ACLs will not be correctly enforced.

Two preconditions are needed to trigger the bug:
1. The administrator decides to remove an ACL
2. The resource associated with the removed ACL continues to have two or more other ACLs associated with it after the removal.

When those two preconditions are met, Kafka will treat the resource as if it had only one ACL associated with it after the removal, rather than the two or more that would be correct.

The incorrect condition is cleared by removing all brokers in ZK mode, or by adding a new ACL to the affected resource. Once the migration is completed, there is no metadata loss (the ACLs all remain).

The full impact depends on the ACLs in use. If only ALLOW ACLs were configured during the migration, the impact would be limited to availability impact. if DENY ACLs were configured, the impact could include confidentiality and integrity impact depending on the ACLs configured, as the DENY ACLs might be ignored due to this vulnerability during the migration period.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22526 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in bandisoft bandiview v7.0, allows local attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via exr image file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22526</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in bandisoft bandiview v7.0, allows local attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via exr image file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29400 | An issue was discovered in RuoYi v4.5.1, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the status parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29400</link><description>An issue was discovered in RuoYi v4.5.1, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the status parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49528 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg version n6.1-3-g466799d4f5, allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49528</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg version n6.1-3-g466799d4f5, allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via the af_dialoguenhance.c:261:5 in the de_stereo component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30614 | An issue in Ametys CMS v4.5.0 and before allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via exposed resources to the error scope.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30614</link><description>An issue in Ametys CMS v4.5.0 and before allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via exposed resources to the error scope.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30850 | An issue in tiagorlampert CHAOS v5.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the BuildClient function within client_service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30850</link><description>An issue in tiagorlampert CHAOS v5.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the BuildClient function within client_service.go</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 05:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22734 | An issue was discovered in AMCS Group Trux Waste Management Software before version 7.19.0018.26912, allows local attackers to obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22734</link><description>An issue was discovered in AMCS Group Trux Waste Management Software before version 7.19.0018.26912, allows local attackers to obtain sensitive information via a static, hard-coded AES Key-IV pair in the TxUtilities.dll and TruxUser.cfg components.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 05:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44855 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44855</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the rdiag, sender, and recipients parameters of the sub_219C4 function in the acu_web file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44856 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44856</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the rstat, sender, and recipients' parameters of the sub_21D24 function in the acu_web file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 04:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44857 | An issue in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the sub_21D24 functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44857</link><description>An issue in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the sub_21D24 function in the acu_web component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 04:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44853 | \An issue was discovered in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44853</link><description>\An issue was discovered in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the sub_219C4 function in the acu_web file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 04:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44852 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44852</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR VSAT Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the c_set_traps_decode function in the acu_web file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 04:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44854 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44854</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cobham SAILOR Ku v.164B019, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the c_set_rslog_decode function in the acu_web file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 03:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45186 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45186</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.9, 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3, and 6.2.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  268691.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2137 | The All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple pricing widge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2137</link><description>The All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple pricing widgets (e.g. Pricing Single, Pricing Icon, Pricing Tab) in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 02:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2801 | The Shopkeeper Extender plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'image_slide' shortcode in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2801</link><description>The Shopkeeper Extender plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'image_slide' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 02:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50307 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50307</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.9, 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3, and 6.2.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  273338.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 02:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22357 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22357</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.9, 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3, and 6.2.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  280894.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 02:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6489 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 01:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6678 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 01:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2279 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 01:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3092 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 01:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>