<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 15:38:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-10401 | D-Link DIR-823x diag_ping command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10401</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-823x up to 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/diag_ping. Performing manipulation of the argument target_addr results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10400 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System ticket-message.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10400</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /routers/ticket-message.php. Such manipulation of the argument ticket_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0164 | IBM QRadar SIEM information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0164</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 through 7.5 Update Pack 13 Independent Fix 01 could allow a local privileged user to perform unauthorized actions on configuration files due to improper permission assignment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10399 | Korzh EasyQuery Query Builder UI fetch sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10399</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Korzh EasyQuery up to 7.4.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/easyquery/models/nwind/fetch of the component Query Builder UI. This manipulation causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36035 | IBM PowerVM Hypervisor denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36035</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW950.00 through FW950.E0, FW1050.00 through FW1050.50, and FW1060.00 through FW1060.40 could allow a local privileged user to cause a denial of service by issuing a specially crafted IBM i hypervisor call that would disclose memory contents or consume excessive memory resources.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10204 | Unauth Admin Reset Password on AC Smart II</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10204</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in AC Smart II where passwords can be changed without authorization. This page contains a hidden form for resetting the administrator password. The attacker can manipulate the page using developer tools to display and use the form. This form allows you to change the administrator password without verifying login status or user permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10398 | fcba_zzm ics-park Smart Park Management System FileUploadUtils.java unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10398</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in fcba_zzm ics-park Smart Park Management System 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file FileUploadUtils.java. The manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10397 | Magicblack MacCMS API server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10397</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Magicblack MacCMS 2025.1000.4050. This affects an unknown part of the component API Handler. The manipulation of the argument cjurl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 11:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10396 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software edit_role.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10396</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_role.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10395 | Magicblack MacCMS Scheduled Task col_url server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10395</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Magicblack MacCMS 2025.1000.4050. Affected by this vulnerability is the function col_url of the component Scheduled Task Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument cjurl results in server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 08:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10394 | fcba_zzm ics-park Smart Park Management System Scheduled Task JobController.java code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10394</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in fcba_zzm ics-park Smart Park Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file ruoyi-quartz/src/main/java/com/ruoyi/quartz/controller/JobController.java of the component Scheduled Task Module. Such manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 06:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10393 | miurla morphic HTTP Status Code 3xx advanced-search fetchHtml server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10393</link><description>A flaw has been found in miurla morphic up to 0.4.5. This impacts the function fetchHtml of the file /api/advanced-search of the component HTTP Status Code 3xx Handler. This manipulation causes server-side request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 06:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10392 | Mercury KM08-708H GiGA WiFi Wave2 HTTP Header stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10392</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Mercury KM08-708H GiGA WiFi Wave2 1.1.14. This affects an unknown function of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Host results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 05:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10391 | CRMEB OutAccountServices.php testOutUrl server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10391</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CRMEB up to 5.6.1. The impacted element is the function testOutUrl of the file app/services/out/OutAccountServices.php. The manipulation of the argument push_token_url leads to server-side request forgery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 05:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59363 | In One Identity OneLogin before 2025.3.0, a request returns the OIDC client secret with GET Apps API v2 (even though this secret should only...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59363</link><description>In One Identity OneLogin before 2025.3.0, a request returns the OIDC client secret with GET Apps API v2 (even though this secret should only be returned when an App is first created),</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 04:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10390 | CRMEB UserAddressServices.php editAddress improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10390</link><description>A weakness has been identified in CRMEB up to 5.6.1. The affected element is the function editAddress of the file app/services/user/UserAddressServices.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 04:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10389 | CRMEB Administrator Password SystemAdminServices.php save improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10389</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CRMEB up to 5.6.1. Impacted is the function Save of the file app/services/system/admin/SystemAdminServices.php of the component Administrator Password Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 04:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10388 | Selleo Mentingo Create New Course Basic Settings enroll-course cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10388</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Selleo Mentingo 2025.08.27. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/course/enroll-course of the component Create New Course Basic Settings. Such manipulation of the argument Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 03:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10387 | codesiddhant Jasmin Ransomware handshake.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10387</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in codesiddhant Jasmin Ransomware up to 1.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /handshake.php. This manipulation of the argument machine_name/computer_user/os/date/time/ip/location/systemid/password causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 03:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10386 | Yida ECMS Consulting Enterprise Management System POST Request login.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10386</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yida ECMS Consulting Enterprise Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /login.do of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument requestUrl results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 02:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10385 | Mercury KM08-708H GiGA WiFi Wave2 mcr_setSysAdm sub_450B2C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10385</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Mercury KM08-708H GiGA WiFi Wave2 1.1. Affected by this issue is the function sub_450B2C of the file /goform/mcr_setSysAdm. The manipulation of the argument ChgUserId leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 02:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10384 | yangzongzhuan RuoYi Role cancelAll improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10384</link><description>A flaw has been found in yangzongzhuan RuoYi up to 4.8.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/role/authUser/cancelAll of the component Role Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument roleId/userIds can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 19:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10374 | Shenzhen Sixun Business Management System OperatorStop improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10374</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Shenzhen Sixun Business Management System 7/11. This affects an unknown part of the file /Adm/OperatorStop. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 19:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10373 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_turma_tipo_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10373</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_turma_tipo_cad.php. Such manipulation of the argument nm_tipo leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10372 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_modulo_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10372</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_modulo_cad.php. This manipulation of the argument nm_tipo/descricao causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10371 | eCharge Hardy Barth Salia PLCC api.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10371</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in eCharge Hardy Barth Salia PLCC 2.2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api.php. The manipulation of the argument setrfidlist results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10370 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID userScripts.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10370</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /htdocs/userScripts.php. The manipulation of the argument Custom script leads to cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 17:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10369 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID cardRegisterNew.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10369</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /htdocs/cardRegisterNew.php. Executing manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 16:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10368 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID manageFilesFolders.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /htdocs/manageFilesFolders.php. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10367 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID cardEdit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10367</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /htdocs/cardEdit.php. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10366 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID inc.setWlanIpMail.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10366</link><description>A flaw has been found in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /htdocs/inc.setWlanIpMail.php. This manipulation of the argument Email address causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10359 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 wireless.cgi sub_404DBC os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10359</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. This impacts the function sub_404DBC of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi. The manipulation of the argument macAddr results in os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10358 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 wireless.cgi sub_404850 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10358</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. This affects the function sub_404850 of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi. The manipulation of the argument delete_list leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10340 | WhatCD Gazelle Commit Message change_log.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10340</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in WhatCD Gazelle up to 63b337026d49b5cf63ce4be20fdabdc880112fa3. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /sections/tools/managers/change_log.php of the component Commit Message Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument Message can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 02:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10332 | cdevroe unmark info.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cdevroe unmark up to 1.9.3. Impacted is an unknown function of the file application/views/marks/info.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Title results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 02:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10331 | cdevroe unmark Marks.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10331</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in cdevroe unmark up to 1.9.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /application/controllers/Marks.php. Such manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 02:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10330 | cdevroe unmark searchform.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10330</link><description>A flaw has been found in cdevroe unmark up to 1.9.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file application/views/layouts/topbar/searchform.php. This manipulation of the argument q causes cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10329 | cdevroe unmark Marks.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10329</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in cdevroe unmark up to 1.9.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /application/controllers/Marks.php. The manipulation of the argument url results in server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10328 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID playsinglefile.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10328</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /htdocs/api/playlist/playsinglefile.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10176 | The Hack Repair Guy&amp;#x27;s Plugin Archiver &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10176</link><description>The The Hack Repair Guy's Plugin Archiver plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the prepare_items function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10327 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID shuffle.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10327</link><description>A weakness has been identified in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /htdocs/api/playlist/shuffle.php. Executing manipulation of the argument playlist can lead to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10326 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID single.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10326</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.8.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /htdocs/api/playlist/single.php. Performing manipulation of the argument playlist results in os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45583 | Incorrect access control in the FTP protocol of Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to authenticate into the servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45583</link><description>Incorrect access control in the FTP protocol of Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to authenticate into the service using any combination of username and password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45584 | Incorrect access control in the web service of Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to download car information with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45584</link><description>Incorrect access control in the web service of Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to download car information without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45585 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45585</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the wifi_sta_ssid or wifi_ap_ssid parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45586 | An issue in Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to arbitrarily overwrite files via supplying a crafted PUT request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45586</link><description>An issue in Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to arbitrarily overwrite files via supplying a crafted PUT request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45587 | A stack overflow in the FTP service of Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45587</link><description>A stack overflow in the FTP service of Audi UTR 2.0 Universal Traffic Recorder 2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10325 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 login.cgi sub_401BA4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10325</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. This impacts the function sub_401340/sub_401BA4 of the file /cgi-bin/login.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument ipaddr leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43795 | Open redirect vulnerability in the System Settings in Liferay Portal 7.1.0 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.4 , ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43795</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in the System Settings in Liferay Portal 7.1.0 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.4 , 7.4 GA through update 92, 7.3 GA through update 35, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_configuration_admin_web_portlet_SystemSettingsPortlet_redirect parameter.

Open redirect vulnerability in the Instance Settings in Liferay Portal 7.1.0 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.4 , 7.4 GA through update 92, 7.3 GA through update 35, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_configuration_admin_web_portlet_InstanceSettingsPortlet_redirect parameter.

Open redirect vulnerability in the Site Settings in Liferay Portal 7.1.0 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.4 , 7.4 GA through update 92, 7.3 GA through update 35, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_site_admin_web_portlet_SiteSettingsPortlet_redirect parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10324 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 firewall.cgi sub_401C5C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10324</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. This affects the function sub_401C5C of the file firewall.cgi. This manipulation of the argument pingFrmWANFilterEnabled/blockSynFloodEnabled/blockPortScanEnabled/remoteManagementEnabled causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43796 | Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.0 through 2023.Q3.4, 7.4 GA through update 92 and 7.3 GA though update 35 do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43796</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.0 through 2023.Q3.4, 7.4 GA through update 92 and 7.3 GA though update 35 does not limit the number of objects returned from a GraphQL queries, which allows remote attackers to perform denial-of-service (DoS) attacks on the application by executing queries that return a large number of objects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10323 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 wizard_rep.shtml sub_409184 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10323</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. The impacted element is the function sub_409184 of the file /wizard_rep.shtml. The manipulation of the argument sel_EncrypTyp results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10322 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 sysinit.html password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10322</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /sysinit.html. The manipulation of the argument newpass/confpass leads to weak password recovery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58434 | Flowise Cloud and Local Deployments have Unauthenticated Password Reset Token Disclosure that Leads to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58434</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. In version 3.0.5 and earlier, the `forgot-password` endpoint in Flowise returns sensitive information including a valid password reset `tempToken` without authentication or verification. This enables any attacker to generate a reset token for arbitrary users and directly reset their password, leading to a complete account takeover (ATO). This vulnerability applies to both the cloud service (`cloud.flowiseai.com`) and self-hosted/local Flowise deployments that expose the same API. Commit 9e178d68873eb876073846433a596590d3d9c863 secures password reset endpoints. Several recommended remediation steps are available. Do not return reset tokens or sensitive account details in API responses. Tokens must only be delivered securely via the registered email channel. Ensure `forgot-password` responds with a generic success message regardless of input, to avoid user enumeration. Require strong validation of the `tempToken` (e.g., single-use, short expiry, tied to request origin, validated against email delivery). Apply the same fixes to both cloud and self-hosted/local deployments. Log and monitor password reset requests for suspicious activity. Consider multi-factor verification for sensitive accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10321 | Wavlink WL-WN578W2 live_online.shtml information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10321</link><description>A flaw has been found in Wavlink WL-WN578W2 221110. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /live_online.shtml. Executing manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4234 | Cortex XDR Microsoft 365 Defender Pack: Cleartext Exposure of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4234</link><description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR Microsoft 365 Defender Pack can result in exposure of user credentials in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4235 | User-ID Credential Agent: Cleartext Exposure of Service Account password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4235</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks User-ID Credential Agent (Windows-based) can expose the service account password under specific non-default configurations. This allows an unprivileged Domain User to escalate privileges by exploiting the account’s permissions. The impact varies by configuration:
  *  Minimally Privileged Accounts: Enable disruption of User-ID Credential Agent operations (e.g., uninstalling or disabling the agent service), weakening network security policies that leverage  Credential Phishing Prevention https://docs.paloaltonetworks.com/advanced-url-filtering/administration/url-filtering-features/credential-phishing-prevention  under a  Domain Credential Filter https://docs.paloaltonetworks.com/advanced-url-filtering/administration/url-filtering-features/credential-phishing-prevention/methods-to-check-for-corporate-credential-submissions  configuration.
  *  Elevated Accounts (Server Operator, Domain Join, Legacy Features): Permit increased impacts, including server control (e.g., shutdown/restart), domain manipulation (e.g., rogue computer objects), and network compromise via reconnaissance or client probing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52074 | PHPGURUKUL Online Shopping Portal 2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to lack of input sanitization in the quantity paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52074</link><description>PHPGURUKUL Online Shopping Portal 2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to lack of input sanitization in the quantity parameter when adding a product to the cart.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56467 | An issue was discovered in AXIS BANK LIMITED Axis Mobile App 9.9 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information without UPI PIN such as ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56467</link><description>An issue was discovered in AXIS BANK LIMITED Axis Mobile App 9.9 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information without UPI PIN such as account information, balances, transaction history, and other unspecified information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45431 | OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x has Improper Input Validation. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45431</link><description>OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x has Improper Input Validation. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of remote L2CAP channel ID (CID). An attacker can leverage this to create an L2CAP channel with the null identifier assigned as a remote CID.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45432 | OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x mishandles a function call. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45432</link><description>OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x mishandles a function call. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. The issue results from an incorrect variable used as a function argument. An attacker can leverage this to cause unexpected behavior or obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45433 | OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x has Incorrect Control Flow Scoping. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth sta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45433</link><description>OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x has Incorrect Control Flow Scoping. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. The issue results from the lack of proper return control flow after detecting an unusual condition. An attacker can leverage this to bypass a security validation and make the incoming data be processed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45434 | OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x has a Use-After-Free. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. The issue ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45434</link><description>OpenSynergy BlueSDK (aka Blue SDK) through 6.x has a Use-After-Free. The specific flaw exists within the BlueSDK Bluetooth stack. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object before performing operations on the object (aka use after free). An attacker can leverage this to achieve remote code execution in the context of a user account under which the Bluetooth process runs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43787 | A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q3.0, 2025.Q2.0 through 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43787</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q3.0, 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.12, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.17, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20 allows an remote authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript through the organization site names. The malicious payload is stored and executed without proper sanitization or escaping.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10320 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS updatePwd weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10320</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in iteachyou Dreamer CMS up to 4.1.3.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/user/updatePwd. Performing manipulation results in weak password requirements. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39792 | dm: Always split write BIOs to zoned device limits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39792</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dm: Always split write BIOs to zoned device limits

Any zoned DM target that requires zone append emulation will use the
block layer zone write plugging. In such case, DM target drivers must
not split BIOs using dm_accept_partial_bio() as doing so can potentially
lead to deadlocks with queue freeze operations. Regular write operations
used to emulate zone append operations also cannot be split by the
target driver as that would result in an invalid writen sector value
return using the BIO sector.

In order for zoned DM target drivers to avoid such incorrect BIO
splitting, we must ensure that large BIOs are split before being passed
to the map() function of the target, thus guaranteeing that the
limits for the mapped device are not exceeded.

dm-crypt and dm-flakey are the only target drivers supporting zoned
devices and using dm_accept_partial_bio().

In the case of dm-crypt, this function is used to split BIOs to the
internal max_write_size limit (which will be suppressed in a different
patch). However, since crypt_alloc_buffer() uses a bioset allowing only
up to BIO_MAX_VECS (256) vectors in a BIO. The dm-crypt device
max_segments limit, which is not set and so default to BLK_MAX_SEGMENTS
(128), must thus be respected and write BIOs split accordingly.

In the case of dm-flakey, since zone append emulation is not required,
the block layer zone write plugging is not used and no splitting of BIOs
required.

Modify the function dm_zone_bio_needs_split() to use the block layer
helper function bio_needs_zone_write_plugging() to force a call to
bio_split_to_limits() in dm_split_and_process_bio(). This allows DM
target drivers to avoid using dm_accept_partial_bio() for write
operations on zoned DM devices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39793 | io_uring/memmap: cast nr_pages to size_t before shifting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39793</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/memmap: cast nr_pages to size_t before shifting

If the allocated size exceeds UINT_MAX, then it's necessary to cast
the mr-&gt;nr_pages value to size_t to prevent it from overflowing. In
practice this isn't much of a concern as the required memory size will
have been validated upfront, and accounted to the user. And &gt; 4GB sizes
will be necessary to make the lack of a cast a problem, which greatly
exceeds normal user locked_vm settings that are generally in the kb to
mb range. However, if root is used, then accounting isn't done, and
then it's possible to hit this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39794 | ARM: tegra: Use I/O memcpy to write to IRAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39794</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ARM: tegra: Use I/O memcpy to write to IRAM

Kasan crashes the kernel trying to check boundaries when using the
normal memcpy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39795 | block: avoid possible overflow for chunk_sectors check in blk_stack_limits()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39795</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

block: avoid possible overflow for chunk_sectors check in blk_stack_limits()

In blk_stack_limits(), we check that the t-&gt;chunk_sectors value is a
multiple of the t-&gt;physical_block_size value.

However, by finding the chunk_sectors value in bytes, we may overflow
the unsigned int which holds chunk_sectors, so change the check to be
based on sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39796 | net: lapbether: ignore ops-locked netdevs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39796</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: lapbether: ignore ops-locked netdevs

Syzkaller managed to trigger lock dependency in xsk_notify via
register_netdevice. As discussed in [0], using register_netdevice
in the notifiers is problematic so skip adding lapbeth for ops-locked
devices.

       xsk_notifier+0xa4/0x280 net/xdp/xsk.c:1645
       notifier_call_chain+0xbc/0x410 kernel/notifier.c:85
       call_netdevice_notifiers_info+0xbe/0x140 net/core/dev.c:2230
       call_netdevice_notifiers_extack net/core/dev.c:2268 [inline]
       call_netdevice_notifiers net/core/dev.c:2282 [inline]
       unregister_netdevice_many_notify+0xf9d/0x2700 net/core/dev.c:12077
       unregister_netdevice_many net/core/dev.c:12140 [inline]
       unregister_netdevice_queue+0x305/0x3f0 net/core/dev.c:11984
       register_netdevice+0x18f1/0x2270 net/core/dev.c:11149
       lapbeth_new_device drivers/net/wan/lapbether.c:420 [inline]
       lapbeth_device_event+0x5b1/0xbe0 drivers/net/wan/lapbether.c:462
       notifier_call_chain+0xbc/0x410 kernel/notifier.c:85
       call_netdevice_notifiers_info+0xbe/0x140 net/core/dev.c:2230
       call_netdevice_notifiers_extack net/core/dev.c:2268 [inline]
       call_netdevice_notifiers net/core/dev.c:2282 [inline]
       __dev_notify_flags+0x12c/0x2e0 net/core/dev.c:9497
       netif_change_flags+0x108/0x160 net/core/dev.c:9526
       dev_change_flags+0xba/0x250 net/core/dev_api.c:68
       devinet_ioctl+0x11d5/0x1f50 net/ipv4/devinet.c:1200
       inet_ioctl+0x3a7/0x3f0 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:1001

0: https://lore.kernel.org/netdev/20250625140357.6203d0af@kernel.org/</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39797 | xfrm: Duplicate SPI Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39797</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xfrm: Duplicate SPI Handling

The issue originates when Strongswan initiates an XFRM_MSG_ALLOCSPI
Netlink message, which triggers the kernel function xfrm_alloc_spi().
This function is expected to ensure uniqueness of the Security Parameter
Index (SPI) for inbound Security Associations (SAs). However, it can
return success even when the requested SPI is already in use, leading
to duplicate SPIs assigned to multiple inbound SAs, differentiated
only by their destination addresses.

This behavior causes inconsistencies during SPI lookups for inbound packets.
Since the lookup may return an arbitrary SA among those with the same SPI,
packet processing can fail, resulting in packet drops.

According to RFC 4301 section 4.4.2 , for inbound processing a unicast SA
is uniquely identified by the SPI and optionally protocol.

Reproducing the Issue Reliably:
To consistently reproduce the problem, restrict the available SPI range in
charon.conf : spi_min = 0x10000000 spi_max = 0x10000002
This limits the system to only 2 usable SPI values.
Next, create more than 2 Child SA. each using unique pair of src/dst address.
As soon as the 3rd Child SA is initiated, it will be assigned a duplicate
SPI, since the SPI pool is already exhausted.
With a narrow SPI range, the issue is consistently reproducible.
With a broader/default range, it becomes rare and unpredictable.

Current implementation:
xfrm_spi_hash() lookup function computes hash using daddr, proto, and family.
So if two SAs have the same SPI but different destination addresses, then
they will:
a. Hash into different buckets
b. Be stored in different linked lists (byspi + h)
c. Not be seen in the same hlist_for_each_entry_rcu() iteration.
As a result, the lookup will result in NULL and kernel allows that Duplicate SPI

Proposed Change:
xfrm_state_lookup_spi_proto() does a truly global search - across all states,
regardless of hash bucket and matches SPI and proto.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39798 | NFS: Fix the setting of capabilities when automounting a new filesystem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39798</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

NFS: Fix the setting of capabilities when automounting a new filesystem

Capabilities cannot be inherited when we cross into a new filesystem.
They need to be reset to the minimal defaults, and then probed for
again.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39799 | ACPI: processor: perflib: Move problematic pr-&amp;gt;performance check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39799</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ACPI: processor: perflib: Move problematic pr-&gt;performance check

Commit d33bd88ac0eb ("ACPI: processor: perflib: Fix initial _PPC limit
application") added a pr-&gt;performance check that prevents the frequency
QoS request from being added when the given processor has no performance
object.  Unfortunately, this causes a WARN() in freq_qos_remove_request()
to trigger on an attempt to take the given CPU offline later because the
frequency QoS object has not been added for it due to the missing
performance object.

Address this by moving the pr-&gt;performance check before calling
acpi_processor_get_platform_limit() so it only prevents a limit from
being set for the CPU if the performance object is not present.  This
way, the frequency QoS request is added as it was before the above
commit and it is present all the time along with the CPU's cpufreq
policy regardless of whether or not the CPU is online.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57577 | An issue in H3C Device R365V300R004 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57577</link><description>An issue in H3C Device R365V300R004 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the default password</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57579 | An issue in TOTOLINK Wi-Fi 6 Router Series Device X2000R-Gh-V2.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the default passwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57579</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK Wi-Fi 6 Router Series Device X2000R-Gh-V2.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the default password</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57578 | An issue in H3C Magic M Device M2V100R006 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57578</link><description>An issue in H3C Magic M Device M2V100R006 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the default password</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55835 | File Upload vulnerability in SueamCMS v.0.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lack of filtering.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55835</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in SueamCMS v.0.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lack of filtering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10319 | JeecgBoot Tenant Log Export exportLog improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10319</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sys/tenant/exportLog of the component Tenant Log Export. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55996 | Viber Desktop 25.6.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection via the text parameter of the message compose/forward interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55996</link><description>Viber Desktop 25.6.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection via the text parameter of the message compose/forward interface</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10364 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary Command Injection in Evertz SDVN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10364</link><description>The Evertz SDVN 3080ipx-10G is a High Bandwidth Ethernet Switching Fabric for Video Application. This device exposes a web management interface on port 80. This web management interface can be used by administrators to control product
features, setup network switching, and register license among other features. The application has been developed in PHP with the webEASY SDK, also named ‘ewb’ by Evertz.

This web interface has two endpoints that are vulnerable to arbitrary command injection (CVE-2025-4009, CVE-2025-10364) and the authentication mechanism has a flaw leading to authentication bypass (CVE-2025-10365).

CVE-2025-4009 covers the command injection in feature-transfer-import.php
CVE-2025-10364 covers the command injection in feature-transfer-export.php

Remote unauthenticated attackers can gain arbitrary command execution with elevated privileges ( root ) on affected devices.

This level of access could lead to serious business impact such as the interruption of media streaming, modification of media being streamed, alteration of closed captions being generated, among others.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10365 | Authentication Bypass in Evertz SDVN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10365</link><description>The Evertz SDVN 3080ipx-10G is a High Bandwidth Ethernet Switching Fabric for Video Application. This device exposes a web management interface on port 80. This web management interface can be used by administrators to control product
features, setup network switching, and register license among other features. The application has been developed in PHP with the webEASY SDK, also named ‘ewb’ by Evertz.

This web interface has two endpoints that are vulnerable to arbitrary command injection (CVE-2025-4009, CVE-2025-10364) and the authentication mechanism has a flaw leading to authentication bypass (CVE-2025-10365).

Remote unauthenticated attackers can gain arbitrary command execution with elevated privileges ( root ) on affected devices.

This level of access could lead to serious business impact such as the interruption of media streaming, modification of media being streamed, alteration of closed captions being generated, among others.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9556 | CVE-2025-9556</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9556</link><description>Langchaingo supports the use of jinja2 syntax when parsing prompts, which is in turn parsed using the gonja library v1.5.3.
Gonja supports include and extends syntax to read files, which leads to a server side template injection vulnerability within langchaingo, allowing an attacker to insert a statement into a prompt to read the "etc/passwd" file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59058 | httpsig-rs&amp;#x27;s HMAC verification is vulnerable to timing attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59058</link><description>httpsig-rs is a Rust implementation of IETF RFC 9421 http message signatures. Prior to version 0.0.19, the HMAC signature comparison is not timing-safe. This makes anyone who uses HS256 signature verification vulnerable to a timing attack that allows the attacker to forge a signature. Version 0.0.19 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59139 | Hono has Body Limit Middleware Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59139</link><description>Hono is a Web application framework that provides support for any JavaScript runtime. In versions prior to 4.9.7, a flaw in the `bodyLimit` middleware could allow bypassing the configured request body size limit when conflicting HTTP headers were present. The middleware previously prioritized the `Content-Length` header even when a `Transfer-Encoding: chunked` header was also included. According to the HTTP specification, `Content-Length` must be ignored in such cases. This discrepancy could allow oversized request bodies to bypass the configured limit. Most standards-compliant runtimes and reverse proxies may reject such malformed requests with `400 Bad Request`, so the practical impact depends on the runtime and deployment environment. If body size limits are used as a safeguard against large or malicious requests, this flaw could allow attackers to send oversized request bodies. The primary risk is denial of service (DoS) due to excessive memory or CPU consumption when handling very large requests. The implementation has been updated to align with the HTTP specification, ensuring that `Transfer-Encoding` takes precedence over `Content-Length`. The issue is fixed in Hono v4.9.7, and all users should upgrade immediately.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59054 | dstack has insecure LUKS2 persistent storage partitions that may be opened and used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59054</link><description>dstack is a software development kit (SDK) to simplify the deployment of arbitrary containerized apps into trusted execution environments. In versions of dstack prior to 0.5.4, a malicious host may provide a crafted LUKS2 data volume to a dstack CVM for use as the `/data` mount. The guest will open the volume and write secret data using a volume key known to the attacker, causing disclosure of Wireguard keys and other secret information. The attacker can also pre-load data on the device, which could potentially compromise guest execution. LUKS2 volume metadata is not authenticated and supports null key-encryption algorithms, allowing an attacker to create a volume such that the volume opens (cryptsetup open) without error using any passphrase or token, records all writes in plaintext (or ciphertext with an attacker-known key), and/or contains arbitrary data chosen by the attacker. Version 0.5.4 of dstack contains a patch that addresses LUKS headers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10318 | JeecgBoot WebSocket Message sendWebSocketMsg improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10318</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/system/sendWebSocketMsg of the component WebSocket Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument userIds leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8699 | Some "Stored Value" Unattended Payment Solutions of KioSoft use vulnerable NFC cards. Attackers could potentially use this vulnerability to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8699</link><description>Some "Stored Value" Unattended Payment Solutions of KioSoft use vulnerable NFC cards. Attackers could potentially use this vulnerability to change the balance on the cards and generate money. The account balance is stored on an insecure MiFare Classic NFC card and can be read and written back. By carefully observing changes in card dumps, one can identify fields that store the cash value of the card. Additionally, a checksum can be identified, which is created by XOR-ing the cash and an unknown field with a certain value. By updating the fields accordingly, arbitrary amounts of money can be loaded onto the card (up to $655,35) to pay for goods.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6638 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in huggingface/transformers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6638</link><description>A Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability was discovered in the Hugging Face Transformers library, specifically affecting the MarianTokenizer's `remove_language_code()` method. This vulnerability is present in version 4.52.4 and has been fixed in version 4.53.0. The issue arises from inefficient regex processing, which can be exploited by crafted input strings containing malformed language code patterns, leading to excessive CPU consumption and potential denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27233 | Zabbix Agent 2 smartctl plugin argument injection in Zabbix 6.0 and later.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27233</link><description>Zabbix Agent 2 smartctl plugin does not properly sanitize smart.disk.get parameters, allowing an attacker to inject unexpected arguments into the smartctl command. This can be used to leak the NTLMv2 hash from a Windows system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27238 | API hostprototype.get lists data to users with insufficient authorization.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27238</link><description>Due to a bug in Zabbix API, the hostprototype.get method lists all host prototypes to users that do not have any user groups assigned to them.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27240 | Secondary-order SQL injection in Zabbix Server when deleting an autoregistered host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27240</link><description>A Zabbix adminitrator can inject arbitrary SQL during the autoremoval of hosts by inserting malicious SQL in the 'Visible name' field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10267 | NewType Infortech｜NUP Portal - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10267</link><description>NUP Portal developed by NewType Infortech has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to directly upload files. If the attacker manages to bypass the file extension restrictions, they could upload a webshell and execute it on the server side.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27234 | Zabbix Agent 2 smartctl plugin RCE vulnerability in Zabbix 5.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27234</link><description>Zabbix Agent 2 smartctl plugin does not properly sanitize smart.disk.get parameters, allowing an attacker to inject unexpected arguments into the smartctl command. In Zabbix 5.0 this allows for remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10265 | Digiever｜NVR - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10265</link><description>Certain models of NVR developed by Digiever has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10266 | NewType Infortech｜NUP Portal - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10266</link><description>NUP Pro developed by NewType Infortech has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10264 | Digiever｜NVR - Exposure of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10264</link><description>Certain models of NVR developed by Digiever has an Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remoter attackers to access the system configuration file and obtain plaintext credentials of the NVR and its connected cameras.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7448 | Man in the middle (MitM) attack vulnerability in Wi-SUN library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7448</link><description>Wi-SUN unexpected 4- Way Handshake packet receptions may lead to predictable keys and potentially leading to Man in the middle (MitM) attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21042 | Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Apr-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21042</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Apr-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21043 | Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21043</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1250 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1250</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.0 before 18.1.6, 18.2 before 18.2.6, and 18.3 before 18.3.2 that could have allowed an authenticated user to stall background job processing by sending specially crafted commit messages, merge request descriptions, or notes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2256 | Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2256</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 7.12 before 18.1.6, 18.2 before 18.2.6, and 18.3 before 18.3.2 that could have allowed unauthorized users to render the GitLab instance unresponsive to legitimate users by sending multiple concurrent large SAML responses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6454 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6454</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.11 before 18.1.6, 18.2 before 18.2.6, and 18.3 before 18.3.2 that could have allowed authenticated users to make unintended internal requests through proxy environments by injecting crafted sequences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6769 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6769</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.1 before 18.1.6, 18.2 before 18.2.6, and 18.3 before 18.3.2 that could have allowed authenticated users to view administrator-only maintenance notes by accessing runner details through specific interfaces.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7337 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7337</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 7.8 before 18.1.6, 18.2 before 18.2.6, and 18.3 before 18.3.2 that could have allowed an authenticated user with Developer-level access to cause a persistent denial of service affecting all users on a GitLab instance by uploading large files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3650 | jQuery Colorbox &amp;lt;= 4.6.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3650</link><description>The jQuery Colorbox WordPress plugin through 4.6.3 uses the colorbox library, which does not sanitize title attributes on links before using them, allowing users with at least the contributor role to conduct XSS attacks against administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8280 | Contact Form 7 reCAPTCHA &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Reflected XSS via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;REQUEST_URI&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8280</link><description>The Contact Form 7 reCAPTCHA WordPress plugin through 1.2.0 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58781 | WTW-EAGLE App does not properly validate server certificates, which may allow a man-in-the-middle attacker to monitor encrypted traffic.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58781</link><description>WTW-EAGLE App does not properly validate server certificates, which may allow a man-in-the-middle attacker to monitor encrypted traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10291 | linlinjava litemall cancel WxAftersaleController improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10291</link><description>A weakness has been identified in linlinjava litemall up to 1.8.0. This affects the function WxAftersaleController of the file /wx/aftersale/cancel. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8575 | LWS Cleaner &amp;lt;= 2.4.1.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion via &amp;#x27;lws_cl_delete_file&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8575</link><description>The LWS Cleaner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'lws_cl_delete_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10148 | predictable WebSocket mask</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10148</link><description>curl's websocket code did not update the 32 bit mask pattern for each new
 outgoing frame as the specification says. Instead it used a fixed mask that
persisted and was used throughout the entire connection.

A predictable mask pattern allows for a malicious server to induce traffic
between the two communicating parties that could be interpreted by an involved
proxy (configured or transparent) as genuine, real, HTTP traffic with content
and thereby poison its cache. That cached poisoned content could then be
served to all users of that proxy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9086 | Out of bounds read for cookie path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9086</link><description>1. A cookie is set using the `secure` keyword for `https://target`
2. curl is redirected to or otherwise made to speak with `http://target` (same
   hostname, but using clear text HTTP) using the same cookie set
3. The same cookie name is set - but with just a slash as path (`path='/'`).
   Since this site is not secure, the cookie *should* just be ignored.
4. A bug in the path comparison logic makes curl read outside a heap buffer
   boundary

The bug either causes a crash or it potentially makes the comparison come to
the wrong conclusion and lets the clear-text site override the contents of the
secure cookie, contrary to expectations and depending on the memory contents
immediately following the single-byte allocation that holds the path.

The presumed and correct behavior would be to plainly ignore the second set of
the cookie since it was already set as secure on a secure host so overriding
it on an insecure host should not be okay.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10288 | roncoo roncoo-pay list improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10288</link><description>A vulnerability was found in roncoo roncoo-pay up to 9428382af21cd5568319eae7429b7e1d0332ff40. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /user/info/list. Performing manipulation results in improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10094 | Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10094</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 10.7 before 18.1.6, 18.2 before 18.2.6, and 18.3 before 18.3.2 that could have allowed authenticated users to disrupt access to token listings and related administrative operations by creating tokens with excessively large names.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10287 | roncoo roncoo-pay orderQuery direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10287</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in roncoo roncoo-pay up to 9428382af21cd5568319eae7429b7e1d0332ff40. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /auth/orderQuery. Such manipulation of the argument orderNo leads to direct request. The attack may be performed from remote. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10278 | YunaiV ruoyi-vue-pro transfer improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10278</link><description>A flaw has been found in YunaiV ruoyi-vue-pro up to 2025.09. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /crm/contact/transfer. This manipulation of the argument ids/newOwnerUserId causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9877 | Embed Google Datastudio &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9877</link><description>The Embed Google Datastudio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'egds' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9879 | Spotify Embed Creator &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9879</link><description>The Spotify Embed Creator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spotify' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9880 | Side Slide Responsive Menu &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9880</link><description>The Side Slide Responsive Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9881 | Ultimate Blogroll &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9881</link><description>The Ultimate Blogroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10277 | YunaiV yudao-cloud submit improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10277</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in YunaiV yudao-cloud up to 2025.09. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /crm/receivable/submit. The manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10269 | Spirit Framework &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10269</link><description>The Spirit Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10276 | YunaiV ruoyi-vue-pro transfer improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10276</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in YunaiV ruoyi-vue-pro up to 2025.09. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /crm/contract/transfer. The manipulation of the argument id/newOwnerUserId leads to improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43788 | The organization selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.124, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 update 81 through ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43788</link><description>The organization selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.124, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 update 81 through update 85 does not check user permission, which allows remote authenticated users to obtain a list of all organizations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43789 | JSON Web Services in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.119, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.9, 7.4 GA through update 92 published...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43789</link><description>JSON Web Services in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.119, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.9, 7.4 GA through update 92 published to OSGi are registered and invoked directly as classes which allows Service Access Policies get executed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58754 | Axios is vulnerable to DoS attack through lack of data size check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58754</link><description>Axios is a promise based HTTP client for the browser and Node.js. When Axios prior to version 1.11.0 runs on Node.js and is given a URL with the `data:` scheme, it does not perform HTTP. Instead, its Node http adapter decodes the entire payload into memory (`Buffer`/`Blob`) and returns a synthetic 200 response. This path ignores `maxContentLength` / `maxBodyLength` (which only protect HTTP responses), so an attacker can supply a very large `data:` URI and cause the process to allocate unbounded memory and crash (DoS), even if the caller requested `responseType: 'stream'`. Version 1.11.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9807 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.15.1 -  Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9807</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘s’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.15.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10275 | YunaiV yudao-cloud transfer improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10275</link><description>A weakness has been identified in YunaiV yudao-cloud up to 2025.09. This affects an unknown part of the file /crm/business/transfer. Executing manipulation of the argument ids/newOwnerUserId can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55319 | Agentic AI and Visual Studio Code Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55319</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10274 | erjinzhi 10OA item cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10274</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in erjinzhi 10OA 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /trial/mvc/item. Performing manipulation of the argument Name results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>