<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-15045 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request Natlimit stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15045</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/Natlimit of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument page causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11419 | Keycloak: keycloak tls client-initiated renegotiation denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11419</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) by repeatedly initiating TLS 1.2 client-initiated renegotiation requests to exhaust server CPU resources, making the service unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15044 | Tenda WH450 NatStaticSetting stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15044</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/NatStaticSetting. The manipulation of the argument page results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65354 | Improper input handling in /Grocery/search_products_itname.php inPuneethReddyHC event-management 1.0 permits SQL injection via the sitem_nam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65354</link><description>Improper input handling in /Grocery/search_products_itname.php inPuneethReddyHC event-management 1.0 permits SQL injection via the sitem_name POST parameter. Crafted payloads can alter query logic and disclose database contents. Exploitation may result in sensitive data disclosure and backend compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47716 | Orangescrum 1.8.0 Cross-Site Scripting via Authenticated Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47716</link><description>Orangescrum 1.8.0 contains multiple cross-site scripting vulnerabilities that allow authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts through various input parameters. Attackers can exploit parameters like 'projid', 'CS_message', and 'name' to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in victim's browsers by submitting crafted payloads through application endpoints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47733 | CMSimple 5.4 Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Unicode Encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47733</link><description>CMSimple 5.4 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass input filtering by using HTML to Unicode encoding. Attackers can inject malicious scripts by encoding payloads like ')-alert(1)// and execute arbitrary JavaScript when victims interact with delete buttons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47737 | CSZ CMS 1.2.7 HTML Injection Vulnerability via Member Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47737</link><description>CSZ CMS 1.2.7 contains an HTML injection vulnerability that allows authenticated users to insert malicious hyperlinks in message titles. Attackers can craft POST requests to the member messaging system with HTML-based links to potentially conduct phishing or social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47720 | Orangescrum 1.8.0 Authenticated SQL Injection via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47720</link><description>Orangescrum 1.8.0 contains an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability that allows authorized users to manipulate database queries through multiple vulnerable parameters. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code into parameters like old_project_id, project_id, uuid, and uniqid to potentially extract or modify database information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47721 | Orangescrum 1.8.0 Authenticated Privilege Escalation via User Session Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47721</link><description>Orangescrum 1.8.0 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows authenticated users to take over other project-assigned accounts by manipulating session cookies. Attackers can extract the victim's unique ID from the page source and replace their own session cookie to gain unauthorized access to another user's account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47722 | Zucchetti Axess CLOKI Access Control 1.64 Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47722</link><description>Zucchetti Axess CLOKI Access Control 1.64 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate access control settings without user interaction. Attackers can craft malicious web pages with hidden forms to disable or modify access control parameters by tricking authenticated users into loading the page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47732 | CMSimple 5.2 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Filebrowser External Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47732</link><description>CMSimple 5.2 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Filebrowser External input field that allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript. Attackers can place unfiltered JavaScript code that executes when users click on Page or Files tabs, enabling persistent script injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47734 | CMSimple 5.4 Authenticated Local File Inclusion Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47734</link><description>CMSimple 5.4 contains an authenticated local file inclusion vulnerability that allows remote attackers to manipulate PHP session files and execute arbitrary code. Attackers can leverage the vulnerability by changing the functions file path and uploading malicious PHP code through session file upload mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47735 | CMSimple 5.4 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Template Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47735</link><description>CMSimple 5.4 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows logged-in attackers to inject malicious PHP code into template files. Attackers can exploit the template editing functionality by crafting a reverse shell payload and saving it through the template editing endpoint with a valid CSRF token.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47736 | CMSimple_XH 1.7.4 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Content Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47736</link><description>CMSimple_XH 1.7.4 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the content editing functionality that allows administrative users to upload malicious PHP files. Attackers with valid credentials can exploit the CSRF token mechanism to create a PHP shell file that enables arbitrary command execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47738 | CSZ CMS 1.2.7 Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Private Messaging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47738</link><description>CSZ CMS 1.2.7 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthorized users to embed malicious JavaScript in private messages. Attackers can send messages with script payloads in the user-agent header, which will execute when an admin views the message in the backend dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47739 | Epic Games Easy Anti-Cheat 4.0 Local Privilege Escalation via Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47739</link><description>Epic Games Easy Anti-Cheat 4.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local non-privileged users to execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the service configuration by inserting malicious code in the system root path that would execute with LocalSystem privileges during application startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53982 | PMB 7.4.6 SQL Injection Vulnerability via Unsanitized Storage Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53982</link><description>PMB 7.4.6 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the storage parameter of the ajax.php endpoint that allows remote attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can exploit the unsanitized 'id' parameter by injecting conditional sleep statements to extract information or perform time-based blind SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25364 | A command injection vulnerability in the me.connectify.SMJobBlessHelper XPC service of Speedify VPN up to v15.0.0 allows attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25364</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the me.connectify.SMJobBlessHelper XPC service of Speedify VPN up to v15.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands with root-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51511 | Cadmium CMS v.0.4.9 has a background arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /admin/content/filemanager/uploads.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51511</link><description>Cadmium CMS v.0.4.9 has a background arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /admin/content/filemanager/uploads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33222 | NVIDIA Isaac Launchable contains a vulnerability where an attacker could exploit a hard-coded credential issue. A successful exploit of this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33222</link><description>NVIDIA Isaac Launchable contains a vulnerability where an attacker could exploit a hard-coded credential issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33223 | NVIDIA Isaac Launchable contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an execution with unnecessary privileges. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33223</link><description>NVIDIA Isaac Launchable contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an execution with unnecessary privileges. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, information disclosure and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33224 | NVIDIA Isaac Launchable contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an execution with unnecessary privileges. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33224</link><description>NVIDIA Isaac Launchable contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an execution with unnecessary privileges. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, information disclosure and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65410 | A stack overflow in the src/main.c component of GNU Unrtf v0.21.10 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65410</link><description>A stack overflow in the src/main.c component of GNU Unrtf v0.21.10 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting a crafted input into the filename parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57521 | SQL Injection vulnerability in RuoYi v.4.7.9 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the createTable function in S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57521</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in RuoYi v.4.7.9 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the createTable function in SqlUtil.java.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65713 | Home Assistant Core before v2025.8.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The Downloader integration does not fully validate file paths dur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65713</link><description>Home Assistant Core before v2025.8.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The Downloader integration does not fully validate file paths during concatenation, leaving a path traversal vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29228 | Linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26 is vulnerable to command injection in the runtime.macClone function via the mc.ip parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29228</link><description>Linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26 is vulnerable to command injection in the runtime.macClone function via the mc.ip parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:48:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29229 | linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26 is vulnerable to command injection in the function ddnsStatus.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29229</link><description>linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26 is vulnerable to command injection in the function ddnsStatus.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45493 | Netgear EX8000 V1.0.0.126 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the iface parameter in the action_bandwidth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45493</link><description>Netgear EX8000 V1.0.0.126 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the iface parameter in the action_bandwidth function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50526 | Netgear EX8000 V1.0.0.126 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the switch_status function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50526</link><description>Netgear EX8000 V1.0.0.126 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the switch_status function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67111 | An integer overflow in the RTPS protocol implementation of OpenDDS DDS before v3.33.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67111</link><description>An integer overflow in the RTPS protocol implementation of OpenDDS DDS before v3.33.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65865 | An integer overflow in eProsima Fast-DDS v3.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65865</link><description>An integer overflow in eProsima Fast-DDS v3.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67108 | eProsima Fast-DDS v3.3 was discovered to contain improper validation for ticket revocation, resulting in insecure communications and connect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67108</link><description>eProsima Fast-DDS v3.3 was discovered to contain improper validation for ticket revocation, resulting in insecure communications and connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67109 | Improper verification of the time certificate in Eclipse Cyclone DDS before v0.10.5 allows attackers to bypass certificate checks and execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67109</link><description>Improper verification of the time certificate in Eclipse Cyclone DDS before v0.10.5 allows attackers to bypass certificate checks and execute commands with System privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9684 | FreyrSCADA/IEC-60870-5-104 server v21.06.008 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending specific message sequences.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9684</link><description>FreyrSCADA/IEC-60870-5-104 server v21.06.008 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending specific message sequences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68338 | net: dsa: microchip: Don&amp;#x27;t free uninitialized ksz_irq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68338</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: dsa: microchip: Don't free uninitialized ksz_irq

If something goes wrong at setup, ksz_irq_free() can be called on
uninitialized ksz_irq (for example when ksz_ptp_irq_setup() fails). It
leads to freeing uninitialized IRQ numbers and/or domains.

Use dsa_switch_for_each_user_port_continue_reverse() in the error path
to iterate only over the fully initialized ports.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68339 | atm/fore200e: Fix possible data race in fore200e_open()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68339</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

atm/fore200e: Fix possible data race in fore200e_open()

Protect access to fore200e-&gt;available_cell_rate with rate_mtx lock in the
error handling path of fore200e_open() to prevent a data race.

The field fore200e-&gt;available_cell_rate is a shared resource used to track
available bandwidth. It is concurrently accessed by fore200e_open(),
fore200e_close(), and fore200e_change_qos().

In fore200e_open(), the lock rate_mtx is correctly held when subtracting
vcc-&gt;qos.txtp.max_pcr from available_cell_rate to reserve bandwidth.
However, if the subsequent call to fore200e_activate_vcin() fails, the
function restores the reserved bandwidth by adding back to
available_cell_rate without holding the lock.

This introduces a race condition because available_cell_rate is a global
device resource shared across all VCCs. If the error path in
fore200e_open() executes concurrently with operations like
fore200e_close() or fore200e_change_qos() on other VCCs, a
read-modify-write race occurs.

Specifically, the error path reads the rate without the lock. If another
CPU acquires the lock and modifies the rate (e.g., releasing bandwidth in
fore200e_close()) between this read and the subsequent write, the error
path will overwrite the concurrent update with a stale value. This results
in incorrect bandwidth accounting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68340 | team: Move team device type change at the end of team_port_add</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68340</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

team: Move team device type change at the end of team_port_add

Attempting to add a port device that is already up will expectedly fail,
but not before modifying the team device header_ops.

In the case of the syzbot reproducer the gre0 device is
already in state UP when it attempts to add it as a
port device of team0, this fails but before that
header_ops-&gt;create of team0 is changed from eth_header to ipgre_header
in the call to team_dev_type_check_change.

Later when we end up in ipgre_header() struct ip_tunnel* points to nonsense
as the private data of the device still holds a struct team.

Example sequence of iproute2 commands to reproduce the hang/BUG():
ip link add dev team0 type team
ip link add dev gre0 type gre
ip link set dev gre0 up
ip link set dev gre0 master team0
ip link set dev team0 up
ping -I team0 1.1.1.1

Move team_dev_type_check_change down where all other checks have passed
as it changes the dev type with no way to restore it in case
one of the checks that follow it fail.

Also make sure to preserve the origial mtu assignment:
  - If port_dev is not the same type as dev, dev takes mtu from port_dev
  - If port_dev is the same type as dev, port_dev takes mtu from dev

This is done by adding a conditional before the call to dev_set_mtu
to prevent it from assigning port_dev-&gt;mtu = dev-&gt;mtu and instead
letting team_dev_type_check_change assign dev-&gt;mtu = port_dev-&gt;mtu.
The conditional is needed because the patch moves the call to
team_dev_type_check_change past dev_set_mtu.

Testing:
  - team device driver in-tree selftests
  - Add/remove various devices as slaves of team device
  - syzbot</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68341 | veth: reduce XDP no_direct return section to fix race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68341</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

veth: reduce XDP no_direct return section to fix race

As explain in commit fa349e396e48 ("veth: Fix race with AF_XDP exposing
old or uninitialized descriptors") for veth there is a chance after
napi_complete_done() that another CPU can manage start another NAPI
instance running veth_pool(). For NAPI this is correctly handled as the
napi_schedule_prep() check will prevent multiple instances from getting
scheduled, but for the remaining code in veth_pool() this can run
concurrent with the newly started NAPI instance.

The problem/race is that xdp_clear_return_frame_no_direct() isn't
designed to be nested.

Prior to commit 401cb7dae813 ("net: Reference bpf_redirect_info via
task_struct on PREEMPT_RT.") the temporary BPF net context
bpf_redirect_info was stored per CPU, where this wasn't an issue. Since
this commit the BPF context is stored in 'current' task_struct. When
running veth in threaded-NAPI mode, then the kthread becomes the storage
area. Now a race exists between two concurrent veth_pool() function calls
one exiting NAPI and one running new NAPI, both using the same BPF net
context.

Race is when another CPU gets within the xdp_set_return_frame_no_direct()
section before exiting veth_pool() calls the clear-function
xdp_clear_return_frame_no_direct().</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68342 | can: gs_usb: gs_usb_receive_bulk_callback(): check actual_length before accessing data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68342</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: gs_usb: gs_usb_receive_bulk_callback(): check actual_length before accessing data

The URB received in gs_usb_receive_bulk_callback() contains a struct
gs_host_frame. The length of the data after the header depends on the
gs_host_frame hf::flags and the active device features (e.g. time
stamping).

Introduce a new function gs_usb_get_minimum_length() and check that we have
at least received the required amount of data before accessing it. Only
copy the data to that skb that has actually been received.

[mkl: rename gs_usb_get_minimum_length() -&gt; +gs_usb_get_minimum_rx_length()]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68343 | can: gs_usb: gs_usb_receive_bulk_callback(): check actual_length before accessing header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68343</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: gs_usb: gs_usb_receive_bulk_callback(): check actual_length before accessing header

The driver expects to receive a struct gs_host_frame in
gs_usb_receive_bulk_callback().

Use struct_group to describe the header of the struct gs_host_frame and
check that we have at least received the header before accessing any
members of it.

To resubmit the URB, do not dereference the pointer chain
"dev-&gt;parent-&gt;hf_size_rx" but use "parent-&gt;hf_size_rx" instead. Since
"urb-&gt;context" contains "parent", it is always defined, while "dev" is not
defined if the URB it too short.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66845 | A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in TechStore version 1.0. The user_name endpoint reflects the id qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66845</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in TechStore version 1.0. The user_name endpoint reflects the id query parameter directly into the HTML response without output encoding or sanitization, allowing execution of arbitrary JavaScript code in a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:02:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13183 | Stored XSS in Hotech&amp;#x27;s Otello</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13183</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hotech Software Inc. Otello allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Otello: from 2.4.0 before 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52210 | WordPress Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52210</link><description>Vulnerability in Tyche softwares Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite.This issue affects Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24844 | WordPress PowerPack Pro for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.6 - Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Reset vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24844</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in IdeaBox Creations PowerPack Pro for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PowerPack Pro for Elementor: from n/a through 2.10.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68546 | WordPress Nika theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68546</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Thembay Nika allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Nika: from n/a through 1.2.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68544 | WordPress Diza theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68544</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Thembay Diza allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Diza: from n/a through 1.3.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68548 | WordPress Responsive Posts Carousel Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 15.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebCodingPlace Responsive Posts Carousel Pro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive Posts Carousel Pro: from n/a through 15.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68550 | WordPress WPBulky plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.13 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68550</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VillaTheme WPBulky allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects WPBulky: from n/a through 1.1.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68551 | WordPress VPSUForm plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.24 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68551</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Vikas Ratudi VPSUForm allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects VPSUForm: from n/a through 3.2.24.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68556 | WordPress HAPPY plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68556</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VillaTheme HAPPY allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HAPPY: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68557 | WordPress Chakra test plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68557</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Vikas Ratudi Chakra test allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Chakra test: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59886 | Improper input validation at one of the endpoints of Eaton xComfort ECI's 

web interface, could lead into an attacker with network access t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59886</link><description>Improper input validation at one of the endpoints of Eaton xComfort ECI's 

web interface, could lead into an attacker with network access to the device executing privileged user commands. As cybersecurity
standards continue to evolve and to meet our requirements today, Eaton has decided to discontinue the
product. Upon retirement or end of support, there will be no new security updates, non-security
updates, or paid assisted support options, or online technical content updates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68559 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor).This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor): from n/a through 5.10.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68560 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.5.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68560</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor).This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor): from n/a through 5.10.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68561 | WordPress AutomatorWP plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ruben Garcia AutomatorWP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects AutomatorWP: from n/a through 5.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14000 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.15 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14000</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'register_form' and 'restrict' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14635 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.20.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom JS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14635</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ha_page_custom_js' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.20.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, despite the intended role restriction of Custom JS to Administrators.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12934 | Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.9.4.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12934</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'duplicate_wpml_layout' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary posts with the content of other existing posts, potentially exposing private and password-protected content and deleting any content that is not saved in revisions or backups. Posts must have been created with Beaver Builder to be copied or updated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14155 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.11.53 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;get_template_content&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14155</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor – Powerful Elementor Templates &amp; Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_template_content' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.11.53. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the content of private, draft, and pending templates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14163 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.11.53 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;insert_inner_template&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14163</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.11.53. This is due to missing nonce validation in the 'insert_inner_template' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary Elementor templates via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator or other user with the edit_posts capability into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14388 | PhastPress &amp;lt;= 3.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Null Byte Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14388</link><description>The PhastPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via null byte injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.7. This is due to a discrepancy between the extension validation in `getExtensionForURL()` which operates on URL-decoded paths, and `appendNormalized()` which strips everything after a null byte before constructing the filesystem path. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files from the webroot, including wp-config.php, by appending a double URL-encoded null byte (%2500) followed by an allowed extension (.txt) to the file path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14548 | Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.3.16 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;event_desc&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14548</link><description>The Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'event_desc' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, granted they can convince an administrator to enable lower privilege users to manage calendar events via the plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15034 | itsourcecode Student Management System record.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15034</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /record.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67743 | Local Deep Research is Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Download Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67743</link><description>Local Deep Research is an AI-powered research assistant for deep, iterative research. In versions from 1.3.0 to before 1.3.9, the download service (download_service.py) makes HTTP requests using raw requests.get() without utilizing the application's SSRF protection (safe_requests.py). This can allow attackers to access internal services and attempt to reach cloud provider metadata endpoints (AWS/GCP/Azure), as well as perform internal network reconnaissance, by submitting malicious URLs through the API, depending on the deployment and surrounding controls. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68615 | Net-SNMP snmptrapd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68615</link><description>net-snmp is a SNMP application library, tools and daemon. Prior to versions 5.9.5 and 5.10.pre2, a specially crafted packet to an net-snmp snmptrapd daemon can cause a buffer overflow and the daemon to crash. This issue has been patched in versions 5.9.5 and 5.10.pre2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68614 | LibreNMS Alert Rule API Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68614</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Prior to version 25.12.0, the Alert Rule API is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. Alert rules can be created or updated via LibreNMS API. The alert rule name is not properly sanitized, and can be used to inject HTML code. This issue has been patched in version 25.12.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47713 | Hasura GraphQL 1.3.3 Denial of Service via Malicious GraphQL Query</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47713</link><description>Hasura GraphQL 1.3.3 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to overwhelm the service by crafting malicious GraphQL queries with excessive nested fields. Attackers can send repeated requests with extremely long query strings and multiple threads to consume server resources and potentially crash the GraphQL endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47714 | Hasura GraphQL 1.3.3 Local File Read via SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47714</link><description>Hasura GraphQL 1.3.3 contains a local file read vulnerability that allows attackers to access system files through SQL injection in the query endpoint. Attackers can exploit the pg_read_file() PostgreSQL function by crafting malicious SQL queries to read arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47715 | Hasura GraphQL 1.3.3 Server-Side Request Forgery via Remote Schema Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47715</link><description>Hasura GraphQL 1.3.3 contains a server-side request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to inject arbitrary remote schema URLs through the add_remote_schema endpoint. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted POST requests to the /v1/query endpoint with malicious URL definitions to potentially access internal network resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50687 | Cobian Backup 11 Gravity 11.2.0.582 Local Denial of Service via Password Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50687</link><description>Cobian Backup 11 Gravity 11.2.0.582 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the FTP password input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can generate a specially crafted 800-byte buffer and paste it into the password field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50688 | Cobian Backup Gravity 11.2.0.582 Unquoted Service Path Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50688</link><description>Cobian Backup Gravity 11.2.0.582 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path in the CobianBackup11 service to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50689 | Cobian Reflector 0.9.93 RC1 Local Denial of Service via Password Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50689</link><description>Cobian Reflector 0.9.93 RC1 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the password input field. Attackers can paste a large 8000-byte buffer into the password field to trigger an application crash during SFTP task configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50690 | Wondershare MirrorGo 2.0.11.346 Local Privilege Escalation via Insecure File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50690</link><description>Wondershare MirrorGo 2.0.11.346 contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability due to incorrect file permissions on executable files. Unprivileged local users can replace the ElevationService.exe with a malicious file to execute arbitrary code with LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53955 | SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x Authorization Bypass via Insecure Object References</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53955</link><description>SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x contains an insecure direct object reference vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authorization and access hidden system resources. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by manipulating user-supplied input to execute privileged functionalities without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53960 | SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x SQL Injection via Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53960</link><description>SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco version 2.x contains an SQL injection vulnerability in the 'index.php' authentication mechanism that allows attackers to manipulate login credentials. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code through the 'password' POST parameter to bypass authentication and potentially gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53961 | SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53961</link><description>SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to perform administrative actions without user consent. Attackers can craft malicious web pages that submit HTTP requests to the radio processing interface, triggering unintended administrative operations when a logged-in user visits the page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53962 | SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x Unauthenticated Directory Traversal File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53962</link><description>SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x contains an unauthenticated directory traversal vulnerability that allows remote attackers to write arbitrary files through the 'upgfile' parameter in upload.cgi. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted multipart form-data POST requests with directory traversal sequences to write files to unintended system locations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53963 | SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x Unauthenticated Remote Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53963</link><description>SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x contains an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary shell commands through the 'password' parameter. Attackers can exploit the login.php and index.php scripts by injecting shell commands via the 'password' POST parameter to execute commands with web server privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53964 | SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x Unauthenticated Factory Reset Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53964</link><description>SOUND4 IMPACT/FIRST/PULSE/Eco v2.x contains an unauthenticated vulnerability in the /usr/cgi-bin/restorefactory.cgi endpoint that allows remote attackers to reset device configuration. Attackers can send a POST request to the endpoint with specific data to trigger a factory reset and bypass authentication, gaining full system control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53965 | SOUND4 Server Service 4.1.102 Local Privilege Escalation via Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53965</link><description>SOUND4 Server Service 4.1.102 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local non-privileged users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path by inserting malicious code in the system root path that could execute with LocalSystem privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53966 | SOUND4 LinkAndShare Transmitter 1.1.2 Format String Stack Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53966</link><description>SOUND4 LinkAndShare Transmitter 1.1.2 contains a format string vulnerability that allows attackers to trigger memory stack overflows through maliciously crafted environment variables. Attackers can manipulate the username environment variable with format string payloads to potentially execute arbitrary code and crash the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53967 | Screen SFT DAB 600/C Firmware 1.9.3 Authentication Bypass Admin Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53967</link><description>Screen SFT DAB 600/C firmware 1.9.3 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows attackers to change the admin password without requiring the current credentials. Attackers can exploit the userManager.cgx API endpoint by sending a crafted POST request with a new MD5-hashed password to directly modify the admin account's authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53968 | Screen SFT DAB 600/C Firmware 1.9.3 Authentication Bypass Erase Account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53968</link><description>Screen SFT DAB 600/C Firmware 1.9.3 contains a session management vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authentication controls by exploiting IP address session binding. Attackers can reuse the same IP address and issue unauthorized requests to the userManager API to remove user accounts without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53969 | Screen SFT DAB 600/C Firmware 1.9.3 Authentication Bypass Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53969</link><description>Screen SFT DAB 600/C firmware 1.9.3 contains a session management vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authentication controls by exploiting IP address session binding. Attackers can reuse the same IP address and issue unauthorized requests to the userManager API to change user passwords without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53970 | Screen SFT DAB 600/C Firmware 1.9.3 Authentication Bypass Reset Board Config</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53970</link><description>Screen SFT DAB 600/C Firmware 1.9.3 contains a weak session management vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authentication controls by reusing IP-bound session identifiers. Attackers can exploit the vulnerable deviceManagement API endpoint to reset device configurations by sending crafted POST requests with manipulated session parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53971 | WebTareas 2.4 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53971</link><description>WebTareas 2.4 contains a file upload vulnerability that allows authenticated users to upload malicious PHP files through the chat photo upload functionality. Attackers can upload a PHP file with arbitrary code to the /files/Messages/ directory and execute it directly through the generated file path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53972 | WebTareas 2.4 Unauthenticated SQL Injection via Session Cookie Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53972</link><description>WebTareas 2.4 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the webTareasSID cookie parameter that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can exploit error-based and time-based blind SQL injection techniques to extract database information and potentially access sensitive system data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53973 | Zillya Total Security 3.0.2367.0 Local Privilege Escalation via Quarantine Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53973</link><description>Zillya Total Security 3.0.2367.0 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows low-privileged users to copy files to unauthorized system locations using the quarantine module. Attackers can leverage symbolic link techniques to restore quarantined files to restricted directories, potentially enabling system-level access through techniques like DLL hijacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53974 | D-Link DSL-124 ME_1.00 Backup Configuration File Disclosure via Unauthenticated Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53974</link><description>D-Link DSL-124 ME_1.00 contains a configuration file disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve router settings through a POST request. Attackers can send a specific POST request to the router's configuration endpoint to download a complete backup file containing sensitive network credentials and system configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53975 | Atom CMS 2.0 Unauthenticated SQL Injection via Admin Index Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53975</link><description>Atom CMS 2.0 contains an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability that allows remote attackers to manipulate database queries through unvalidated parameters. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code in the 'id' parameter of the admin index page to execute time-based blind SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53976 | myBB Forums 1.8.26 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Template Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53976</link><description>myBB Forums 1.8.26 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the template management system that allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious scripts when creating new templates. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by inserting script payloads in the template title field when adding new templates through the 'Templates and Style' &gt; 'Templates' &gt; 'Manage Templates' &gt; 'Global Templates' interface, causing arbitrary JavaScript to execute when the template is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53977 | myBB Forums 1.8.26 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Forum Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53977</link><description>myBB Forums 1.8.26 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the forum management system that allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious scripts when creating new forums. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by inserting script payloads in the forum title field when adding new forums through the 'Forums and Posts' &gt; 'Forum Management' interface, causing arbitrary JavaScript to execute when the forum listing is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53978 | myBB Forums 1.8.26 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Forum Announcements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53978</link><description>myBB Forums 1.8.26 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the forum announcement system that allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious scripts when creating announcements. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by inserting script payloads in the announcement title field when adding announcements through the 'Forums and Posts' &gt; 'Forum Announcements' interface, causing arbitrary JavaScript to execute when the announcement is displayed on the forum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53979 | MyBB 1.8.32 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Chained Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53979</link><description>MyBB 1.8.32 contains a chained vulnerability that allows authenticated administrators to bypass avatar upload restrictions and execute arbitrary code. Attackers can modify upload path settings, upload a malicious PHP-embedded image file, and execute commands through the language configuration editing interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53980 | ProjectSend r1605 Remote Code Execution via File Extension Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53980</link><description>ProjectSend r1605 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to upload malicious files by manipulating file extensions. Attackers can upload shell scripts with disguised extensions through the upload.process.php endpoint to execute arbitrary commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53981 | PhotoShow 3.0 Remote Code Execution via Exiftran Path Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53981</link><description>PhotoShow 3.0 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious commands through the exiftran path configuration. Attackers can exploit the ffmpeg configuration settings by base64 encoding a reverse shell command and executing it through a crafted video upload process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65857 | An issue was discovered in Xiongmai XM530 IP cameras on firmware V5.00.R02.000807D8.10010.346624.S.ONVIF 21.06. The GetStreamUri exposes RTS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65857</link><description>An issue was discovered in Xiongmai XM530 IP cameras on firmware V5.00.R02.000807D8.10010.346624.S.ONVIF 21.06. The GetStreamUri exposes RTSP URIs containing hardcoded credentials enabling direct unauthorized video stream access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67436 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) in PluXml CMS 5.8.22 allows an attacker with administrator panel access to inject a malicious PHP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67436</link><description>Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) in PluXml CMS 5.8.22 allows an attacker with administrator panel access to inject a malicious PHP webshell into a theme file (e.g., home.php).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68476 | KEDA has Arbitrary File Read via Insufficient Path Validation in HashiCorp Vault Service Account Credential</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68476</link><description>KEDA is a Kubernetes-based Event Driven Autoscaling component. Prior to versions 2.17.3 and 2.18.3, an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability has been identified in KEDA, potentially affecting any KEDA resource that uses TriggerAuthentication to configure HashiCorp Vault authentication. The vulnerability stems from an incorrect or insufficient path validation when loading the Service Account Token specified in spec.hashiCorpVault.credential.serviceAccount. An attacker with permissions to create or modify a TriggerAuthentication resource can exfiltrate the content of any file from the node's filesystem (where the KEDA pod resides) by directing the file's content to a server under their control, as part of the Vault authentication request. The potential impact includes the exfiltration of sensitive system information, such as secrets, keys, or the content of files like /etc/passwd. This issue has been patched in versions 2.17.3 and 2.18.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34457 | wb2osz/direwolf &amp;lt;= 1.8 Stack-based Buffer Overflow DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34457</link><description>wb2osz/direwolf (Dire Wolf) versions up to and including 1.8, prior to commit 694c954, contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the function kiss_rec_byte() located in src/kiss_frame.c. When processing crafted KISS frames that reach the maximum allowed frame length (MAX_KISS_LEN), the function appends a terminating FEND byte without reserving sufficient space in the stack buffer. This results in an out-of-bounds write followed by an out-of-bounds read during the subsequent call to kiss_unwrap(), leading to stack memory corruption or application crashes. This vulnerability may allow remote unauthenticated attackers to trigger a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34458 | wb2osz/direwolf &amp;lt;= 1.8 Reachable Assertion DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34458</link><description>wb2osz/direwolf (Dire Wolf) versions up to and including 1.8, prior to commit 3658a87, contain a reachable assertion vulnerability in the APRS MIC-E decoder function aprs_mic_e() located in src/decode_aprs.c. When processing a specially crafted AX.25 frame containing a MIC-E message with an empty or truncated comment field, the application triggers an unhandled assertion checking for a non-empty comment. This assertion failure causes immediate process termination, allowing a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service by sending malformed APRS traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68475 | Fedify has ReDoS Vulnerability in HTML Parsing Regex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68475</link><description>Fedify is a TypeScript library for building federated server apps powered by ActivityPub. Prior to versions 1.6.13, 1.7.14, 1.8.15, and 1.9.2, a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in Fedify's document loader. The HTML parsing regex at packages/fedify/src/runtime/docloader.ts:259 contains nested quantifiers that cause catastrophic backtracking when processing maliciously crafted HTML responses. This issue has been patched in versions 1.6.13, 1.7.14, 1.8.15, and 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68480 | Marshmallow has DoS in Schema.load(many)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68480</link><description>Marshmallow is a lightweight library for converting complex objects to and from simple Python datatypes. In versions from 3.0.0rc1 to before 3.26.2 and from 4.0.0 to before 4.1.2, Schema.load(data, many=True) is vulnerable to denial of service attacks. A moderately sized request can consume a disproportionate amount of CPU time. This issue has been patched in version 3.26.2 and 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65856 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in Xiongmai XM530 IP cameras on Firmware V5.00.R02.000807D8.10010.346624.S.ONVIF 21.06 allows unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65856</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in Xiongmai XM530 IP cameras on Firmware V5.00.R02.000807D8.10010.346624.S.ONVIF 21.06 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to access sensitive device information and live video streams. The ONVIF implementation fails to enforce authentication on 31 critical endpoints, enabling direct unauthorized video stream access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66735 | youlai-boot V2.21.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The getRoleForm function in SysRoleController.java does not perform permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66735</link><description>youlai-boot V2.21.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The getRoleForm function in SysRoleController.java does not perform permission checks, which may allow non-root users to directly access root roles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66736 | youlai-boot V2.21.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The importUsers function in SysUserController.java does not perform a permiss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66736</link><description>youlai-boot V2.21.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The importUsers function in SysUserController.java does not perform a permission check on the current user's identity, which may allow regular users to import user data into the database, resulting in an authorization bypass vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65817 | LSC Smart Connect Indoor IP Camera 1.4.13 contains a RCE vulnerability in start_app.sh.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65817</link><description>LSC Smart Connect Indoor IP Camera 1.4.13 contains a RCE vulnerability in start_app.sh.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27708 | Iframe injection vulnerability in airc.pt/solucoes-servicos.solucoes MyNET v.26.06 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27708</link><description>Iframe injection vulnerability in airc.pt/solucoes-servicos.solucoes MyNET v.26.06 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the src parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67290 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Page Settings module of Piranha CMS v12.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67290</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Page Settings module of Piranha CMS v12.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Excerpt field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67291 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Media module of Piranha CMS v12.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67291</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Media module of Piranha CMS v12.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Name field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65837 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Content Search module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65837</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Content Search module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65790 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in FuguHub 8.1 when serving SVG files through the /fs/ file manager interface. F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65790</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in FuguHub 8.1 when serving SVG files through the /fs/ file manager interface. FuguHub does not sanitize or restrict script execution inside SVG content. When a victim opens a crafted SVG containing an inline</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67418 | ClipBucket 5.5.2 is affected by an improper access control issue where the product is shipped or deployed with hardcoded default administrat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67418</link><description>ClipBucket 5.5.2 is affected by an improper access control issue where the product is shipped or deployed with hardcoded default administrative credentials. An unauthenticated remote attacker can log in to the administrative panel using these default credentials, resulting in full administrative control of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25812 | MyNET up to v26.05 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the src parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25812</link><description>MyNET up to v26.05 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the src parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25814 | MyNET up to v26.05 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the msg parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25814</link><description>MyNET up to v26.05 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the msg parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35321 | MyNET up to v26.08 was discovered to contain a Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the msgtipo parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35321</link><description>MyNET up to v26.08 was discovered to contain a Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the msgtipo parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15033 | WooCommerce - Subscriber/Customer+ Order Data Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15033</link><description>A vulnerability in WooCommerce 8.1 to 10.4.2 can allow logged-in customers to access order data of guest customers on sites with a certain configuration. This has been fixed in WooCommerce 10.4.3, as well as all the previously affected versions through point releases, starting from 8.1, where it has been fixed in 8.1.3. It does not affect WooCommerce 8.0 or earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26787 | An error in the SignServer container startup logic was found in Keyfactor SignServer versions prior to 7.2. The Admin CLI command used to co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26787</link><description>An error in the SignServer container startup logic was found in Keyfactor SignServer versions prior to 7.2. The Admin CLI command used to configure Certificate access to the initial startup of the container sets a property of "allowany" to allow any user with a valid and trusted client auth certificate to connect. Admins can then set more restricted access to specific certificates. A logic error caused this admin CLI command to be run on each restart of the container instead of only the first startup as intended resetting the configuration to "allowany".</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63662 | Insecure permissions in the /api/v1/agents API of GT Edge AI Platform before v2.0.10-dev allows unauthorized attackers to access sensitive i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63662</link><description>Insecure permissions in the /api/v1/agents API of GT Edge AI Platform before v2.0.10-dev allows unauthorized attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63663 | Incorrect access control in the /api/v1/conversations/*/files API of GT Edge AI Platform before v2.0.10 allows unauthorized attackers to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63663</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /api/v1/conversations/*/files API of GT Edge AI Platform before v2.0.10 allows unauthorized attackers to access other users' uploaded files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63664 | Incorrect access control in the /api/v1/conversations/*/messages API of GT Edge AI Platform before v2.0.10-dev allows unauthorized attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63664</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /api/v1/conversations/*/messages API of GT Edge AI Platform before v2.0.10-dev allows unauthorized attackers to access other users' message history with AI agents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67288 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Umbraco CMS v16.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67288</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Umbraco CMS v16.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65270 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ClinCapture EDC 3.0 and 2.2.3, allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65270</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ClinCapture EDC 3.0 and 2.2.3, allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute JavaScript code in the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67289 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Attachments module of Frappe Framework v15.89.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67289</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Attachments module of Frappe Framework v15.89.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted XML file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68645 | A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the Webmail Classic UI of Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 10.0 and 10.1 because of improper ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68645</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the Webmail Classic UI of Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 10.0 and 10.1 because of improper handling of user-supplied request parameters in the RestFilter servlet. An unauthenticated remote attacker can craft requests to the /h/rest endpoint to influence internal request dispatching, allowing inclusion of arbitrary files from the WebRoot directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67443 | Schlix CMS before v2.2.9-5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). Due to lack of javascript sanitization in the login form, incorrect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67443</link><description>Schlix CMS before v2.2.9-5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). Due to lack of javascript sanitization in the login form, incorrect login attempts in logs are triggered as XSS in the admin panel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68326 | drm/xe/guc: Fix stack_depot usage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68326</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/guc: Fix stack_depot usage

Add missing stack_depot_init() call when CONFIG_DRM_XE_DEBUG_GUC is
enabled to fix the following call stack:

	[] BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
	[] Workqueue:  drm_sched_run_job_work [gpu_sched]
	[] RIP: 0010:stack_depot_save_flags+0x172/0x870
	[] Call Trace:
	[]  
	[]  fast_req_track+0x58/0xb0 [xe]

(cherry picked from commit 64fdf496a6929a0a194387d2bb5efaf5da2b542f)</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68327 | usb: renesas_usbhs: Fix synchronous external abort on unbind</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68327</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: renesas_usbhs: Fix synchronous external abort on unbind

A synchronous external abort occurs on the Renesas RZ/G3S SoC if unbind is
executed after the configuration sequence described above:

modprobe usb_f_ecm
modprobe libcomposite
modprobe configfs
cd /sys/kernel/config/usb_gadget
mkdir -p g1
cd g1
echo "0x1d6b" &gt; idVendor
echo "0x0104" &gt; idProduct
mkdir -p strings/0x409
echo "0123456789" &gt; strings/0x409/serialnumber
echo "Renesas." &gt; strings/0x409/manufacturer
echo "Ethernet Gadget" &gt; strings/0x409/product
mkdir -p functions/ecm.usb0
mkdir -p configs/c.1
mkdir -p configs/c.1/strings/0x409
echo "ECM" &gt; configs/c.1/strings/0x409/configuration

if [ ! -L configs/c.1/ecm.usb0 ]; then
        ln -s functions/ecm.usb0 configs/c.1
fi

echo 11e20000.usb &gt; UDC
echo 11e20000.usb &gt; /sys/bus/platform/drivers/renesas_usbhs/unbind

The displayed trace is as follows:

 Internal error: synchronous external abort: 0000000096000010 [#1] SMP
 CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 188 Comm: sh Tainted: G M 6.17.0-rc7-next-20250922-00010-g41050493b2bd #55 PREEMPT
 Tainted: [M]=MACHINE_CHECK
 Hardware name: Renesas SMARC EVK version 2 based on r9a08g045s33 (DT)
 pstate: 604000c5 (nZCv daIF +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
 pc : usbhs_sys_function_pullup+0x10/0x40 [renesas_usbhs]
 lr : usbhsg_update_pullup+0x3c/0x68 [renesas_usbhs]
 sp : ffff8000838b3920
 x29: ffff8000838b3920 x28: ffff00000d585780 x27: 0000000000000000
 x26: 0000000000000000 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: ffff00000c3e3810
 x23: ffff00000d5e5c80 x22: ffff00000d5e5d40 x21: 0000000000000000
 x20: 0000000000000000 x19: ffff00000d5e5c80 x18: 0000000000000020
 x17: 2e30303230316531 x16: 312d7968703a7968 x15: 3d454d414e5f4344
 x14: 000000000000002c x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 0000000000000000
 x11: ffff00000f358f38 x10: ffff00000f358db0 x9 : ffff00000b41f418
 x8 : 0101010101010101 x7 : 7f7f7f7f7f7f7f7f x6 : fefefeff6364626d
 x5 : 8080808000000000 x4 : 000000004b5ccb9d x3 : 0000000000000000
 x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : ffff800083790000 x0 : ffff00000d5e5c80
 Call trace:
 usbhs_sys_function_pullup+0x10/0x40 [renesas_usbhs] (P)
 usbhsg_pullup+0x4c/0x7c [renesas_usbhs]
 usb_gadget_disconnect_locked+0x48/0xd4
 gadget_unbind_driver+0x44/0x114
 device_remove+0x4c/0x80
 device_release_driver_internal+0x1c8/0x224
 device_release_driver+0x18/0x24
 bus_remove_device+0xcc/0x10c
 device_del+0x14c/0x404
 usb_del_gadget+0x88/0xc0
 usb_del_gadget_udc+0x18/0x30
 usbhs_mod_gadget_remove+0x24/0x44 [renesas_usbhs]
 usbhs_mod_remove+0x20/0x30 [renesas_usbhs]
 usbhs_remove+0x98/0xdc [renesas_usbhs]
 platform_remove+0x20/0x30
 device_remove+0x4c/0x80
 device_release_driver_internal+0x1c8/0x224
 device_driver_detach+0x18/0x24
 unbind_store+0xb4/0xb8
 drv_attr_store+0x24/0x38
 sysfs_kf_write+0x7c/0x94
 kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x128/0x1b8
 vfs_write+0x2ac/0x350
 ksys_write+0x68/0xfc
 __arm64_sys_write+0x1c/0x28
 invoke_syscall+0x48/0x110
 el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0xc0/0xe0
 do_el0_svc+0x1c/0x28
 el0_svc+0x34/0xf0
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0xa0/0xe4
 el0t_64_sync+0x198/0x19c
 Code: 7100003f 1a9f07e1 531c6c22 f9400001 (79400021)
 ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
 note: sh[188] exited with irqs disabled
 note: sh[188] exited with preempt_count 1

The issue occurs because usbhs_sys_function_pullup(), which accesses the IP
registers, is executed after the USBHS clocks have been disabled. The
problem is reproducible on the Renesas RZ/G3S SoC starting with the
addition of module stop in the clock enable/disable APIs. With module stop
functionality enabled, a bus error is expected if a master accesses a
module whose clock has been stopped and module stop activated.

Disable the IP clocks at the end of remove.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68328 | firmware: stratix10-svc: fix bug in saving controller data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68328</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: stratix10-svc: fix bug in saving controller data

Fix the incorrect usage of platform_set_drvdata and dev_set_drvdata. They
both are of the same data and overrides each other. This resulted in the
rmmod of the svc driver to fail and throw a kernel panic for kthread_stop
and fifo free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68329 | tracing: Fix WARN_ON in tracing_buffers_mmap_close for split VMAs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68329</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tracing: Fix WARN_ON in tracing_buffers_mmap_close for split VMAs

When a VMA is split (e.g., by partial munmap or MAP_FIXED), the kernel
calls vm_ops-&gt;close on each portion. For trace buffer mappings, this
results in ring_buffer_unmap() being called multiple times while
ring_buffer_map() was only called once.

This causes ring_buffer_unmap() to return -ENODEV on subsequent calls
because user_mapped is already 0, triggering a WARN_ON.

Trace buffer mappings cannot support partial mappings because the ring
buffer structure requires the complete buffer including the meta page.

Fix this by adding a may_split callback that returns -EINVAL to prevent
VMA splits entirely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68330 | iio: accel: bmc150: Fix irq assumption regression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68330</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iio: accel: bmc150: Fix irq assumption regression

The code in bmc150-accel-core.c unconditionally calls
bmc150_accel_set_interrupt() in the iio_buffer_setup_ops,
such as on the runtime PM resume path giving a kernel
splat like this if the device has no interrupts:

Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual
  address 00000001 when read

PC is at bmc150_accel_set_interrupt+0x98/0x194
LR is at __pm_runtime_resume+0x5c/0x64
(...)
Call trace:
bmc150_accel_set_interrupt from bmc150_accel_buffer_postenable+0x40/0x108
bmc150_accel_buffer_postenable from __iio_update_buffers+0xbe0/0xcbc
__iio_update_buffers from enable_store+0x84/0xc8
enable_store from kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x154/0x1b4

This bug seems to have been in the driver since the beginning,
but it only manifests recently, I do not know why.

Store the IRQ number in the state struct, as this is a common
pattern in other drivers, then use this to determine if we have
IRQ support or not.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68331 | usb: uas: fix urb unmapping issue when the uas device is remove during ongoing data transfer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68331</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: uas: fix urb unmapping issue when the uas device is remove during ongoing data transfer

When a UAS device is unplugged during data transfer, there is
a probability of a system panic occurring. The root cause is
an access to an invalid memory address during URB callback handling.
Specifically, this happens when the dma_direct_unmap_sg() function
is called within the usb_hcd_unmap_urb_for_dma() interface, but the
sg-&gt;dma_address field is 0 and the sg data structure has already been
freed.

The SCSI driver sends transfer commands by invoking uas_queuecommand_lck()
in uas.c, using the uas_submit_urbs() function to submit requests to USB.
Within the uas_submit_urbs() implementation, three URBs (sense_urb,
data_urb, and cmd_urb) are sequentially submitted. Device removal may
occur at any point during uas_submit_urbs execution, which may result
in URB submission failure. However, some URBs might have been successfully
submitted before the failure, and uas_submit_urbs will return the -ENODEV
error code in this case. The current error handling directly calls
scsi_done(). In the SCSI driver, this eventually triggers scsi_complete()
to invoke scsi_end_request() for releasing the sgtable. The successfully
submitted URBs, when being unlinked to giveback, call
usb_hcd_unmap_urb_for_dma() in hcd.c, leading to exceptions during sg
unmapping operations since the sg data structure has already been freed.

This patch modifies the error condition check in the uas_submit_urbs()
function. When a UAS device is removed but one or more URBs have already
been successfully submitted to USB, it avoids immediately invoking
scsi_done() and save the cmnd to devinfo-&gt;cmnd array. If the successfully
submitted URBs is completed before devinfo-&gt;resetting being set, then
the scsi_done() function will be called within uas_try_complete() after
all pending URB operations are finalized. Otherwise, the scsi_done()
function will be called within uas_zap_pending(), which is executed after
usb_kill_anchored_urbs().

The error handling only takes effect when uas_queuecommand_lck() calls
uas_submit_urbs() and returns the error value -ENODEV . In this case,
the device is disconnected, and the flow proceeds to uas_disconnect(),
where uas_zap_pending() is invoked to call uas_try_complete().</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68332 | comedi: c6xdigio: Fix invalid PNP driver unregistration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68332</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: c6xdigio: Fix invalid PNP driver unregistration

The Comedi low-level driver "c6xdigio" seems to be for a parallel port
connected device.  When the Comedi core calls the driver's Comedi
"attach" handler `c6xdigio_attach()` to configure a Comedi to use this
driver, it tries to enable the parallel port PNP resources by
registering a PNP driver with `pnp_register_driver()`, but ignores the
return value.  (The `struct pnp_driver` it uses has only the `name` and
`id_table` members filled in.)  The driver's Comedi "detach" handler
`c6xdigio_detach()` unconditionally unregisters the PNP driver with
`pnp_unregister_driver()`.

It is possible for `c6xdigio_attach()` to return an error before it
calls `pnp_register_driver()` and it is possible for the call to
`pnp_register_driver()` to return an error (that is ignored).  In both
cases, the driver should not be calling `pnp_unregister_driver()` as it
does in `c6xdigio_detach()`.  (Note that `c6xdigio_detach()` will be
called by the Comedi core if `c6xdigio_attach()` returns an error, or if
the Comedi core decides to detach the Comedi device from the driver for
some other reason.)

The unconditional call to `pnp_unregister_driver()` without a previous
successful call to `pnp_register_driver()` will cause
`driver_unregister()` to issue a warning "Unexpected driver
unregister!".  This was detected by Syzbot [1].

Also, the PNP driver registration and unregistration should be done at
module init and exit time, respectively, not when attaching or detaching
Comedi devices to the driver.  (There might be more than one Comedi
device being attached to the driver, although that is unlikely.)

Change the driver to do the PNP driver registration at module init time,
and the unregistration at module exit time.  Since `c6xdigio_detach()`
now only calls `comedi_legacy_detach()`, remove the function and change
the Comedi driver "detach" handler to `comedi_legacy_detach`.

-------------------------------------------
[1] Syzbot sample crash report:
Unexpected driver unregister!
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 5970 at drivers/base/driver.c:273 driver_unregister drivers/base/driver.c:273 [inline]
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 5970 at drivers/base/driver.c:273 driver_unregister+0x90/0xb0 drivers/base/driver.c:270
Modules linked in:
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 5970 Comm: syz.0.17 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/02/2025
RIP: 0010:driver_unregister drivers/base/driver.c:273 [inline]
RIP: 0010:driver_unregister+0x90/0xb0 drivers/base/driver.c:270
Code: 48 89 ef e8 c2 e6 82 fc 48 89 df e8 3a 93 ff ff 5b 5d e9 c3 6d d9 fb e8 be 6d d9 fb 90 48 c7 c7 e0 f8 1f 8c e8 51 a2 97 fb 90 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 90 90 5b 5d e9 a5 6d d9 fb e8 e0 f4 41 fc eb 94 e8 d9 f4 41
RSP: 0018:ffffc9000373f9a0 EFLAGS: 00010282
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffffff8ff24720 RCX: ffffffff817b6ee8
RDX: ffff88807c932480 RSI: ffffffff817b6ef5 RDI: 0000000000000001
RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000001 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: ffffffff8ff24660
R13: dffffc0000000000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffff88814cca0000
FS:  000055556dab1500(0000) GS:ffff8881249d9000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 000055f77f285cd0 CR3: 000000007d871000 CR4: 00000000003526f0
Call Trace:
 
 comedi_device_detach_locked+0x12f/0xa50 drivers/comedi/drivers.c:207
 comedi_device_detach+0x67/0xb0 drivers/comedi/drivers.c:215
 comedi_device_attach+0x43d/0x900 drivers/comedi/drivers.c:1011
 do_devconfig_ioctl+0x1b1/0x710 drivers/comedi/comedi_fops.c:872
 comedi_unlocked_ioctl+0x165d/0x2f00 drivers/comedi/comedi_fops.c:2178
 vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
 __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:597 [inline]
 __se_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:583 [inline]
 __x64_sys_ioctl+0x18e/0x210 fs/ioctl.c:583
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_sys
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68333 | sched_ext: Fix possible deadlock in the deferred_irq_workfn()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68333</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sched_ext: Fix possible deadlock in the deferred_irq_workfn()

For PREEMPT_RT=y kernels, the deferred_irq_workfn() is executed in
the per-cpu irq_work/* task context and not disable-irq, if the rq
returned by container_of() is current CPU's rq, the following scenarios
may occur:

lock(&amp;amp;rq-&gt;__lock);

  lock(&amp;amp;rq-&gt;__lock);

This commit use IRQ_WORK_INIT_HARD() to replace init_irq_work() to
initialize rq-&gt;scx.deferred_irq_work, make the deferred_irq_workfn()
is always invoked in hard-irq context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68334 | platform/x86/amd/pmc: Add support for Van Gogh SoC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68334</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86/amd/pmc: Add support for Van Gogh SoC

The ROG Xbox Ally (non-X) SoC features a similar architecture to the
Steam Deck. While the Steam Deck supports S3 (s2idle causes a crash),
this support was dropped by the Xbox Ally which only S0ix suspend.

Since the handler is missing here, this causes the device to not suspend
and the AMD GPU driver to crash while trying to resume afterwards due to
a power hang.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68335 | comedi: pcl818: fix null-ptr-deref in pcl818_ai_cancel()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68335</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: pcl818: fix null-ptr-deref in pcl818_ai_cancel()

Syzbot identified an issue [1] in pcl818_ai_cancel(), which stems from
the fact that in case of early device detach via pcl818_detach(),
subdevice dev-&gt;read_subdev may not have initialized its pointer to
&amp;amp;struct comedi_async as intended. Thus, any such dereferencing of
&amp;amp;s-&gt;async-&gt;cmd will lead to general protection fault and kernel crash.

Mitigate this problem by removing a call to pcl818_ai_cancel() from
pcl818_detach() altogether. This way, if the subdevice setups its
support for async commands, everything async-related will be
handled via subdevice's own -&gt;cancel() function in
comedi_device_detach_locked() even before pcl818_detach(). If no
support for asynchronous commands is provided, there is no need
to cancel anything either.

[1] Syzbot crash:
Oops: general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000005: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN PTI
KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000028-0x000000000000002f]
CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 6050 Comm: syz.0.18 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 08/18/2025
RIP: 0010:pcl818_ai_cancel+0x69/0x3f0 drivers/comedi/drivers/pcl818.c:762
...
Call Trace:
 
 pcl818_detach+0x66/0xd0 drivers/comedi/drivers/pcl818.c:1115
 comedi_device_detach_locked+0x178/0x750 drivers/comedi/drivers.c:207
 do_devconfig_ioctl drivers/comedi/comedi_fops.c:848 [inline]
 comedi_unlocked_ioctl+0xcde/0x1020 drivers/comedi/comedi_fops.c:2178
 vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
 __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:597 [inline]
...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68336 | locking/spinlock/debug: Fix data-race in do_raw_write_lock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68336</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

locking/spinlock/debug: Fix data-race in do_raw_write_lock

KCSAN reports:

BUG: KCSAN: data-race in do_raw_write_lock / do_raw_write_lock

write (marked) to 0xffff800009cf504c of 4 bytes by task 1102 on cpu 1:
 do_raw_write_lock+0x120/0x204
 _raw_write_lock_irq
 do_exit
 call_usermodehelper_exec_async
 ret_from_fork

read to 0xffff800009cf504c of 4 bytes by task 1103 on cpu 0:
 do_raw_write_lock+0x88/0x204
 _raw_write_lock_irq
 do_exit
 call_usermodehelper_exec_async
 ret_from_fork

value changed: 0xffffffff -&gt; 0x00000001

Reported by Kernel Concurrency Sanitizer on:
CPU: 0 PID: 1103 Comm: kworker/u4:1 6.1.111

Commit 1a365e822372 ("locking/spinlock/debug: Fix various data races") has
adressed most of these races, but seems to be not consistent/not complete.

&gt;From do_raw_write_lock() only debug_write_lock_after() part has been
converted to WRITE_ONCE(), but not debug_write_lock_before() part.
Do it now.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68337 | jbd2: avoid bug_on in jbd2_journal_get_create_access() when file system corrupted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68337</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

jbd2: avoid bug_on in jbd2_journal_get_create_access() when file system corrupted

There's issue when file system corrupted:
------------[ cut here ]------------
kernel BUG at fs/jbd2/transaction.c:1289!
Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN PTI
CPU: 5 UID: 0 PID: 2031 Comm: mkdir Not tainted 6.18.0-rc1-next
RIP: 0010:jbd2_journal_get_create_access+0x3b6/0x4d0
RSP: 0018:ffff888117aafa30 EFLAGS: 00010202
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff88811a86b000 RCX: ffffffff89a63534
RDX: 1ffff110200ec602 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffff888100763010
RBP: ffff888100763000 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffff888100763028
R10: 0000000000000003 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: ffff88812c432000 R14: ffff88812c608000 R15: ffff888120bfc000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f91d6970c99 CR3: 00000001159c4000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
Call Trace:
 
 __ext4_journal_get_create_access+0x42/0x170
 ext4_getblk+0x319/0x6f0
 ext4_bread+0x11/0x100
 ext4_append+0x1e6/0x4a0
 ext4_init_new_dir+0x145/0x1d0
 ext4_mkdir+0x326/0x920
 vfs_mkdir+0x45c/0x740
 do_mkdirat+0x234/0x2f0
 __x64_sys_mkdir+0xd6/0x120
 do_syscall_64+0x5f/0xfa0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e

The above issue occurs with us in errors=continue mode when accompanied by
storage failures. There have been many inconsistencies in the file system
data.
In the case of file system data inconsistency, for example, if the block
bitmap of a referenced block is not set, it can lead to the situation where
a block being committed is allocated and used again. As a result, the
following condition will not be satisfied then trigger BUG_ON. Of course,
it is entirely possible to construct a problematic image that can trigger
this BUG_ON through specific operations. In fact, I have constructed such
an image and easily reproduced this issue.
Therefore, J_ASSERT() holds true only under ideal conditions, but it may
not necessarily be satisfied in exceptional scenarios. Using J_ASSERT()
directly in abnormal situations would cause the system to crash, which is
clearly not what we want. So here we directly trigger a JBD abort instead
of immediately invoking BUG_ON.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10021 | A Use of Uninitialized Variable vulnerability exists in Open Design Alliance Drawings SDK static versions (mt) before 2026.12. Static object...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10021</link><description>A Use of Uninitialized Variable vulnerability exists in Open Design Alliance Drawings SDK static versions (mt) before 2026.12. Static object `COdaMfcAppApp theApp` may access `OdString::kEmpty` before its initialization. Due to undefined initialization order of static objects across translation units (Static Initialization Order Fiasco), the application accesses uninitialized memory. This results in application crash on startup, causing denial of service. Due to undefined behavior,  memory corruption and potential arbitrary code execution cannot be ruled out in specific exploitation scenarios.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67826 | An issue was discovered in K7 Ultimate Security 17.0.2045. A Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerability in the K7 Ultimate Security anti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67826</link><description>An issue was discovered in K7 Ultimate Security 17.0.2045. A Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerability in the K7 Ultimate Security antivirus can be exploited by a local unprivileged user on default installations of the product. Insecure access to a named pipe allows unprivileged users to edit any registry key, leading to a full compromise as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61740 | Johnson Controls IQ Panels2, 2+, IQHub, IQPanel 4, PowerG Origin Validation Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61740</link><description>Authentication issue that does not verify the source of a packet which could allow an attacker to create a denial-of-service condition or modify the configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26379 | Johnson Controls IQ Panels2, 2+, IQHub, IQPanel 4, PowerG use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26379</link><description>Use of a weak pseudo-random number generator, which may allow an attacker to read or inject encrypted PowerG packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14018 | Unquoted Service Path in NetBT Consultancy&amp;#x27;s e-Fatura</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14018</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in NetBT Consulting Services Inc. E-Fatura allows Leveraging/Manipulating Configuration File Search Paths, Redirect Access to Libraries.This issue affects e-Fatura: before 1.2.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14273 | Mattermost Jira plugin user spoofing enables Jira request forgery.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14273</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.0, 11.0.x &lt;= 11.0.5, 10.12.x &lt;= 10.12.3, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.7 with the Jira plugin enabled and Mattermost Jira plugin versions &lt;=4.4.0 fail to enforce authentication and issue-key path restrictions in the Jira plugin, which allows an unauthenticated attacker who knows a valid user ID to issue authenticated GET and POST requests to the Jira server via crafted plugin payloads that spoof the user ID and inject arbitrary issue key paths. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00555</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54890 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the Hostgroups configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54890</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Hostgroup configuration page) allows Stored 

XSS by users with elevated privileges.This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.15, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.19, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12514 | A user with elevated privileges is able to introduce a SQL Injection using the Open-tickets Notification rules configuration parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12514</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring - Open-tickets (Notification rules configuration parameters, Open tickets modules) allows 

SQL Injection to user with elevated privileges.This issue affects Infra Monitoring - Open-tickets: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.5, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.5, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8460 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the Notification rules configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Notification rules, Open tickets module) 

allows Stored 

XSS by users with elevated privileges.This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.5, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.5, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61739 | Johnson Controls IQ Panels2, 2+, IQHub, IQPanel 4, PowerG reusing a nonce, key pair in encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61739</link><description>Due to Nonce reuse, attackers can perform reply attack or decrypt captured packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61738 | Johnson Controls PowerG and IQPanel cleartext transmission of sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61738</link><description>Under certain circumstances, attacker can capture the network key, read or write encrypted packets on the PowerG network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62094 | WordPress Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62094</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Voidthemes Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder.This issue affects Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 2.0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62107 | WordPress Feather Login Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62107</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PluginOps Feather Login Page allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Feather Login Page: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62880 | WordPress Custom 404 Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62880</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kunal Nagar Custom 404 Pro allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Custom 404 Pro: from n/a through 3.12.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8305 | Information Disclosure in Identity Agent Debug Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8305</link><description>An authenticated local user can obtain information that allows claiming security policy rules of another user due to sensitive information being printed in plaintext in Identity Agent for Terminal Services debug files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8304 | Information Disclosure in Identity Agent Registry Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8304</link><description>An authenticated local user can obtain information that allows claiming security policy rules of another user due to sensitive information being accessible in the Windows Registry keys for Check Point Identity Agent running on a Terminal Server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11544 | Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11544</link><description>Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauthorized firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11545 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11545</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may improperly access the HTTP server and execute arbitrary actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11540 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may access and read any files within the projector.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11540</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may access and read any files within the projector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11541 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and program...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11541</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and programs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11542 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and program...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11542</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and programs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11543 | Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11543</link><description>Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauthorized firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12049 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions Media Player MP-01 All Verisons allows a attacker may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12049</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions Media Player MP-01 All Verisons allows a attacker may access to the web interface of the affected product without authentication and change settings or perform other operations, and deliver content from the authoring software to the affected product without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15014 | loganhong php loganSite Article article_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15014</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in loganhong php loganSite up to c035fb5c3edd0b2a5e32fd4051cbbc9e61a31426. This affects an unknown function of the file /includes/article_detail.php of the component Article Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15013 | floooh sokol sokol_gfx.h _sg_validate_pipeline_desc stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15013</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in floooh sokol up to 5d11344150973f15e16d3ec4ee7550a73fb995e0. The impacted element is the function _sg_validate_pipeline_desc in the library sokol_gfx.h. Such manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The name of the patch is b95c5245ba357967220c9a860c7578a7487937b0. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15012 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15012</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /home/home.php. This manipulation of the argument a causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15011 | code-projects Simple Stock System logout.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15011</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /logout.php. The manipulation of the argument uname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15015 | Ragic｜Enterprise Cloud Database - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15015</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database developed by Ragic has a Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15016 | Ragic｜Enterprise Cloud Database - Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15016</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database developed by Ragic has a Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit the fixed key to generate verification information and log into the system as any user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15010 | Tenda WH450 SafeUrlFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15010</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SafeUrlFilter. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59301 | Modbus/TCP Dos Vulnerability in DVP15MC11T</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59301</link><description>Delta Electronics DVP15MC11T lacks proper validation of the modbus/tcp packets and can lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15008 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request L7Port stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15008</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/L7Port of the component HTTP Request Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument page results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15009 | liweiyi ChestnutCMS Filename upload FilenameUtils.getExtension unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15009</link><description>A flaw has been found in liweiyi ChestnutCMS up to 1.5.8. This vulnerability affects the function FilenameUtils.getExtension of the file /dev-api/common/upload of the component Filename Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15007 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request L7Im stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15007</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/L7Im of the component HTTP Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15006 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request CheckTools stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15006</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/CheckTools of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument ipaddress causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15005 | CouchCMS reCAPTCHA config.example.php hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15005</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CouchCMS up to 2.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file couch/config.example.php of the component reCAPTCHA Handler. The manipulation of the argument K_RECAPTCHA_SITE_KEY/K_RECAPTCHA_SECRET_KEY results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15004 | DedeCMS freelist_main.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15004</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in DedeCMS up to 5.7.118. This impacts an unknown function of the file /freelist_main.php. The manipulation of the argument orderby leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15003 | SeaCMS admin_video.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15003</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SeaCMS up to 13.3. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file admin_video.php. Performing manipulation of the argument e_id results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15002 | SeaCMS mysqli.class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15002</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SeaCMS up to 13.3. The affected element is an unknown function of the file js/player/dmplayer/dmku/class/mysqli.class.php. Such manipulation of the argument page/limit leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62901 | WordPress WP Microdata plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62901</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tormorten WP Microdata allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Microdata: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62926 | WordPress TempTool plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HappyDevs TempTool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TempTool: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62955 | WordPress TempTool plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62955</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in HappyDevs TempTool allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects TempTool: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14995 | Tenda FH1201 SetIpBind sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14995</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH1201 1.2.0.14(408). Affected is the function sprintf of the file /goform/SetIpBind. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 08:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14800 | Redirection for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Copy via move_file_to_upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14800</link><description>The Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'move_file_to_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to copy arbitrary files on the affected site's server. If 'allow_url_fopen' is set to 'On', it is possible to upload a remote file to the server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14855 | SureForms &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14855</link><description>The SureForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form field parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14994 | Tenda FH1201/FH1206 HTTP Request webtypelibrary strcat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14994</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda FH1201 and FH1206 1.2.0.14(408)/1.2.0.8(8155). This impacts the function strcat of the file /goform/webtypelibrary of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument webSiteId causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14993 | Tenda AC18 HTTP Request SetDlnaCfg sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14993</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. This affects the function sprintf of the file /goform/SetDlnaCfg of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument scanList results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14992 | Tenda AC18 HTTP Request GetParentControlInfo strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14992</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12398 | Product Table for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12398</link><description>The Product Table for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12654 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 0.9.120 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary Directory Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12654</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary directory creation in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.120. This is due to the check_filesystem_permissions() function not properly restricting the directories that can be created, or in what location. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to create arbitrary directories.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13220 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13220</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13361 | Web to SugarCRM Lead &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom Field Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13361</link><description>The Web to SugarCRM Lead plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the custom field deletion functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete custom fields via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13693 | Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid &amp;lt;= 3.6.8 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Custom Scripts&amp;#x27; Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13693</link><description>The Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Custom scripts' setting in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14991 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System bwdates-reports-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14991</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. Executing manipulation of the argument fromdate can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9343 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9343</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ticket subjects in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14990 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14990</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. Performing manipulation of the argument viewid results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68644 | Yealink RPS before 2025-06-27 allows unauthorized access to information, including AutoP URL addresses. This was fixed by deploying an enhan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68644</link><description>Yealink RPS before 2025-06-27 allows unauthorized access to information, including AutoP URL addresses. This was fixed by deploying an enhanced authentication mechanism through a security update to all cloud instances.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11496 | Five Star Restaurant Reservations – WordPress Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11496</link><description>The Five Star Restaurant Reservations – WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rtb-name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12980 | Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks for News, Magazines, Blog Websites – PostX &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12980</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks for News, Magazines, Blog Websites – PostX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the '/ultp/v2/get_dynamic_content/' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive user metadata, including password hashes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13838 | WishSuite &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;button_text&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13838</link><description>The WishSuite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button_text' parameter of the 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14043 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Metadata Section Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14043</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized metadata section creation due to missing authorization checks in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the `create_item_permissions_check()` function unconditionally returning true, which bypasses authentication and authorization validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary metadata sections for any collection via the public REST API granted they can access the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14054 | WC Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;heading_color&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14054</link><description>The WC Builder – WooCommerce Page Builder for WPBakery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'heading_color' parameter (and multiple other styling parameters) of the `wpbforwpbakery_product_additional_information` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14071 | Live Composer – Free WordPress Website Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection via dslc_module_posts_output Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14071</link><description>The Live Composer – Free WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via deserialization of untrusted input in the dslc_module_posts_output shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14080 | Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14080</link><description>The Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This is due to missing authorization checks on the post update functionality in the fpsml_form_process AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary posts by providing a post_id parameter via the guest posting form, allowing them to change post titles, content, excerpts, and remove post authors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25445 | WordPress HappyFiles Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25445</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HappyFiles HappyFiles Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HappyFiles Pro: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25446 | WordPress HappyFiles Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25446</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HappyFiles HappyFiles Pro happyfiles-pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HappyFiles Pro: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47232 | WordPress WP Affiliate Disclosure plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47232</link><description>Vulnerability in mojofywp WP Affiliate Disclosure wp-affiliate-disclosure.This issue affects WP Affiliate Disclosure: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25068 | WordPress Magazine Edge theme &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Authenticated Arbitrary Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25068</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mapro Collins Magazine Edge allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Magazine Edge: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>