<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:51:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-1701 | itsourcecode Student Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1701</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /enrollment/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1702 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software User Management user.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1702</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/operation/user.php of the component User Management. Performing a manipulation of the argument group_id results in improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1691 | bolo-solo SnakeYAML BackupService.java importMarkdownsSync deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1691</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in bolo-solo up to 2.6.4. This impacts the function importMarkdownsSync of the file src/main/java/org/b3log/solo/bolo/prop/BackupService.java of the component SnakeYAML. Such manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1700 | projectworlds House Rental and Property Listing sms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1700</link><description>A weakness has been identified in projectworlds House Rental and Property Listing 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /app/sms.php. This manipulation of the argument Message causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1689 | Tenda HG10 Login formLogin checkUserFromLanOrWan command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1689</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda HG10 US_HG7_HG9_HG10re_300001138_en_xpon. The impacted element is the function checkUserFromLanOrWan of the file /boaform/admin/formLogin of the component Login Interface. The manipulation of the argument Host results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1690 | Tenda HG10 formSysCmd system command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1690</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda HG10 US_HG7_HG9_HG10re_300001138_en_xpon. This affects the function system of the file /boaform/formSysCmd. This manipulation of the argument sysCmd causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36966 | Dolibarr 11.0.3 - &amp;#x27;ldap.php&amp;#x27; - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36966</link><description>Dolibarr 11.0.3 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in LDAP synchronization settings that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts through multiple parameters. Attackers can exploit the host, slave, and port parameters in /dolibarr/admin/ldap.php to execute arbitrary JavaScript and potentially steal user cookie information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36996 | PHPFusion 9.03.50 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36996</link><description>PHPFusion 9.03.50 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the print.php page that fails to properly sanitize user-submitted message content. Attackers can inject malicious JavaScript through forum messages that will execute when the print page is generated, allowing script execution in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36998 | forma.lms The E-Learning Suite 2.3.0.2 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36998</link><description>Forma.lms The E-Learning Suite 2.3.0.2 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in multiple course and profile parameters. Attackers can inject malicious scripts in course code, name, description fields, and email parameter to execute arbitrary JavaScript without proper input sanitization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37003 | Sellacious eCommerce 4.6 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37003</link><description>Sellacious eCommerce 4.6 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Manage Your Addresses module that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can exploit multiple address input fields like full name, company, and address to execute persistent script code that can hijack user sessions and manipulate application modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37014 | Tryton 5.4 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37014</link><description>Tryton 5.4 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the user profile name input that allows remote attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by inserting script payloads in the name field, which execute in the frontend and backend user interfaces.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37019 | Orchard Core RC1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37019</link><description>Orchard Core RC1 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows remote attackers to inject malicious scripts through blog post creation. Attackers can create blog posts with embedded JavaScript in the MarkdownBodyPart.Source parameter to execute arbitrary scripts in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37022 | OpenZ ERP 3.6.60 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37022</link><description>OpenZ ERP 3.6.60 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Employee module's name and description parameters. Attackers can inject malicious scripts through POST requests to , enabling session hijacking and manipulation of application modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37030 | Outline Service 1.3.3  - &amp;#x27;Outline Service &amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37030</link><description>Outline Service 1.3.3 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path in C:\Program Files (x86)\Outline to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37058 | Andrea ST Filters Service 1.0.64.7 - Unquoted service path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37058</link><description>Andrea ST Filters Service 1.0.64.7 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration. Local attackers can exploit the unquoted path to inject malicious code that will execute with elevated LocalSystem privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37059 | Popcorn Time 6.2 - &amp;#x27;Update service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37059</link><description>Popcorn Time 6.2.1.14 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local non-privileged users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can insert malicious executables in Program Files (x86) or system root directories to be executed with SYSTEM-level permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37060 | Atomic Alarm Clock x86 6.3 - &amp;#x27;AtomicAlarmClock&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37060</link><description>Atomic Alarm Clock 6.3 contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability in its service configuration that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path by placing a malicious executable named 'Program.exe' to gain persistent system-level access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4686 | Time-Based Blind SQLi in Kodmatic Computer&amp;#x27;s Online Exam and Assessment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4686</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Kodmatic Computer Software Tourism Construction Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Online Exam and Assessment allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Online Exam and Assessment: through 30012026. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1687 | Tenda HG10 Boa Webserver formSamba command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1687</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda HG10 US_HG7_HG9_HG10re_300001138_en_xpon. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /boaform/formSamba of the component Boa Webserver. Executing a manipulation of the argument serverString can lead to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1688 | itsourcecode Directory Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1688</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Directory Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7964 | Zigbee Router Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7964</link><description>After receiving a 

malformed 802.15.4 MAC Data Request

 the Zigbee Coordinator sends a ‘network leave’ request to Zigbee router resulting in the Zigbee Router getting stuck in a non-rejoinable state. If a suitable parent is not available, the end devices will be unable to rejoin. A manual recommissioning is required to recover the Zigbee Router.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1686 | Totolink A3600R app.so setAppEasyWizardConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1686</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Totolink A3600R 5.9c.4959. This issue affects the function setAppEasyWizardConfig in the library /lib/cste_modules/app.so. Performing a manipulation of the argument apcliSsid results in buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24854 | Church CRM has SQL injection in PaddleNumEditor.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24854</link><description>ChurchCRM is an open-source church management system. A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in endpoint `/PaddleNumEditor.php` in ChurchCRM prior to version 6.7.2. Any authenticated user, including one with zero assigned permissions, can exploit SQL injection through the `PerID` parameter. Version 6.7.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24855 | ChurchCRM has Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Create Events in Church Calendar, Leading to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24855</link><description>ChurchCRM is an open-source church management system. Versions prior to 6.7.2 have a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability occurs in Create Events in Church Calendar. Users with low privileges can create XSS payloads in the Description field. This payload is stored in the database, and when other users view that event (including the admin), the payload is triggered, leading to account takeover. Version 6.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25050 | Vendure vulnerable to timing attack that enables user enumeration in NativeAuthenticationStrategy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25050</link><description>Vendure is an open-source headless commerce platform. Prior to version 3.5.3, the `NativeAuthenticationStrategy.authenticate()` method is vulnerable to a timing attack that allows attackers to enumerate valid usernames (email addresses). In `packages/core/src/config/auth/native-authentication-strategy.ts`, the authenticate method returns immediately if a user is not found. The significant timing difference (~200-400ms for bcrypt vs ~1-5ms for DB miss) allows attackers to reliably distinguish between existing and non-existing accounts. Version 3.5.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25128 | fast-xml-parser has RangeError DoS Numeric Entities Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25128</link><description>fast-xml-parser allows users to validate XML, parse XML to JS object, or build XML from JS object without C/C++ based libraries and no callback. In versions 4.3.6 through 5.3.3, a RangeError vulnerability exists in the numeric entity processing of fast-xml-parser when parsing XML with out-of-range entity code points (e.g., `&amp;#9999999;` or `&amp;#xffffff;`). This causes the parser to throw an uncaught exception, crashing any application that processes untrusted XML input. Version 5.3.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1684 | Free5GC SMF PFCP UDP Endpoint pfcp_reports.go HandleReports denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1684</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Free5GC SMF up to 4.1.0. Affected by this issue is the function HandleReports of the file /internal/context/pfcp_reports.go of the component PFCP UDP Endpoint. The manipulation results in denial of service. The attack can be executed remotely. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1685 | D-Link DIR-823X Login sub_40AC74 excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1685</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_40AC74 of the component Login. Such manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4027 | Undertow: outofmemoryerror in httpservletrequestimpl.getparameternames() can cause remote dos attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4027</link><description>A flaw was found in Undertow. Servlets using a method that calls HttpServletRequestImpl.getParameterNames() can cause an OutOfMemoryError when the client sends a request with large parameter names. This issue can be exploited by an unauthorized user to cause a remote denial-of-service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6723 | Untrusted user data can lead to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6723</link><description>Chef InSpec up to version 5.23 creates named pipes with overly permissive default Windows access controls. A local attacker may interfere with the pipe connection process and exploit the insufficient access restrictions to assume the InSpec execution context, potentially resulting in elevated privileges or operational disruption.

This issue affects Chef Inspec: through 5.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1682 | Free5GC SMF PFCP UDP Endpoint handler.go HandlePfcpAssociationReleaseRequest null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1682</link><description>A flaw has been found in Free5GC SMF up to 4.1.0. Affected is the function HandlePfcpAssociationReleaseRequest of the file internal/pfcp/handler/handler.go of the component PFCP UDP Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to null pointer dereference. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1683 | Free5GC SMF PFCP handler.go HandlePfcpSessionReportRequest denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1683</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Free5GC SMF up to 4.1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function HandlePfcpSessionReportRequest of the file internal/pfcp/handler/handler.go of the component PFCP. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9226 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9226</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine OpManager, NetFlow Analyzer, and OpUtils versions prior to 128582 are affected by a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Subnet Details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1498 | WatchGuard Firebox LDAP Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1498</link><description>An LDAP Injection vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to retrieve sensitive information from a connected LDAP authentication server through an exposed authentication or management web interface. This vulnerability may also allow a remote attacker to authenticate as an LDAP user with a partial identifier if they additionally have that user's valid passphrase.This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.11.6, from 12.5 through 12.5.15, from 2025.1 through 2026.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13176 | Local privilege escalation in ESET Inspect Connector for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13176</link><description>Planting a custom configuration file

in 

ESET Inspect Connector allow load a malicious DLL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26385 | Metasys product command injection vulnerability could allow remote SQL execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26385</link><description>Johnson Controls Metasys component listed below have  Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (Command Injection) Vulnerability . Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote SQL execution This issue affects 



  *  Metasys: Application and Data Server (ADS) installed with SQL Express deployed as part of the Metasys 14.1 and prior installation, 
  *  Extended Application and Data Server (ADX) installed with SQL Express deployed as part of the Metasys 14.1 installation, 
  *  LCS8500 or NAE8500 installed with SQL Express deployed as part of the Metasys installation Releases 12.0 through 14.1, 
  *  System Configuration Tool (SCT) installed with SQL Express deployed as part of the SCT installation 17.1 and prior, 
  *  Controller Configuration Tool (CCT) installed with SQL Express deployed as part of the CCT installation 17.0 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0709 | Some Hikvision Wireless Access Points are vulnerable to authenticated command execution due to insufficient input validation. Attackers with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0709</link><description>Some Hikvision Wireless Access Points are vulnerable to authenticated command execution due to insufficient input validation. Attackers with valid credentials can exploit this flaw by sending crafted packets containing malicious commands to affected devices, leading to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22623 | Due to insufficient input parameter validation on the interface, authenticated users of certain HIKSEMI NAS products can execute arbitrary c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22623</link><description>Due to insufficient input parameter validation on the interface, authenticated users of certain HIKSEMI NAS products can execute arbitrary commands on the device by crafting specific messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22624 | Due to inadequate access control, authenticated users of certain HIKSEMI NAS products can manipulate other users' file resources without pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22624</link><description>Due to inadequate access control, authenticated users of certain HIKSEMI NAS products can manipulate other users' file resources without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22625 | Improper handling of filenames in certain HIKSEMI NAS products may lead to the exposure of sensitive system files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22625</link><description>Improper handling of filenames in certain HIKSEMI NAS products may lead to the exposure of sensitive system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22626 | Due to insufficient input parameter validation on the interface, authenticated users of certain HIKSEMI NAS products can cause abnormal devi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22626</link><description>Due to insufficient input parameter validation on the interface, authenticated users of certain HIKSEMI NAS products can cause abnormal device behavior by crafting specific messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1699 | In the Eclipse Theia Website repository, the GitHub Actions workflow .github/workflows/preview.yml used pull_request_target trigger while ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1699</link><description>In the Eclipse Theia Website repository, the GitHub Actions workflow .github/workflows/preview.yml used pull_request_target trigger while checking out and executing untrusted pull request code. This allowed any GitHub user to execute arbitrary code in the repository's CI environment with access to repository secrets and a GITHUB_TOKEN with extensive write permissions (contents:write, packages:write, pages:write, actions:write). An attacker could exfiltrate secrets, publish malicious packages to the eclipse-theia organization, modify the official Theia website, and push malicious code to the repository.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1395 | Sensitive Data Exposure in CoDeriApp&amp;#x27;s HeyGarson</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1395</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Codriapp Innovation and Software Technologies Inc. HeyGarson allows Fuzzing for application mapping.This issue affects HeyGarson: through 30012026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 08:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21418 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.5.2 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injecti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21418</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.5.2 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary command execution with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 08:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22277 | Dell UnityVSA, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Inject...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22277</link><description>Dell UnityVSA, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary command execution with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 08:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25211 | Llama Stack (aka llama-stack) before 0.4.0rc3 does not censor the pgvector password in the initialization log.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25211</link><description>Llama Stack (aka llama-stack) before 0.4.0rc3 does not censor the pgvector password in the initialization log.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25210 | In libexpat before 2.7.4, the doContent function does not properly determine the buffer size bufSize because there is no integer overflow ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25210</link><description>In libexpat before 2.7.4, the doContent function does not properly determine the buffer size bufSize because there is no integer overflow check for tag buffer reallocation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0805 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) in Crafty Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0805</link><description>An input neutralization vulnerability in the Backup Configuration component of Crafty Controller allows a remote, authenticated attacker to perform file tampering and remote code execution via path traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0963 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) in Crafty Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0963</link><description>An input neutralization vulnerability in the File Operations API Endpoint component of Crafty Controller allows a remote, authenticated attacker to perform file tampering and remote code execution via path traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1680 | Local Privilege Escalation in Local Admin Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1680</link><description>Improper access control in the WCF endpoint in Edgemo (now owned by Danoffice IT) Local Admin Service 1.2.7.23180 on Windows allows a local user to escalate their privileges to local administrator via direct communication with the LocalAdminService.exe named pipe, bypassing client-side group membership restrictions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12899 | net: icmp: Out of bound memory read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12899</link><description>A flaw in Zephyr’s network stack allows an IPv4 packet containing ICMP type 128 to be misclassified as an ICMPv6 Echo Request. This results in an out-of-bounds memory read and creates a potential information-leak vulnerability in the networking subsystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24714 | Some end of service NETGEAR products provide "TelnetEnable" functionality, which allows a magic packet to activate telnet service on the box...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24714</link><description>Some end of service NETGEAR products provide "TelnetEnable" functionality, which allows a magic packet to activate telnet service on the box.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24728 | Interinfo DreamMaker - Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24728</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in the /servlet/baServer3 endpoint of Interinfo DreamMaker versions before 2025/10/22 allows remote attackers to access exposed administrative functionality without prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24729 | Interinfo DreamMaker - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24729</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in the file upload function of Interinfo DreamMaker versions before 2025/10/22 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a malicious class file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15322 | Tanium addressed an improper access controls vulnerability in Tanium Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15322</link><description>Tanium addressed an improper access controls vulnerability in Tanium Server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:03:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1638 | Tenda AC21 mDMZSetCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1638</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda AC21 1.1.1.1/1.dmzip/16.03.08.16. The impacted element is the function mDMZSetCfg of the file /goform/mDMZSetCfg. The manipulation of the argument dmzIp results in command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1665 | Command Injection in nvm via NVM_AUTH_HEADER in wget code path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1665</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in nvm (Node Version Manager) versions 0.40.3 and below. The nvm_download() function uses eval to execute wget commands, and the NVM_AUTH_HEADER environment variable was not sanitized in the wget code path (though it was sanitized in the curl code path). An attacker who can set environment variables in a victim's shell environment (e.g., via malicious CI/CD configurations, compromised dotfiles, or Docker images) can inject arbitrary shell commands that execute when the victim runs nvm commands that trigger downloads, such as 'nvm install' or 'nvm ls-remote'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1637 | Tenda AC21 AdvSetMacMtuWan fromAdvSetMacMtuWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1637</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. The affected element is the function fromAdvSetMacMtuWan of the file /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1624 | D-Link DWR-M961 formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1624</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M961 1.1.47. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom. Such manipulation of the argument fota_url leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1625 | D-Link DWR-M961 SMS Message formSmsManage sub_4250E0 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1625</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DWR-M961 1.1.47. The impacted element is the function sub_4250E0 of the file /boafrm/formSmsManage of the component SMS Message. Performing a manipulation of the argument action_value results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25126 | PolarLearn&amp;#x27;s unvalidated vote direction allows vote count manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25126</link><description>PolarLearn is a free and open-source learning program. Prior to version 0-PRERELEASE-15, the vote API route (`POST /api/v1/forum/vote`) trusts the JSON body’s `direction` value without runtime validation. TypeScript types are not enforced at runtime, so an attacker can send arbitrary strings (e.g., `"x"`) as `direction`. Downstream (`VoteServer`) treats any non-`"up"` and non-`null` value as a downvote and persists the invalid value in `votes_data`. This can be exploited to bypass intended business logic. Version 0-PRERELEASE-15 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25117 | pwn.college DOJO vulnerable to sandbox escape leading to arbitrary javascript execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25117</link><description>pwn.college DOJO is an education platform for learning cybersecurity. Prior to commit e33da14449a5abcff507e554f66e2141d6683b0a, missing sandboxing on `/workspace/*` routes allows challenge authors to inject arbitrary javascript which runs on the same origin as `http[:]//dojo[.]website`. This is a sandbox escape leading to arbitrary javascript execution as the dojo's origin. A challenge author can craft a page that executes any dangerous actions that the user could. Version e33da14449a5abcff507e554f66e2141d6683b0a patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25116 | Runtipi vulnerable to unauthenticated docker-compose.yml Overwrite via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25116</link><description>Runtipi is a personal homeserver orchestrator. Starting in version 4.5.0 and prior to version 4.7.2, an unauthenticated Path Traversal vulnerability in the `UserConfigController` allows any remote user to overwrite the system's `docker-compose.yml` configuration file. By exploiting insecure URN parsing, an attacker can replace the primary stack configuration with a malicious one, resulting in full Remote Code Execution (RCE) and host filesystem compromise the next time the instance is restarted by the operator. Version 4.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1281 | A code injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile allowing attackers to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1281</link><description>A code injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile allowing attackers to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1340 | A code injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile allowing attackers to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1340</link><description>A code injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile allowing attackers to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24905 | Inspektor Gadget has a Command Injection vulnerability in Makefile.build</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24905</link><description>Inspektor Gadget is a set of tools and framework for data collection and system inspection on Kubernetes clusters and Linux hosts using eBPF. The `ig` binary provides a subcommand for image building, used to generate custom gadget OCI images. A part of this functionality is implemented in the file `inspektor-gadget/cmd/common/image/build.go`. The `Makefile.build` file is the Makefile template employed during the building process. This file includes user-controlled data in an unsafe fashion, specifically some parameters are embedded without an adequate escaping in the commands inside the Makefile. Prior to version 0.48.1, this implementation is vulnerable to command injection: an attacker able to control values in the `buildOptions` structure would be able to execute arbitrary commands during the building process. An attacker able to exploit this vulnerability would be able to execute arbitrary command on the Linux host where the `ig` command is launched, if images are built with the `--local` flag or on the build container invoked by `ig`, if the `--local` flag is not provided. The `buildOptions` structure is extracted from the YAML gadget manifest passed to the `ig image build` command. Therefore, the attacker would need a way to control either the full `build.yml` file passed to the `ig image build` command, or one of its options. Typically, this could happen in a CI/CD scenario that builds untrusted gadgets to verify correctness. Version 0.48.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25040 | Budibase Vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via API Abuse – Creator Can Invite Users with Admin/Any Role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25040</link><description>Budibase is a low code platform for creating internal tools, workflows, and admin panels. In versions up to and including 3.26.3, a Creator-level user, who normally has no UI permission to invite users, can manipulate API requests to invite new users with any role, including Admin, Creator, or App Viewer, and assign them to any group in the organization. This allows full privilege escalation, bypassing UI restrictions, and can lead to complete takeover of the workspace or organization. As of time of publication, no known fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25046 | [Kimi VS Code] Command Injection in publish scripts vsix-publish.js and ovsx-publish.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25046</link><description>Kimi Agent SDK is a set of libraries that expose the Kimi Code (Kimi CLI) agent runtime in applications. The vsix-publish.js and ovsx-publish.js scripts pass filenames to execSync() as shell command strings. Prior to version 0.1.6, filenames containing shell metacharacters like $(cmd) could execute arbitrary commands. Note: This vulnerability exists only in the repository's development scripts. The published VSCode extension does not include these files and end users are not affected. This is fixed in version 0.1.6 by replacing execSync with execFileSync using array arguments. As a workaround, ensure .vsix files in the project directory have safe filenames before running publish scripts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25047 | deepHas vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via constructor.prototype</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25047</link><description>deepHas provides a test for the existence of a nested object key and optionally returns that key. A prototype pollution vulnerability exists in version 1.0.7 of the deephas npm package that allows an attacker to modify global object behavior. This issue was fixed in version 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25061 | tcpflow has TIM Element OOB Write in wifipcap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25061</link><description>tcpflow is a TCP/IP packet demultiplexer. In versions up to and including 1.61, wifipcap parses 802.11 management frame elements and performs a length check on the wrong field when handling the TIM element. A crafted frame with a large TIM length can cause a 1-byte out-of-bounds write past `tim.bitmap[251]`. The overflow is small and DoS is the likely impact; code execution is potential, but still up in the air. The affected structure is stack-allocated in `handle_beacon()` and related handlers. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25063 | gradle-completion has a Bash command injection issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25063</link><description>gradle-completion provides Bash and Zsh completion support for Gradle. A command injection vulnerability was found in gradle-completion up to and including 9.3.0 that allows arbitrary code execution when a user triggers Bash tab completion in a project containing a malicious Gradle build file. The `gradle-completion` script for Bash fails to adequately sanitize Gradle task names and task descriptions, allowing command injection via a malicious Gradle build file when the user completes a command in Bash (without them explicitly running any task in the build). For example, given a task description that includes a string between backticks, then that string would be evaluated as a command when presenting the task description in the completion list. While task execution is the core feature of Gradle, this inherent execution may lead to unexpected outcomes. The vulnerability does not affect zsh completion. The first patched version is 9.3.1. As a workaround, it is possible and effective to temporarily disable bash completion for Gradle by removing `gradle-completion` from `.bashrc` or `.bash_profile`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24902 | TrustTunnel has SSRF and private network restriction bypass via numeric address destinations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24902</link><description>TrustTunnel is an open-source VPN protocol with a server-side request forgery and and private network restriction bypass in versions prior to 0.9.114. In `tcp_forwarder.rs`, SSRF protection for `allow_private_network_connections = false` was only applied in the `TcpDestination::HostName(peer)` path. The `TcpDestination::Address(peer) =&gt; peer` path proceeded to `TcpStream::connect()` without equivalent checks (for example `is_global_ip`, `is_loopback`), allowing loopback/private targets to be reached by supplying a numeric IP. The vulnerability is fixed in version 0.9.114.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24904 | TrustTunnel has `client_random_prefix` rule bypass via fragmented or partial TLS ClientHello</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24904</link><description>TrustTunnel is an open-source VPN protocol with a rule bypass issue in versions prior to 0.9.115. In `tls_listener.rs`, `TlsListener::listen()` peeks 1024 bytes and calls `extract_client_random(...)`. If `parse_tls_plaintext` fails (for example, a fragmented/partial ClientHello split across TCP writes), `extract_client_random` returns `None`. In `rules.rs`, `RulesEngine::evaluate` only evaluates `client_random_prefix` when `client_random` is `Some(...)`. As a result, when extraction fails (`client_random == None`), any rule that relies on `client_random_prefix` matching is skipped and evaluation falls through to later rules. As an important semantics note: `client_random_prefix` is a match condition only. It does not mean "block non-matching prefixes" by itself. A rule with `client_random_prefix = ...` triggers its `action` only when the prefix matches (and the field is available to evaluate). Non-matches (or `None`) simply do not match that rule and continue to fall through. The vulnerability is fixed in version 0.9.115.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24845 | malcontent&amp;#x27;s OCI image scanning could expose registry credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24845</link><description>malcontent discovers supply-chain compromises through. context, differential analysis, and YARA. Starting in version 0.10.0 and prior to version 1.20.3, malcontent could be made to expose Docker registry credentials if it scanned a specially crafted OCI image reference. malcontent uses google/go-containerregistry for OCI image pulls, which by default uses the Docker credential keychain. A malicious registry could return a `WWW-Authenticate` header redirecting token authentication to an attacker-controlled endpoint, causing credentials to be sent to that endpoint. Version 1.20.3 fixes the issue by defaulting to anonymous auth for OCI pulls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24846 | malcontent&amp;#x27;s archive extraction could write outside extraction directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24846</link><description>malcontent discovers supply-chain compromises through. context, differential analysis, and YARA. Starting in version 1.8.0 and prior to version 1.20.3, malcontent could be made to create symlinks outside the intended extraction directory when scanning a specially crafted tar or deb archive. The `handleSymlink` function received arguments in the wrong order, causing the symlink target to be used as the symlink location. Additionally, symlink targets were not validated to ensure they resolved within the extraction directory. Version 1.20.3 introduces fixes that swap handleSymlink arguments, validate symlink location, and validate symlink targets that resolve within an extraction directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1623 | Totolink A7000R cstecgi.cgi setUpgradeFW command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1623</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Totolink A7000R 4.1cu.4154. Impacted is the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. This manipulation of the argument FileName causes command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15288 | Tanium addressed an improper access controls vulnerability in Interact.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15288</link><description>Tanium addressed an improper access controls vulnerability in Interact.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69604 | An issue in Shirt Pocket's SuperDuper! 3.11 and earlier allow a local attacker to modify the default task template to install an arbitrary p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69604</link><description>An issue in Shirt Pocket's SuperDuper! 3.11 and earlier allow a local attacker to modify the default task template to install an arbitrary package that can run shell scripts with root privileges and Full Disk Access, thus bypassing macOS privacy controls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63650 | An out-of-bounds read in the mk_ptr_to_buf in mk_core function (mk_memory.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63650</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the mk_ptr_to_buf in mk_core function (mk_memory.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63651 | A use-after-free in the mk_string_char_search function (mk_core/mk_string.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63651</link><description>A use-after-free in the mk_string_char_search function (mk_core/mk_string.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63652 | A use-after-free in the mk_http_request_end function (mk_server/mk_http.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63652</link><description>A use-after-free in the mk_http_request_end function (mk_server/mk_http.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63653 | An out-of-bounds read in the mk_vhost_fdt_close function (mk_server/mk_vhost.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63653</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the mk_vhost_fdt_close function (mk_server/mk_vhost.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63655 | A NULL pointer dereference in the mk_http_range_parse function (mk_server/mk_http.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63655</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in the mk_http_range_parse function (mk_server/mk_http.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63656 | An out-of-bounds read in the header_cmp function (mk_server/mk_http_parser.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63656</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the header_cmp function (mk_server/mk_http_parser.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63657 | An out-of-bounds read in the mk_mimetype_find function (mk_server/mk_mimetype.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63657</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the mk_mimetype_find function (mk_server/mk_mimetype.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63658 | A stack overflow in the mk_http_index_lookup function (mk_server/mk_http.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63658</link><description>A stack overflow in the mk_http_index_lookup function (mk_server/mk_http.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted HTTP request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22806 | vCluster Platform&amp;#x27;s Access Keys Allows Access Beyond Scope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22806</link><description>vCluster Platform provides a Kubernetes platform for managing virtual clusters, multi-tenancy, and cluster sharing. Prior to versions 4.6.0, 4.5.4, 4.4.2, and 4.3.10, when an access key is created with a limited scope, the scope can be bypassed to access resources outside of it. However, the user still cannot access resources beyond what is accessible to the owner of the access key. Versions 4.6.0, 4.5.4, 4.4.2, and 4.3.10 fix the vulnerability. Some other mitigations are available. Users can limit exposure by reviewing access keys which are scoped and ensuring any users with access to them have appropriate permissions set. Creating automation users with very limited permissions and using access keys for these automation users can be used as a temporary workaround where upgrading is not immediately possible but scoped access keys are needed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24687 | Umbraco.Forms has path traversal and file enumeration vulnerability in Linux/Mac</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24687</link><description>Umbraco Forms is a form builder that integrates with the Umbraco content management system. It's possible for an authenticated backoffice-user to enumerate and traverse paths/files on the systems filesystem and read their contents, on Mac/Linux Umbraco installations using Forms. As Umbraco Cloud runs in a Windows environment, Cloud users aren't affected. This issue affects versions 16 and 17 of Umbraco Forms and is patched in 16.4.1 and 17.1.1. If upgrading is not immediately possible, users can mitigate this vulnerability by configuring a WAF or reverse proxy to block requests containing path traversal sequences (`../`, `..\`) in the `fileName` parameter of the export endpoint, restricting network access to the Umbraco backoffice to trusted IP ranges, and/or blocking the `/umbraco/forms/api/v1/export` endpoint entirely if the export feature is not required. However, upgrading to the patched version is strongly recommended.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15549 | FluentCMS 2026 Stored XSS via SVG Upload in File Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15549</link><description>FluentCMS 2026 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated administrators to upload SVG files with embedded JavaScript via the File Management module. Attackers can upload malicious SVG files that execute JavaScript in the browser of any user accessing the uploaded file URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15550 | birkir prime &amp;lt;= 0.4.0.beta.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery in GraphQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15550</link><description>birkir prime &lt;= 0.4.0.beta.0 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability in its GraphQL endpoint that allows attackers to exploit GET-based query requests. Attackers can craft malicious GET requests to trigger unauthorized actions against privileged users by manipulating GraphQL query parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63649 | An out-of-bounds read in the http_parser_transfer_encoding_chunked function (mk_server/mk_http_parser.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63649</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the http_parser_transfer_encoding_chunked function (mk_server/mk_http_parser.c) of monkey commit f37e984 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sending a crafted POST request to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69516 | A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the /reporting/templates/preview/ endpoint of Amidaware Tactical RMM, affecting ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69516</link><description>A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the /reporting/templates/preview/ endpoint of Amidaware Tactical RMM, affecting versions equal to or earlier than v1.3.1, allows low-privileged users with Report Viewer or Report Manager permissions to achieve remote command execution on the server. This occurs due to improper sanitization of the template_md parameter, enabling direct injection of Jinja2 templates. This occurs due to misuse of the generate_html() function, the user-controlled value is inserted into `env.from_string`, a function that processes Jinja2 templates arbitrarily, making an SSTI possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69929 | An issue in N3uron Web User Interface v.1.21.7-240207.1047 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the password hashing on the c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69929</link><description>An issue in N3uron Web User Interface v.1.21.7-240207.1047 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the password hashing on the client side using the MD5 algorithm over a predictable string format</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25068 | alsa-lib 1.2.15.2 Topology Decoder Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25068</link><description>alsa-lib versions 1.2.2 up to and including 1.2.15.2, prior to commit 5f7fe33, contain a heap-based buffer overflow in the topology mixer control decoder. The tplg_decode_control_mixer1() function reads the num_channels field from untrusted .tplg data and uses it as a loop bound without validating it against the fixed-size channel array (SND_TPLG_MAX_CHAN). A crafted topology file with an excessive num_channels value can cause out-of-bounds heap writes, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1453 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in KiloView Encoder Series</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1453</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in KiloView Encoder Series could allow an unauthenticated attacker to create or delete administrator accounts. This vulnerability can grant the attacker full administrative control over the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1457 | Authenticated RCE Vulnerability Due to Buffer Overflow on TP-Link VIGI C385</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1457</link><description>An authenticated buffer handling flaw in TP-Link VIGI C385 V1 Web API lacking input sanitization, may allow memory corruption leading to remote code execution. Authenticated attackers may trigger buffer overflow and potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1610 | Tenda AX12 Pro V2 Telnet Service hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1610</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AX12 Pro V2 16.03.49.24_cn. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Telnet Service. Performing a manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1601 | Totolink A7000R cstecgi.cgi setUploadUserData command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1601</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Totolink A7000R 4.1cu.4154. The impacted element is the function setUploadUserData of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Executing a manipulation of the argument FileName can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13399 | Insecure Encryption in Communication with the Web Interface on TP-Link VX800v</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13399</link><description>A weakness in the web interface’s application layer encryption in VX800v v1.0 allows an adjacent attacker to brute force the weak AES key and decrypt intercepted traffic. Successful exploitation requires network proximity but no authentication, and may result in high impact to confidentiality, integrity, and availability of transmitted data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15541 | Access to System Files via SFTP on TP-Link VX800v</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15541</link><description>Improper link resolution in the VX800v v1.0 SFTP service allows authenticated adjacent attackers to use crafted symbolic links to access system files, resulting in high confidentiality impact and limited integrity risk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15542 | Denial of Service (DoS) of VoIP Communication on TP-Link VX800v</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15542</link><description>Improper handling of exceptional conditions in VX800v v1.0 in SIP processing allows an attacker to flood the device with crafted INVITE messages, blocking all voice lines and causing a denial of service on incoming calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15543 | Read-Only Root Access via USB Storage Device in TP-Link VX800v</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15543</link><description>Improper link resolution in USB HTTP access path in VX800v v1.0 allows a crafted USB device to expose root filesystem contents, giving an attacker with physical access read‑only access to system files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15548 | Missing Application-Layer Encryption in Web Interface Endpoints on TP-Link VX800v</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15548</link><description>Some VX800v v1.0 web interface endpoints transmit sensitive information over unencrypted HTTP due to missing application layer encryption, allowing a network adjacent attacker to intercept this traffic and compromise its confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69749 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in tale v.2.0.5 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69749</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in tale v.2.0.5 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1600 | Bdtask Bhojon All-In-One Restaurant Management System Add-to-Cart Submission Endpoint addtocart logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1600</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Bdtask Bhojon All-In-One Restaurant Management System up to 20260116. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /hungry/addtocart of the component Add-to-Cart Submission Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument price/allprice leads to business logic errors. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1599 | Bdtask Bhojon All-In-One Restaurant Management System Checkout placeorder logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1599</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Bdtask Bhojon All-In-One Restaurant Management System up to 20260116. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /hungry/placeorder of the component Checkout. Executing a manipulation of the argument orggrandTotal/vat/service_charge/grandtotal can lead to business logic errors. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24414 | Icinga for Windows certificate can have too-open permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24414</link><description>The Icinga PowerShell Framework provides configuration and check possibilities to ensure integration and monitoring of Windows environments. In versions prior to 1.13.4, 1.12.4, and 1.11.2, permissions of the Icinga for Windows `certificate` directory grant every user read access, which results in the exposure of private key of the Icinga certificate for the given host. All installations are affected. Versions 1.13.4, 1.12.4, and 1.11.2 contains a patch. Please note that upgrading to a fixed version of Icinga for Windows will also automatically fix a similar issue present in Icinga 2, CVE-2026-24413. As a workaround, the permissions can be restricted manually by updating the ACL for the given folder `C:\Program Files\WindowsPowerShell\modules\icinga-powershell-framework\certificate` (and `C:\ProgramData\icinga2\var` to fix the issue for the Icinga 2 agent as well) including every sub-folder and item to restrict access for general users, only allowing the Icinga service user and administrators access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24780 | AutoGPT is Vulnerable to RCE via Disabled Block Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24780</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents that automate complex workflows. Prior to autogpt-platform-beta-v0.6.44, AutoGPT Platform's block execution endpoints (both main web API and external API) allow executing blocks by UUID without checking the `disabled` flag. Any authenticated user can execute the disabled `BlockInstallationBlock`, which writes arbitrary Python code to the server filesystem and executes it via `__import__()`, achieving Remote Code Execution. In default self-hosted deployments where Supabase signup is enabled, an attacker can self-register; if signup is disabled (e.g., hosted), the attacker needs an existing account. autogpt-platform-beta-v0.6.44 contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15545 | Insufficient Backup File Upload Input Validation on TP-Link Archer RE605X</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15545</link><description>The backup restore function does not properly validate unexpected or unrecognized tags within the backup file. When such a crafted file is restored, the injected tag is interpreted by a shell, allowing execution of arbitrary commands with root privileges. Successful exploitation allows the attacker to gain root-level command execution, compromising confidentiality, integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24054 | Kata Containers Runtime: Host block device can be hotplugged to the VM if the container image is malformed or contains no layers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24054</link><description>Kata Containers is an open source project focusing on a standard implementation of lightweight Virtual Machines (VMs) that perform like containers. In versions prior to 3.26.0, when a container image is malformed or contains no layers, containerd falls back to bind-mounting an empty snapshotter directory for the container rootfs. When the Kata runtime attempts to mount the container rootfs, the bind mount causes the rootfs to be detected as a block device, leading to the underlying device being hotplugged to the guest. This can cause filesystem-level errors on the host due to double inode allocation, and may lead to the host's block device being mounted as read-only. Version 3.26.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24413 | Icinga has insecure permission of %ProgramData%\icinga2\var on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24413</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. Starting in version 2.3.0 and prior to versions 2.13.14, 2.14.8, and 2.15.2, the Icinga 2 MSI did not set appropriate permissions for the `%ProgramData%\icinga2\var` folder on Windows. This resulted in the its contents - including the private key of the user and synced configuration - being readable by all local users. All installations on Windows are affected. Versions 2.13.14, 2.14.8, and 2.15.2 contains a fix. There are two possibilities to work around the issue without upgrading Icinga 2. Upgrade Icinga for Windows to at least version v1.13.4, v1.12.4, or v1.11.2. These version will automatically fix the ACLs for the Icinga 2 agent as well. Alternatively, manually update the ACL for the given folder `C:\ProgramData\icinga2\var` (and `C:\Program Files\WindowsPowerShell\modules\icinga-powershell-framework\certificate` to fix the issue for the Icinga for Windows as well) including every sub-folder and item to restrict access for general users, only allowing the Icinga service user and administrators access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45160 | A HTML injection vulnerability exists in the file upload functionality of Cacti &lt;= 1.2.29. When a file with an invalid format is uploaded, t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45160</link><description>A HTML injection vulnerability exists in the file upload functionality of Cacti &lt;= 1.2.29. When a file with an invalid format is uploaded, the application reflects the submitted filename back into an error popup without proper sanitization. As a result, attackers can inject arbitrary HTML elements (e.g., &lt;h1&gt;, &lt;b&gt;, &lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;) into the rendered page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1598 | Bdtask Bhojon All-In-One Restaurant Management System User Information profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1598</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Bhojon All-In-One Restaurant Management System up to 20260116. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/home/profile of the component User Information Module. Performing a manipulation of the argument fullname results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23896 | immich API Key Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23896</link><description>immich is a high performance self-hosted photo and video management solution. Prior to version 2.5.0, API keys can escalate their own permissions by calling the update endpoint, allowing a low-privilege API key to grant itself full administrative access to the system. Version 2.5.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1597 | Bdtask SalesERP Administrative Endpoint improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1597</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask SalesERP up to 20260116. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Administrative Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument ci_session leads to improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62514 | `libparsec_crypto` does not check for weak order point of curve 25519</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62514</link><description>Parsec is a cloud-based application for cryptographically secure file sharing. In versions on the 3.x branch prior to 3.6.0, `libparsec_crypto`, a component of the Parsec application, does not check for weak order point of Curve25519 when compiled with its RustCrypto backend. In practice this means an attacker in a man-in-the-middle position would be able to provide weak order points to both parties in the Diffie-Hellman exchange, resulting in a high probability to for both parties to obtain the same shared key (hence leading to a successful SAS code exchange, misleading both parties into thinking no MITM has occurred) which is also known by the attacker. Note only Parsec web is impacted (as Parsec desktop uses `libparsec_crypto` with the libsodium backend). Version 3.6.0 of Parsec patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0936 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Logfile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0936</link><description>An Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in B&amp;amp;R PVI client versions prior to 6.5 may be abused by an authenticated local attacker to gather credential information which is processed by the PVI client application. The logging function of the PVI client application is disabled by default and must be explicitly enabled by the user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1595 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_student_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1595</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit_student_query.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1596 | D-Link DWR-M961 formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel sub_419920 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1596</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M961 1.1.47. This vulnerability affects the function sub_419920 of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel. This manipulation of the argument fota_url causes command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13905 | CWE-276: Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability exists that could cause  privilege escalation through the reverse shell when  one or mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13905</link><description>CWE-276: Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability exists that could cause  privilege escalation through the reverse shell when  one or more executable service binaries are modified in the installation folder by a local user with normal privilege upon service restart.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71011 | An input validation vulnerability in the flow.Tensor.new_empty/flow.Tensor.new_ones/flow.Tensor.new_zeros component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71011</link><description>An input validation vulnerability in the flow.Tensor.new_empty/flow.Tensor.new_ones/flow.Tensor.new_zeros component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71008 | A segmentation violation in the oneflow._oneflow_internal.autograd.Function.FunctionCtx.mark_non_differentiable component of OneFlow v0.9.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71008</link><description>A segmentation violation in the oneflow._oneflow_internal.autograd.Function.FunctionCtx.mark_non_differentiable component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71009 | An input validation vulnerability in the flow.scatter/flow.scatter_add component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71009</link><description>An input validation vulnerability in the flow.scatter/flow.scatter_add component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted indices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7714 | Time Based SQLi in Global Medya&amp;#x27;s PHP CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7714</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Global Interactive Design Media Software Inc. Content Management System (CMS) allows Command Line Execution through SQL Injection.This issue affects Content Management System (CMS): through 21072025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36994 | QlikView 12.50.20000.0 - &amp;#x27;FTP Server Address&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36994</link><description>QlikView 12.50.20000.0 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the FTP server address input field that allows local attackers to crash the application. Attackers can paste a 300-character buffer into the FTP server address field to trigger an application crash and prevent normal functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36995 | Mocha Telnet Lite for iOS 4.2 - &amp;#x27;User&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36995</link><description>Mocha Telnet Lite for iOS 4.2 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by manipulating the user configuration input. Attackers can overwrite the 'User' field with 350 bytes of repeated characters to trigger an application crash and prevent normal functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36997 | BacklinkSpeed 2.4 - Buffer Overflow PoC (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36997</link><description>BacklinkSpeed 2.4 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to corrupt the Structured Exception Handler (SEH) chain through malicious file import. Attackers can craft a specially designed payload file to overwrite SEH addresses, potentially executing arbitrary code and gaining control of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36999 | elaniin CMS 1.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36999</link><description>Elaniin CMS 1.0 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows attackers to access the dashboard by manipulating the login page with SQL injection. Attackers can bypass authentication by sending crafted email and password parameters with '=''or' payload to login.php, granting unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37000 | Free MP3 CD Ripper 2.8 - Stack Buffer Overflow (SEH + Egghunter)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37000</link><description>Free MP3 CD Ripper 2.8 contains a stack buffer overflow vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by crafting a malicious WAV file with oversized payload. Attackers can leverage a specially crafted exploit file with shellcode, SEH bypass, and egghunter technique to achieve remote code execution on vulnerable Windows systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37001 | Frigate Professional 3.36.0.9 - &amp;#x27;Pack File&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow (SEH Egghunter)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37001</link><description>Frigate Professional 3.36.0.9 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the Pack File feature that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overflowing the 'Archive To' input field. Attackers can craft a malicious payload that overwrites the Structured Exception Handler (SEH) and uses an egghunter technique to execute a reverse shell payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37002 | Ajenti 2.1.36 - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37002</link><description>Ajenti 2.1.36 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands after successful login. Attackers can leverage the /api/terminal/create endpoint to send a netcat reverse shell payload targeting a specified IP and port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37004 | Ultimate Project Manager CRM PRO 2.0.5 - SQLi Credentials Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37004</link><description>Ultimate Project Manager CRM PRO 2.0.5 contains a blind SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to extract usernames and password hashes from the tbl_users database table. Attackers can exploit the /frontend/get_article_suggestion/ endpoint by crafting malicious search parameters to progressively guess and retrieve user credentials through boolean-based inference techniques.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37005 | TimeClock Software 1.01 Authenticated Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37005</link><description>TimeClock Software 1.01 contains an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to enumerate valid usernames by manipulating the 'notes' parameter. Attackers can inject conditional time delays in the add_entry.php endpoint to determine user existence by measuring response time differences.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37006 | berliCRM 1.0.24 - &amp;#x27;src_record&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37006</link><description>berliCRM 1.0.24 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the 'src_record' parameter that allows remote attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code through a crafted POST request to the index.php endpoint to potentially extract or modify database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37007 | Liman 0.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (Change Password)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37007</link><description>Liman 0.7 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate user account settings without proper request validation. Attackers can craft malicious HTML forms to change user passwords or modify account information by tricking logged-in users into submitting unauthorized requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37008 | EasyPMS 1.0.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37008</link><description>EasyPMS 1.0.0 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unprivileged users to manipulate SQL queries in JSON requests to access admin user information. Attackers can exploit weak input validation by injecting single quotes in ID parameters and modify admin user passwords without proper token authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37009 | MedDream PACS Server 6.8.3.751 - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37009</link><description>MedDream PACS Server 6.8.3.751 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows authorized users to upload malicious PHP files. Attackers can exploit the uploadImage.php endpoint by authenticating and uploading a PHP shell to execute arbitrary system commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37010 | BearShare Lite 5.2.5 - &amp;#x27;Advanced Search&amp;#x27;Buffer Overflow in (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37010</link><description>BearShare Lite 5.2.5 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the Advanced Search keywords input that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can craft a specially designed payload to overwrite the EIP register and execute shellcode by pasting malicious content into the search keywords field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37011 | Gnome Fonts Viewer 3.34.0 Heap Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37011</link><description>Gnome Fonts Viewer 3.34.0 contains a heap corruption vulnerability that allows attackers to trigger an out-of-bounds write by crafting a malicious TTF font file. Attackers can generate a specially crafted TTF file with an oversized pattern to cause an infinite malloc() loop and potentially crash the gnome-font-viewer process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37012 | Tea LaTex 1.0 - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37012</link><description>Tea LaTex 1.0 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shell commands through the /api.php endpoint. Attackers can craft a malicious LaTeX payload with shell commands that are executed when processed by the application's tex2png API action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37013 | Audio Playback Recorder 3.2.2 - Local Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37013</link><description>Audio Playback Recorder 3.2.2 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the eject and registration parameters that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can craft malicious payloads and overwrite Structured Exception Handler (SEH) to execute shellcode when pasting specially crafted input into the application's input fields.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37015 | Ruijie Networks Switch eWeb S29_RGOS 11.4 - Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37015</link><description>Ruijie Networks Switch eWeb S29_RGOS 11.4 contains a directory traversal vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive configuration files by manipulating file path parameters. Attackers can exploit the /download.do endpoint with '../' sequences to retrieve system configuration files containing credentials and network settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37016 | BarcodeOCR 19.3.6 - &amp;#x27;BarcodeOCR&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37016</link><description>BarcodeOCR 19.3.6 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges during system startup. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious executables that will run with LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37017 | CodeMeter 6.60 - &amp;#x27;CodeMeter.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37017</link><description>CodeMeter 6.60 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path in the CodeMeter Runtime Server service to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37018 | GOautodial 4.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37018</link><description>GOautodial 4.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated agents to inject malicious scripts through message subjects. Attackers can craft messages with embedded JavaScript that will execute when an administrator reads the message, potentially stealing session cookies or executing client-side attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37020 | SonarQube 8.3.1 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37020</link><description>SonarQube 8.3.1 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to gain SYSTEM privileges by exploiting the service executable path. Attackers can replace the wrapper.exe in the service path with a malicious executable to execute code with highest system privileges during service restart.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37021 | Bandwidth Monitor 3.9 - &amp;#x27;Svc10StrikeBandMontitor&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37021</link><description>10-Strike Bandwidth Monitor 3.9 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in multiple services that allows local attackers to escalate privileges. Attackers can place a malicious executable in specific file path locations to achieve privilege escalation to SYSTEM during service startup.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7713 | Reflected XSS in Global Medya&amp;#x27;s PHP CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7713</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Global Interactive Design Media Software Inc. Content Management System (CMS) allows XSS Through HTTP Headers.This issue affects Content Management System (CMS): through 21072025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1593 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_expenses_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1593</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_expenses_query.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument detail can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1594 | itsourcecode Society Management System add_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1594</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_expenses.php. The manipulation of the argument detail leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1589 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1589</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/inquiry/index.php. This manipulation of the argument txtsearch causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1590 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1590</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/faculty/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7013 | IDOR in QRMenumPro&amp;#x27;s Menu Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7013</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in QR Menu Pro Smart Menu Systems Menu Panel allows Exploitation of Trusted Identifiers.This issue affects Menu Panel: through 29012026. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7014 | Session Hijacking in QRMenumPro&amp;#x27;s Menu Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7014</link><description>Session Fixation vulnerability in QR Menu Pro Smart Menu Systems Menu Panel allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects Menu Panel: through 29012026. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1616 | osim: Path Traversal via query parameters in Nginx configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1616</link><description>The $uri$args concatenation in nginx configuration file present in Open Security Issue Management (OSIM) prior v2025.9.0 allows path traversal attacks via query parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1588 | jishenghua jshERP installByPath install path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1588</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jishenghua jshERP up to 3.6. The impacted element is the function install of the file /jshERP-boot/plugin/installByPath of the component com.gitee.starblues.integration.operator.DefaultPluginOperator. The manipulation of the argument path results in path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1586 | Open5GS SGWC s11-handler.c ogs_gtp2_f_teid_to_ip denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1586</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. Impacted is the function ogs_gtp2_f_teid_to_ip of the file /sgwc/s11-handler.c of the component SGWC. Executing a manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1587 | Open5GS SGWC s11-handler.c sgwc_s11_handle_modify_bearer_request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1587</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. The affected element is the function sgwc_s11_handle_modify_bearer_request of the file /sgwc/s11-handler.c of the component SGWC. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7016 | Improper Access Control in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7016</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Akın Software Computer Import Export Industry and Trade Ltd. QR Menu allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects QR Menu: before s1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7015 | Session Hijacking in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7015</link><description>Session Fixation vulnerability in Akın Software Computer Import Export Industry and Trade Ltd. QR Menu allows Session Fixation.This issue affects QR Menu: before s1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1469 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in RLE NOVA&amp;#x27;s PlanManager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1469</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in RLE NOVA's PlanManager. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by injecting malicious payload through the ‘comment’ and ‘brand’ parameters in ‘/index.php’. The payload is stored by the application and subsequently displayed without proper sanitization when other users access it. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22764 | Dell OpenManage Network Integration, versions prior to 3.9, contains an Improper Authentication vulnerability. A low privileged attacker wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22764</link><description>Dell OpenManage Network Integration, versions prior to 3.9, contains an Improper Authentication vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:07:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23563 | Privilege escalation in TeamViewer DEX via DeleteFileByPath instruction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23563</link><description>Improper Link Resolution Before File Access (invoked by 1E‑Explorer‑TachyonCore‑DeleteFileByPath instruction) in TeamViewer DEX - 1E Client before version 26.1 on Windows allows a low‑privileged local attacker to delete protected system files via a crafted RPC control junction or symlink that is followed when the delete instruction executes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23564 | Transmission of Unencrypted Data in Content Distribution Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23564</link><description>A vulnerability in TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows an attacker on the adjacent network to cause normally encrypted UDP traffic to be sent in cleartext. This can result in disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23565 | Denial-of-Service in Content Distribution Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23565</link><description>A vulnerability in TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows an attacker on the adjacent network to cause the NomadBranch.exe process to terminate via crafted requests. This can result in a denial-of-service condition of the Content Distribution Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23566 | Log Injection in Content Distribution Service UDP Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23566</link><description>A vulnerability in TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows an attacker on the adjacent network to inject, tamper with, or forge log entries in \Nomad Branch.log via crafted data sent to the UDP network handler. This can impact log integrity and nonrepudiation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23567 | Integer underflow in Content Distribution Service UDP handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23567</link><description>An integer underflow in the UDP command handler of the TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows an adjacent network attacker to trigger a heap-based buffer overflow and cause a denial-of-service (service crash) via specially crafted UDP packets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23568 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Content Distribution Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23568</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows an attacker on the adjacent network to cause information disclosure or denial-of-service via a special crafted packet. The leaked memory could be used to bypass ASLR and facilitate further exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23569 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Content Distribution Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23569</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows a remote attacker to leak stack memory and cause a denial of service via a crafted request. The leaked stack memory could be used to bypass ASLR remotely and facilitate exploitation of other vulnerabilities on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23570 | Log timestamp tampering vulnerability in Content Distribution Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23570</link><description>A missing validation of a user-controlled value in the TeamViewer DEX Client (former 1E Client) - Content Distribution Service (NomadBranch.exe) prior version 26.1 for Windows allows an adjacent network attacker to tamper with log timestamps via crafted UDP Sync command. This could result in forged or nonsensical datetime prefixes and compromising log integrity and forensic correlation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23571 | Command Injection in 1E-Nomad-RunPkgStatusRequest Instruction in TeamViewer DEX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23571</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was discovered in TeamViewer DEX (former 1E DEX), specifically within the 1E-Nomad-RunPkgStatusRequest instruction. Improper input validation allows authenticated attackers with actioner privilege to run elevated arbitrary commands on connected hosts via malicious commands injected into the instruction’s input field. Users of 1E Client version 24.5 or higher are not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1188 | In the Eclipse OMR port library component since release 0.2.0, an API function to return the textual names of all supported processor featur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1188</link><description>In the Eclipse OMR port library component since release 0.2.0, an API function to return the textual names of all supported processor features was not accounting for the separator inserted between processor features. If the output buffer supplied to this function was incorrectly sized, failing to account for the separator when determining when a write to the buffer was safe could lead to a buffer overflow. This issue is fixed in Eclipse OMR version 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14975 | Custom Login Page Customizer &amp;lt; 2.5.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14975</link><description>The Custom Login Page Customizer WordPress plugin before 2.5.4 does not have a proper password reset process, allowing a few unauthenticated requests to reset the password of any user by knowing their username, such as administrator ones, and therefore gain access to their account</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 07:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25067 | SmarterTools SmarterMail &amp;lt; Build 9518 Unauthenticated background-of-the-day Path Coercion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25067</link><description>SmarterTools SmarterMail versions prior to build 9518  contain an unauthenticated path coercion vulnerability in the background-of-the-day preview endpoint. The application base64-decodes attacker-supplied input and uses it as a filesystem path without validation. On Windows systems, this allows UNC paths to be resolved, causing the SmarterMail service to initiate outbound SMB authentication attempts to attacker-controlled hosts. This can be abused for credential coercion, NTLM relay attacks, and unauthorized network authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53869 | Multiple MFPs provided by Brother Industries, Ltd. does not properly validate server certificates, which may allow a man-in-the-middle attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53869</link><description>Multiple MFPs provided by Brother Industries, Ltd. does not properly validate server certificates, which may allow a man-in-the-middle attacker to replace the set of root certificates used by the product with a set of arbitrary certificates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55704 | Hidden functionality issue exists in multiple MFPs provided by Brother Industries, Ltd., which may allow an attacker to obtain the logs of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55704</link><description>Hidden functionality issue exists in multiple MFPs provided by Brother Industries, Ltd., which may allow an attacker to obtain the logs of the affected product and obtain sensitive information within the logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1552 | SEMCMS SEMCMS_Info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1552</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SEMCMS 5.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /SEMCMS_Info.php. The manipulation of the argument searchml leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 02:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15344 | Tanium addressed a SQL injection vulnerability in Asset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15344</link><description>Tanium addressed a SQL injection vulnerability in Asset.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1551 | itsourcecode School Management System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1551</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ramonsys/course/controller.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1549 | jishenghua jshERP PluginController uploadPluginConfigFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1549</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in jishenghua jshERP up to 3.6. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /jshERP-boot/plugin/uploadPluginConfigFile of the component PluginController. Such manipulation of the argument configFile leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1550 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System Admin Dashboard adminviews.py improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1550</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /hms/hospital/docappsystem/adminviews.py of the component Admin Dashboard Page. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1548 | Totolink A7000R cstecgi.cgi CloudACMunualUpdateUserdata command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1548</link><description>A flaw has been found in Totolink A7000R 4.1cu.4154. This impacts the function CloudACMunualUpdateUserdata of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. This manipulation of the argument url causes command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24897 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24897</link><description>Erugo is a self-hosted file-sharing platform. In versions up to and including 0.2.14, an authenticated low-privileged user can upload arbitrary files to any specified location due to insufficient validation of user‑supplied paths when creating shares.
By specifying a writable path within the public web root, an attacker can upload and execute arbitrary code on the server, resulting in remote code execution (RCE). This vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to fully compromise the affected Erugo instance. Version 0.2.15 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1546 | jishenghua jshERP com.jsh.erp.datasource.mappers.DepotItemMapperEx importItemExcel getBillItemByParam sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1546</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in jishenghua jshERP up to 3.6. The impacted element is the function getBillItemByParam of the file /jshERP-boot/depotItem/importItemExcel of the component com.jsh.erp.datasource.mappers.DepotItemMapperEx. The manipulation of the argument barCodes leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1547 | Totolink A7000R cstecgi.cgi setUnloadUserData command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1547</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Totolink A7000R 4.1cu.4154. This affects the function setUnloadUserData of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument plugin_name results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24889 | soroban-sdk has overflow in Bytes::slice, Vec::slice, GenRange::gen_range for u64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24889</link><description>soroban-sdk is a Rust SDK for Soroban contracts. Arithmetic overflow can be triggered in the `Bytes::slice`, `Vec::slice`, and `Prng::gen_range` (for `u64`) methods in the `soroban-sdk` in versions up to and including `25.0.1`, `23.5.1`, and `25.0.2`. Contracts that pass user-controlled or computed range bounds to `Bytes::slice`, `Vec::slice`, or `Prng::gen_range` may silently operate on incorrect data ranges or generate random numbers from an unintended range, potentially resulting in corrupted contract state. Note that the best practice when using the `soroban-sdk` and building Soroban contracts is to always enable `overflow-checks = true`. The `stellar contract init` tool that prepares the boiler plate for a Soroban contract, as well as all examples and docs, encourage the use of configuring `overflow-checks = true` on `release` profiles so that these arithmetic operations fail rather than silently wrap. Contracts are only impacted if they use `overflow-checks = false` either explicitly or implicitly. It is anticipated the majority of contracts could not be impacted because the best practice encouraged by tooling is to enable `overflow-checks`. The fix available in `25.0.1`, `23.5.1`, and `25.0.2` replaces bare arithmetic with `checked_add` / `checked_sub`, ensuring overflow traps regardless of the `overflow-checks` profile setting. As a workaround, contract workspaces can be configured with a profile available in the GitHub Securtity Advisory to enable overflow checks on the arithmetic operations. This is the best practice when developing Soroban contracts, and the default if using the contract boilerplate generated using `stellar contract init`. Alternatively, contracts can validate range bounds before passing them to `slice` or `gen_range` to ensure the conversions cannot overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1544 | D-Link DIR-823X set_mode sub_41E2A0 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1544</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Impacted is the function sub_41E2A0 of the file /goform/set_mode. Performing a manipulation of the argument lan_gateway results in os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1545 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1545</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /course/index.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24857 | bulk_extractor has Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24857</link><description>`bulk_extractor` is a digital forensics exploitation tool. Starting in version 1.4, `bulk_extractor`’s embedded unrar code has a heap‑buffer‑overflow in the RAR PPM LZ decoding path. A crafted RAR inside a disk image causes an out‑of‑bounds write in `Unpack::CopyString`, leading to a crash under ASAN (and likely a crash or memory corruption in production builds). There's potential for using this for RCE. As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24888 | Maker.js Vulnerable to Unsafe Property Copying in makerjs.extendObject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24888</link><description>Maker.js is a 2D vector line drawing and shape modeling for CNC and laser cutters. In versions up to and including 0.19.1, the `makerjs.extendObject` function copies properties from source objects without proper validation, potentially exposing applications to security risks. The function lacks `hasOwnProperty()` checks and does not filter dangerous keys, allowing inherited properties and potentially malicious properties to be copied to target objects. A patch is available in commit 85e0f12bd868974b891601a141974f929dec36b8, which is expected to be part of version 0.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71007 | An input validation vulnerability in the oneflow.index_add component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71007</link><description>An input validation vulnerability in the oneflow.index_add component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1534 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminEditUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1534</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminEditUser.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1535 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminReply.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1535</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminReply.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24856 | iccDEV has UB runtime error in &amp;lt;icTagTypeSignature&amp;gt;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24856</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have an undefined behavior issue when floating-point NaN values are converted to unsigned short integer types during ICC profile XML parsing potentially corrupting memory structures and enabling arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. ICC Profile Injection vulnerabilities arise when user-controllable input is incorporated into ICC profile data or other structured binary blobs in an unsafe manner. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a fix for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71006 | A floating point exception (FPE) in the oneflow.reshape component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71006</link><description>A floating point exception (FPE) in the oneflow.reshape component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1532 | D-Link DCS-700L Music File Upload Service setUploadMusic uploadmusic path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1532</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DCS-700L 1.03.09. The affected element is the function uploadmusic of the file /setUploadMusic of the component Music File Upload Service. The manipulation of the argument UploadMusic leads to path traversal. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1533 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminAddCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1533</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddCategory.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24767 | NocoDB has Blind SSRF via Unvalidated HEAD Request in uploadViaURL Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24767</link><description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Prior to version 0.301.0, a blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the `uploadViaURL` functionality due to an unprotected `HEAD` request. While the subsequent file retrieval logic correctly enforces SSRF protections, the initial metadata request executes without validation. This allows limited outbound requests to arbitrary URLs before SSRF controls are applied. Version 0.301.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24768 | NocoDB has Unvalidated Redirect in Login Flow via continueAfterSignIn Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24768</link><description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Prior to version 0.301.0, an unvalidated redirect (open redirect) vulnerability exists in NocoDB’s login flow due to missing validation of the `continueAfterSignIn` parameter. During authentication, NocoDB processes a user-controlled redirect value and conditionally performs client-side navigation without enforcing any restrictions on the destination’s origin, domain or protocol. This allows attackers to redirect authenticated users to arbitrary external websites after login. This vulnerability enables phishing attacks by leveraging user trust in the legitimate NocoDB login flow. While it does not directly expose credentials or bypass authentication, it increases the likelihood of credential theft through social engineering. The issue does not allow arbitrary code execution or privilege escalation, but it undermines authentication integrity. Version 0.301.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24769 | NocoDB Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24769</link><description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Prior to version 0.301.0, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in NocoDB’s attachment handling mechanism. Authenticated users can upload malicious SVG files containing embedded JavaScript, which are later rendered inline and executed in the browsers of other users who view the attachment. Because the malicious payload is stored server-side and executed under the application’s origin, successful exploitation can lead to account compromise, data exfiltration and unauthorized actions performed on behalf of affected users. Version 0.301.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24835 | Podman Desktop Extension System Vulnerable to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24835</link><description>Podman Desktop is a graphical tool for developing on containers and Kubernetes. A critical authentication bypass vulnerability in Podman Desktop prior to version 1.25.1 allows any extension to completely circumvent permission checks and gain unauthorized access to all authentication sessions. The `isAccessAllowed()` function unconditionally returns `true`, enabling malicious extensions to impersonate any user, hijack authentication sessions, and access sensitive resources without authorization. This vulnerability affects all versions of Podman Desktop. Version 1.25.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71003 | An input validation vulnerability in the flow.arange() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71003</link><description>An input validation vulnerability in the flow.arange() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71005 | A floating point exception (FPE) in the oneflow.view component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71005</link><description>A floating point exception (FPE) in the oneflow.view component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24739 | Symfony has incorrect argument escaping under MSYS2/Git Bash on Windows that can lead to destructive file operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24739</link><description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Prior to versions 5.4.51, 6.4.33, 7.3.11, 7.4.5, and 8.0.5, the Symfony Process component did not correctly treat some characters (notably `=`) as “special” when escaping arguments on Windows. When PHP is executed from an MSYS2-based environment (e.g. Git Bash) and Symfony Process spawns native Windows executables, MSYS2’s argument/path conversion can mis-handle unquoted arguments containing these characters. This can cause the spawned process to receive corrupted/truncated arguments compared to what Symfony intended. If an application (or tooling such as Composer scripts) uses Symfony Process to invoke file-management commands (e.g. `rmdir`, `del`, etc.) with a path argument containing `=`, the MSYS2 conversion layer may alter the argument at runtime. In affected setups this can result in operations being performed on an unintended path, up to and including deletion of the contents of a broader directory or drive. The issue is particularly relevant when untrusted input can influence process arguments (directly or indirectly, e.g. via repository paths, extracted archive paths, temporary directories, or user-controlled configuration). Versions 5.4.51, 6.4.33, 7.3.11, 7.4.5, and 8.0.5 contains a patch for the issue. Some workarounds are available. Avoid running PHP/one's own tooling from MSYS2-based shells on Windows; prefer cmd.exe or PowerShell for workflows that spawn native executables. Avoid passing paths containing `=` (and similar MSYS2-sensitive characters) to Symfony Process when operating under Git Bash/MSYS2. Where applicable, configure MSYS2 to disable or restrict argument conversion (e.g. via `MSYS2_ARG_CONV_EXCL`), understanding this may affect other tooling behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24766 | NocoDB Vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in Connection Test Endpoint, Leading to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24766</link><description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Prior to version 0.301.0, an authenticated user with org-level-creator permissions can exploit prototype pollution in the `/api/v2/meta/connection/test` endpoint, causing all database write operations to fail application-wide until server restart. While the pollution technically bypasses SUPER_ADMIN authorization checks, no practical privileged actions can be performed because database operations fail immediately after pollution. Version 0.301.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71004 | A segmentation violation in the oneflow.logical_or component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71004</link><description>A segmentation violation in the oneflow.logical_or component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23743 | Discourse allows permalinks to restricted resources to leak resource slugs to unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23743</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, permalinks pointing to access-restricted resources (private topics, categories, posts, or hidden tags) were redirecting users to URLs containing the resource slug, even when the user didn't have access to view the resource. This leaked potentially sensitive information (e.g., private topic titles) via the redirect Location header and the 404 page's search box. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24742 | Discourse staff action logs expose sensitive information to moderators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24742</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, non-admin moderators can view sensitive information in staff action logs that should be restricted to administrators only. The exposed information includes webhook payload URLs and secrets, API key details, site setting changes, private message content, restricted category names and structures, and private chat channel titles. This allows moderators to bypass intended access controls and extract confidential data by monitoring the staff action logs. With leaked webhook secrets, an attacker could potentially spoof webhook events to integrated services. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. As a workaround, site administrators should review and limit moderator appointments to fully trusted users. There is no configuration-based workaround to prevent this access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37525 | HCL BigFix Compliance is vulnerable to a sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37525</link><description>A sensitive information disclosure in HCL BigFix Compliance allows a remote attacker to access files under the WEB-INF directory, which may contain Java class files and configuration information, leading to unauthorized access to application internals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13979 | Mini site - Moderately critical - Cross-Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-117</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13979</link><description>Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions vulnerability in Drupal Mini site allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mini site: from 0.0.0 before 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13980 | CKEditor 5 Premium Features - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-118</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13980</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal CKEditor 5 Premium Features allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects CKEditor 5 Premium Features: from 0.0.0 before 1.2.10, from 1.3.0 before 1.3.6, from 1.4.0 before 1.4.3, from 1.5.0 before 1.5.1, from 1.6.0 before 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13981 | AI (Artificial Intelligence) - Moderately critical - Cross-Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-119</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13981</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ("Cross-site Scripting") vulnerability in Drupal AI (Artificial Intelligence) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects AI (Artificial Intelligence): from 0.0.0 before 1.0.7, from 1.1.0 before 1.1.7, from 1.2.0 before 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13982 | Login Time Restriction - Moderately critical - Cross-Site Request Forgery - SA-CONTRIB-2025-120</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13982</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Drupal Login Time Restriction allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Login Time Restriction: from 0.0.0 before 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13983 | Tagify - Moderately critical - Cross-site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-121</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13983</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ("Cross-site Scripting") vulnerability in Drupal Tagify allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Tagify: from 0.0.0 before 1.2.44.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13984 | Next.js - Critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-122</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13984</link><description>Permissive Cross-domain Security Policy with Untrusted Domains vulnerability in Drupal Next.Js allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Next.Js: from 0.0.0 before 1.6.4, from 2.0.0 before 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13985 | Entity Share - Moderately critical - Access bypass, Information Disclosure - SA-CONTRIB-2025-123</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13985</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Drupal Entity Share allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Entity Share: from 0.0.0 before 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13986 | Disable Login Page - Critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-124</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13986</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal Disable Login Page allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Disable Login Page: from 0.0.0 before 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14472 | Acquia Content Hub - Moderately critical - Cross-Site Request Forgery - SA-CONTRIB-2025-125</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14472</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Drupal Acquia Content Hub allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Acquia Content Hub: from 0.0.0 before 3.6.4, from 3.7.0 before 3.7.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14840 | HTTP Client Manager - Less critical - Information disclosure - SA-CONTRIB-2025-126</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14840</link><description>Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Drupal HTTP Client Manager allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects HTTP Client Manager: from 0.0.0 before 9.3.13, from 10.0.0 before 10.0.2, from 11.0.0 before 11.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21865 | Discourse topic conversion permission vulnerability for moderators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21865</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, moderators can convert some personal messages to public topics when they shouldn't have access. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. As a workaround, site admin can temporarily revoke the moderation role from untrusted moderators or remove the moderator group from the "personal message enabled groups" site setting until the Discourse instance has been upgraded to a version that has been patched.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46691 | Dell PremierColor Panel Driver, versions prior to 1.0.0.1 A01, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A low privileged attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46691</link><description>Dell PremierColor Panel Driver, versions prior to 1.0.0.1 A01, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69289 | DIscourse has insecure default configuration that allows non-admin moderators to takeover any non-staff account via email change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69289</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. A privilege escalation vulnerability in versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0 allows a non-admin moderator to bypass email-change restrictions, allowing a takeover of non-staff accounts. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. As a workaround, ensure moderators are trusted or enable the "require_change_email_confirmation" setting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61726 | Memory exhaustion in query parameter parsing in net/url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61726</link><description>The net/url package does not set a limit on the number of query parameters in a query. While the maximum size of query parameters in URLs is generally limited by the maximum request header size, the net/http.Request.ParseForm method can parse large URL-encoded forms. Parsing a large form containing many unique query parameters can cause excessive memory consumption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61728 | Excessive CPU consumption when building archive index in archive/zip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61728</link><description>archive/zip uses a super-linear file name indexing algorithm that is invoked the first time a file in an archive is opened. This can lead to a denial of service when consuming a maliciously constructed ZIP archive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61730 | Handshake messages may be processed at the incorrect encryption level in crypto/tls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61730</link><description>During the TLS 1.3 handshake if multiple messages are sent in records that span encryption level boundaries (for instance the Client Hello and Encrypted Extensions messages), the subsequent messages may be processed before the encryption level changes. This can cause some minor information disclosure if a network-local attacker can inject messages during the handshake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61731 | Arbitrary file write using cgo pkg-config directive in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61731</link><description>Building a malicious file with cmd/go can cause can cause a write to an attacker-controlled file with partial control of the file content. The "#cgo pkg-config:" directive in a Go source file provides command-line arguments to provide to the Go pkg-config command. An attacker can provide a "--log-file" argument to this directive, causing pkg-config to write to an attacker-controlled location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68119 | Unexpected code execution when invoking toolchain in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68119</link><description>Downloading and building modules with malicious version strings can cause local code execution. On systems with Mercurial (hg) installed, downloading modules from non-standard sources (e.g., custom domains) can cause unexpected code execution due to how external VCS commands are constructed. This issue can also be triggered by providing a malicious version string to the toolchain. On systems with Git installed, downloading and building modules with malicious version strings can allow an attacker to write to arbitrary files on the filesystem. This can only be triggered by explicitly providing the malicious version strings to the toolchain and does not affect usage of @latest or bare module paths.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68933 | Discourse non-admin moderators can exfiltrate private content via post ownership transfer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68933</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, non-admin moderators with the `moderators_change_post_ownership` setting enabled can change ownership of posts in private messages and restricted categories they cannot access, then export their data to view the content. This is a broken access control vulnerability affecting sites that grant moderators post ownership transfer permissions. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. The patch adds visibility checks for both the topic and posts before allowing ownership transfer. As a workaround, disable the `moderators_change_post_ownership` site setting to prevent non-admin moderators from using the post ownership transfer feature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68934 | Discourse Has Denial of Service (DoS) Vulnerability in Drafts Creation Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68934</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, authenticated users can submit crafted payloads to /drafts.json that cause O(n^2) processing in Base62.decode, tying up workers for 35-60 seconds per request. This affects all users as the shared worker pool becomes exhausted. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. Lowering the max_draft_length site setting reduces attack surface but does not fully mitigate the issue, as payloads under the limit can still trigger the slow code path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69218 | Discourse moderators can access admin-only reports exposing private upload URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69218</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, moderators can access the `top_uploads` admin report which should be restricted to admins only. This report displays direct URLs to all uploaded files on the site, including sensitive content such as user data exports, admin backups, and other private attachments that moderators should not have access to. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. There is no workaround. Limit moderator privileges to trusted users until the patch is applied.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71002 | A floating-point exception (FPE) in the flow.column_stack component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71002</link><description>A floating-point exception (FPE) in the flow.column_stack component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68662 | FinalDestination hostname matching allows SSRF protection bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68662</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, a hostname validation issue in FinalDestination could allow bypassing SSRF protections under certain conditions. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68666 | Discourse users archives leaked to users with moderation privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68666</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, users archives are viewable by users with moderation privileges even though moderators should not have access to the archives. Private topic/post content made by the users are leaked through the archives leading to a breach of confidentiality. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. To work around this problem, a site admin can temporarily revoke the moderation role from all moderators until the Discourse instance has been upgraded to a version that has been patched.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68660 | Discourse AI Discover&amp;#x27;s continue conversation allows threat actor to impersonate user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68660</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, an endpoint lets any authenticated user bypass the ai_discover_persona access controls and gain ongoing DM access to personas that may be wired to staff-only categories, RAG document sets, or automated tooling, enabling unauthorized data disclosure. Because the controller also accepts arbitrary user_id, an attacker can impersonate other accounts to trigger unwanted AI conversations on their behalf, generating confusing or abusive PM traffic. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0749 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Drupal Form Builder Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0749</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Form Builder allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Drupal: from 7.X-1.0 through 7.X-1.22.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0750 | Payment bypass in Commerce Paybox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0750</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Drupal Drupal Commerce Paybox Commerce Paybox on Drupal 7.X allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Drupal Commerce Paybox: from 7-x-1.0 through 7.X-1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40619 | FunJSQ, a third-party module integrated on some NETGEAR routers and Orbi WiFi Systems, exposes an HTTP server over the LAN interface of affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40619</link><description>FunJSQ, a third-party module integrated on some NETGEAR routers and Orbi WiFi Systems, exposes an HTTP server over the LAN interface of affected devices. This interface is vulnerable to unauthenticated arbitrary command injection through the funjsq_access_token parameter. This affects R6230 before 1.1.0.112, R6260 before 1.1.0.88, R7000 before 1.0.11.134, R8900 before 1.0.5.42, R9000 before 1.0.5.42, and XR300 before 1.0.3.72 and Orbi RBR20 before 2.7.2.26, RBR50 before 2.7.4.26, RBS20 before 2.7.2.26, and RBS50 before 2.7.4.26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40620 | FunJSQ, a third-party module integrated on some NETGEAR routers and Orbi WiFi Systems, does not properly validate TLS certificates when down...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40620</link><description>FunJSQ, a third-party module integrated on some NETGEAR routers and Orbi WiFi Systems, does not properly validate TLS certificates when downloading update packages through its auto-update mechanism. An attacker (suitably positioned on the network) could intercept the update request and deliver a malicious update package in order to gain arbitrary code execution on affected devices. This affects R6230 before 1.1.0.112, R6260 before 1.1.0.88, R7000 before 1.0.11.134, R8900 before 1.0.5.42, R9000 before 1.0.5.42, and XR300 before 1.0.3.72 and Orbi RBR20 before 2.7.2.26, RBR50 before 2.7.4.26, RBS20 before 2.7.2.26, and RBS50 before 2.7.4.26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68479 | Discourse subscriptions are susceptible to takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68479</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. In versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0, some subscription endpoints lack proper checking for ownership before making changes. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68659 | Discourse has DoS vulnerability in username change endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68659</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0 have an application level denial of service vulnerabilityin the username change functionality at try.discourse.org. The vulnerability allows attackers to cause noticeable server delays and resource exhaustion by sending large JSON payloads to the username preference endpoint PUT /u//preferences/username, resulting in degraded performance for other users and endpoints. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69601 | A directory traversal (Zip Slip) vulnerability exists in the “Static Sites” feature of 66biolinks v44.0.0 by AltumCode. Uploaded ZIP archive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69601</link><description>A directory traversal (Zip Slip) vulnerability exists in the “Static Sites” feature of 66biolinks v44.0.0 by AltumCode. Uploaded ZIP archives are automatically extracted without validating or sanitizing file paths. An attacker can include traversal sequences (e.g., ../) in ZIP entries to write files outside the intended extraction directory. This allows static files (html, js, css, images) file write to unintended locations, or overwriting existing HTML files, potentially leading to content defacement and, in certain deployments, further impact if sensitive files are overwritten.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69602 | A session fixation vulnerability exists in 66biolinks v62.0.0 by AltumCode, where the application does not regenerate the session identifier...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69602</link><description>A session fixation vulnerability exists in 66biolinks v62.0.0 by AltumCode, where the application does not regenerate the session identifier after successful authentication. As a result, the same session cookie value is reused for users logging in from the same browser, allowing an attacker who can set or predict a session ID to potentially hijack an authenticated session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67723 | Discourse vulnerable to stored Cross-site Scripting via Katex in discourse-math plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67723</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0 have a content-security-policy-mitigated cross-site scriptinv vulnerability on the Discourse Math plugin when using its KaTeX variant. This issue is patched in versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0. As a workaround, the Discourse Math plugin can be disabled, or the Mathjax provider can be used instead of KaTeX.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66488 | Discourse allows script execution in uploaded HTML/XML files on S3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66488</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. A vulnerability present in versions prior to 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0 affects anyone who uses S3 for uploads. While scripts may be executed, they will only be run in the context of the S3/CDN domain, with no site credentials. Versions 3.5.4, 2025.11.2, 2025.12.1, and 2026.1.0 fix the issue. As a workaround, disallow html or xml files for uploads in authorized_extensions. For existing html xml uploads, site owners can consider deleting them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71001 | A segmentation violation in the flow.column_stack component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71001</link><description>A segmentation violation in the flow.column_stack component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24772 | OpenProject has SSRF and CSWSH in Hocuspocus Synchronization Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24772</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. To enable the real time collaboration on documents, OpenProject 17.0 introduced a synchronization server. The OpenPrioject backend generates an authentication token that is currently valid for 24 hours, encrypts it with a shared secret only known to the synchronization server. The frontend hands this encrypted token and the backend URL over to the synchronization server to check user's ability to work on the document and perform intermittent saves while editing. The synchronization server does not properly validate the backend URL and sends a request with the decrypted authentication token to the endpoint that was given to the server. An attacker could use this vulnerability to decrypt a token that he intercepted by other means to gain an access token to interact with OpenProject on the victim's behalf. This vulnerability was introduced with OpenProject 17.0.0 and was fixed in 17.0.2. As a workaround, disable the collaboration feature via Settings -&gt; Documents -&gt; Real time collaboration -&gt; Disable. Additionally the `hocuspocus` container should also be disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24775 | OpenProject has Forced Actions, Content Spoofing, and Persistent DoS via ID Manipulation in OpenProject Blocknote Editor Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24775</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. In the new editor for collaborative documents based on BlockNote, OpenProject maintainers added a custom extension in OpenProject version 17.0.0 that allows to mention OpenProject work packages in the document. To show work package details, the editor loads details about the work package via the OpenProject API. For this API call, the extension to the BlockNote editor did not properly validate the given work package ID to be only a number. This allowed an attacker to generate a document with relative links that upon opening could make arbitrary `GET` requests to any URL within the OpenProject instance. This issue was patched in version version 0.0.22 of op-blocknote-extensions, which was shipped with OpenProject 17.0.2. If users cannot update immediately to version 17.0.2 of OpenProject, administrators can disable collaborative document editing in Settings -&gt; Documents -&gt; Real time collaboration -&gt; Disable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33217 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker could trigger a use after free. A successful exploit of this vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33217</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker could trigger a use after free. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33218 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer (nvlddmkm.sys), where an attacker could cause an int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33218</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer (nvlddmkm.sys), where an attacker could cause an integer overflow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33219 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA kernel module where an attacker could cause an integer overflow or wr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33219</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA kernel module where an attacker could cause an integer overflow or wraparound. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33220 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause heap memory access after the m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33220</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause heap memory access after the memory is freed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33237 | NVIDIA HD Audio Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker could exploit a NULL pointer dereference issue. A successful e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33237</link><description>NVIDIA HD Audio Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker could exploit a NULL pointer dereference issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57795 | Unauthenticated Remote File Download in Explorance Blue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57795</link><description>Explorance Blue versions prior to 8.14.13 contain an authenticated remote file download vulnerability in a web service component. In default configurations, this flaw can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57796 | Use of a hardcoded static key to protect sensitive data in Explorance Blue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57796</link><description>Explorance Blue versions prior to 8.14.12 use reversible symmetric encryption with a hardcoded static key to protect sensitive data, including user passwords and system configurations. This approach allows stored values to be decrypted offline if the encrypted data are obtained.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71000 | An issue in the flow.cuda.BoolTensor component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71000</link><description>An issue in the flow.cuda.BoolTensor component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36943 | aSc TimeTables 2021.6.2 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36943</link><description>aSc TimeTables 2021.6.2 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overwriting subject title fields with excessive data. Attackers can generate a 10,000-character buffer and paste it into the subject title to trigger application instability and potential crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36944 | ILIAS Learning Management System 4.3 - SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36944</link><description>ILIAS Learning Management System 4.3 contains a server-side request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to read local files through portfolio PDF export functionality. Attackers can inject a script that uses XMLHttpRequest to retrieve local file contents when the portfolio is exported to PDF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36945 | WebDamn User Registration &amp;amp; Login System with User Panel - SQLi Auth Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36945</link><description>WebDamn User Registration Login System contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass login authentication by manipulating email credentials. Attackers can inject the payload '' OR '1'='1' in both username and password fields to gain unauthorized access to the user panel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36961 | 10-Strike Network Inventory Explorer 8.65 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36961</link><description>10-Strike Network Inventory Explorer 8.65 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in exception handling that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can craft a malicious file with 209 bytes of padding and a specially constructed Structured Exception Handler to trigger code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36962 | Tendenci 12.3.1 - CSV/ Formula Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36962</link><description>Tendenci 12.3.1 contains a CSV formula injection vulnerability in the contact form message field that allows attackers to inject malicious formulas during export. Attackers can submit crafted payloads like '=10+20+cmd|' /C calc'!A0' in the message field to trigger arbitrary command execution when the CSV is opened in spreadsheet applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36963 | Intelbras Router RF 301K 1.1.2 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36963</link><description>Intelbras Router RF 301K firmware version 1.1.2 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to download router configuration files. Attackers can send a specific HTTP GET request to /cgi-bin/DownloadCfg/RouterCfm.cfg to retrieve sensitive router configuration without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36964 | YATinyWinFTP - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36964</link><description>YATinyWinFTP contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the FTP service by sending a 272-byte buffer with a trailing space. Attackers can exploit the service by connecting and sending a malformed command that triggers a buffer overflow and service crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36965 | docPrint Pro 8.0 - &amp;#x27;Add URL&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow (SEH Egghunter)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36965</link><description>docPrint Pro 8.0 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the 'Add URL' input field that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting memory. Attackers can craft a malicious payload that triggers a structured exception handler (SEH) overwrite to execute shellcode and gain remote system access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36967 | Zortam Mp3 Media Studio 27.60 - Remote Code Execution (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36967</link><description>Zortam Mp3 Media Studio 27.60 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the library creation file selection process that allows remote code execution. Attackers can craft a malicious text file with shellcode to trigger a structured exception handler (SEH) overwrite and execute arbitrary commands on the target system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36968 | M/Monit 3.7.4 - Password Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36968</link><description>M/Monit 3.7.4 contains an authentication vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to retrieve user password hashes through an administrative API endpoint. Attackers can send requests to the /api/1/admin/users/list and /api/1/admin/users/get endpoints to extract MD5 password hashes for all users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36969 | M/Monit 3.7.4 - Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36969</link><description>M/Monit 3.7.4 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows authenticated users to modify user permissions by manipulating the admin parameter. Attackers can send a POST request to the /api/1/admin/users/update endpoint with a crafted payload to grant administrative access to a standard user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36970 | PMB 5.6 - &amp;#x27;chemin&amp;#x27; Local File Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36970</link><description>PMB 5.6 contains a local file disclosure vulnerability in getgif.php that allows attackers to read arbitrary system files by manipulating the 'chemin' parameter. Attackers can exploit the unsanitized file path input to access sensitive files like /etc/passwd by sending crafted requests to the getgif.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36971 | Nidesoft 3GP Video Converter 2.6.18 - Local Stack Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36971</link><description>Nidesoft 3GP Video Converter 2.6.18 contains a local stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the license registration parameter. Attackers can craft a malicious payload and paste it into the 'License Code' field to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36972 | SmartBlog 2.0.1 - &amp;#x27;id_post&amp;#x27; Blind SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36972</link><description>SmartBlog 2.0.1 contains a blind SQL injection vulnerability in the 'id_post' parameter of the details controller that allows attackers to extract database information. Attackers can systematically test and retrieve database contents by injecting crafted SQL queries that compare character-by-character of database information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36973 | PDW File Browser 1.3 - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36973</link><description>PDW File Browser 1.3 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows authenticated users to upload and rename webshell files to arbitrary web server locations. Attackers can upload a .txt webshell, rename it to .php, and move it to accessible directories using double-encoded path traversal techniques.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46306 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26, Keynote 15.1, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Processing a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46306</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26, Keynote 15.1, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Processing a maliciously crafted Keynote file may disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46316 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Pages 15.1, macOS Tahoe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46316</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Pages 15.1, macOS Tahoe 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted Pages document may result in unexpected termination or disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57792 | SQL Injection Vulnerability in Explorance Blue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57792</link><description>Explorance Blue versions prior to 8.14.9 contain a SQL injection vulnerability caused by insufficient validation of user input in a web application endpoint. An attacker can supply crafted input that is executed as part of backend database queries. The issue is exploitable without authentication, significantly raising the risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57794 | Unrestricted File Upload Vulnerability in Explorance Blue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57794</link><description>Explorance Blue versions prior to 8.14.9 contain an authenticated unrestricted file upload vulnerability in the administrative interface. The application does not adequately restrict uploaded file types, allowing malicious files to be uploaded and executed by the server. This condition enables remote code execution under default configurations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57793 | SQL Injection Vulnerability in Explorance Blue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57793</link><description>Explorance Blue versions prior to 8.14.9 contain a SQL injection vulnerability caused by insufficient validation of user-supplied input in a web application component. Crafted input can be executed as part of backend database queries. The issue is exploitable without authentication, significantly elevating the risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65891 | A GPU device-ID validation flaw in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to trigger a Denial of Dervice (DoS) by invoking flow.cuda.get_device_pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65891</link><description>A GPU device-ID validation flaw in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to trigger a Denial of Dervice (DoS) by invoking flow.cuda.get_device_properties() with an invalid or negative device index.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70999 | A GPU device-ID validation flaw in the flow.cuda.get_device_capability() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70999</link><description>A GPU device-ID validation flaw in the flow.cuda.get_device_capability() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted device ID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65889 | A type validation flaw in the flow.dstack() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65889</link><description>A type validation flaw in the flow.dstack() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65890 | A device-ID validation flaw in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by calling flow.cuda.synchronize() with an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65890</link><description>A device-ID validation flaw in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by calling flow.cuda.synchronize() with an invalid or out-of-range GPU device index.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13918 | Elevation of Privileges in Symantec Endpoint Protection Windows Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13918</link><description>Symantec Endpoint Protection, prior to 14.3 RU10 Patch 1, RU9 Patch 2, and RU8 Patch 3, may be susceptible to a Elevation of Privilege vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an attacker may attempt to compromise the software application to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected from an application or user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13919 | Component Object Model (COM) Hijacking in Symantec Endpoint Protection Windows Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13919</link><description>Symantec Endpoint Protection, prior to 14.3 RU10 Patch 1, RU9 Patch 2, and RU8 Patch 3, may be susceptible to a COM Hijacking vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an attacker attempts to establish persistence and evade detection by hijacking COM references in the Windows Registry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24685 | OpenProject has Argument Injection on Repository module that allows Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24685</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Versions prior to 16.6.6 and 17.0.2 have an arbitrary file write vulnerability in OpenProject’s repository diff download endpoint (`/projects/:project_id/repository/diff.diff`) when rendering a single revision via git show. By supplying a specially crafted rev value (for example, `rev=--output=/tmp/poc.txt)`, an attacker can inject git show command-line options. When OpenProject executes the SCM command, Git interprets the attacker-controlled rev as an option and writes the output to an attacker-chosen path. As a result, any user with the `:browse_repository` permission on the project can create or overwrite arbitrary files that the OpenProject process user is permitted to write. The written contents consist of git show output (commit metadata and patch), but overwriting application or configuration files still leads to data loss and denial of service, impacting integrity and availability. The issue has been fixed in OpenProject 17.0.2 and 16.6.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13917 | Elevation of Privileges in Web Security Services (WSS) Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13917</link><description>WSS Agent, prior to 9.8.5, may be susceptible to a Elevation of Privilege vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an attacker may attempt to compromise the software application to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected from an application or user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65887 | A division-by-zero vulnerability in the flow.floor_divide() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65887</link><description>A division-by-zero vulnerability in the flow.floor_divide() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input tensor with zero.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65888 | A dimension validation flaw in the flow.empty() component of OneFlow 0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a negativ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65888</link><description>A dimension validation flaw in the flow.empty() component of OneFlow 0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a negative or excessively large dimension value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1522 | Open5GS SGWC s5c-handler.c sgwc_s5c_handle_modify_bearer_response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1522</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This vulnerability affects the function sgwc_s5c_handle_modify_bearer_response of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c of the component SGWC. Executing a manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This patch is called b19cf6a. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65886 | A shape mismatch vulnerability in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted tensor shapes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65886</link><description>A shape mismatch vulnerability in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted tensor shapes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22243 | EGroupware has SQL Injection in Nextmatch Filter Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22243</link><description>EGroupware is a Web based groupware server written in PHP. A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the core components of EGroupware prior to versions 23.1.20260113 and 26.0.20260113, specifically in the `Nextmatch` filter processing. The flaw allows authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands into the `WHERE` clause of database queries. This is achieved by exploiting a PHP type juggling issue where JSON decoding converts numeric strings into integers, bypassing the `is_int()` security check used by the application. Versions 23.1.20260113 and 26.0.20260113 patch the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61140 | The value function in jsonpath 1.1.1 lib/index.js is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61140</link><description>The value function in jsonpath 1.1.1 lib/index.js is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57283 | The Node.js package browserstack-local 1.5.8 contains a command injection vulnerability. This occurs because the logfile variable is not pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57283</link><description>The Node.js package browserstack-local 1.5.8 contains a command injection vulnerability. This occurs because the logfile variable is not properly sanitized in lib/Local.js.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58150 | x86: buffer overrun with shadow paging + tracing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58150</link><description>Shadow mode tracing code uses a set of per-CPU variables to avoid
cumbersome parameter passing.  Some of these variables are written to
with guest controlled data, of guest controllable size.  That size can
be larger than the variable, and bounding of the writes was missing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69517 | An issue in Amidaware Inc Tactical RMM v1.3.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /api/tacticalrmm/apiv3/v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69517</link><description>An issue in Amidaware Inc Tactical RMM v1.3.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /api/tacticalrmm/apiv3/views.py component</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23553 | x86: incomplete IBPB for vCPU isolation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23553</link><description>In the context switch logic Xen attempts to skip an IBPB in the case of
a vCPU returning to a CPU on which it was the previous vCPU to run.
While safe for Xen's isolation between vCPUs, this prevents the guest
kernel correctly isolating between tasks.  Consider:

 1) vCPU runs on CPU A, running task 1.
 2) vCPU moves to CPU B, idle gets scheduled on A.  Xen skips IBPB.
 3) On CPU B, guest kernel switches from task 1 to 2, issuing IBPB.
 4) vCPU moves back to CPU A.  Xen skips IBPB again.

Now, task 2 is running on CPU A with task 1's training still in the BTB.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70336 | A Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 'Create New Live Item' in PodcastGenerator 3.2.9 allows remote attackers to inject arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70336</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 'Create New Live Item' in PodcastGenerator 3.2.9 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary script or HTML via the 'TITLE', 'SHORT DESCRIPTION' and 'LONG DESCRIPTION' parameters. The saved payload gets executed on 'View All Live Items' and 'Live Stream' pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1536 | Libsoup: libsoup: http header injection or response splitting via crlf injection in content-disposition header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1536</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. An attacker who can control the input for the Content-Disposition header can inject CRLF (Carriage Return Line Feed) sequences into the header value. These sequences are then interpreted verbatim when the HTTP request or response is constructed, allowing arbitrary HTTP headers to be injected. This vulnerability can lead to HTTP header injection or HTTP response splitting without requiring authentication or user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1539 | Libsoup: libsoup: credential leakage via http redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1539</link><description>A flaw was found in the libsoup HTTP library that can cause proxy authentication credentials to be sent to unintended destinations. When handling HTTP redirects, libsoup removes the Authorization header but does not remove the Proxy-Authorization header if the request is redirected to a different host. As a result, sensitive proxy credentials may be leaked to third-party servers. Applications using libsoup for HTTP communication may unintentionally expose proxy authentication data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1237 | Vulnerable cross-model authorization in juju. If a charm's cross-model permissions are revoked or expire, a malicious user who is able to up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1237</link><description>Vulnerable cross-model authorization in juju. If a charm's cross-model permissions are revoked or expire, a malicious user who is able to update database records can mint an invalid macaroon that is incorrectly validated by the juju controller, enabling a charm to maintain otherwise revoked or expired permissions. This allows a charm to continue relating to another charm in a cross-model relation, and use their workload without their permission. No fix is available as of the time of writing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1520 | rethinkdb Secondary Index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1520</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in rethinkdb up to 2.4.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Secondary Index Handler. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1521 | Open5GS SGWC s5c-handler.c denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1521</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This affects the function sgwc_s5c_handle_bearer_resource_failure_indication of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c of the component SGWC. Performing a manipulation results in denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is named 69b53add90a9479d7960b822fc60601d659c328b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1060 | WP Adminify &amp;lt;= 4.0.7.7 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;get-addons-list&amp;#x27; REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1060</link><description>The WP Adminify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.7.7 via the /wp-json/adminify/v1/get-addons-list REST API endpoint. The endpoint is registered with permission_callback set to __return_true, allowing unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the complete list of available addons, their installation status, version numbers, and download URLs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23014 | perf: Ensure swevent hrtimer is properly destroyed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23014</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

perf: Ensure swevent hrtimer is properly destroyed

With the change to hrtimer_try_to_cancel() in
perf_swevent_cancel_hrtimer() it appears possible for the hrtimer to
still be active by the time the event gets freed.

Make sure the event does a full hrtimer_cancel() on the free path by
installing a perf_event::destroy handler.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14795 | Stop Spammers Classic &amp;lt;= 2026.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via Email Allowlist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14795</link><description>The Stop Spammers Classic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2026.1. This is due to missing nonce validation in the ss_addtoallowlist class. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary email addresses to the spam allowlist via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2026.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36984 | EPSON 1.124 - &amp;#x27;seksmdb.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36984</link><description>EPSON 1.124 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the SENADB service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\EPSON_P2B\Printer Software\Status Monitor\ to inject malicious executables that will run with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36985 | IP Watcher v3.0.0.30 - &amp;#x27;PACService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36985</link><description>IP Watcher 3.0.0.30 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path to inject malicious executables that will be launched with elevated LocalSystem privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36986 | Prey 1.9.6 - &amp;quot;CronService&amp;quot; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36986</link><description>Prey 1.9.6 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the CronService to insert malicious code that would execute during application startup or system reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36987 | Program Access Controller v1.2.0.0 - &amp;#x27;PACService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36987</link><description>Program Access Controller 1.2.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in PACService.exe that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36988 | PDW File Browser &amp;lt;= v1.3 - Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36988</link><description>PDW File Browser version 1.3 contains stored and reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities that allow authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts through file rename and path parameters. Attackers can craft malicious URLs or rename files with XSS payloads to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers when they access the file browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36989 | ForensiTAppxService 2.2.0.4 - &amp;#x27;ForensiTAppxService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36989</link><description>ForensiT AppX Management Service 2.2.0.4 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem account permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36990 | Input Director 1.4.3 - &amp;#x27;Input Director&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36990</link><description>Input Director 1.4.3 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36991 | ShareMouse 5.0.43 - &amp;#x27;ShareMouse Service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36991</link><description>ShareMouse 5.0.43 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the insecure service path configuration by placing malicious executables in specific system directories to gain elevated access during service startup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36992 | Nord VPN-6.31.13.0 - &amp;#x27;nordvpn-service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36992</link><description>Nord VPN 6.31.13.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its nordvpn-service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path during system startup or reboot to potentially run malicious code with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36993 | LimeSurvey &amp;lt;= 4.3.10 - &amp;#x27;Survey Menu&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36993</link><description>LimeSurvey 4.3.10 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Survey Menu functionality of the administration panel. Attackers can inject malicious SVG scripts through the Surveymenu[title] and Surveymenu[parent_id] parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in administrative contexts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14865 | Passster – Password Protect Pages and Content &amp;lt;= 4.2.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14865</link><description>The Passster – Password Protect Pages and Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'content_protector' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.2.21.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1056 | Snow Monkey Forms &amp;lt;= 12.0.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1056</link><description>The Snow Monkey Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'generate_user_dirpath' function in all versions up to, and including, 12.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59896 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59896</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in '/add_command?sid=', affecting the 'command_name' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59897 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59897</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in '/edit_command?sid=', affecting the 'source_dir' and ‘dest_dir’ parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59898 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59898</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in '/add_exclude_dir?sid=', affecting the 'exclude_dir' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59899 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59899</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in  '/server_options?sid=', affecting the 'tasks_logs_dir', 'errors_logs_dir', 'error_notifications_address', 'status_notifications_address', and 'status_reports_address' parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59900 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59900</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in  '/server_options?sid=', affecting the 'tasks_logs_dir', 'errors_logs_dir', 'error_notifications_address', 'status_notifications_address', and 'status_reports_address' parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59901 | authenticated reflected XSS vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59901</link><description>Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 has an authenticated reflected XSS vulnerability in the '/monitor_directory?sid=' endpoint, caused by insufficient validation of the 'monitor_directory' parameter sent by POST. An attacker could exploit this weakness to send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59891 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59891</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to change a user's password or create users via '/setup_login?sid=', affecting the 'username', 'password', and 'cpassword' parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59892 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59892</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to delete commands individually via '/delete_command?sid=', using the 'cid' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59893 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59893</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to rename commands via '/rename_command?sid=', affecting the 'command_name' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59894 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59894</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to delete all commands via '/delete_all_commands?sid='.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59895 | remote denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59895</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a remote denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in the configuration restore functionality. The issue is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied data during this process. An attacker could send malicious requests to alter the configuration file, causing the application to become unresponsive. In a successful scenario, the service may not recover on its own and require a complete reinstallation, as the configuration becomes corrupted and prevents the service from restarting, even manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0483 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LiveHelperChat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0483</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PDF file upload functionality of Live Helper Chat, versions prior to 4.72. An attacker can upload a malicious PDF file containing an XSS payload, which will be executed in the user's context when they download and open the file via the link generated by the application. The vulnerability allows arbitrary JavaScript code to be executed in the user's local context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14063 | SEO Links Interlinking &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;google_error&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14063</link><description>The SEO Links Interlinking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'google_error' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14283 | BlockArt Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder Blocks ,WordPress Block Plugin, Sections &amp;amp; Template Library &amp;lt;= 2.2.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14283</link><description>The BlockArt Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder Blocks ,WordPress Block Plugin, Sections &amp; Template Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the BlockArt Counter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14386 | Search Atlas SEO – Premier SEO Plugin for One-Click WP Publishing &amp;amp; Integrated AI Optimization 2.4.4 - 2.5.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14386</link><description>The Search Atlas SEO – Premier SEO Plugin for One-Click WP Publishing &amp; Integrated AI Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to a missing capability check on the 'generate_sso_url' and 'validate_sso_token' functions in versions 2.4.4 to 2.5.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract the 'nonce_token' authentication value to log in to the first Administrator's account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14616 | Recooty &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14616</link><description>The Recooty – Job Widget (Old Dashboard) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This is due to missing nonce validation on the recooty_save_maybe() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the recooty_key option and inject malicious content into iframe src attributes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15511 | Rupantorpay &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Order Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15511</link><description>The Rupantorpay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_webhook() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify WooCommerce order statuses by sending crafted requests to the WooCommerce API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26386 | Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) tool has Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26386</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU): iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) tool version 6.9.7 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0844 | Simple User Registration &amp;lt;= 6.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via profile_save_field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0844</link><description>The Simple User Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 6.7 due to insufficient restriction on the 'profile_save_field' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as a subscriber, to modify their user role by supplying the 'wp_capabilities' parameter during a profile update.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1280 | Frontend File Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 23.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Sharing via &amp;#x27;file_id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1280</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized file sharing due to a missing capability check on the 'wpfm_send_file_in_email' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 23.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to share arbitrary uploaded files via email by supplying a file ID. Since file IDs are sequential integers, attackers can enumerate all uploaded files on the site and exfiltrate sensitive data that was intended to be restricted to administrators only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1377 | imwptip &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1377</link><description>The imwptip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1380 | Bitcoin Donate Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1380</link><description>The Bitcoin Donate Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings, including donation addresses and display configurations, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1391 | Vzaar Media Management &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1391</link><description>The Vzaar Media Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the $_SERVER['PHP_SELF'] variable. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1398 | Change WP URL &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1398</link><description>The Change WP URL plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'change-wp-url' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the WP Login URL via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1399 | WP Google Ad Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Admin Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1399</link><description>The WP Google Ad Manager Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41351 | Weak encryption on Funambol&amp;#x27;s cloud server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41351</link><description>Vulnerability that allows a Padding Oracle Attack to be performed on the Funambol v30.0.0.20 cloud server. The thumbnail display URL allows an attacker to decrypt and encrypt the parameters used by the application to generate ‘self-signed’ access URLs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7740 | Use of default credentials vulnerability in Hitachi Energy SuprOS product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7740</link><description>Default credentials vulnerability exists in SuprOS
product. If exploited, this could allow an authenticated
local attacker to use an admin account created during
product deployment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0702 | VidShop – Shoppable Videos for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated Time-Based SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;fields&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0702</link><description>The VidShop – Shoppable Videos for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'fields' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1053 | Ivory Search &amp;lt;= 5.5.13 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;menu_gcse&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;nothing_found_text&amp;#x27; Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1053</link><description>The Ivory Search – WordPress Search Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1381 | Order Minimum/Maximum Amount Limits for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.6.8 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Hide Add to Cart Content Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1381</link><description>The Order Minimum/Maximum Amount Limits for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1400 | AI Engine &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Editor+) Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;filename&amp;#x27; Parameter in update_media_metadata Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1400</link><description>The AI Engine – The Chatbot and AI Framework for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the `rest_helpers_update_media_metadata` function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The attacker can upload a benign image file, then use the `update_media_metadata` endpoint to rename it to a PHP file, creating an executable PHP file in the uploads directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40537 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Hardcoded Credentials Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40537</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a hardcoded credentials vulnerability that, under certain situations, could allow access to administrative functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40551 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40551</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an untrusted data deserialization vulnerability that could lead to remote code execution, which would allow an attacker to run commands on the host machine. This could be exploited without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40552 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40552</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an authentication bypass vulnerability that if exploited, would allow a malicious actor to execute actions and methods that should be protected by authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40553 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40553</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an untrusted data deserialization vulnerability that could lead to remote code execution, which would allow an attacker to run commands on the host machine. This could be exploited without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40554 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40554</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an authentication bypass vulnerability that, if exploited, could allow an attacker to invoke specific actions within Web Help Desk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0818 | CSS-based exfiltration of the content from partially encrypted emails when allowing remote content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0818</link><description>CSS-based exfiltration of the content from partially encrypted emails when allowing remote content. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 147.0.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 140.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40536 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Security Control Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40536</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a security control bypass vulnerability that if exploited, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to gain access to certain restricted functionality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1054 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt;= 6.0.7.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1054</link><description>The RegistrationMagic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 6.0.7.4. This is due to missing nonce verification and capability checks on the rm_set_otp AJAX action handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary plugin settings, including reCAPTCHA keys, security settings, and frontend menu titles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1389 | Document Embedder &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Document Library Entry Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1389</link><description>The Document Embedder – Embed PDFs, Word, Excel, and Other Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This is due to the plugin not verifying that a user has permission to access the requested resource in the 'bplde_save_document_library', 'bplde_get_single', and 'bplde_delete_document_library' AJAX actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to read, modify, and delete Document Library entries created by other users, including administrators, via the 'id' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12709 | Interactions – Create Interactive Experiences in the Block Editor &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12709</link><description>The Interactions – Create Interactive Experiences in the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via event selectors in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14039 | Simple Folio &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Client name&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;Link&amp;#x27; Meta Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14039</link><description>The Simple Folio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the '_simple_folio_item_client_name' and '_simple_folio_item_link' meta fields in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9082 | WPBITS Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9082</link><description>The WPBITS Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widget parameters in versions up to, and including, 1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when dynamic content is enabled. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level permissions and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0825 | Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Form Data Exfiltration via CSV Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0825</link><description>The Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks on the CSV export functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download sensitive form submission data containing personally identifiable information (PII) by accessing the CSV export endpoint with an export key that is exposed in publicly accessible page source code. The vulnerability is created because while the shortcode properly filters displayed entries by user, the CSV export handler completely bypasses this filtering and exports all entries regardless of user permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0832 | New User Approve &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Approval, Denial, and Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0832</link><description>The New User Approve plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple REST API endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve or deny user accounts, retrieve sensitive user information including emails and roles, and force logout of privileged users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1244 | Forms Bridge &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1244</link><description>The Forms Bridge – Infinite integrations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' shortcode attribute in the 'financoop_campaign' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user-supplied 'id' parameter in the forms_bridge_financoop_shortcode_error function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1295 | Buy Now Plus &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1295</link><description>The Buy Now Plus – Buy Now buttons for Stripe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'buynowplus' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on shortcode attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1310 | Simple calendar for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Calendar Entry Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1310</link><description>The Simple calendar for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This is due to missing capability checks on the `miga_ajax_editor_cal_delete` function that is hooked to the `miga_editor_cal_delete` AJAX action with both authenticated and unauthenticated access enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary calendar entries by sending a request with a valid nonce and the calendar entry ID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1466 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in Jirafeau</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1466</link><description>Jirafeau normally prevents browser preview for text files due to the possibility that for example SVG and HTML documents could be exploited for cross site scripting. This was done by storing the MIME type of a file and allowing only browser preview for MIME types beginning with image (except for image/svg+xml, see CVE-2022-30110, CVE-2024-12326 and CVE-2025-7066), video and audio. However, it was possible to bypass this check by sending a manipulated HTTP request with an invalid MIME type like image. When doing the preview, the browser tries to automatically detect the MIME type resulting in detecting SVG and possibly executing JavaScript code. To prevent this, MIME sniffing is disabled by sending the HTTP header X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13471 | User Activity Log &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13471</link><description>The User Activity Log WordPress plugin through 2.2 does not properly handle failed login attempts in some cases, allowing unauthenticated users to set arbitrary options to 1 (for example to enable User Registration when it has been turned off)</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14610 | TableMaster for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;csv_url&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14610</link><description>The TableMaster for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This is due to the plugin not restricting which URLs can be fetched when importing CSV data from a URL in the Data Table widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations, including localhost and internal network services, and read sensitive files such as wp-config.php via the 'csv_url' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8072 | Target Video Easy Publish &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via placeholder_img Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8072</link><description>The Target Video Easy Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘placeholder_img’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1083 | Appointment Hour Booking – Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.5.60 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Min/Max Length&amp;#x27; Field Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1083</link><description>The Appointment Hour Booking – Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form field configuration parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.60 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'Min length/characters' and 'Max length/characters' field configuration values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the form builder interface. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1298 | Easy Replace Image &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Attachment Replacement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1298</link><description>The Easy Replace Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2. This is due to missing capability checks on the `image_replacement_from_url` function that is hooked to the `eri_from_url` AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to replace arbitrary image attachments on the site with images from external URLs, potentially enabling site defacement, phishing attacks, or content manipulation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1514 | 2100 Technology｜Official Document Management System - Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1514</link><description>Official Document Management System developed by 2100 Technology has a Incorrect Authorization vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to modify front-end code to read all official documents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1506 | D-Link DIR-615 MAC Filter Configuration adv_mac_filter.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1506</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /adv_mac_filter.php of the component MAC Filter Configuration. This manipulation of the argument mac causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1505 | D-Link DIR-615 URL Filter set_temp_nodes.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /set_temp_nodes.php of the component URL Filter. The manipulation results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1513 | billboard.js before 3.18.0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization during chart option binding.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1513</link><description>billboard.js before 3.18.0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization during chart option binding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21569 | This High severity XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.1.0 of Crowd Data Center and Server. 
	
	Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21569</link><description>This High severity XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.1.0 of Crowd Data Center and Server. 
	
	This XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.9, allows an authenticated attacker to access local and remote content which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Crowd Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		* Crowd Data Center and Server 7.1: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.1.3
		
		
	
	See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/crowd/crowd-release-notes-199094.html). You can download the latest version of Crowd Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/crowd/download-archive). 
	
	This vulnerability was reported via our Atlassian (Internal) program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24850 | ML-DSA Signature Verification Accepts Signatures with Repeated Hint Indices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24850</link><description>The ML-DSA crate is a Rust implementation of the Module-Lattice-Based Digital Signature Standard (ML-DSA). Starting in version 0.0.4 and prior to version 0.1.0-rc.4, the ML-DSA signature verification implementation in the RustCrypto `ml-dsa` crate incorrectly accepts signatures with repeated (duplicate) hint indices. According to the ML-DSA specification (FIPS 204 / RFC 9881), hint indices within each polynomial must be **strictly increasing**. The current implementation uses a non-strict monotonic check (`&lt;=` instead of `&lt;`), allowing duplicate indices. This is a regression bug. The original implementation was correct, but a commit in version 0.0.4 inadvertently changed the strict `&lt;` comparison to `&lt;=`, introducing the vulnerability. Version 0.1.0-rc.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24852 | iccDEV has a heap-buffer-overflow in icXmlParseTextString()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24852</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, a heap buffer over-read when the strlen() function attempts to read a non-null-terminated buffer potentially leaking heap memory contents and causing application termination. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. ICC Profile Injection vulnerabilities arise when user-controllable input is incorporated into ICC profile data or other structured binary blobs in an unsafe manner. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a fix for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24838 | DotNetNuke.Core Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Module Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24838</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Prior to versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0,  module title supports richtext which could include scripts that would execute in certain scenarios. Versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24839 | Dokploy has a clickjacking vulnerability - Missing X-Frame-Options and CSP frame-ancestors headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24839</link><description>Dokploy is a free, self-hostable Platform as a Service (PaaS). In versions prior to 0.26.6, the Dokploy web interface is vulnerable to Clickjacking attacks due to missing frame-busting headers. This allows attackers to embed Dokploy pages in malicious iframes and trick authenticated users into performing unintended actions. Version 0.26.6 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24840 | Dokploy uses hardcoded credentials in installation script, which could result in database access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24840</link><description>Dokploy is a free, self-hostable Platform as a Service (PaaS). In versions prior to 0.26.6, a hardcoded credential in the provided installation script (located at https://dokploy.com/install.sh, line 154) uses a hardcoded password when creating the database container. This means that nearly all Dokploy installations use the same database credentials and could be compromised. Version 0.26.6 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24841 | Dokploy Vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Command Injection in Docker Container Terminal WebSocket Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24841</link><description>Dokploy is a free, self-hostable Platform as a Service (PaaS). In versions prior to 0.26.6, a critical command injection vulnerability exists in Dokploy's WebSocket endpoint `/docker-container-terminal`. The `containerId` and `activeWay` parameters are directly interpolated into shell commands without sanitization, allowing authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the host server. Version 0.26.6 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24842 | node-tar Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Creation/Overwrite via Hardlink Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24842</link><description>node-tar,a Tar for Node.js, contains a vulnerability in versions prior to 7.5.7 where the security check for hardlink entries uses different path resolution semantics than the actual hardlink creation logic. This mismatch allows an attacker to craft a malicious TAR archive that bypasses path traversal protections and creates hardlinks to arbitrary files outside the extraction directory. Version 7.5.7 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>