<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:38:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-1825 | CodeAstro House Rental Management System User Registration Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1825</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component User Registration Page. The manipulation of the argument address with the input &lt;img src="1" onerror="console.log(1)"&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254613 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51392 | Silicon Labs EFR32xxx parts with classic key storage do not use hardware accelerated AES-CCM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51392</link><description>Ember ZNet between v7.2.0 and v7.4.0 used software AES-CCM instead of integrated hardware cryptographic accelerators, potentially increasing risk of electromagnetic and differential power analysis sidechannel attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1824 | CodeAstro House Rental Management System signing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1824</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file signing.php. The manipulation of the argument uname/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254612.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26150 | `@backstage/backend-common` vulnerable to path traversal through symlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26150</link><description>`@backstage/backend-common` is a common functionality library for backends for Backstage, an open platform for building developer portals. In `@backstage/backend-common` prior to versions 0.21.1, 0.20.2, and 0.19.10, paths checks with the `resolveSafeChildPath` utility were not exhaustive enough, leading to risk of path traversal vulnerabilities if symlinks can be injected by attackers. This issue is patched in `@backstage/backend-common` versions 0.21.1, 0.20.2, and 0.19.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1822 | PHPGurukul Tourism Management System user-bookings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1822</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Tourism Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file user-bookings.php. The manipulation of the argument Full Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254610 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1823 | CodeAstro Simple Voting System Backend users.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1823</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CodeAstro Simple Voting System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file users.php of the component Backend. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254611.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1820 | code-projects Crime Reporting System inchargelogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1820</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file inchargelogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254608.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1821 | code-projects Crime Reporting System police_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1821</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file police_add.php. The manipulation of the argument police_name/police_id/police_spec/password leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254609 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25629 | c-ares out of bounds read in ares__read_line()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25629</link><description>c-ares is a C library for asynchronous DNS requests. `ares__read_line()` is used to parse local configuration files such as `/etc/resolv.conf`, `/etc/nsswitch.conf`, the `HOSTALIASES` file, and if using a c-ares version prior to 1.27.0, the `/etc/hosts` file. If any of these configuration files has an embedded `NULL` character as the first character in a new line, it can lead to attempting to read memory prior to the start of the given buffer which may result in a crash. This issue is fixed in c-ares 1.27.0. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52453 | hisi_acc_vfio_pci: Update migration data pointer correctly on saving/resume</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52453</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hisi_acc_vfio_pci: Update migration data pointer correctly on saving/resume

When the optional PRE_COPY support was added to speed up the device
compatibility check, it failed to update the saving/resuming data
pointers based on the fd offset. This results in migration data
corruption and when the device gets started on the destination the
following error is reported in some cases,

[  478.907684] arm-smmu-v3 arm-smmu-v3.2.auto: event 0x10 received:
[  478.913691] arm-smmu-v3 arm-smmu-v3.2.auto:  0x0000310200000010
[  478.919603] arm-smmu-v3 arm-smmu-v3.2.auto:  0x000002088000007f
[  478.925515] arm-smmu-v3 arm-smmu-v3.2.auto:  0x0000000000000000
[  478.931425] arm-smmu-v3 arm-smmu-v3.2.auto:  0x0000000000000000
[  478.947552] hisi_zip 0000:31:00.0: qm_axi_rresp [error status=0x1] found
[  478.955930] hisi_zip 0000:31:00.0: qm_db_timeout [error status=0x400] found
[  478.955944] hisi_zip 0000:31:00.0: qm sq doorbell timeout in function 2</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52454 | nvmet-tcp: Fix a kernel panic when host sends an invalid H2C PDU length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52454</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvmet-tcp: Fix a kernel panic when host sends an invalid H2C PDU length

If the host sends an H2CData command with an invalid DATAL,
the kernel may crash in nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec().

Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at
virtual address 0000000000000000
lr : nvmet_tcp_io_work+0x6ac/0x718 [nvmet_tcp]
Call trace:
  process_one_work+0x174/0x3c8
  worker_thread+0x2d0/0x3e8
  kthread+0x104/0x110

Fix the bug by raising a fatal error if DATAL isn't coherent
with the packet size.
Also, the PDU length should never exceed the MAXH2CDATA parameter which
has been communicated to the host in nvmet_tcp_handle_icreq().</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52455 | iommu: Don&amp;#x27;t reserve 0-length IOVA region</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52455</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommu: Don't reserve 0-length IOVA region

When the bootloader/firmware doesn't setup the framebuffers, their
address and size are 0 in "iommu-addresses" property. If IOVA region is
reserved with 0 length, then it ends up corrupting the IOVA rbtree with
an entry which has pfn_hi &lt; pfn_lo.
If we intend to use display driver in kernel without framebuffer then
it's causing the display IOMMU mappings to fail as entire valid IOVA
space is reserved when address and length are passed as 0.
An ideal solution would be firmware removing the "iommu-addresses"
property and corresponding "memory-region" if display is not present.
But the kernel should be able to handle this by checking for size of
IOVA region and skipping the IOVA reservation if size is 0. Also, add
a warning if firmware is requesting 0-length IOVA region reservation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52456 | serial: imx: fix tx statemachine deadlock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52456</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

serial: imx: fix tx statemachine deadlock

When using the serial port as RS485 port, the tx statemachine is used to
control the RTS pin to drive the RS485 transceiver TX_EN pin. When the
TTY port is closed in the middle of a transmission (for instance during
userland application crash), imx_uart_shutdown disables the interface
and disables the Transmission Complete interrupt. afer that,
imx_uart_stop_tx bails on an incomplete transmission, to be retriggered
by the TC interrupt. This interrupt is disabled and therefore the tx
statemachine never transitions out of SEND. The statemachine is in
deadlock now, and the TX_EN remains low, making the interface useless.

imx_uart_stop_tx now checks for incomplete transmission AND whether TC
interrupts are enabled before bailing to be retriggered. This makes sure
the state machine handling is reached, and is properly set to
WAIT_AFTER_SEND.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52457 | serial: 8250: omap: Don&amp;#x27;t skip resource freeing if pm_runtime_resume_and_get() failed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52457</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

serial: 8250: omap: Don't skip resource freeing if pm_runtime_resume_and_get() failed

Returning an error code from .remove() makes the driver core emit the
little helpful error message:

	remove callback returned a non-zero value. This will be ignored.

and then remove the device anyhow. So all resources that were not freed
are leaked in this case. Skipping serial8250_unregister_port() has the
potential to keep enough of the UART around to trigger a use-after-free.

So replace the error return (and with it the little helpful error
message) by a more useful error message and continue to cleanup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52458 | block: add check that partition length needs to be aligned with block size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52458</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

block: add check that partition length needs to be aligned with block size

Before calling add partition or resize partition, there is no check
on whether the length is aligned with the logical block size.
If the logical block size of the disk is larger than 512 bytes,
then the partition size maybe not the multiple of the logical block size,
and when the last sector is read, bio_truncate() will adjust the bio size,
resulting in an IO error if the size of the read command is smaller than
the logical block size.If integrity data is supported, this will also
result in a null pointer dereference when calling bio_integrity_free.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52459 | media: v4l: async: Fix duplicated list deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52459</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: v4l: async: Fix duplicated list deletion

The list deletion call dropped here is already called from the
helper function in the line before. Having a second list_del()
call results in either a warning (with CONFIG_DEBUG_LIST=y):

list_del corruption, c46c8198-&gt;next is LIST_POISON1 (00000100)

If CONFIG_DEBUG_LIST is disabled the operation results in a
kernel error due to NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52460 | drm/amd/display: Fix NULL pointer dereference at hibernate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52460</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Fix NULL pointer dereference at hibernate

During hibernate sequence the source context might not have a clk_mgr.
So don't use it to look for DML2 support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52461 | drm/sched: Fix bounds limiting when given a malformed entity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52461</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/sched: Fix bounds limiting when given a malformed entity

If we're given a malformed entity in drm_sched_entity_init()--shouldn't
happen, but we verify--with out-of-bounds priority value, we set it to an
allowed value. Fix the expression which sets this limit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52462 | bpf: fix check for attempt to corrupt spilled pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52462</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: fix check for attempt to corrupt spilled pointer

When register is spilled onto a stack as a 1/2/4-byte register, we set
slot_type[BPF_REG_SIZE - 1] (plus potentially few more below it,
depending on actual spill size). So to check if some stack slot has
spilled register we need to consult slot_type[7], not slot_type[0].

To avoid the need to remember and double-check this in the future, just
use is_spilled_reg() helper.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52463 | efivarfs: force RO when remounting if SetVariable is not supported</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52463</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

efivarfs: force RO when remounting if SetVariable is not supported

If SetVariable at runtime is not supported by the firmware we never assign
a callback for that function. At the same time mount the efivarfs as
RO so no one can call that.  However, we never check the permission flags
when someone remounts the filesystem as RW. As a result this leads to a
crash looking like this:

$ mount -o remount,rw /sys/firmware/efi/efivars
$ efi-updatevar -f PK.auth PK

[  303.279166] Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 0000000000000000
[  303.280482] Mem abort info:
[  303.280854]   ESR = 0x0000000086000004
[  303.281338]   EC = 0x21: IABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
[  303.282016]   SET = 0, FnV = 0
[  303.282414]   EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
[  303.282821]   FSC = 0x04: level 0 translation fault
[  303.283771] user pgtable: 4k pages, 48-bit VAs, pgdp=000000004258c000
[  303.284913] [0000000000000000] pgd=0000000000000000, p4d=0000000000000000
[  303.286076] Internal error: Oops: 0000000086000004 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[  303.286936] Modules linked in: qrtr tpm_tis tpm_tis_core crct10dif_ce arm_smccc_trng rng_core drm fuse ip_tables x_tables ipv6
[  303.288586] CPU: 1 PID: 755 Comm: efi-updatevar Not tainted 6.3.0-rc1-00108-gc7d0c4695c68 #1
[  303.289748] Hardware name: Unknown Unknown Product/Unknown Product, BIOS 2023.04-00627-g88336918701d 04/01/2023
[  303.291150] pstate: 60400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[  303.292123] pc : 0x0
[  303.292443] lr : efivar_set_variable_locked+0x74/0xec
[  303.293156] sp : ffff800008673c10
[  303.293619] x29: ffff800008673c10 x28: ffff0000037e8000 x27: 0000000000000000
[  303.294592] x26: 0000000000000800 x25: ffff000002467400 x24: 0000000000000027
[  303.295572] x23: ffffd49ea9832000 x22: ffff0000020c9800 x21: ffff000002467000
[  303.296566] x20: 0000000000000001 x19: 00000000000007fc x18: 0000000000000000
[  303.297531] x17: 0000000000000000 x16: 0000000000000000 x15: 0000aaaac807ab54
[  303.298495] x14: ed37489f673633c0 x13: 71c45c606de13f80 x12: 47464259e219acf4
[  303.299453] x11: ffff000002af7b01 x10: 0000000000000003 x9 : 0000000000000002
[  303.300431] x8 : 0000000000000010 x7 : ffffd49ea8973230 x6 : 0000000000a85201
[  303.301412] x5 : 0000000000000000 x4 : ffff0000020c9800 x3 : 00000000000007fc
[  303.302370] x2 : 0000000000000027 x1 : ffff000002467400 x0 : ffff000002467000
[  303.303341] Call trace:
[  303.303679]  0x0
[  303.303938]  efivar_entry_set_get_size+0x98/0x16c
[  303.304585]  efivarfs_file_write+0xd0/0x1a4
[  303.305148]  vfs_write+0xc4/0x2e4
[  303.305601]  ksys_write+0x70/0x104
[  303.306073]  __arm64_sys_write+0x1c/0x28
[  303.306622]  invoke_syscall+0x48/0x114
[  303.307156]  el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x44/0xec
[  303.307803]  do_el0_svc+0x38/0x98
[  303.308268]  el0_svc+0x2c/0x84
[  303.308702]  el0t_64_sync_handler+0xf4/0x120
[  303.309293]  el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194
[  303.309794] Code: ???????? ???????? ???????? ???????? (????????)
[  303.310612] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

Fix this by adding a .reconfigure() function to the fs operations which
we can use to check the requested flags and deny anything that's not RO
if the firmware doesn't implement SetVariable at runtime.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52464 | EDAC/thunderx: Fix possible out-of-bounds string access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52464</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

EDAC/thunderx: Fix possible out-of-bounds string access

Enabling -Wstringop-overflow globally exposes a warning for a common bug
in the usage of strncat():

  drivers/edac/thunderx_edac.c: In function 'thunderx_ocx_com_threaded_isr':
  drivers/edac/thunderx_edac.c:1136:17: error: 'strncat' specified bound 1024 equals destination size [-Werror=stringop-overflow=]
   1136 |                 strncat(msg, other, OCX_MESSAGE_SIZE);
        |                 ^~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
   ...
   1145 |                                 strncat(msg, other, OCX_MESSAGE_SIZE);
   ...
   1150 |                                 strncat(msg, other, OCX_MESSAGE_SIZE);

   ...

Apparently the author of this driver expected strncat() to behave the
way that strlcat() does, which uses the size of the destination buffer
as its third argument rather than the length of the source buffer. The
result is that there is no check on the size of the allocated buffer.

Change it to strlcat().

  [ bp: Trim compiler output, fixup commit message. ]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26595 | mlxsw: spectrum_acl_tcam: Fix NULL pointer dereference in error path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26595</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mlxsw: spectrum_acl_tcam: Fix NULL pointer dereference in error path

When calling mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_region_destroy() from an error path after
failing to attach the region to an ACL group, we hit a NULL pointer
dereference upon 'region-&gt;group-&gt;tcam' [1].

Fix by retrieving the 'tcam' pointer using mlxsw_sp_acl_to_tcam().

[1]
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
[...]
RIP: 0010:mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_region_destroy+0xa0/0xd0
[...]
Call Trace:
 mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_vchunk_get+0x88b/0xa20
 mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_ventry_add+0x25/0xe0
 mlxsw_sp_acl_rule_add+0x47/0x240
 mlxsw_sp_flower_replace+0x1a9/0x1d0
 tc_setup_cb_add+0xdc/0x1c0
 fl_hw_replace_filter+0x146/0x1f0
 fl_change+0xc17/0x1360
 tc_new_tfilter+0x472/0xb90
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x313/0x3b0
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x58/0x100
 netlink_unicast+0x244/0x390
 netlink_sendmsg+0x1e4/0x440
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x164/0x260
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x9a/0xe0
 __sys_sendmsg+0x7a/0xc0
 do_syscall_64+0x40/0xe0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26596 | net: dsa: fix netdev_priv() dereference before check on non-DSA netdevice events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26596</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: dsa: fix netdev_priv() dereference before check on non-DSA netdevice events

After the blamed commit, we started doing this dereference for every
NETDEV_CHANGEUPPER and NETDEV_PRECHANGEUPPER event in the system.

static inline struct dsa_port *dsa_user_to_port(const struct net_device *dev)
{
	struct dsa_user_priv *p = netdev_priv(dev);

	return p-&gt;dp;
}

Which is obviously bogus, because not all net_devices have a netdev_priv()
of type struct dsa_user_priv. But struct dsa_user_priv is fairly small,
and p-&gt;dp means dereferencing 8 bytes starting with offset 16. Most
drivers allocate that much private memory anyway, making our access not
fault, and we discard the bogus data quickly afterwards, so this wasn't
caught.

But the dummy interface is somewhat special in that it calls
alloc_netdev() with a priv size of 0. So every netdev_priv() dereference
is invalid, and we get this when we emit a NETDEV_PRECHANGEUPPER event
with a VLAN as its new upper:

$ ip link add dummy1 type dummy
$ ip link add link dummy1 name dummy1.100 type vlan id 100
[   43.309174] ==================================================================
[   43.316456] BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in dsa_user_prechangeupper+0x30/0xe8
[   43.323835] Read of size 8 at addr ffff3f86481d2990 by task ip/374
[   43.330058]
[   43.342436] Call trace:
[   43.366542]  dsa_user_prechangeupper+0x30/0xe8
[   43.371024]  dsa_user_netdevice_event+0xb38/0xee8
[   43.375768]  notifier_call_chain+0xa4/0x210
[   43.379985]  raw_notifier_call_chain+0x24/0x38
[   43.384464]  __netdev_upper_dev_link+0x3ec/0x5d8
[   43.389120]  netdev_upper_dev_link+0x70/0xa8
[   43.393424]  register_vlan_dev+0x1bc/0x310
[   43.397554]  vlan_newlink+0x210/0x248
[   43.401247]  rtnl_newlink+0x9fc/0xe30
[   43.404942]  rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x378/0x580

Avoid the kernel oops by dereferencing after the type check, as customary.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26597 | net: qualcomm: rmnet: fix global oob in rmnet_policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26597</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: qualcomm: rmnet: fix global oob in rmnet_policy

The variable rmnet_link_ops assign a *bigger* maxtype which leads to a
global out-of-bounds read when parsing the netlink attributes. See bug
trace below:

==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: global-out-of-bounds in validate_nla lib/nlattr.c:386 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: global-out-of-bounds in __nla_validate_parse+0x24af/0x2750 lib/nlattr.c:600
Read of size 1 at addr ffffffff92c438d0 by task syz-executor.6/84207

CPU: 0 PID: 84207 Comm: syz-executor.6 Tainted: G                 N 6.1.0 #3
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.13.0-1ubuntu1.1 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:88 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x8b/0xb3 lib/dump_stack.c:106
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:284 [inline]
 print_report+0x172/0x475 mm/kasan/report.c:395
 kasan_report+0xbb/0x1c0 mm/kasan/report.c:495
 validate_nla lib/nlattr.c:386 [inline]
 __nla_validate_parse+0x24af/0x2750 lib/nlattr.c:600
 __nla_parse+0x3e/0x50 lib/nlattr.c:697
 nla_parse_nested_deprecated include/net/netlink.h:1248 [inline]
 __rtnl_newlink+0x50a/0x1880 net/core/rtnetlink.c:3485
 rtnl_newlink+0x64/0xa0 net/core/rtnetlink.c:3594
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x43c/0xd70 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6091
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x14f/0x410 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2540
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1319 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x54e/0x800 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1345
 netlink_sendmsg+0x930/0xe50 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1921
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:714 [inline]
 sock_sendmsg+0x154/0x190 net/socket.c:734
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x6df/0x840 net/socket.c:2482
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x110/0x1b0 net/socket.c:2536
 __sys_sendmsg+0xf3/0x1c0 net/socket.c:2565
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:50 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0x3b/0x90 arch/x86/entry/common.c:80
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd
RIP: 0033:0x7fdcf2072359
Code: 28 00 00 00 75 05 48 83 c4 28 c3 e8 f1 19 00 00 90 48 89 f8 48 89 f7 48 89 d6 48 89 ca 4d 89 c2 4d 89 c8 4c 8b 4c 24 08 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 c7 c1 b8 ff ff ff f7 d8 64 89 01 48
RSP: 002b:00007fdcf13e3168 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 000000000000002e
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007fdcf219ff80 RCX: 00007fdcf2072359
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000020000200 RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 00007fdcf20bd493 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: 00007fffbb8d7bdf R14: 00007fdcf13e3300 R15: 0000000000022000
 &lt;/TASK&gt;

The buggy address belongs to the variable:
 rmnet_policy+0x30/0xe0

The buggy address belongs to the physical page:
page:0000000065bdeb3c refcount:1 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0x0 pfn:0x155243
flags: 0x200000000001000(reserved|node=0|zone=2)
raw: 0200000000001000 ffffea00055490c8 ffffea00055490c8 0000000000000000
raw: 0000000000000000 0000000000000000 00000001ffffffff 0000000000000000
page dumped because: kasan: bad access detected

Memory state around the buggy address:
 ffffffff92c43780: f9 f9 f9 f9 00 00 00 02 f9 f9 f9 f9 00 00 00 07
 ffffffff92c43800: f9 f9 f9 f9 00 00 00 05 f9 f9 f9 f9 06 f9 f9 f9
&gt;ffffffff92c43880: f9 f9 f9 f9 00 00 00 00 00 00 f9 f9 f9 f9 f9 f9
                                                 ^
 ffffffff92c43900: 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 07 f9 f9 f9 f9 f9 f9 f9
 ffffffff92c43980: 00 00 00 07 f9 f9 f9 f9 00 00 00 05 f9 f9 f9 f9

According to the comment of `nla_parse_nested_deprecated`, the maxtype
should be len(destination array) - 1. Hence use `IFLA_RMNET_MAX` here.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26598 | KVM: arm64: vgic-its: Avoid potential UAF in LPI translation cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26598</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: arm64: vgic-its: Avoid potential UAF in LPI translation cache

There is a potential UAF scenario in the case of an LPI translation
cache hit racing with an operation that invalidates the cache, such
as a DISCARD ITS command. The root of the problem is that
vgic_its_check_cache() does not elevate the refcount on the vgic_irq
before dropping the lock that serializes refcount changes.

Have vgic_its_check_cache() raise the refcount on the returned vgic_irq
and add the corresponding decrement after queueing the interrupt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26599 | pwm: Fix out-of-bounds access in of_pwm_single_xlate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26599</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pwm: Fix out-of-bounds access in of_pwm_single_xlate()

With args-&gt;args_count == 2 args-&gt;args[2] is not defined. Actually the
flags are contained in args-&gt;args[1].</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1818 | CodeAstro Membership Management System Logo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1818</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /uploads/ of the component Logo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1819 | CodeAstro Membership Management System Add Members Tab unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1819</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component Add Members Tab. The manipulation of the argument Member Photo leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254607.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22776 | Wallos 0.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in all text-based input fields without proper validation, excluding those requiring s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22776</link><description>Wallos 0.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in all text-based input fields without proper validation, excluding those requiring specific formats like date fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1817 | Demososo DM Enterprise Website Building System Cookie indexDM_load.php dmlogin improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1817</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Demososo DM Enterprise Website Building System up to 2022.8 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function dmlogin of the file indexDM_load.php of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument is_admin with the input y leads to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26594 | ksmbd: validate mech token in session setup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26594</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: validate mech token in session setup

If client send invalid mech token in session setup request, ksmbd
validate and make the error if it is invalid.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25928 | WordPress Sitepact&amp;#x27;s Contact Form 7 Extension For Klaviyo Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Sitepact.This issue affects Sitepact: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25915 | WordPress Pexels: Free Stock Photos Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25915</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Raaj Trambadia Pexels: Free Stock Photos.This issue affects Pexels: Free Stock Photos: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24416 | WordPress All In One Favicon Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24416</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Arne Franken All In One Favicon.This issue affects All In One Favicon: from n/a through 4.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1360 | The Colibri WP theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.94. This is due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1360</link><description>The Colibri WP theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.94. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the colibriwp_install_plugin() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install recommended plugins via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1361 | The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.253. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1361</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.253. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the apiCall() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call a limited set of functions that can be used to import images, delete posts, or save theme data via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1362 | The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.253. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1362</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.253. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cp_shortcode_refresh() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1590 | The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1590</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Button Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4826 | Socialdriver &amp;lt; 2024 - Prototype Pollution to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4826</link><description>The SocialDriver WordPress theme before version 2024 has a prototype pollution vulnerability that could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary properties resulting in a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26593 | i2c: i801: Fix block process call transactions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26593</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i2c: i801: Fix block process call transactions

According to the Intel datasheets, software must reset the block
buffer index twice for block process call transactions: once before
writing the outgoing data to the buffer, and once again before
reading the incoming data from the buffer.

The driver is currently missing the second reset, causing the wrong
portion of the block buffer to be read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0563 | Denial of service condition in M-Files Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0563</link><description>Denial of service condition in M-Files Server in versions before 24.2 (excluding 23.2 SR7 and 23.8 SR5) allows anonymous user to cause denial of service against other anonymous users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 08:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37540 | HCL Sametime Chat is affected by an unimplemented feature in the UI </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37540</link><description>Sametime Connect desktop chat client includes, but does not use or require, the use of an Eclipse feature called Secure Storage. Using this Eclipse feature to store sensitive data can lead to exposure of that data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 07:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1776 | The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'form-id' parameter in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1776</link><description>The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'form-id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1777 | The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1777</link><description>The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings update function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1778 | The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1778</link><description>The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the zt_dcfcf_change_bookmark() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to alter bookmark statuses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1779 | The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1779</link><description>The Admin side data storage for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the zt_dcfcf_change_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to alter the message read status of messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22243 | CVE-2024-22243: Spring Framework URL Parsing with Host Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22243</link><description>Applications that use UriComponentsBuilder to parse an externally provided URL (e.g. through a query parameter) AND perform validation checks on the host of the parsed URL may be vulnerable to a  open redirect https://cwe.mitre.org/data/definitions/601.html  attack or to a SSRF attack if the URL is used after passing validation checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 05:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1784 | Limbas main_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1784</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Limbas 5.2.14. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file main_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument tab_group leads to sql injection. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254575. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1786 | D-Link DIR-600M C1 Telnet Service buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1786</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-600M C1 3.08. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation of the argument username leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254576. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1683 | DLL Injection in Tenable Identity Exposure Secure Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1683</link><description>A DLL injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, low-privileged local attacker could modify application files on the TIE Secure Relay host, which could allow for overriding of the configuration and running of new Secure Relay services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1781 | Totolink X6000R AX3000 shttpd cstecgi.cgi setWizardCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1781</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1783 | Totolink LR1200GB Web Interface cstecgi.cgi loginAuth stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1783</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25753 | Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25753</link><description>Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the formSetDeviceName function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 22:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25748 | A Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in tenda AC9 AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25748</link><description>A Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in tenda AC9 AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the fromSetIpMacBind function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 22:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25756 | A Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25756</link><description>A Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the formWifiBasicSet function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 22:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25746 | Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25746</link><description>Stack Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC9 v.3.0 with firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_white_node function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 21:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26152 | Label Studio vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting if `&amp;lt;Choices&amp;gt;` or `&amp;lt;Labels&amp;gt;` are used in labeling config </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26152</link><description>### Summary
On all Label Studio versions prior to 1.11.0, data imported via file upload feature is not properly sanitized prior to being rendered within a [`Choices`](https://labelstud.io/tags/choices) or [`Labels`](https://labelstud.io/tags/labels) tag, resulting in an XSS vulnerability.

### Details
Need permission to use the "data import" function. This was reproduced on Label Studio 1.10.1.

### PoC

1. Create a project.
![Create a project](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/9b1536ad-feac-4238-a1bd-ca9b1b798673)

2. Upload a file containing the payload using the "Upload Files" function.
![2  Upload a file containing the payload using the Upload Files function](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/26bb7af1-1cd2-408f-9adf-61e31a5b7328)
![3  complete](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/f2f62774-1fa6-4456-9e6f-8fa1ca0a2d2e)

The following are the contents of the files used in the PoC
```
{
  "data": {
    "prompt": "labelstudio universe image",
    "images": [
      {
        "value": "id123#0",
        "style": "margin: 5px",
        "html": "&lt;img width='400' src='https://labelstud.io/_astro/images-tab.64279c16_ZaBSvC.avif' onload=alert(document.cookie)&gt;"
      }
    ]
  }
}
```

3. Select the text-to-image generation labeling template of Ranking and scoring
![3  Select the text-to-image generation labelling template for Ranking and scoring](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/f227f49c-a718-4738-bc2a-807da4f97155)
![5  save](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/9b529f8a-8e99-4bb0-bdf6-bb7a95c9b75d)

4. Select a task
![4  Select a task](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/71856b7a-2b1f-44ea-99ab-fc48bc20caa7)

5. Check that the script is running
![5  Check that the script is running](https://github.com/HumanSignal/label-studio/assets/3943358/e396ae7b-a591-4db7-afe9-5bab30b48cb9)

### Impact
Malicious scripts can be injected into the code, and when linked with vulnerabilities such as CSRF, it can cause even greater damage. In particular, It can become a source of further attacks, especially when linked to social engineering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 21:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25377 | The ACME-challenge endpoint in Appwrite 0.5.0 through 0.12.x before 0.12.2 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary local files via ../ dir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25377</link><description>The ACME-challenge endpoint in Appwrite 0.5.0 through 0.12.x before 0.12.2 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary local files via ../ directory traversal. In order to be vulnerable, APP_STORAGE_CERTIFICATES/.well-known/acme-challenge must exist on disk. (This pathname is automatically created if the user chooses to install Let's Encrypt certificates via Appwrite.)</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 21:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1750 | TemmokuMVC Image Download images_get_down.php img_replace deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1750</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TemmokuMVC up to 2.3. Affected is the function get_img_url/img_replace in the library lib/images_get_down.php of the component Image Download Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254532. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1748 | van_der_Schaar LAB AutoPrognosis Release Note load_model_from_file deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1748</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in van_der_Schaar LAB AutoPrognosis 0.1.21. This vulnerability affects the function load_model_from_file of the component Release Note Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254530 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1749 | Bdtask Bhojon Best Restaurant Management Software Message Page message cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1749</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Bdtask Bhojon Best Restaurant Management Software 2.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dashboard/message of the component Message Page. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254531. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25369 | A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FUEL CMS 1.5.2allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string after the gr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25369</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FUEL CMS 1.5.2allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string after the group_id parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25385 | An issue in flvmeta v.1.2.2 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the flvmeta/src/flv.c:375:21 function in flv_close.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25385</link><description>An issue in flvmeta v.1.2.2 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the flvmeta/src/flv.c:375:21 function in flv_close.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22547 | WayOS IBR-7150 &lt;17.06.23 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22547</link><description>WayOS IBR-7150 &lt;17.06.23 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26128 | baserCMS Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Content Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26128</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 5.0.9, there is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the content management feature. Version 5.0.9 contains a fix for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 18:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26151 | Potentially untrusted input is rendered as HTML in final output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26151</link><description>The `mjml` PyPI package, found at the `FelixSchwarz/mjml-python` GitHub repo, is an unofficial Python port of MJML, a markup language created by Mailjet. All users of `FelixSchwarz/mjml-python` who insert untrusted data into mjml templates unless that data is checked in a very strict manner. User input like `&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;` would be rendered as `&lt;script&gt;` in the final HTML output. The attacker must be able to control some data which is later injected in an mjml template which is then send out as email to other users. The attacker could control contents of email messages sent through the platform. The problem has been fixed in version 0.11.0 of this library. Versions before 0.10.0 are not affected by this security issue. As a workaround, ensure that potentially untrusted user input does not contain any sequences which could be rendered as HTML.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 18:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25130 | Tuleap&amp;#x27;s mass update clears the permissions on artifact field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25130</link><description>Tuleap is an open source suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Prior to version 15.5.99.76 of Tuleap Community Edition and prior to versions 15.5-4 and 15.4-7 of Tuleap Enterprise Edition, users with a read access to a tracker where the mass update feature is used might get access to restricted information. Tuleap Community Edition 15.5.99.76, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.5-4, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.4-7 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 18:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25129 | Limited data exfiltration in CodeQL CLI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25129</link><description>The CodeQL CLI repo holds binaries for the CodeQL command line interface (CLI). Prior to version 2.16.3, an XML parser used by the CodeQL CLI to read various auxiliary files is vulnerable to an XML External Entity attack. If a vulnerable version of the CLI is used to process either a maliciously modified CodeQL database, or a specially prepared set of QL query sources, the CLI can be made to make an outgoing HTTP request to an URL that contains material read from a local file chosen by the attacker. This may result in a loss of privacy of exfiltration of secrets. Security researchers and QL authors who receive databases or QL source files from untrusted sources may be impacted. A single untrusted `.ql` or `.qll` file cannot be affected, but a zip archive or tarball containing QL sources may unpack auxiliary files that will trigger an attack when CodeQL sees them in the file system. Those using CodeQL for routine analysis of source trees with a preselected set of trusted queries are not affected. In particular, extracting XML files from a source tree into the CodeQL database does not make one vulnerable. The problem is fixed in release 2.16.3 of the CodeQL CLI. Other than upgrading, workarounds include not accepting CodeQL databases or queries from untrusted sources, or only processing such material on a machine without an Internet connection. Customers who use older releases of CodeQL for security scanning in an automated CI system and cannot upgrade for compliance reasons can continue using that version. That use case is safe. If such customers have a private query pack and use the `codeql pack create` command to precompile them before using them in the CI system, they should be using the production CodeQL release to run `codeql pack create`. That command is safe as long as the QL source it precompiled is trusted. All other development of the query pack should use an upgraded CLI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 18:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24817 | User can see invitees in events created in PMs and private categories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24817</link><description>Discourse Calendar adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic on the open-source discussion platform Discourse. Prior to version 0.4, event invitees created in topics in private categories or PMs (private messages) can be retrieved by anyone, even if they're not logged in. This problem is resolved in version 0.4 of the discourse-calendar plugin. While no known workaround is available, putting the site behind `login_required` will disallow this endpoint to be used by anonymous users, but logged in users can still get the list of invitees in the private topics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25802 | SKINsoft S-Museum 7.02.3 allows Unrestricted File Upload via the Add Media function. Unlike in CVE-2024-25801, the attack payload is the fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25802</link><description>SKINsoft S-Museum 7.02.3 allows Unrestricted File Upload via the Add Media function. Unlike in CVE-2024-25801, the attack payload is the file content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52161 | The Access Point functionality in eapol_auth_key_handle in eapol.c in iNet wireless daemon (IWD) before 2.14 allows attackers to gain unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52161</link><description>The Access Point functionality in eapol_auth_key_handle in eapol.c in iNet wireless daemon (IWD) before 2.14 allows attackers to gain unauthorized access to a protected Wi-Fi network. An attacker can complete the EAPOL handshake by skipping Msg2/4 and instead sending Msg4/4 with an all-zero key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52160 | The implementation of PEAP in wpa_supplicant through 2.10 allows authentication bypass. For a successful attack, wpa_supplicant must be conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52160</link><description>The implementation of PEAP in wpa_supplicant through 2.10 allows authentication bypass. For a successful attack, wpa_supplicant must be configured to not verify the network's TLS certificate during Phase 1 authentication, and an eap_peap_decrypt vulnerability can then be abused to skip Phase 2 authentication. The attack vector is sending an EAP-TLV Success packet instead of starting Phase 2. This allows an adversary to impersonate Enterprise Wi-Fi networks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52443 | apparmor: avoid crash when parsed profile name is empty</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52443</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

apparmor: avoid crash when parsed profile name is empty

When processing a packed profile in unpack_profile() described like

 "profile :ns::samba-dcerpcd /usr/lib*/samba/{,samba/}samba-dcerpcd {...}"

a string ":samba-dcerpcd" is unpacked as a fully-qualified name and then
passed to aa_splitn_fqname().

aa_splitn_fqname() treats ":samba-dcerpcd" as only containing a namespace.
Thus it returns NULL for tmpname, meanwhile tmpns is non-NULL. Later
aa_alloc_profile() crashes as the new profile name is NULL now.

general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000000: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN NOPTI
KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000000-0x0000000000000007]
CPU: 6 PID: 1657 Comm: apparmor_parser Not tainted 6.7.0-rc2-dirty #16
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.2-3-gd478f380-rebuilt.opensuse.org 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:strlen+0x1e/0xa0
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 ? strlen+0x1e/0xa0
 aa_policy_init+0x1bb/0x230
 aa_alloc_profile+0xb1/0x480
 unpack_profile+0x3bc/0x4960
 aa_unpack+0x309/0x15e0
 aa_replace_profiles+0x213/0x33c0
 policy_update+0x261/0x370
 profile_replace+0x20e/0x2a0
 vfs_write+0x2af/0xe00
 ksys_write+0x126/0x250
 do_syscall_64+0x46/0xf0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76
 &lt;/TASK&gt;
---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
RIP: 0010:strlen+0x1e/0xa0

It seems such behaviour of aa_splitn_fqname() is expected and checked in
other places where it is called (e.g. aa_remove_profiles). Well, there
is an explicit comment "a ns name without a following profile is allowed"
inside.

AFAICS, nothing can prevent unpacked "name" to be in form like
":samba-dcerpcd" - it is passed from userspace.

Deny the whole profile set replacement in such case and inform user with
EPROTO and an explaining message.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org).</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52444 | f2fs: fix to avoid dirent corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52444</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: fix to avoid dirent corruption

As Al reported in link[1]:

f2fs_rename()
...
	if (old_dir != new_dir &amp;&amp; !whiteout)
		f2fs_set_link(old_inode, old_dir_entry,
					old_dir_page, new_dir);
	else
		f2fs_put_page(old_dir_page, 0);

You want correct inumber in the ".." link.  And cross-directory
rename does move the source to new parent, even if you'd been asked
to leave a whiteout in the old place.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/all/20231017055040.GN800259@ZenIV/

With below testcase, it may cause dirent corruption, due to it missed
to call f2fs_set_link() to update ".." link to new directory.
- mkdir -p dir/foo
- renameat2 -w dir/foo bar

[ASSERT] (__chk_dots_dentries:1421)  --&gt; Bad inode number[0x4] for '..', parent parent ino is [0x3]
[FSCK] other corrupted bugs                           [Fail]</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52445 | media: pvrusb2: fix use after free on context disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52445</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: pvrusb2: fix use after free on context disconnection

Upon module load, a kthread is created targeting the
pvr2_context_thread_func function, which may call pvr2_context_destroy
and thus call kfree() on the context object. However, that might happen
before the usb hub_event handler is able to notify the driver. This
patch adds a sanity check before the invalid read reported by syzbot,
within the context disconnection call stack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52446 | bpf: Fix a race condition between btf_put() and map_free()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52446</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix a race condition between btf_put() and map_free()

When running `./test_progs -j` in my local vm with latest kernel,
I once hit a kasan error like below:

  [ 1887.184724] BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in bpf_rb_root_free+0x1f8/0x2b0
  [ 1887.185599] Read of size 4 at addr ffff888106806910 by task kworker/u12:2/2830
  [ 1887.186498]
  [ 1887.186712] CPU: 3 PID: 2830 Comm: kworker/u12:2 Tainted: G           OEL     6.7.0-rc3-00699-g90679706d486-dirty #494
  [ 1887.188034] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.14.0-0-g155821a1990b-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
  [ 1887.189618] Workqueue: events_unbound bpf_map_free_deferred
  [ 1887.190341] Call Trace:
  [ 1887.190666]  &lt;TASK&gt;
  [ 1887.190949]  dump_stack_lvl+0xac/0xe0
  [ 1887.191423]  ? nf_tcp_handle_invalid+0x1b0/0x1b0
  [ 1887.192019]  ? panic+0x3c0/0x3c0
  [ 1887.192449]  print_report+0x14f/0x720
  [ 1887.192930]  ? preempt_count_sub+0x1c/0xd0
  [ 1887.193459]  ? __virt_addr_valid+0xac/0x120
  [ 1887.194004]  ? bpf_rb_root_free+0x1f8/0x2b0
  [ 1887.194572]  kasan_report+0xc3/0x100
  [ 1887.195085]  ? bpf_rb_root_free+0x1f8/0x2b0
  [ 1887.195668]  bpf_rb_root_free+0x1f8/0x2b0
  [ 1887.196183]  ? __bpf_obj_drop_impl+0xb0/0xb0
  [ 1887.196736]  ? preempt_count_sub+0x1c/0xd0
  [ 1887.197270]  ? preempt_count_sub+0x1c/0xd0
  [ 1887.197802]  ? _raw_spin_unlock+0x1f/0x40
  [ 1887.198319]  bpf_obj_free_fields+0x1d4/0x260
  [ 1887.198883]  array_map_free+0x1a3/0x260
  [ 1887.199380]  bpf_map_free_deferred+0x7b/0xe0
  [ 1887.199943]  process_scheduled_works+0x3a2/0x6c0
  [ 1887.200549]  worker_thread+0x633/0x890
  [ 1887.201047]  ? __kthread_parkme+0xd7/0xf0
  [ 1887.201574]  ? kthread+0x102/0x1d0
  [ 1887.202020]  kthread+0x1ab/0x1d0
  [ 1887.202447]  ? pr_cont_work+0x270/0x270
  [ 1887.202954]  ? kthread_blkcg+0x50/0x50
  [ 1887.203444]  ret_from_fork+0x34/0x50
  [ 1887.203914]  ? kthread_blkcg+0x50/0x50
  [ 1887.204397]  ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20
  [ 1887.204913]  &lt;/TASK&gt;
  [ 1887.204913]  &lt;/TASK&gt;
  [ 1887.205209]
  [ 1887.205416] Allocated by task 2197:
  [ 1887.205881]  kasan_set_track+0x3f/0x60
  [ 1887.206366]  __kasan_kmalloc+0x6e/0x80
  [ 1887.206856]  __kmalloc+0xac/0x1a0
  [ 1887.207293]  btf_parse_fields+0xa15/0x1480
  [ 1887.207836]  btf_parse_struct_metas+0x566/0x670
  [ 1887.208387]  btf_new_fd+0x294/0x4d0
  [ 1887.208851]  __sys_bpf+0x4ba/0x600
  [ 1887.209292]  __x64_sys_bpf+0x41/0x50
  [ 1887.209762]  do_syscall_64+0x4c/0xf0
  [ 1887.210222]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b
  [ 1887.210868]
  [ 1887.211074] Freed by task 36:
  [ 1887.211460]  kasan_set_track+0x3f/0x60
  [ 1887.211951]  kasan_save_free_info+0x28/0x40
  [ 1887.212485]  ____kasan_slab_free+0x101/0x180
  [ 1887.213027]  __kmem_cache_free+0xe4/0x210
  [ 1887.213514]  btf_free+0x5b/0x130
  [ 1887.213918]  rcu_core+0x638/0xcc0
  [ 1887.214347]  __do_softirq+0x114/0x37e

The error happens at bpf_rb_root_free+0x1f8/0x2b0:

  00000000000034c0 &lt;bpf_rb_root_free&gt;:
  ; {
    34c0: f3 0f 1e fa                   endbr64
    34c4: e8 00 00 00 00                callq   0x34c9 &lt;bpf_rb_root_free+0x9&gt;
    34c9: 55                            pushq   %rbp
    34ca: 48 89 e5                      movq    %rsp, %rbp
  ...
  ;       if (rec &amp;&amp; rec-&gt;refcount_off &gt;= 0 &amp;&amp;
    36aa: 4d 85 ed                      testq   %r13, %r13
    36ad: 74 a9                         je      0x3658 &lt;bpf_rb_root_free+0x198&gt;
    36af: 49 8d 7d 10                   leaq    0x10(%r13), %rdi
    36b3: e8 00 00 00 00                callq   0x36b8 &lt;bpf_rb_root_free+0x1f8&gt;
                                        &lt;==== kasan function
    36b8: 45 8b 7d 10                   movl    0x10(%r13), %r15d
                                        &lt;==== use-after-free load
    36bc: 45 85 ff                      testl   %r15d, %r15d
    36bf: 78 8c                         js      0x364d &lt;bpf_rb_root_free+0x18d&gt;

So the problem 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52447 | bpf: Defer the free of inner map when necessary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52447</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Defer the free of inner map when necessary

When updating or deleting an inner map in map array or map htab, the map
may still be accessed by non-sleepable program or sleepable program.
However bpf_map_fd_put_ptr() decreases the ref-counter of the inner map
directly through bpf_map_put(), if the ref-counter is the last one
(which is true for most cases), the inner map will be freed by
ops-&gt;map_free() in a kworker. But for now, most .map_free() callbacks
don't use synchronize_rcu() or its variants to wait for the elapse of a
RCU grace period, so after the invocation of ops-&gt;map_free completes,
the bpf program which is accessing the inner map may incur
use-after-free problem.

Fix the free of inner map by invoking bpf_map_free_deferred() after both
one RCU grace period and one tasks trace RCU grace period if the inner
map has been removed from the outer map before. The deferment is
accomplished by using call_rcu() or call_rcu_tasks_trace() when
releasing the last ref-counter of bpf map. The newly-added rcu_head
field in bpf_map shares the same storage space with work field to
reduce the size of bpf_map.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52448 | gfs2: Fix kernel NULL pointer dereference in gfs2_rgrp_dump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52448</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gfs2: Fix kernel NULL pointer dereference in gfs2_rgrp_dump

Syzkaller has reported a NULL pointer dereference when accessing
rgd-&gt;rd_rgl in gfs2_rgrp_dump().  This can happen when creating
rgd-&gt;rd_gl fails in read_rindex_entry().  Add a NULL pointer check in
gfs2_rgrp_dump() to prevent that.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52449 | mtd: Fix gluebi NULL pointer dereference caused by ftl notifier</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52449</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mtd: Fix gluebi NULL pointer dereference caused by ftl notifier

If both ftl.ko and gluebi.ko are loaded, the notifier of ftl
triggers NULL pointer dereference when trying to access
‘gluebi-&gt;desc’ in gluebi_read().

ubi_gluebi_init
  ubi_register_volume_notifier
    ubi_enumerate_volumes
      ubi_notify_all
        gluebi_notify    nb-&gt;notifier_call()
          gluebi_create
            mtd_device_register
              mtd_device_parse_register
                add_mtd_device
                  blktrans_notify_add   not-&gt;add()
                    ftl_add_mtd         tr-&gt;add_mtd()
                      scan_header
                        mtd_read
                          mtd_read_oob
                            mtd_read_oob_std
                              gluebi_read   mtd-&gt;read()
                                gluebi-&gt;desc - NULL

Detailed reproduction information available at the Link [1],

In the normal case, obtain gluebi-&gt;desc in the gluebi_get_device(),
and access gluebi-&gt;desc in the gluebi_read(). However,
gluebi_get_device() is not executed in advance in the
ftl_add_mtd() process, which leads to NULL pointer dereference.

The solution for the gluebi module is to run jffs2 on the UBI
volume without considering working with ftl or mtdblock [2].
Therefore, this problem can be avoided by preventing gluebi from
creating the mtdblock device after creating mtd partition of the
type MTD_UBIVOLUME.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52450 | perf/x86/intel/uncore: Fix NULL pointer dereference issue in upi_fill_topology()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52450</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

perf/x86/intel/uncore: Fix NULL pointer dereference issue in upi_fill_topology()

Get logical socket id instead of physical id in discover_upi_topology()
to avoid out-of-bound access on 'upi = &amp;type-&gt;topology[nid][idx];' line
that leads to NULL pointer dereference in upi_fill_topology()</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52451 | powerpc/pseries/memhp: Fix access beyond end of drmem array</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52451</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

powerpc/pseries/memhp: Fix access beyond end of drmem array

dlpar_memory_remove_by_index() may access beyond the bounds of the
drmem lmb array when the LMB lookup fails to match an entry with the
given DRC index. When the search fails, the cursor is left pointing to
&amp;drmem_info-&gt;lmbs[drmem_info-&gt;n_lmbs], which is one element past the
last valid entry in the array. The debug message at the end of the
function then dereferences this pointer:

        pr_debug("Failed to hot-remove memory at %llx\n",
                 lmb-&gt;base_addr);

This was found by inspection and confirmed with KASAN:

  pseries-hotplug-mem: Attempting to hot-remove LMB, drc index 1234
  ==================================================================
  BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in dlpar_memory+0x298/0x1658
  Read of size 8 at addr c000000364e97fd0 by task bash/949

  dump_stack_lvl+0xa4/0xfc (unreliable)
  print_report+0x214/0x63c
  kasan_report+0x140/0x2e0
  __asan_load8+0xa8/0xe0
  dlpar_memory+0x298/0x1658
  handle_dlpar_errorlog+0x130/0x1d0
  dlpar_store+0x18c/0x3e0
  kobj_attr_store+0x68/0xa0
  sysfs_kf_write+0xc4/0x110
  kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x26c/0x390
  vfs_write+0x2d4/0x4e0
  ksys_write+0xac/0x1a0
  system_call_exception+0x268/0x530
  system_call_vectored_common+0x15c/0x2ec

  Allocated by task 1:
   kasan_save_stack+0x48/0x80
   kasan_set_track+0x34/0x50
   kasan_save_alloc_info+0x34/0x50
   __kasan_kmalloc+0xd0/0x120
   __kmalloc+0x8c/0x320
   kmalloc_array.constprop.0+0x48/0x5c
   drmem_init+0x2a0/0x41c
   do_one_initcall+0xe0/0x5c0
   kernel_init_freeable+0x4ec/0x5a0
   kernel_init+0x30/0x1e0
   ret_from_kernel_user_thread+0x14/0x1c

  The buggy address belongs to the object at c000000364e80000
   which belongs to the cache kmalloc-128k of size 131072
  The buggy address is located 0 bytes to the right of
   allocated 98256-byte region [c000000364e80000, c000000364e97fd0)

  ==================================================================
  pseries-hotplug-mem: Failed to hot-remove memory at 0

Log failed lookups with a separate message and dereference the
cursor only when it points to a valid entry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52452 | bpf: Fix accesses to uninit stack slots</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52452</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix accesses to uninit stack slots

Privileged programs are supposed to be able to read uninitialized stack
memory (ever since 6715df8d5) but, before this patch, these accesses
were permitted inconsistently. In particular, accesses were permitted
above state-&gt;allocated_stack, but not below it. In other words, if the
stack was already "large enough", the access was permitted, but
otherwise the access was rejected instead of being allowed to "grow the
stack". This undesired rejection was happening in two places:
- in check_stack_slot_within_bounds()
- in check_stack_range_initialized()
This patch arranges for these accesses to be permitted. A bunch of tests
that were relying on the old rejection had to change; all of them were
changed to add also run unprivileged, in which case the old behavior
persists. One tests couldn't be updated - global_func16 - because it
can't run unprivileged for other reasons.

This patch also fixes the tracking of the stack size for variable-offset
reads. This second fix is bundled in the same commit as the first one
because they're inter-related. Before this patch, writes to the stack
using registers containing a variable offset (as opposed to registers
with fixed, known values) were not properly contributing to the
function's needed stack size. As a result, it was possible for a program
to verify, but then to attempt to read out-of-bounds data at runtime
because a too small stack had been allocated for it.

Each function tracks the size of the stack it needs in
bpf_subprog_info.stack_depth, which is maintained by
update_stack_depth(). For regular memory accesses, check_mem_access()
was calling update_state_depth() but it was passing in only the fixed
part of the offset register, ignoring the variable offset. This was
incorrect; the minimum possible value of that register should be used
instead.

This tracking is now fixed by centralizing the tracking of stack size in
grow_stack_state(), and by lifting the calls to grow_stack_state() to
check_stack_access_within_bounds() as suggested by Andrii. The code is
now simpler and more convincingly tracks the correct maximum stack size.
check_stack_range_initialized() can now rely on enough stack having been
allocated for the access; this helps with the fix for the first issue.

A few tests were changed to also check the stack depth computation. The
one that fails without this patch is verifier_var_off:stack_write_priv_vs_unpriv.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26586 | mlxsw: spectrum_acl_tcam: Fix stack corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26586</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mlxsw: spectrum_acl_tcam: Fix stack corruption

When tc filters are first added to a net device, the corresponding local
port gets bound to an ACL group in the device. The group contains a list
of ACLs. In turn, each ACL points to a different TCAM region where the
filters are stored. During forwarding, the ACLs are sequentially
evaluated until a match is found.

One reason to place filters in different regions is when they are added
with decreasing priorities and in an alternating order so that two
consecutive filters can never fit in the same region because of their
key usage.

In Spectrum-2 and newer ASICs the firmware started to report that the
maximum number of ACLs in a group is more than 16, but the layout of the
register that configures ACL groups (PAGT) was not updated to account
for that. It is therefore possible to hit stack corruption [1] in the
rare case where more than 16 ACLs in a group are required.

Fix by limiting the maximum ACL group size to the minimum between what
the firmware reports and the maximum ACLs that fit in the PAGT register.

Add a test case to make sure the machine does not crash when this
condition is hit.

[1]
Kernel panic - not syncing: stack-protector: Kernel stack is corrupted in: mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_group_update+0x116/0x120
[...]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x36/0x50
 panic+0x305/0x330
 __stack_chk_fail+0x15/0x20
 mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_group_update+0x116/0x120
 mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_group_region_attach+0x69/0x110
 mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_vchunk_get+0x492/0xa20
 mlxsw_sp_acl_tcam_ventry_add+0x25/0xe0
 mlxsw_sp_acl_rule_add+0x47/0x240
 mlxsw_sp_flower_replace+0x1a9/0x1d0
 tc_setup_cb_add+0xdc/0x1c0
 fl_hw_replace_filter+0x146/0x1f0
 fl_change+0xc17/0x1360
 tc_new_tfilter+0x472/0xb90
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x313/0x3b0
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x58/0x100
 netlink_unicast+0x244/0x390
 netlink_sendmsg+0x1e4/0x440
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x164/0x260
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x9a/0xe0
 __sys_sendmsg+0x7a/0xc0
 do_syscall_64+0x40/0xe0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26587 | net: netdevsim: don&amp;#x27;t try to destroy PHC on VFs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26587</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: netdevsim: don't try to destroy PHC on VFs

PHC gets initialized in nsim_init_netdevsim(), which
is only called if (nsim_dev_port_is_pf()).

Create a counterpart of nsim_init_netdevsim() and
move the mock_phc_destroy() there.

This fixes a crash trying to destroy netdevsim with
VFs instantiated, as caught by running the devlink.sh test:

    BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 00000000000000b8
    RIP: 0010:mock_phc_destroy+0xd/0x30
    Call Trace:
     &lt;TASK&gt;
     nsim_destroy+0x4a/0x70 [netdevsim]
     __nsim_dev_port_del+0x47/0x70 [netdevsim]
     nsim_dev_reload_destroy+0x105/0x120 [netdevsim]
     nsim_drv_remove+0x2f/0xb0 [netdevsim]
     device_release_driver_internal+0x1a1/0x210
     bus_remove_device+0xd5/0x120
     device_del+0x159/0x490
     device_unregister+0x12/0x30
     del_device_store+0x11a/0x1a0 [netdevsim]
     kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x130/0x1d0
     vfs_write+0x30b/0x4b0
     ksys_write+0x69/0xf0
     do_syscall_64+0xcc/0x1e0
     entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6f/0x77</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26588 | LoongArch: BPF: Prevent out-of-bounds memory access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26588</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

LoongArch: BPF: Prevent out-of-bounds memory access

The test_tag test triggers an unhandled page fault:

  # ./test_tag
  [  130.640218] CPU 0 Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address ffff80001b898004, era == 9000000003137f7c, ra == 9000000003139e70
  [  130.640501] Oops[#3]:
  [  130.640553] CPU: 0 PID: 1326 Comm: test_tag Tainted: G      D    O       6.7.0-rc4-loong-devel-gb62ab1a397cf #47 61985c1d94084daa2432f771daa45b56b10d8d2a
  [  130.640764] Hardware name: QEMU QEMU Virtual Machine, BIOS unknown 2/2/2022
  [  130.640874] pc 9000000003137f7c ra 9000000003139e70 tp 9000000104cb4000 sp 9000000104cb7a40
  [  130.641001] a0 ffff80001b894000 a1 ffff80001b897ff8 a2 000000006ba210be a3 0000000000000000
  [  130.641128] a4 000000006ba210be a5 00000000000000f1 a6 00000000000000b3 a7 0000000000000000
  [  130.641256] t0 0000000000000000 t1 00000000000007f6 t2 0000000000000000 t3 9000000004091b70
  [  130.641387] t4 000000006ba210be t5 0000000000000004 t6 fffffffffffffff0 t7 90000000040913e0
  [  130.641512] t8 0000000000000005 u0 0000000000000dc0 s9 0000000000000009 s0 9000000104cb7ae0
  [  130.641641] s1 00000000000007f6 s2 0000000000000009 s3 0000000000000095 s4 0000000000000000
  [  130.641771] s5 ffff80001b894000 s6 ffff80001b897fb0 s7 9000000004090c50 s8 0000000000000000
  [  130.641900]    ra: 9000000003139e70 build_body+0x1fcc/0x4988
  [  130.642007]   ERA: 9000000003137f7c build_body+0xd8/0x4988
  [  130.642112]  CRMD: 000000b0 (PLV0 -IE -DA +PG DACF=CC DACM=CC -WE)
  [  130.642261]  PRMD: 00000004 (PPLV0 +PIE -PWE)
  [  130.642353]  EUEN: 00000003 (+FPE +SXE -ASXE -BTE)
  [  130.642458]  ECFG: 00071c1c (LIE=2-4,10-12 VS=7)
  [  130.642554] ESTAT: 00010000 [PIL] (IS= ECode=1 EsubCode=0)
  [  130.642658]  BADV: ffff80001b898004
  [  130.642719]  PRID: 0014c010 (Loongson-64bit, Loongson-3A5000)
  [  130.642815] Modules linked in: [last unloaded: bpf_testmod(O)]
  [  130.642924] Process test_tag (pid: 1326, threadinfo=00000000f7f4015f, task=000000006499f9fd)
  [  130.643062] Stack : 0000000000000000 9000000003380724 0000000000000000 0000000104cb7be8
  [  130.643213]         0000000000000000 25af8d9b6e600558 9000000106250ea0 9000000104cb7ae0
  [  130.643378]         0000000000000000 0000000000000000 9000000104cb7be8 90000000049f6000
  [  130.643538]         0000000000000090 9000000106250ea0 ffff80001b894000 ffff80001b894000
  [  130.643685]         00007ffffb917790 900000000313ca94 0000000000000000 0000000000000000
  [  130.643831]         ffff80001b894000 0000000000000ff7 0000000000000000 9000000100468000
  [  130.643983]         0000000000000000 0000000000000000 0000000000000040 25af8d9b6e600558
  [  130.644131]         0000000000000bb7 ffff80001b894048 0000000000000000 0000000000000000
  [  130.644276]         9000000104cb7be8 90000000049f6000 0000000000000090 9000000104cb7bdc
  [  130.644423]         ffff80001b894000 0000000000000000 00007ffffb917790 90000000032acfb0
  [  130.644572]         ...
  [  130.644629] Call Trace:
  [  130.644641] [&lt;9000000003137f7c&gt;] build_body+0xd8/0x4988
  [  130.644785] [&lt;900000000313ca94&gt;] bpf_int_jit_compile+0x228/0x4ec
  [  130.644891] [&lt;90000000032acfb0&gt;] bpf_prog_select_runtime+0x158/0x1b0
  [  130.645003] [&lt;90000000032b3504&gt;] bpf_prog_load+0x760/0xb44
  [  130.645089] [&lt;90000000032b6744&gt;] __sys_bpf+0xbb8/0x2588
  [  130.645175] [&lt;90000000032b8388&gt;] sys_bpf+0x20/0x2c
  [  130.645259] [&lt;9000000003f6ab38&gt;] do_syscall+0x7c/0x94
  [  130.645369] [&lt;9000000003121c5c&gt;] handle_syscall+0xbc/0x158
  [  130.645507]
  [  130.645539] Code: 380839f6  380831f9  28412bae &lt;24000ca6&gt; 004081ad  0014cb50  004083e8  02bff34c  58008e91
  [  130.645729]
  [  130.646418] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

On my machine, which has CONFIG_PAGE_SIZE_16KB=y, the test failed at
loading a BPF prog with 2039 instructions:

  prog = (struct bpf_prog *)ffff80001b894000
  insn = (struct bpf_insn *)(prog-&gt;insnsi)fff
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26589 | bpf: Reject variable offset alu on PTR_TO_FLOW_KEYS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26589</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Reject variable offset alu on PTR_TO_FLOW_KEYS

For PTR_TO_FLOW_KEYS, check_flow_keys_access() only uses fixed off
for validation. However, variable offset ptr alu is not prohibited
for this ptr kind. So the variable offset is not checked.

The following prog is accepted:

  func#0 @0
  0: R1=ctx() R10=fp0
  0: (bf) r6 = r1                       ; R1=ctx() R6_w=ctx()
  1: (79) r7 = *(u64 *)(r6 +144)        ; R6_w=ctx() R7_w=flow_keys()
  2: (b7) r8 = 1024                     ; R8_w=1024
  3: (37) r8 /= 1                       ; R8_w=scalar()
  4: (57) r8 &amp;= 1024                    ; R8_w=scalar(smin=smin32=0,
  smax=umax=smax32=umax32=1024,var_off=(0x0; 0x400))
  5: (0f) r7 += r8
  mark_precise: frame0: last_idx 5 first_idx 0 subseq_idx -1
  mark_precise: frame0: regs=r8 stack= before 4: (57) r8 &amp;= 1024
  mark_precise: frame0: regs=r8 stack= before 3: (37) r8 /= 1
  mark_precise: frame0: regs=r8 stack= before 2: (b7) r8 = 1024
  6: R7_w=flow_keys(smin=smin32=0,smax=umax=smax32=umax32=1024,var_off
  =(0x0; 0x400)) R8_w=scalar(smin=smin32=0,smax=umax=smax32=umax32=1024,
  var_off=(0x0; 0x400))
  6: (79) r0 = *(u64 *)(r7 +0)          ; R0_w=scalar()
  7: (95) exit

This prog loads flow_keys to r7, and adds the variable offset r8
to r7, and finally causes out-of-bounds access:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffc90014c80038
  [...]
  Call Trace:
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   bpf_dispatcher_nop_func include/linux/bpf.h:1231 [inline]
   __bpf_prog_run include/linux/filter.h:651 [inline]
   bpf_prog_run include/linux/filter.h:658 [inline]
   bpf_prog_run_pin_on_cpu include/linux/filter.h:675 [inline]
   bpf_flow_dissect+0x15f/0x350 net/core/flow_dissector.c:991
   bpf_prog_test_run_flow_dissector+0x39d/0x620 net/bpf/test_run.c:1359
   bpf_prog_test_run kernel/bpf/syscall.c:4107 [inline]
   __sys_bpf+0xf8f/0x4560 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5475
   __do_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5561 [inline]
   __se_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5559 [inline]
   __x64_sys_bpf+0x73/0xb0 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5559
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0x3f/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

Fix this by rejecting ptr alu with variable offset on flow_keys.
Applying the patch rejects the program with "R7 pointer arithmetic
on flow_keys prohibited".</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26590 | erofs: fix inconsistent per-file compression format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26590</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

erofs: fix inconsistent per-file compression format

EROFS can select compression algorithms on a per-file basis, and each
per-file compression algorithm needs to be marked in the on-disk
superblock for initialization.

However, syzkaller can generate inconsistent crafted images that use
an unsupported algorithmtype for specific inodes, e.g. use MicroLZMA
algorithmtype even it's not set in `sbi-&gt;available_compr_algs`.  This
can lead to an unexpected "BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference" if
the corresponding decompressor isn't built-in.

Fix this by checking against `sbi-&gt;available_compr_algs` for each
m_algorithmformat request.  Incorrect !erofs_sb_has_compr_cfgs preset
bitmap is now fixed together since it was harmless previously.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26591 | bpf: Fix re-attachment branch in bpf_tracing_prog_attach</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26591</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix re-attachment branch in bpf_tracing_prog_attach

The following case can cause a crash due to missing attach_btf:

1) load rawtp program
2) load fentry program with rawtp as target_fd
3) create tracing link for fentry program with target_fd = 0
4) repeat 3

In the end we have:

- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;dst_trampoline == NULL
- tgt_prog == NULL (because we did not provide target_fd to link_create)
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;attach_btf == NULL (the program was loaded with attach_prog_fd=X)
- the program was loaded for tgt_prog but we have no way to find out which one

    BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000058
    Call Trace:
     &lt;TASK&gt;
     ? __die+0x20/0x70
     ? page_fault_oops+0x15b/0x430
     ? fixup_exception+0x22/0x330
     ? exc_page_fault+0x6f/0x170
     ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x22/0x30
     ? bpf_tracing_prog_attach+0x279/0x560
     ? btf_obj_id+0x5/0x10
     bpf_tracing_prog_attach+0x439/0x560
     __sys_bpf+0x1cf4/0x2de0
     __x64_sys_bpf+0x1c/0x30
     do_syscall_64+0x41/0xf0
     entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76

Return -EINVAL in this situation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26592 | ksmbd: fix UAF issue in ksmbd_tcp_new_connection()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26592</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix UAF issue in ksmbd_tcp_new_connection()

The race is between the handling of a new TCP connection and
its disconnection. It leads to UAF on `struct tcp_transport` in
ksmbd_tcp_new_connection() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51389 | HertzBeat SnakeYAML Deser RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51389</link><description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. At the interface of `/define/yml`, SnakeYAML is used as a parser to parse yml content, but no security configuration is used, resulting in a YAML deserialization vulnerability. Version 1.4.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25828 | cmseasy V7.7.7.9 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in lib/admin/template_admin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25828</link><description>cmseasy V7.7.7.9 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in lib/admin/template_admin.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51388 | HertzBeat AviatorScript Inject RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51388</link><description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In `CalculateAlarm.java`, `AviatorEvaluator` is used to directly execute the expression function, and no security policy is configured, resulting in AviatorScript (which can execute any static method by default) script injection. Version 1.4.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51653 | Hertzbeat JMX JNDI RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51653</link><description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In the implementation of `JmxCollectImpl.java`, `JMXConnectorFactory.connect` is vulnerable to JNDI injection. The corresponding interface is `/api/monitor/detect`. If there is a URL field, the address will be used by default. When the URL is `service:jmx:rmi:///jndi/rmi://xxxxxxx:1099/localHikari`, it can be exploited to cause remote code execution. Version 1.4.1 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1563 | An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1563</link><description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme and a timeout race condition. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26281 | Upon scanning a JavaScript URI with the QR code scanner, an attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on the current top origin site...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26281</link><description>Upon scanning a JavaScript URI with the QR code scanner, an attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on the current top origin sites in the URL bar. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26282 | Using an AMP url with a canonical element, an attacker could have executed JavaScript from an opened bookmarked page. This vulnerability aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26282</link><description>Using an AMP url with a canonical element, an attacker could have executed JavaScript from an opened bookmarked page. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26283 | An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26283</link><description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26284 | Utilizing a 302 redirect, an attacker could have conducted a Universal Cross-Site Scripting (UXSS) on a victim website, if the victim had a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26284</link><description>Utilizing a 302 redirect, an attacker could have conducted a Universal Cross-Site Scripting (UXSS) on a victim website, if the victim had a link to the attacker's website. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51450 | baserCMS OS command injection vulnerability in Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51450</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 5.0.9, there is an OS Command Injection vulnerability in the site search feature of baserCMS. Version 5.0.9 contains a fix for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44379 | baserCMS Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Site search Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44379</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 5.0.9, there is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the site search feature. Version 5.0.9 contains a fix for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25851 | Netis WF2780 v2.1.40144 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the config_sequence parameter in other_para of cgite...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25851</link><description>Netis WF2780 v2.1.40144 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the config_sequence parameter in other_para of cgitest.cgi.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25850 | Netis WF2780 v2.1.40144 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the wps_ap_ssid5g parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25850</link><description>Netis WF2780 v2.1.40144 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the wps_ap_ssid5g parameter</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23094 | Flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /cover/addons/info_media_gallery/action/ed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23094</link><description>Flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /cover/addons/info_media_gallery/action/edit_addon_post.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25873 | Enhavo v0.13.1 was discovered to contain an HTML injection vulnerability in the Author text field under the Blockquote module. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25873</link><description>Enhavo v0.13.1 was discovered to contain an HTML injection vulnerability in the Author text field under the Blockquote module. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25874 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the New/Edit Article module of Enhavo CMS v0.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25874</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the New/Edit Article module of Enhavo CMS v0.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Create Tag text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25875 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Header module of Enhavo CMS v0.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or H...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25875</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Header module of Enhavo CMS v0.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Undertitle text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25876 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Header module of Enhavo CMS v0.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or H...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25876</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Header module of Enhavo CMS v0.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Title text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26445 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_place.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26445</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_place.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26349 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_translation.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26349</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_translation.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26350 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_contact_form_settings.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26350</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_contact_form_settings.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26351 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_place.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26351</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_place.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26352 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/add_places.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26352</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/add_places.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3966 | Openvswsitch: ovs-vswitch fails to recover after malformed geneve metadata packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3966</link><description>A flaw was found in Open vSwitch where multiple versions are vulnerable to crafted Geneve packets, which may result in a denial of service and invalid memory accesses. Triggering this issue requires that hardware offloading via the netlink path is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 12:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25021 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25021</link><description>IBM AIX 7.3, VIOS 4.1's Perl implementation could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.  IBM X-Force ID:  281320.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 11:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1104 | Temporary denial of service during a brute force attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1104</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can bypass the brute force prevention mechanism and disturb the webservice for all users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 11:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0220 | B&amp;amp;R products use insufficient communication encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0220</link><description>B&amp;R Automation Studio Upgrade Service and B&amp;R Technology Guarding use insufficient cryptography for communication to the upgrade and the licensing servers. A network-based attacker could exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the products or sniff sensitive data.



Missing Encryption of Sensitive Data, Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information, Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection'), Inadequate Encryption Strength vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation B&amp;R Automation Studio (Upgrade Service modules), B&amp;R Industrial Automation Technology Guarding.This issue affects B&amp;R Automation Studio: &lt;4.6; Technology Guarding: &lt;1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22393 | Apache Answer: Pixel Flood Attack by uploading the large pixel file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22393</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Pixel Flood Attack by uploading large pixel files will cause server out of memory. A logged-in user can cause such an attack by uploading an image when posting content.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23349 | Apache Answer: XSS vulnerability when submitting summary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

XSS attack when user enters summary. A logged-in user, when modifying their own submitted question, can input malicious code in the summary to create such an attack.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29179 | A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, Fortiproxy version 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29179</link><description>A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, Fortiproxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.10 allows attacker to denial of service via  specially crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29180 | A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 through 6.2.14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29180</link><description>A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 through 6.2.14, 6.0.0 through 6.0.16, FortiProxy 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, 2.0.0 through 2.0.12, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7 allows attacker to denial of service via specially crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29181 | A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29181</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 through 6.2.14, 6.0.0 through 6.0.16, FortiProxy 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, 2.0.0 through 2.0.12, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7, FortiPAM 1.0.0 through 1.0.3 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26578 | Apache Answer: Repeated submission at registration created duplicate users with the same name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26578</link><description>Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Repeated submission during registration resulted in the registration of the same user. When users register, if they rapidly submit multiple registrations using scripts, it can result in the creation of multiple user accounts simultaneously with the same name.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0903 | The User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0903</link><description>The User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page_submitted' 'link' value in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in the feedback submission page that will execute when a user clicks the link, while also pressing the command key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1053 | The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1053</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'email' action in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to email the attendees list to themselves.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26489 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Social block links' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26489</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Social block links' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Profile Name text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26490 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Simple module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26490</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Simple module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Title text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26491 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Media Gallery with description' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26491</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Media Gallery with description' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Gallery name text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25801 | SKINsoft S-Museum 7.02.3 allows XSS via the filename of an uploaded file. Unlike in CVE-2024-25802, the attack payload is in the name (not t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25801</link><description>SKINsoft S-Museum 7.02.3 allows XSS via the filename of an uploaded file. Unlike in CVE-2024-25802, the attack payload is in the name (not the content) of a file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26481 | Kirby CMS v4.1.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the URL parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26481</link><description>Kirby CMS v4.1.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the URL parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26482 | An HTML injection vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26482</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26483 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Profile Image module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26483</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Profile Image module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26484 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26484</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Link field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23136 | A maliciously crafted STP file when ASMKERN228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to dereference an untrusted pointer. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23136</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when ASMKERN228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to dereference an untrusted pointer. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23137 | A maliciously crafted STP or SLDPRT file when ODXSW_DLL.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to uninitialized variable. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23137</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP or SLDPRT file when ODXSW_DLL.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to uninitialized variable. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27283 | A vulnerability was discovered in Veritas eDiscovery Platform before 10.2.5. The application administrator can upload potentially malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27283</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in Veritas eDiscovery Platform before 10.2.5. The application administrator can upload potentially malicious files to arbitrary locations on the server on which the application is installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23135 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when ASMkern228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23135</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when ASMkern228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23134 | A maliciously crafted IGS file when tbb.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23134</link><description>A maliciously crafted IGS file when tbb.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23132 | A maliciously crafted STP file in atf_dwg_consumer.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23132</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file in atf_dwg_consumer.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23133 | A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23133</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23131 | A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMKERN228A.dll or ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23131</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMKERN228A.dll or ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23130 | A maliciously crafted SLDASM, or SLDPRT files in ODXSW_DLL.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23130</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDASM, or SLDPRT files in ODXSW_DLL.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23129 | A maliciously crafted MODEL 3DM, STP or SLDASM files in opennurbs.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23129</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL 3DM, STP or SLDASM files in opennurbs.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23128 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file in libodxdll.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by wr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23128</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file in libodxdll.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23127 | A maliciously crafted MODEL, SLDPRT or SLDASM file when parsed VCRUNTIME140.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Heap-based O...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23127</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL, SLDPRT or SLDASM file when parsed VCRUNTIME140.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23125 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23125</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23126 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23126</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23124 | A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23124</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23122 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23122</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23123 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23123</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23121 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23121</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25251 | code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 is suffers from Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25251</link><description>code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 is suffers from Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4895 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25423 | An issue in MAXON CINEMA 4D R2024.2.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted c4d_base.xdl64 file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25423</link><description>An issue in MAXON CINEMA 4D R2024.2.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted c4d_base.xdl64 file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23120 | A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23120</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6477 | Improper Privilege Management in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0410 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link><description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0861 | Improper Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1451 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1525 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1525</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0446 | A maliciously crafted STP, CATPART or MODEL file when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0446</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP, CATPART or MODEL file when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3509 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26148 | Querybook&amp;#x27;s Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability allows Privilege Elevation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26148</link><description>Querybook is a user interface for querying big data. Prior to version 3.31.1, there is a vulnerability in Querybook's rich text editor that enables users to input arbitrary URLs without undergoing necessary validation. This particular security flaw allows the use of `javascript:` protocol which can potentially trigger arbitrary client-side execution. The most extreme exploit of this flaw could occur when an admin user unknowingly clicks on a cross-site scripting URL, thereby unintentionally compromising admin role access to the attacker. A patch to rectify this issue has been introduced in Querybook version `3.31.1`. The fix is backward compatible and automatically fixes existing DataDocs. There are no known workarounds for this issue, except for manually checking each URL prior to clicking on them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26147 | Helm&amp;#x27;s Missing YAML Content Leads To Panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26147</link><description>Helm is a package manager for Charts for Kubernetes. Versions prior to 3.14.2 contain an uninitialized variable vulnerability when Helm parses index and plugin yaml files missing expected content. When either an `index.yaml` file or a plugins `plugin.yaml` file were missing all metadata a panic would occur in Helm. In the Helm SDK, this is found when using the `LoadIndexFile` or `DownloadIndexFile` functions in the `repo` package or the `LoadDir` function in the `plugin` package. For the Helm client this impacts functions around adding a repository and all Helm functions if a malicious plugin is added as Helm inspects all known plugins on each invocation. This issue has been resolved in Helm v3.14.2. If a malicious plugin has been added which is causing all Helm client commands to panic, the malicious plugin can be manually removed from the filesystem. If using Helm SDK versions prior to 3.14.2, calls to affected functions can use `recover` to catch the panic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52155 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/sauvegarde/run.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52155</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/sauvegarde/run.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the sauvegardes variable through the /admin/sauvegarde/run.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52153 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in /pmb/opac_css/includes/sessions.inc.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote unauthenticated attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52153</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in /pmb/opac_css/includes/sessions.inc.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands via the PmbOpac-LOGIN cookie value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52154 | File Upload vulnerability in pmb/camera_upload.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted PHT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52154</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in pmb/camera_upload.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted PHTML files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51828 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/convert/export.class.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier versions allows remote unauthenticated attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51828</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/convert/export.class.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier versions allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the query parameter in get_next_notice function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37177 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PMB Services PMB v.7.4.7 and before allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37177</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PMB Services PMB v.7.4.7 and before allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via the query parameter in the /admin/convert/export_z3950.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38844 | SQL injection vulnerability in PMB v.7.4.7 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the thesaurus parameter in exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38844</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PMB v.7.4.7 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the thesaurus parameter in export_skos.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25124 | Fiber has Insecure CORS Configuration, Allowing Wildcard Origin with Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25124</link><description>Fiber is a web framework written in go. Prior to version 2.52.1, the CORS middleware allows for insecure configurations that could potentially expose the application to multiple CORS-related vulnerabilities. Specifically, it allows setting the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header to a wildcard (`*`) while also having the Access-Control-Allow-Credentials set to true, which goes against recommended security best practices. The impact of this misconfiguration is high as it can lead to unauthorized access to sensitive user data and expose the system to various types of attacks listed in the PortSwigger article linked in the references. Version 2.52.1 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, users may manually validate the CORS configurations in their implementation to ensure that they do not allow a wildcard origin when credentials are enabled. The browser fetch api, as well as browsers and utilities that enforce CORS policies, are not affected by this.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24333 | A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC21 with firmware version US_AC21V1.0re_V16.03.08.15_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24333</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC21 with firmware version US_AC21V1.0re_V16.03.08.15_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to /goform/openSchedWifi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24334 | A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC23 with firmware version US_AC23V1.0re_V16.03.07.45_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24334</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC23 with firmware version US_AC23V1.0re_V16.03.07.45_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via schedStartTime parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24332 | A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC6 with firmware version US_AC6V5.0re_V03.03.02.01_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24332</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC6 with firmware version US_AC6V5.0re_V03.03.02.01_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to /goform/PowerSaveSet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23654 | discourse-ai admin-initiated SSRF when interacting with AI services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23654</link><description>discourse-ai is the AI plugin for the open-source discussion platform Discourse. Prior to commit 94ba0dadc2cf38e8f81c3936974c167219878edd, interactions with different AI services are vulnerable to admin-initiated SSRF attacks. Versions of the plugin that include commit 94ba0dadc2cf38e8f81c3936974c167219878edd contain a patch. As a workaround, one may disable the discourse-ai plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24331 | Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 816 with firmware version DIR-816_A2_v1.10CNB04 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24331</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 816 with firmware version DIR-816_A2_v1.10CNB04 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the urlAdd parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24330 | Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 882 with firmware version DIR882A1_FW130B06 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24330</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 882 with firmware version DIR882A1_FW130B06 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to /HNAP1/.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25461 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Terrasoft, Creatio Terrasoft CRM v.7.18.4.1532 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25461</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Terrasoft, Creatio Terrasoft CRM v.7.18.4.1532 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the terrasoft.axd component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6533 | Silicon Labs PC Controller Denial of Service Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6533</link><description>Malformed Device Reset Locally Command Class packets can be sent to the controller, causing the controller to assume the end device has left the network. After this, frames sent by the end device will not be acknowledged by the controller. This vulnerability exists in PC Controller v5.54.0, and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6640 | Silicon Labs PC Controller v5.54.0 and Earlier Denial of Service Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6640</link><description>Malformed S2 Nonce Get Command Class packets can be sent to crash PC Controller v5.54.0 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25249 | An issue in He3 App for macOS version 2.0.17, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectAr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25249</link><description>An issue in He3 App for macOS version 2.0.17, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26310 | Archer Platform 6.8 before 6.14 P2 (6.14.0.2) contains an improper access control vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26310</link><description>Archer Platform 6.8 before 6.14 P2 (6.14.0.2) contains an improper access control vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user could potentially exploit this to gain access to API information that should only be accessible with extra privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26311 | Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF1 (6.14.0.2.1) contains a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26311</link><description>Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF1 (6.14.0.2.1) contains a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this by tricking a victim application user into supplying malicious JavaScript code to the vulnerable web application. This code is then reflected to the victim and gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24476 | A buffer overflow in Wireshark before 4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the pan/addr_resolv.c, and ws_manuf_lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24476</link><description>A buffer overflow in Wireshark before 4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the pan/addr_resolv.c, and ws_manuf_lookup_str(), size components. NOTE: this is disputed by the vendor because neither release 4.2.0 nor any other release was affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24479 | A Buffer Overflow in Wireshark before 4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the wsutil/to_str.c, and format_fracti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24479</link><description>A Buffer Overflow in Wireshark before 4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the wsutil/to_str.c, and format_fractional_part_nsecs components. NOTE: this is disputed by the vendor because neither release 4.2.0 nor any other release was affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25381 | There is a Stored XSS Vulnerability in Emlog Pro 2.2.8 Article Publishing, due to non-filtering of quoted content.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25381</link><description>There is a Stored XSS Vulnerability in Emlog Pro 2.2.8 Article Publishing, due to non-filtering of quoted content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50975 | The TD Bank TD Advanced Dashboard client through 3.0.3 for macOS allows arbitrary code execution because of the lack of electron::fuses::IsR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50975</link><description>The TD Bank TD Advanced Dashboard client through 3.0.3 for macOS allows arbitrary code execution because of the lack of electron::fuses::IsRunAsNodeEnabled (i.e., ELECTRON_RUN_AS_NODE can be used in production). This makes it easier for a compromised process to access banking information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1707 | GARO WALLBOX GLB+ T2EV7 Software Update index.jsp#settings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1707</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GARO WALLBOX GLB+ T2EV7 0.5. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.jsp#settings of the component Software Update Handler. The manipulation of the argument Reference leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254397 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22473 | Uninitialized TRNG used for ECDSA after EM2/EM3 sleep for VSE devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22473</link><description>TRNG is used before initialization by ECDSA signing driver when exiting EM2/EM3 on Virtual Secure Vault (VSE) devices. This defect may allow Signature Spoofing by Key Recreation.This issue affects Gecko SDK through v4.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1706 | ZKTeco ZKBio Access IVS Department Name Search Bar cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1706</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ZKTeco ZKBio Access IVS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Department Name Search Bar. The manipulation with the input &lt;marquee&gt;hi leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254396. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25897 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCatalog.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25897</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCatalog.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25898 | A XSS vulnerability was found in the ChurchCRM v.5.5.0 functionality, edit your event, where malicious JS or HTML code can be inserted in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25898</link><description>A XSS vulnerability was found in the ChurchCRM v.5.5.0 functionality, edit your event, where malicious JS or HTML code can be inserted in the Event Sermon field in EventEditor.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25892 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 ConfirmReport.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the familyId GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25892</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 ConfirmReport.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the familyId GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25893 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCertificates.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25893</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCertificates.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25894 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 /EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EventCount POST parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25894</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 /EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EventCount POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25896 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EID POST parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25896</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EID POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25891 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRBidSheets.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25891</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRBidSheets.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25895 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChurchCRM 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25895</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChurchCRM 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the type parameter of /EventAttendance.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1212 | LoadMaster Pre-Authenticated OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1212</link><description>Unauthenticated remote attackers can access the system through the LoadMaster management interface, enabling arbitrary system command execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1704 | ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB crud delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB 5.2.2. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function save/delete of the file /adminapi/system/crud. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254392. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1705 | Shopwind Installation DefaultController.php actionCreate code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shopwind up to 4.6. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function actionCreate of the file /public/install/controllers/DefaultController.php of the component Installation. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254393 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26145 | Uninvited user is able to join and mark the attendance of the the private event</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26145</link><description>Discourse Calendar adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic on Discourse. Uninvited users are able to gain access to private events by crafting a request to update their attendance. This problem is resolved in commit dfc4fa15f340189f177a1d1ab2cc94ffed3c1190. As a workaround, one may use post visibility to limit access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1703 | ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB openfile absolute path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1703</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB 5.2.2. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function openfile of the file /adminapi/system/file/openfile. The manipulation leads to absolute path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254391. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26138 | License information is public, exposing instance id and license holder details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26138</link><description>The XWiki licensor application, which manages and enforce application licenses for paid extensions, includes the document `Licenses.Code.LicenseJSON` that provides information for admins regarding active licenses. This document is public and thus exposes this information publicly. The information includes the instance's id as well as first and last name and email of the license owner. This is a leak of information that isn't supposed to be public. The instance id allows associating data on the active installs data with the concrete XWiki instance. Active installs assures that "there's no way to find who's having a given UUID" (referring to the instance id). Further, the information who the license owner is and information about the obtained licenses can be used for targeted phishing attacks. Also, while user information is normally public, email addresses might only be displayed obfuscated,  depending on the configuration. This has been fixed in Application Licensing 1.24.2. There are no known workarounds besides upgrading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26133 | EventStoreDB Projections Subsystem has potential password leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26133</link><description>EventStoreDB (ESDB) is an operational database built to store events. A vulnerability has been identified in the projections subsystem in versions 20 prior to 20.10.6, 21 prior to 21.10.11, 22 prior to 22.10.5, and 23 prior to 23.10.1. Only database instances that use custom projections are affected by this vulnerability. User passwords may become accessible to those who have access to the chunk files on disk, and users who have read access to system streams. Only users in the `$admins` group can access system streams by default. ESDB 23.10.1, 22.10.5, 21.10.11, and 20.10.6 contain a patch for this issue. Users should upgrade EventStoreDB, reset the passwords for current and previous members of `$admins` and `$ops` groups, and, if a password was reused in any other system, reset it in those systems to a unique password to follow best practices. If an upgrade cannot be done immediately, reset the passwords for current and previous members of `$admins` and `$ops` groups. Avoid creating custom projections until the patch has been applied.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1702 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1702</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254390 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26130 | cryptography NULL pointer deference with pkcs12.serialize_key_and_certificates when called with a non-matching certificate and private key and an hmac_hash override</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26130</link><description>cryptography is a package designed to expose cryptographic primitives and recipes to Python developers. Starting in version 38.0.0 and prior to version 42.0.4, if `pkcs12.serialize_key_and_certificates` is called with both a certificate whose public key did not match the provided private key and an `encryption_algorithm` with `hmac_hash` set (via `PrivateFormat.PKCS12.encryption_builder().hmac_hash(...)`, then a NULL pointer dereference would occur, crashing the Python process. This has been resolved in version 42.0.4, the first version in which a `ValueError` is properly raised.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25117 | php-svg-lib lacks path validation on font through SVG inline styles </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25117</link><description>php-svg-lib is a scalable vector graphics (SVG) file parsing/rendering library. Prior to version 0.5.2, php-svg-lib fails to validate that font-family doesn't contain a PHAR url, which might leads to RCE on PHP &lt; 8.0, and doesn't validate if external references are allowed. This might leads to bypass of restrictions or RCE on projects that are using it, if they do not strictly revalidate the fontName that is passed by php-svg-lib. The `Style::fromAttributes(`), or the `Style::parseCssStyle()` should check the content of the `font-family` and prevents it to use a PHAR url, to avoid passing an invalid and dangerous `fontName` value to other libraries. The same check as done in the `Style::fromStyleSheets` might be reused. Libraries using this library as a dependency might be vulnerable to some bypass of restrictions, or even remote code execution, if they do not double check the value of the `fontName` that is passed by php-svg-lib. Version 0.5.2 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20325 | A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20325</link><description>A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modify data in a repository that belongs to an internal service on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient access control implementations on cluster configuration CLI requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a cluster configuration CLI request to specific directories on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and modify data that is handled by an internal service on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23346 | pymatgen arbitrary code execution when parsing a maliciously crafted JonesFaithfulTransformation transformation_string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23346</link><description>Pymatgen (Python Materials Genomics) is an open-source Python library for materials analysis. A critical security vulnerability exists in the `JonesFaithfulTransformation.from_transformation_str()` method within the `pymatgen` library prior to version 2024.2.20. This method insecurely utilizes `eval()` for processing input, enabling execution of arbitrary code when parsing untrusted input. Version 2024.2.20 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24478 | An issue in Wireshark before 4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the packet-bgp.c, dissect_bgp_open(tvbuff_t*tvb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24478</link><description>An issue in Wireshark before 4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the packet-bgp.c, dissect_bgp_open(tvbuff_t*tvb, proto_tree*tree, packet_info*pinfo), optlen components. NOTE: this is disputed by the vendor because neither release 4.2.0 nor any other release was affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25288 | SLIMS (Senayan Library Management Systems) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via pop-scope-vocabolary.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25288</link><description>SLIMS (Senayan Library Management Systems) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via pop-scope-vocabolary.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46241 | Potential account take over due to unverified emails from Microsoft Identity Platform </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46241</link><description>`discourse-microsoft-auth` is a plugin that enables authentication via Microsoft. On sites with the `discourse-microsoft-auth` plugin enabled, an attack can potentially take control of a victim's Discourse account. Sites that have configured their application's account type to any options other than `Accounts in this organizational directory only (O365 only - Single tenant)` are vulnerable. This vulnerability has been patched in commit c40665f44509724b64938c85def9fb2e79f62ec8 of `discourse-microsoft-auth`. A `microsoft_auth:revoke` rake task has also been added which will deactivate and log out all users that have connected their accounts to Microsoft. User API keys as well as API keys created by those users will also be revoked. The rake task will also remove the connection records to Microsoft for those users. This will allow affected users to re-verify their account emails as well as reconnect their Discourse account to Microsoft for authentication. As a workaround, disable the `discourse-microsoft-auth` plugin by setting the `microsoft_auth_enabled` site setting to `false`. Run the `microsoft_auth:log_out_users` rake task to log out all users with associated Microsoft accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49100 | Trusted Firmware-A (TF-A) before 2.10 has a potential read out-of-bounds in the SDEI service. The input parameter passed in register x1 is n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49100</link><description>Trusted Firmware-A (TF-A) before 2.10 has a potential read out-of-bounds in the SDEI service. The input parameter passed in register x1 is not validated well enough in the function sdei_interrupt_bind. The parameter is passed to a call to plat_ic_get_interrupt_type. It can be any arbitrary value passing checks in the function plat_ic_is_sgi. A compromised Normal World (Linux kernel) can enable a root-privileged attacker to issue arbitrary SMC calls. Using this primitive, he can control the content of registers x0 through x6, which are used to send parameters to TF-A. Out-of-bounds addresses can be read in the context of TF-A (EL3). Because the read value is never returned to non-secure memory or in registers, no leak is possible. An attacker can still crash TF-A, however.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22220 | An issue was discovered in Terminalfour 7.4 through 7.4.0004 QP3 and 8 through 8.3.19, and Formbank through 2.1.10-FINAL. Unauthenticated St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22220</link><description>An issue was discovered in Terminalfour 7.4 through 7.4.0004 QP3 and 8 through 8.3.19, and Formbank through 2.1.10-FINAL. Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting can occur, with resultant Admin Session Hijacking. The attack vectors are Form Builder and Form Preview.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45169 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A URL Redirection to an Untrusted Site (Open Redirect) can occur under ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45169</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A URL Redirection to an Untrusted Site (Open Redirect) can occur under the /api/v1/notification/createnotification endpoint, allowing an authenticated user to send an arbitrary push notification to any other user of the system. This push notification can include an (invisible) clickable link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45177 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. An Observable Response Discrepancy can occur under the /api/v1/vdeskint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45177</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. An Observable Response Discrepancy can occur under the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/user/isenableuser endpoint, the /api/v1/sharedsearch?search={NAME]+{SURNAME] endpoint, and the /login endpoint. The web application provides different responses to incoming requests in a way that reveals internal state information to an unauthorized actor outside of the intended control sphere.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45179 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A basic XSS vulnerability exists under the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/tod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45179</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A basic XSS vulnerability exists under the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/todo/createorupdate endpoint via the title parameter and /dashboard/reminders. A remote user (authenticated to the product) can store arbitrary HTML code in the reminder section title in order to corrupt the web page (for example, by creating phishing sections to exfiltrate victims' credentials).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1474 | WS_FTP Server Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in Administrative Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1474</link><description>In WS_FTP Server versions before 8.8.5, reflected cross-site scripting issues have been identified on various user supplied inputs on the WS_FTP Server administrative interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1709 | Authentication bypass using an alternate path or channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1709</link><description>ConnectWise ScreenConnect 23.9.7 and prior are affected by an Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel

 vulnerability, which may allow an attacker direct access to confidential information or 

critical systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1700 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1700</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument username with the input &lt;script&gt;alert("xss")&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254388. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1701 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System edit.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1701</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254389 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1708 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory (“path traversal”)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1708</link><description>ConnectWise ScreenConnect 23.9.7 and prior are affected by path-traversal vulnerability, which may allow an attacker 

the ability to execute remote code or directly impact confidential data or critical systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26582 | net: tls: fix use-after-free with partial reads and async decrypt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26582</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: tls: fix use-after-free with partial reads and async decrypt

tls_decrypt_sg doesn't take a reference on the pages from clear_skb,
so the put_page() in tls_decrypt_done releases them, and we trigger
a use-after-free in process_rx_list when we try to read from the
partially-read skb.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26583 | tls: fix race between async notify and socket close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26583</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: fix race between async notify and socket close

The submitting thread (one which called recvmsg/sendmsg)
may exit as soon as the async crypto handler calls complete()
so any code past that point risks touching already freed data.

Try to avoid the locking and extra flags altogether.
Have the main thread hold an extra reference, this way
we can depend solely on the atomic ref counter for
synchronization.

Don't futz with reiniting the completion, either, we are now
tightly controlling when completion fires.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26584 | net: tls: handle backlogging of crypto requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26584</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: tls: handle backlogging of crypto requests

Since we're setting the CRYPTO_TFM_REQ_MAY_BACKLOG flag on our
requests to the crypto API, crypto_aead_{encrypt,decrypt} can return
 -EBUSY instead of -EINPROGRESS in valid situations. For example, when
the cryptd queue for AESNI is full (easy to trigger with an
artificially low cryptd.cryptd_max_cpu_qlen), requests will be enqueued
to the backlog but still processed. In that case, the async callback
will also be called twice: first with err == -EINPROGRESS, which it
seems we can just ignore, then with err == 0.

Compared to Sabrina's original patch this version uses the new
tls_*crypt_async_wait() helpers and converts the EBUSY to
EINPROGRESS to avoid having to modify all the error handling
paths. The handling is identical.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26585 | tls: fix race between tx work scheduling and socket close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26585</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: fix race between tx work scheduling and socket close

Similarly to previous commit, the submitting thread (recvmsg/sendmsg)
may exit as soon as the async crypto handler calls complete().
Reorder scheduling the work before calling complete().
This seems more logical in the first place, as it's
the inverse order of what the submitting thread will do.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33843 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33843</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  256544.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50955 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50955</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow an authenticated privileged user to obtain the absolute path of the web server installation which could aid in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275777.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22778 | HackMD CodiMD &lt;2.5.2 is vulnerable to Denial of Service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22778</link><description>HackMD CodiMD &lt;2.5.2 is vulnerable to Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47795 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Document and Media widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.18 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47795</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Document and Media widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.18 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 update 18 through 92 allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a document's “Title” text field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7235 | The OpenVPN GUI installer before version 2.6.9 did not set the proper access control restrictions to the installation directory of OpenVPN b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7235</link><description>The OpenVPN GUI installer before version 2.6.9 did not set the proper access control restrictions to the installation directory of OpenVPN binaries when using a non-standard installation path, which allows an attacker to replace binaries to run arbitrary executables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 10:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24798 | WordPress Debug Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24798</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SoniNow Team Debug.This issue affects Debug: from n/a through 1.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52442 | ksmbd: validate session id and tree id in compound request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52442</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: validate session id and tree id in compound request

`smb2_get_msg()` in smb2_get_ksmbd_tcon() and smb2_check_user_session()
will always return the first request smb2 header in a compound request.
if `SMB2_TREE_CONNECT_HE` is the first command in compound request, will
return 0, i.e. The tree id check is skipped.
This patch use ksmbd_req_buf_next() to get current command in compound.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24802 | WordPress JTRT Responsive Tables Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24802</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in John Tendik JTRT Responsive Tables.This issue affects JTRT Responsive Tables: from n/a through 4.1.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52440 | ksmbd: fix slub overflow in ksmbd_decode_ntlmssp_auth_blob()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52440</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix slub overflow in ksmbd_decode_ntlmssp_auth_blob()

If authblob-&gt;SessionKey.Length is bigger than session key
size(CIFS_KEY_SIZE), slub overflow can happen in key exchange codes.
cifs_arc4_crypt copy to session key array from SessionKey from client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52441 | ksmbd: fix out of bounds in init_smb2_rsp_hdr()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52441</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix out of bounds in init_smb2_rsp_hdr()

If client send smb2 negotiate request and then send smb1 negotiate
request, init_smb2_rsp_hdr is called for smb1 negotiate request since
need_neg is set to false. This patch ignore smb1 packets after -&gt;need_neg
is set to false.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24837 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FG PrestaShop, FG Drupal and FG Joomla WordPress plugins </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24837</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Frédéric GILLES FG PrestaShop to WooCommerce, Frédéric GILLES FG Drupal to WordPress, Frédéric GILLES FG Joomla to WordPress.This issue affects FG PrestaShop to WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.44.3; FG Drupal to WordPress: from n/a through 3.67.0; FG Joomla to WordPress: from n/a through 4.15.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24843 | WordPress PowerPack Pro for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt; 2.10.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24843</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PowerPack Addons for Elementor PowerPack Pro for Elementor.This issue affects PowerPack Pro for Elementor: from n/a before 2.10.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24849 | WordPress Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24849</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mark Stockton Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin.This issue affects Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24872 | WordPress Themify Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24872</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Themify Themify Builder.This issue affects Themify Builder: from n/a through 7.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24876 | WordPress Admin Menu Editor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24876</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Janis Elsts Admin Menu Editor.This issue affects Admin Menu Editor: from n/a through 1.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0593 | The Simple Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data| due to insufficient authorization checking on the fe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0593</link><description>The Simple Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data| due to insufficient authorization checking on the fetch_quick_job() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to fetch arbitrary posts, which can be password protected or private and contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1081 | The 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bookmark feature...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1081</link><description>The 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bookmark feature in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25904 | WordPress TinyMCE Professional Formats and Styles Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25904</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in David Stockl TinyMCE and TinyMCE Advanced Professsional Formats and Styles.This issue affects TinyMCE and TinyMCE Advanced Professsional Formats and Styles: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25905 | WordPress Multi Step Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25905</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mondula GmbH Multi Step Form.This issue affects Multi Step Form: from n/a through 1.7.18.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42823 | The issue was resolved by sanitizing logging This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42823</link><description>The issue was resolved by sanitizing logging This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42835 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker may be able to access user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42835</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker may be able to access user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42839 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42839</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42848 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42848</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42853 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42853</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42858 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42858</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42873 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42873</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42878 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42878</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42946 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42946</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42834 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42834</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42836 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42836</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2. An attacker may be able to access connected network volumes mounted in the home directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42838 | An access issue was addressed with improvements to the sandbox. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42838</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improvements to the sandbox. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code out of its sandbox or with certain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42840 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42840</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42843 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42843</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, Safari 17.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42855 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42855</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to silently persist an Apple ID on an erased device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42859 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42859</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42860 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42860</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42877 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42877</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42889 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42889</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42928 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to gain elevated pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42928</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to gain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42939 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user's private browsing activity may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42939</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user's private browsing activity may be unexpectedly saved in the App Privacy Report.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42942 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42942</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42945 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may gain unauthorized acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42945</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may gain unauthorized access to Bluetooth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42951 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user may be unable to delete br...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42951</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user may be unable to delete browsing history items.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42952 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42952</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1. An app with root privileges may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42953 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42953</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22235 | VMware Aria Operations contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with administrative access to the local system...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22235</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with administrative access to the local system can escalate privileges to 'root'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1501 | The Database Reset plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.22. This is due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1501</link><description>The Database Reset plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.22. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the install_wpr() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install the WP Reset Plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1562 | The WooCommerce Google Sheet Connector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1562</link><description>The WooCommerce Google Sheet Connector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the execute_post_data function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25151 | The Calendar module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25151</link><description>The Calendar module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions does not escape user supplied data in the default notification email template, which allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the title of a calendar event or the user's name. This may lead to a content spoofing or cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks depending on the capability of the receiver's mail client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1669 | Out of bounds memory access in Blink in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1669</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in Blink in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1670 | Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1670</link><description>Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1671 | Inappropriate implementation in Site Isolation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1671</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Site Isolation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security policy via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1672 | Inappropriate implementation in Content Security Policy in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1672</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Content Security Policy in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security policy via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1673 | Use after free in Accessibility in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1673</link><description>Use after free in Accessibility in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1674 | Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass navigation restrictio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1674</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass navigation restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1675 | Insufficient policy enforcement in Download in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass filesystem restricti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1675</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in Download in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass filesystem restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1676 | Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to spoof security UI via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1676</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to spoof security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40191 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the instance settings for Accounts in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.44 through 7.4.3.97, and Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40191</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the instance settings for Accounts in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.44 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 update 44 through 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the “Blocked Email Domains” text field</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1108 | The Plugin Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_ini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1108</link><description>The Plugin Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_init() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the settings of the plugin, which can also cause a denial of service due to a misconfiguration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42498 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Language Override edit screen in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.97, and Life...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42498</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Language Override edit screen in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 5, and 7.4 update 4 through 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the _com_liferay_portal_language_override_web_internal_portlet_PLOPortlet_key parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26269 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Frontend JS module's portlet.js in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.37, and Liferay DXP 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26269</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Frontend JS module's portlet.js in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.37, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 38, 7.3 before update 11, 7.2 before fix pack 20, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the anchor (hash) part of a URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26266 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.13, and older unsupported versions, and Lif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26266</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.13, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 10, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allow remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the first/middle/last name text field of the user who creates an entry in the (1) Announcement widget, or (2) Alerts widget.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42496 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the add assignees to a role page in Liferay Portal 7.3.3 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42496</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the add assignees to a role page in Liferay Portal 7.3.3 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, 7.4 GA through update 92, and 7.3 before update 34 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the _com_liferay_roles_admin_web_portlet_RolesAdminPortlet_tabs2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1631 | agent-js: Insecure Key Generation in `Ed25519KeyIdentity.generate`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1631</link><description>Impact: The library offers a function to generate an ed25519 key pair via Ed25519KeyIdentity.generate with an optional param to provide a 32 byte seed value, which will then be used as the secret key. When no seed value is provided, it is expected that the library generates the secret key using secure randomness. However, a recent change broke this guarantee and uses an insecure seed for key pair generation. Since the private key of this identity (535yc-uxytb-gfk7h-tny7p-vjkoe-i4krp-3qmcl-uqfgr-cpgej-yqtjq-rqe) is compromised, one could lose funds associated with the principal on ledgers or lose access to a canister where this principal is the controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25603 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Dynamic Data Mapping module's DDMForm in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and ol...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25603</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Dynamic Data Mapping module's DDMForm in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the instanceId parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25152 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Message Board widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25152</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Message Board widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the filename of an attachment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25601 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Expando module's geolocation custom fields in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and old...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25601</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Expando module's geolocation custom fields in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the name text field of a geolocation custom field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25602 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Users Admin module's edit user page in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25602</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Users Admin module's edit user page in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into an organization’s “Name” text field</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25147 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HtmlUtil.escapeJsLink in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25147</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HtmlUtil.escapeJsLink in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via crafted javascript: style links.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>