<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 16:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-0994 | Trimble Cityworks versions prior to 23.10 are vulnerable to a deserialization vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated user to perfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0994</link><description>Trimble Cityworks versions prior to 23.10 are vulnerable to a deserialization vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated user to perform a remote code execution attack against a customer’s Microsoft Internet Information Services (IIS) web server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 16:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-31764 | Apache ShardingSphere ElasticJob-UI allows RCE via event trace data source JDBC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31764</link><description>The Lite UI of Apache ShardingSphere ElasticJob-UI allows an attacker to perform RCE by constructing a special JDBC URL of H2 database. This issue affects Apache ShardingSphere ElasticJob-UI version 3.0.1 and prior versions. This vulnerability has been fixed in ElasticJob-UI 3.0.2.
The premise of this attack is that the attacker has obtained the account and password. Otherwise, the attacker cannot perform this attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 14:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5878 | OneWireless command injection possible when updating firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5878</link><description>Honeywell OneWireless 

Wireless Device Manager (WDM) for the following versions R310.x, R320.x, R321.x, R322.1, R322.2, R323.x, R330.1 contains a command injection vulnerability. An attacker who is authenticated could use the firmware update process to potentially exploit the vulnerability, leading to a command injection. Honeywell recommends updating to 

 R322.3, R330.2 or the most recent version of this product2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 14:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1074 | Webkul QloApps URL mylogout cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1074</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Webkul QloApps 1.6.1. Affected is the function logout of the file /en/?mylogout of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure. They are aware about it and are working on resolving it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24911 | Out of Bounds read in the CPCA process on Check Point Management Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24911</link><description>In rare scenarios, the cpca process on the Security Management Server / Domain Management Server may exit unexpectedly, creating a core dump file. When the cpca process is down, VPN and SIC connectivity issues may occur if the CRL is not present in the Security Gateway's CRL cache.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1076 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in Holded</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1076</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (Stored XSS) vulnerability has been found in the Holded application. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to store a JavaScript payload within the editable ‘name’ and ‘icon’ parameters of the Activities functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12602 | Identity verification vulnerability in the ParamWatcher module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12602</link><description>Identity verification vulnerability in the ParamWatcher module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57954 | Permission verification vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57954</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57955 | Arbitrary write vulnerability in the Gallery module 
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57955</link><description>Arbitrary write vulnerability in the Gallery module 
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57956 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the interpreter string module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57956</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the interpreter string module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57957 | Vulnerability of improper log information control in the UI framework module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57957</link><description>Vulnerability of improper log information control in the UI framework module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57958 | Out-of-bounds array read vulnerability in the FFRT module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perfor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57958</link><description>Out-of-bounds array read vulnerability in the FFRT module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57959 | Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability in the display module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57959</link><description>Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability in the display module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57960 | Input verification vulnerability in the ExternalStorageProvider module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57960</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the ExternalStorageProvider module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57961 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the emcom module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57961</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the emcom module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57962 | Vulnerability of incomplete verification information in the VPN service module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57962</link><description>Vulnerability of incomplete verification information in the VPN service module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0982 | Sandbox Escape in Google Cloud Application Integration&amp;#x27;s JavaScript Task (Rhino Engine)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0982</link><description>Sandbox escape in the JavaScript Task feature of Google Cloud Application Integration allows an actor to execute arbitrary unsandboxed code via crafted JavaScript code executed by the Rhino engine. Effective January 24, 2025, Application Integration will no longer support Rhino as the JavaScript execution engine. No further fix actions are needed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37358 | Apache James: denial of service through the use of IMAP literals</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37358</link><description>Similarly to CVE-2024-34055, Apache James is vulnerable to denial of service through the abuse of IMAP literals from both authenticated and unauthenticated users, which could be used to cause unbounded memory allocation and very long computations

Version 3.7.6 and 3.8.2 restrict such illegitimate use of IMAP literals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45626 | Apache James: denial of service through JMAP HTML to text conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45626</link><description>Apache James server JMAP HTML to text plain implementation in versions below 3.8.2 and 3.7.6 is subject to unbounded memory consumption that can result in a denial of service.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.7.6 and 3.8.2, which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0859 | Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid &amp;lt;= 1.27.6 - Path Traversal to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read via template_via_url Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0859</link><description>The Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid – Visual Drag and Drop Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.27.6 via the template_via_url() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 09:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20094 | Unprotected Windows messaging channel ('Shatter') issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20094</link><description>Unprotected Windows messaging channel ('Shatter') issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker sends a specially crafted message to the specific process of the Windows system where the product is running, arbitrary code may be executed with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22894 | Unprotected Windows messaging channel ('Shatter') issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22894</link><description>Unprotected Windows messaging channel ('Shatter') issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker sends a specially crafted message to the specific process of the Windows system where the product is running, arbitrary files in the system may be altered. As a result, an arbitrary DLL may be executed with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23236 | Buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker performs a specific operation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23236</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker performs a specific operation, SYSTEM privilege of the Windows system where the product is running may be obtained.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24483 | NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker provides specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24483</link><description>NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker provides specially crafted data to the specific process of the Windows system where the product is running, the system may cause a Blue Screen of Death (BSOD), and as a result, cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24845 | Improper neutralization of argument delimiters in a command ('Argument Injection') issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24845</link><description>Improper neutralization of argument delimiters in a command ('Argument Injection') issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker provides specially crafted data to the specific process of the Windows system where the product is running, the system may cause a Blue Screen of Death (BSOD), and as a result, cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22890 | Execution with unnecessary privileges issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker performs a spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22890</link><description>Execution with unnecessary privileges issue exists in Defense Platform Home Edition Ver.3.9.51.x and earlier. If an attacker performs a specific operation, SYSTEM privilege of the Windows system where the product is running may be obtained.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13487 | CURCY – Multi Currency for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via get_products_price Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13487</link><description>The The CURCY – Multi Currency for WooCommerce – The best free currency exchange plugin – Run smoothly on WooCommerce 9.x plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via the get_products_price() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0522 | LikeBot – Decentralized like-system &amp;lt;= 0.85 - Admin+ Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0522</link><description>The LikeBot  WordPress plugin through 0.85 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51547 | Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51547</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in ABB ASPECT-Enterprise, ABB NEXUS Series, ABB MATRIX Series.This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 04:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49814 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49814</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0 through 10.0.3 could allow a locally authenticated user to increase their privileges due to execution with unnecessary privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51450 | IBM Security Verify Directory Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51450</link><description>IBM Security Verify Directory 10.0.0 through 10.0.3 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0799 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0799</link><description>IBM App Connect enterprise 12.0.1.0 through 12.0.12.10 and 13.0.1.0 through 13.0.2.1 could allow an authenticated user to write to an arbitrary file on the system during bar configuration deployment due to improper pathname limitations on restricted directories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49800 | IBM ApplinX Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49800</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 stores sensitive information in cleartext in memory that could be obtained by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49798 | IBM ApplinX Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49798</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49796 | IBM ApplinX Clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49796</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49797 | IBM ApplinX Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49797</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49794 | IBM ApplinX Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49794</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49795 | IBM ApplinX Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49795</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1066 | CVE-2025-1066</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1066</link><description>OpenPLC_V3 contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability, which could be leveraged for malvertising or phishing campaigns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49792 | IBM ApplinX Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49792</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49793 | IBM ApplinX Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49793</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49791 | IBM ApplinX Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49791</link><description>IBM ApplinX 11.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56472 | IBM Aspera Shares Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56472</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6  is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56473 | IBM Aspera Shares Data Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56473</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6  could allow an attacker to spoof their IP address, which is written to log files, due to improper verification of 'Client-IP' headers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56470 | IBM Aspera Shares Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56470</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6  is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56471 | IBM Aspera Shares Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56471</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6  is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38318 | IBM Aspera Shares HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38318</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38317 | IBM Aspera Shares Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38317</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6  is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38316 | IBM Aspera Shares Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38316</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.0 through 1.10.0 PL6 does not properly rate limit the frequency that an authenticated user can send emails, which could result in email flooding or a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57598 | A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in Bento4 1.6.0-641 in function AP4_TfraAtom() of Ap4TfraAtom.cpp w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57598</link><description>A floating point exception (divide-by-zero) vulnerability was discovered in Bento4 1.6.0-641 in function AP4_TfraAtom() of Ap4TfraAtom.cpp which allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54853 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified affecting Skybox Change Manager versions 13.2.170 and earlier that allows r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54853</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified affecting Skybox Change Manager versions 13.2.170 and earlier that allows remote authenticated users to store malicious payloads in the affected field that would then execute in an unsuspecting victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57068 | A prototype pollution in the lib.mutateMergeDeep function of @tanstack/form-core v0.35.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57068</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.mutateMergeDeep function of @tanstack/form-core v0.35.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57520 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in asterisk v22 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the action_createconfig function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57520</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in asterisk v22 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the action_createconfig function</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57699 | A security issue was found in Netplex Json-smart 2.5.0 through 2.5.1. When loading a specially crafted JSON input, containing a large number...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57699</link><description>A security issue was found in Netplex Json-smart 2.5.0 through 2.5.1. When loading a specially crafted JSON input, containing a large number of ’{’, a stack exhaustion can be trigger, which could allow an attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS). This issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-1370.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36084 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SourceCodester Responsive E-Learning System 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject sql query in /elearning/del...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36084</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in SourceCodester Responsive E-Learning System 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject sql query in /elearning/delete_teacher_students.php?id= parameter via id field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57063 | A prototype pollution in the lib function of php-date-formatter v1.3.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57063</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib function of php-date-formatter v1.3.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57064 | A prototype pollution in the lib.setValue function of @syncfusion/ej2-spreadsheet v27.2.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57064</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.setValue function of @syncfusion/ej2-spreadsheet v27.2.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57067 | A prototype pollution in the lib.parse function of dot-qs v0.2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57067</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.parse function of dot-qs v0.2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57069 | A prototype pollution in the lib function of expand-object v0.4.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57069</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib function of expand-object v0.4.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57071 | A prototype pollution in the lib.combine function of php-parser v3.2.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57071</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.combine function of php-parser v3.2.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57065 | A prototype pollution in the lib.createPath function of utile v0.3.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57065</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.createPath function of utile v0.3.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57066 | A prototype pollution in the lib.deep function of @ndhoule/defaults v2.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57066</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.deep function of @ndhoule/defaults v2.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57072 | A prototype pollution in the lib.requireFromString function of module-from-string v3.3.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57072</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.requireFromString function of module-from-string v3.3.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57078 | A prototype pollution in the lib.merge function of cli-util v1.1.27 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57078</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.merge function of cli-util v1.1.27 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57084 | A prototype pollution in the function lib.parse of dot-properties v1.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57084</link><description>A prototype pollution in the function lib.parse of dot-properties v1.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57074 | A prototype pollution in the lib.merge function of xe-utils v3.5.31 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57074</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.merge function of xe-utils v3.5.31 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57075 | A prototype pollution in the lib.Logger function of eazy-logger v4.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57075</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.Logger function of eazy-logger v4.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57076 | A prototype pollution in the lib.post function of ajax-request v1.2.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57076</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.post function of ajax-request v1.2.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57077 | The latest version of utils-extend (1.0.8) is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution through the entry function(s) lib.extend. An attacker can su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57077</link><description>The latest version of utils-extend (1.0.8) is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution through the entry function(s) lib.extend. An attacker can supply a payload with Object.prototype setter to introduce or modify properties within the global prototype chain, causing denial of service (DoS) a the minimum consequence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57080 | A prototype pollution in the lib.install function of vxe-table v4.8.10 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57080</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.install function of vxe-table v4.8.10 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57086 | A prototype pollution in the function fieldsToJson of node-opcua-alarm-condition v2.134.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57086</link><description>A prototype pollution in the function fieldsToJson of node-opcua-alarm-condition v2.134.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48394 | A Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability has been identified in the driver of the NDD Print solution, which could allow an unpr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48394</link><description>A Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability has been identified in the driver of the NDD Print solution, which could allow an unprivileged user to exploit this flaw and gain SYSTEM-level access on the device. The vulnerability affects version 5.24.3 and before of the software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57079 | A prototype pollution in the lib.deepMerge function of @zag-js/core v0.50.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplyin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57079</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.deepMerge function of @zag-js/core v0.50.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57081 | A prototype pollution in the lib.fromQuery function of underscore-contrib v0.3.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via sup...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57081</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.fromQuery function of underscore-contrib v0.3.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57082 | A prototype pollution in the lib.createUploader function of @rpldy/uploader v1.8.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57082</link><description>A prototype pollution in the lib.createUploader function of @rpldy/uploader v1.8.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57085 | A prototype pollution in the function deepMerge of @stryker-mutator/util v8.6.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57085</link><description>A prototype pollution in the function deepMerge of @stryker-mutator/util v8.6.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24803 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in MobSF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24803</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is an automated, all-in-one mobile application (Android/iOS/Windows) pen-testing, malware analysis and security assessment framework. According to Apple's documentation for bundle ID's, it must contain only alphanumeric characters (A–Z, a–z, and 0–9), hyphens (-), and periods (.). However, an attacker can manually modify this value in the `Info.plist` file and add special characters to the `CFBundleIdentifier` value. The `dynamic_analysis.html` file does not sanitize the received bundle value from Corellium and as a result, it is possible to break the HTML context and achieve Stored XSS. This issue has been addressed in version 4.3.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24804 | Partial Denial of Service (DoS) in MobSF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24804</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is an automated, all-in-one mobile application (Android/iOS/Windows) pen-testing, malware analysis and security assessment framework. According to Apple's documentation for bundle ID's, it must contain only alphanumeric characters (A–Z, a–z, and 0–9), hyphens (-), and periods (.). However, an attacker can manually modify this value in the `Info.plist` file and add special characters to the `CFBundleIdentifier` value. When the application parses the wrong characters in the bundle ID, it encounters an error. As a result, it will not display content and will throw a 500 error instead. The only way to make the pages work again is to manually remove the malicious application from the system. This issue has been addressed in version 4.3.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24805 | Local Privilege Escalation in MobSF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24805</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is an automated, all-in-one mobile application (Android/iOS/Windows) pen-testing, malware analysis and security assessment framework. A local user with minimal privileges is able to make use of an access token for materials for scopes which it should not be accepted. This issue has been addressed in version 4.3.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24372 | XSS vector in user uploaded images in group/org and user profiles in ckan</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24372</link><description>CKAN is an open-source DMS (data management system) for powering data hubs and data portals. Using a specially crafted file, a user could potentially upload a file containing code that when executed could send arbitrary requests to the server. If that file was opened by an administrator, it could lead to escalation of privileges of the original submitter or other malicious actions. Users must have been registered to the site to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability has been fixed in CKAN 2.10.7 and 2.11.2. Users are advised to upgrade. On versions prior to CKAN 2.10.7 and 2.11.2, site maintainers can restrict the file types supported for uploading using the `ckan.upload.user.mimetypes` / `ckan.upload.user.types` and `ckan.upload.group.mimetypes` / `ckan.upload.group.types` config options. To entirely disable file uploads users can use: `ckan.upload.user.types = none`</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56132 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56132</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.

This issue affects:



 Product 





Affected Versions 





LoadMaster 





From 7.2.55.0 to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive) 





  





From 7.2.49.0 to 7.2.54.12 (inclusive) 





  





7.2.48.12 and all prior versions 








ECS





All prior versions to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive)</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56133 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56133</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.

This issue affects:



 Product 





Affected Versions 





LoadMaster 





From 7.2.55.0 to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive) 





  





From 7.2.49.0 to 7.2.54.12 (inclusive) 





  





7.2.48.12 and all prior versions 









ECS





All prior versions to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive)</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56134 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56134</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.

This issue affects:



 Product 





Affected Versions 





LoadMaster 





From 7.2.55.0 to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive) 





  





From 7.2.49.0 to 7.2.54.12 (inclusive) 





  





7.2.48.12 and all prior versions 








Multi-Tenant Hypervisor 





7.1.35.12 and all prior versions 











ECS





All prior versions to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive)</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56135 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56135</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.

This issue affects:



 Product 





Affected Versions 





LoadMaster 





From 7.2.55.0 to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive) 





  





From 7.2.49.0 to 7.2.54.12 (inclusive) 





  





7.2.48.12 and all prior versions 








ECS





All prior versions to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive)</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56131 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56131</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows : OS Command Injection.

This issue affects:



 Product 





Affected Versions 





LoadMaster 





From 7.2.55.0 to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive) 





  





From 7.2.49.0 to 7.2.54.12 (inclusive) 





  





7.2.48.12 and all prior versions 








Multi-Tenant Hypervisor 





7.1.35.12 and all prior versions 










ECS





All prior versions to 7.2.60.1 (inclusive)</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7596 | Generic UDP Encapsulation (GUE) (IETF Draft) do not validate or verify the source of a network packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7596</link><description>Proposed Generic UDP Encapsulation (GUE) (IETF Draft) do not validate or verify the source of a network packet allowing an attacker to spoof and route arbitrary traffic via an exposed network interface that can lead to spoofing, access control bypass, and other unexpected network behaviors.

This can be considered similar to CVE-2020-10136.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7595 | GRE and GRE6 Protocols (RFC2784) do not validate or verify the source of a network packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7595</link><description>GRE and GRE6 Protocols (RFC2784) do not validate or verify the source of a network packet allowing an attacker to spoof and route arbitrary traffic via an exposed network interface that can lead to spoofing, access control bypass, and other unexpected network behaviors.

This can be considered similar to CVE-2020-10136.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20029 | BIG-IP iControl REST and tmsh vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20029</link><description>Command injection vulnerability exists in iControl REST and BIG-IP TMOS Shell (tmsh) save command, which may allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary system commands.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20045 | BIG-IP SIP MRF Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20045</link><description>When SIP session Application Level Gateway mode (ALG) profile with Passthru Mode enabled and SIP router ALG profile are configured on a Message Routing type virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20058 | BIG-IP message routing vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20058</link><description>When a BIG-IP message routing profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21087 | TMM Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21087</link><description>When Client or Server SSL profiles are configured on a Virtual Server, or DNSSEC signing operations are in use, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in memory and CPU resource utilization.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21091 | BIG-IP SNMP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21091</link><description>When SNMP v1 or v2c are disabled on the BIG-IP, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22846 | BIG-IP SIP Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22846</link><description>When SIP Session and Router ALG profiles are configured on a Message Routing type virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.



  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22891 | BIG-IP PEM Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22891</link><description>When BIG-IP PEM Control Plane listener Virtual Server is configured with Diameter Endpoint profile, undisclosed traffic can cause the Virtual Server to stop processing new client connections and an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23239 | BIG-IP iControl REST vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23239</link><description>When running in Appliance mode, an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23412 | BIG-IP APM access profile vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23412</link><description>When BIG-IP APM Access Profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed request can cause TMM to terminate.



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23413 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23413</link><description>When users log in through the webUI or API using local authentication, BIG-IP Next Central Manager may log sensitive information in the pgaudit log files. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23415 | BIG-IP APM Endpoint Inspection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23415</link><description>An insufficient verification of data authenticity vulnerability exists in BIG-IP APM Access Policy endpoint inspection that may allow an attacker to bypass endpoint inspection checks for VPN connection initiated thru BIG-IP APM browser network access VPN client for Windows, macOS and Linux.

 




Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23419 | TLS Session Resumption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23419</link><description>When multiple server blocks are configured to share the same IP address and port, an attacker can use session resumption to bypass client certificate authentication requirements on these servers. This vulnerability arises when  TLS Session Tickets https://nginx.org/en/docs/http/ngx_http_ssl_module.html#ssl_session_ticket_key  are used and/or the  SSL session cache https://nginx.org/en/docs/http/ngx_http_ssl_module.html#ssl_session_cache  are used in the default server and the default server is performing client certificate authentication.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24312 | BIG-IP AFM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24312</link><description>When BIG-IP AFM is provisioned with IPS module enabled and protocol inspection profile is configured on a virtual server or firewall rule or policy, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in CPU resource utilization.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24319 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24319</link><description>When BIG-IP Next Central Manager is running, undisclosed requests to the BIG-IP Next Central Manager API can cause the BIG-IP Next Central Manager Node's Kubernetes service to terminate.



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24320 | BIG-IP Configuration utility vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24320</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user. This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for  CVE-2024-31156 https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K000138636 . 

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24326 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF/ASM BADoS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24326</link><description>When BIG-IP Advanced WAF/ASM Behavioral DoS (BADoS) TLS Signatures feature is configured, undisclosed traffic can case an increase in memory resource utilization.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24497 | BIG-IP PEM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24497</link><description>When URL categorization is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause TMM to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20169 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20169</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20170 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20170</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20171 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20171</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20172 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software, Cisco IOS XE Software, and Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20172</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software, Cisco IOS XE Software, and Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. For Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. For Cisco IOS XR Software, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNMP process to restart, resulting in an interrupted SNMP response from an affected device. Devices that are running Cisco IOS XR Software will not reload.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20173 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20173</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20174 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20174</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20175 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20175</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20176 | A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20176</link><description>A vulnerability in the SNMP subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when parsing SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability affects SNMP versions 1, 2c, and 3. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v2c or earlier, the attacker must know a valid read-write or read-only SNMP community string for the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMP v3, the attacker must have valid SNMP user credentials for the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20124 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Java Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20124</link><description>A vulnerability in an API of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insecure deserialization of user-supplied Java byte streams by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted serialized Java object to an affected API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device and elevate privileges.
Note:&amp;nbsp;To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid read-only administrative credentials. In a single-node deployment, new devices will not be able to authenticate during the reload time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20125 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Insufficient Authorization Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20125</link><description>A vulnerability in an API of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with valid read-only credentials to obtain sensitive information, change node configurations, and restart the node.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of authorization in a specific API and improper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a specific API on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to attacker to obtain information, modify system configuration, and reload the device.
Note:&amp;nbsp;To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid read-only administrative credentials. In a single-node deployment, new devices will not be able to authenticate during the reload time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20179 | Cisco Expressway Series Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20179</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Expressway Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.
Note:&amp;nbsp;Cisco Expressway Series refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20180 | Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager and Secure Email Gateway Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20180</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager and Secure Email Gateway could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid credentials for a user account with at least the role of Operator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20183 | Cisco Secure Web Appliance Range Request Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20183</link><description>A vulnerability in a policy-based Cisco Application Visibility and Control (AVC) implementation of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Web Appliance could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to evade the antivirus scanner and download a malicious file onto an endpoint.&amp;nbsp;

The vulnerability is due to improper handling of a crafted range request header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an HTTP request with a crafted range request header through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to evade the antivirus scanner and download malware onto the endpoint without detection by Cisco Secure Web Appliance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20184 | Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager and Secure Web Appliance Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20184</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email Gateway and Cisco Secure Web Appliance could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device. The attacker must authenticate with valid administrator credentials.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of XML configuration files by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted XML configuration file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject commands to the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20185 | Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, Secure Email Gateway, and Secure Web Appliance Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20185</link><description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the remote access functionality of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, Cisco Secure Email Gateway, and Cisco Secure Web Appliance could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root. The attacker must authenticate with valid administrator credentials.

This vulnerability is due to an architectural flaw in the password generation algorithm for the remote access functionality. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by generating a temporary password for the service account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root and access the underlying operating system.
Note: The Security Impact Rating (SIR) for this vulnerability is Medium due to the unrestricted scope of information that is accessible to an attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20204 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20204</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the interface.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20205 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20205</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the interface.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20207 | Cisco Secure Email Gateway, Cisco Secure Email and Web Appliance and Cisco Secure Web Appliance SNMP Polling Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20207</link><description>A vulnerability in Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) polling for Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, Cisco Secure Email Gateway, and Cisco Secure Web Appliance could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain confidential information about the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability exists because the appliances do not protect confidential information at rest in response to SNMP poll requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP poll request to the affected appliance. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to discover confidential information that should be restricted. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have the configured SNMP credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39564 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of malformed BGP path attributes leads to RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39564</link><description>This is a similar, but different vulnerability than the issue reported as CVE-2024-39549.

A double-free vulnerability in the routing process daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an attacker to send a malformed BGP Path attribute update which allocates memory used to log the bad path attribute. This double free of memory is causing an rpd crash, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).


This issue affects:

Junos OS:   *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S4.


Junos OS Evolved:  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S4-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 15:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42207 | HCL iAutomate is affected by a session fixation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42207</link><description>HCL iAutomate is affected by a session fixation vulnerability.  An attacker could hijack a victim's session ID from their authenticated session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 15:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0858 | Edge E – Path Traversal Vulnerability - Arbitrary File Access by Unauthorized User</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0858</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 8.2.1.0820 in Poly Edge E devices. The firmware flaw does not properly prevent path traversal and could lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21117 | Dell Avamar, version 19.4 or later, contains an access token reuse vulnerability in the AUI. A low privileged local attacker could potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21117</link><description>Dell Avamar, version 19.4 or later, contains an access token reuse vulnerability in the AUI. A low privileged local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to fully impersonating the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9097 | IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9097</link><description>ManageEngine Endpoint Central versions before 11.3.2440.09 are vulnerable to IDOR vulnerability which allows the attacker to change the username in the chat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2878 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2878</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.7 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service by crafting unusual search terms for branch names.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 12:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3976 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3976</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 14.0 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. It was possible to disclose via the UI the confidential issues title and description from a public project to unauthorised instance users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 12:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49348 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49348</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2, 19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3, 20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1, and 22.0.2 



allows restricting access to organizational data to valid contexts. The fact that tasks of type comment can be reassigned via API implicitly grants access to user queries in an unexpected context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52365 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52365</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2, 19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3, 20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1, and 22.0.2 

is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52364 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52364</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2, 19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3, 20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1, and 22.0.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 11:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49352 | IBM Cognos Anaytics XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49352</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, and 12.0.4 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 11:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5528 | Incomplete Comparison with Missing Factors in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5528</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows a subdomain takeover in GitLab Pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 10:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9631 | Inefficient Algorithmic Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9631</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.6 prior to 17.2.9, starting from 17.3 prior to 17.3.5, and starting from 17.4 prior to 17.4.2, where viewing diffs of MR with conflicts can be slow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 10:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6356 | Incorrect User Management in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6356</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2, which allowed cross project access for Security policy bot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 10:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1539 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1539</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.2 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. It was possible to disclose updates to issues to a banned group member using the API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6386 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6386</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, affecting all versions from 15.11 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5 and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resource usage resulting in service degradation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0725 | gzip integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0725</link><description>When libcurl is asked to perform automatic gzip decompression of
content-encoded HTTP responses with the `CURLOPT_ACCEPT_ENCODING` option,
**using zlib 1.2.0.3 or older**, an attacker-controlled integer overflow would
make libcurl perform a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52924 | netfilter: nf_tables: don&amp;#x27;t skip expired elements during walk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52924</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: don't skip expired elements during walk

There is an asymmetry between commit/abort and preparation phase if the
following conditions are met:

1. set is a verdict map ("1.2.3.4 : jump foo")
2. timeouts are enabled

In this case, following sequence is problematic:

1. element E in set S refers to chain C
2. userspace requests removal of set S
3. kernel does a set walk to decrement chain-&gt;use count for all elements
   from preparation phase
4. kernel does another set walk to remove elements from the commit phase
   (or another walk to do a chain-&gt;use increment for all elements from
    abort phase)

If E has already expired in 1), it will be ignored during list walk, so its use count
won't have been changed.

Then, when set is culled, -&gt;destroy callback will zap the element via
nf_tables_set_elem_destroy(), but this function is only safe for
elements that have been deactivated earlier from the preparation phase:
lack of earlier deactivate removes the element but leaks the chain use
count, which results in a WARN splat when the chain gets removed later,
plus a leak of the nft_chain structure.

Update pipapo_get() not to skip expired elements, otherwise flush
command reports bogus ENOENT errors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52925 | netfilter: nf_tables: don&amp;#x27;t fail inserts if duplicate has expired</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52925</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: don't fail inserts if duplicate has expired

nftables selftests fail:
run-tests.sh testcases/sets/0044interval_overlap_0
Expected: 0-2 . 0-3, got:
W: [FAILED]     ./testcases/sets/0044interval_overlap_0: got 1

Insertion must ignore duplicate but expired entries.

Moreover, there is a strange asymmetry in nft_pipapo_activate:

It refetches the current element, whereas the other -&gt;activate callbacks
(bitmap, hash, rhash, rbtree) use elem-&gt;priv.
Same for .remove: other set implementations take elem-&gt;priv,
nft_pipapo_remove fetches elem-&gt;priv, then does a relookup,
remove this.

I suspect this was the reason for the change that prompted the
removal of the expired check in pipapo_get() in the first place,
but skipping exired elements there makes no sense to me, this helper
is used for normal get requests, insertions (duplicate check)
and deactivate callback.

In first two cases expired elements must be skipped.

For -&gt;deactivate(), this gets called for DELSETELEM, so it
seems to me that expired elements should be skipped as well, i.e.
delete request should fail with -ENOENT error.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0167 | netrc and default credential leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0167</link><description>When asked to use a `.netrc` file for credentials **and** to follow HTTP
redirects, curl could leak the password used for the first host to the
followed-to host under certain circumstances.

This flaw only manifests itself if the netrc file has a `default` entry that
omits both login and password. A rare circumstance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0665 | eventfd double close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0665</link><description>libcurl would wrongly close the same eventfd file descriptor twice when taking
down a connection channel after having completed a threaded name resolve.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 09:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13829 | WordPress form builder plugin for contact forms, surveys and quizzes – Tripetto &amp;lt;= 8.0.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13829</link><description>The WordPress form builder plugin for contact forms, surveys and quizzes – Tripetto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 8.0.8 via the 'attachments.php' file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including files uploaded via forms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1022 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.5 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation in the setHtml function, invoked by Brow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1022</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.5 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation in the setHtml function, invoked by Browsershot::html(), which can be bypassed by omitting the slashes in the file URI (e.g., file:../../../../etc/passwd). This is due to missing validations of the user input that should be blocking file URI schemes (e.g., file:// and file:/) in the HTML content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1025 | Versions of the package cockpit-hq/cockpit before 2.4.1 are vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload where an attacker can use different extensio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1025</link><description>Versions of the package cockpit-hq/cockpit before 2.4.1 are vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload where an attacker can use different extension to bypass the upload filter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1026 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.5 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to improper URL validation through t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1026</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.5 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to improper URL validation through the setUrl method, which results in a Local File Inclusion allowing the attacker to read sensitive files.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is a bypass of the fix for [CVE-2024-21549](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-PHP-SPATIEBROWSERSHOT-8533023).</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25246 | NETGEAR XR1000 before 1.0.0.74, XR1000v2 before 1.1.0.22, and XR500 before 2.3.2.134 allow remote code execution by unauthenticated users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25246</link><description>NETGEAR XR1000 before 1.0.0.74, XR1000v2 before 1.1.0.22, and XR500 before 2.3.2.134 allow remote code execution by unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 04:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1028 | Contact Manager &amp;lt;= 8.6.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Double File Extension Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1028</link><description>The Contact Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the contact form upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 8.6.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible in specific configurations where the first extension is processed over the final. This vulnerability also requires successfully exploiting a race condition in order to exploit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 03:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23114 | A vulnerability in Veeam Updater component allows Man-in-the-Middle attackers to execute arbitrary code on the affected server. This issue o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23114</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam Updater component allows Man-in-the-Middle attackers to execute arbitrary code on the affected server. This issue occurs due to a failure to properly validate TLS certificate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 02:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53962 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53962</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53963 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (DOM-based XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53963</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited by a low privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's browser session. By manipulating a DOM element through a crafted URL or user input, the attacker can inject malicious scripts that run when the page is rendered. This type of attack requires user interaction, as the victim would need to access a manipulated link or input data into a vulnerable page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53964 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53964</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53965 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (DOM-based XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53965</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited by a low privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's browser session. By manipulating a DOM element through a crafted URL or user input, the attacker can inject malicious scripts that run when the page is rendered. This type of attack requires user interaction, as the victim would need to access a manipulated link or input data into a vulnerable page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53966 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53966</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0413 | Parallels Desktop Technical Data Reporter Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0413</link><description>Parallels Desktop Technical Data Reporter Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. 
This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Technical Data Reporter component. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to change the permissions of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25014.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39943 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39943</link><description>In Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt versions prior to v12 SP2 Build (1204.200), the affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing XE files. This could lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11468 | Omnissa Horizon Client for macOS contains a Local privilege escalation (LPE) Vulnerability due to a flaw in the installation process. Succes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11468</link><description>Omnissa Horizon Client for macOS contains a Local privilege escalation (LPE) Vulnerability due to a flaw in the installation process. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow attackers with user privileges to escalate their privileges to root on the system where the Horizon Client for macOS is installed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40222 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40222</link><description>In Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt versions prior to v12 SP2 Build (1204.200), the affected application lacks proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing CO files. This could lead to a heap-based buffer overflow. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11467 | Omnissa Horizon Client for macOS contains a Local privilege escalation (LPE) Vulnerability due to a logic flaw. Successful exploitation of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11467</link><description>Omnissa Horizon Client for macOS contains a Local privilege escalation (LPE) Vulnerability due to a logic flaw. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow attackers with user privileges to escalate their privileges to root on the system where the Horizon Client for macOS is installed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48445 | An issue in compop.ca ONLINE MALL v.3.5.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the rid, tid, et, and ts parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48445</link><description>An issue in compop.ca ONLINE MALL v.3.5.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the rid, tid, et, and ts parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13722 | Checkmk NagVis Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13722</link><description>The "NagVis" component within Checkmk is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting. An attacker can craft a malicious link that will execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the browser once clicked. The attack can be performed on both authenticated and unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:10:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13723 | Checkmk NagVis Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13723</link><description>The "NagVis" component within Checkmk is vulnerable to remote code execution. An authenticated attacker with administrative level privileges is able to upload a malicious PHP file and modify specific settings to execute the contents of the file as PHP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:10:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8125 | A remote code vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Content Management.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8125</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Type of Input vulnerability in OpenText™ Content Management (Extended ECM) allows Parameter Injection. 

A bad actor with the required OpenText Content Management privileges (not root) could expose
the vulnerability to carry out a remote code execution attack on the target system.

This issue affects Content Management (Extended ECM): from 10.0 through 24.4 

 with WebReports module
installed and enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53266 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via topic titles when CSP disabled in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53266</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions with some combinations of plugins, and with CSP disabled, activity streams in the user's profile page may be vulnerable to XSS. This has been patched in the latest version of Discourse core. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should ensure CSP is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53851 | Partial denial of service via inline oneboxes in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53851</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions the endpoint for generating inline oneboxes for URLs wasn't enforcing limits on the number of URLs that it accepted, allowing a malicious user to inflict denial of service on some parts of the app. This vulnerability is only exploitable by authenticated users. This issue has been patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed versions of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should turn off the `enable inline onebox on all domains` site setting and remove all entries from the `allowed inline onebox domains` site setting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53994 | Potential bypass of chat permissions in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53994</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions users who disable chat in preferences could still be reachable in some cases. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable the chat plugin within site settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55948 | Anonymous cache poisoning via XHR requests in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55948</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can make craft an XHR request to poison the anonymous cache (for example, the cache may have a response with missing  preloaded data). This issue only affects anonymous visitors of the site. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable anonymous cache by setting the `DISCOURSE_DISABLE_ANON_CACHE` environment variable to a non-empty value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56197 | Users can see other user&amp;#x27;s tagged PMs in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56197</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. PM titles and metadata can be read by other users when the "PM tags allowed for groups" option is enabled, the other user is a member of a group added to this option, and the PM has been tagged. This issue has been patched in the latest `stable`, `beta` and `tests-passed` versions of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should remove all groups from the the "PM tags allowed for groups" option.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56328 | HTMLi(XSS without CSP) via Onebox urls in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56328</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. An attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users' browsers by posting a maliciously crafted onebox url. This issue only affects sites with CSP disabled. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should enable CSP, disable inline Oneboxes globally, or allow specific domains for Oneboxing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22601 | Client Side Path Traversal using activate account route in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22601</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can trick a target user to make changes to their own username via carefully crafted link using the `activate-account` route. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22602 | Stored DOM-based XSS (without CSP) via video placeholders in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22602</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users' browsers by posting a malicious video placeholder html element. This issue only affects sites with CSP disabled. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should enable CSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23023 | Anonymous cache poisoning via request headers in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23023</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can carefully craft a request with the right request headers to poison the anonymous cache (for example, the cache may have a response with missing  preloaded data). This issue only affects anonymous visitors of the site. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may disable anonymous cache by setting the `DISCOURSE_DISABLE_ANON_CACHE` environment variable to a non-empty value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35138 | IBM Security Verify Access cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35138</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43187 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43187</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 transmits sensitive or security-critical data in cleartext in a communication channel that can be sniffed by unauthorized actors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45657 | IBM Security Verify Access incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45657</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a local privileged user to perform unauthorized actions due to incorrect permissions assignment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40700 | IBM Security Verify Access cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40700</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45658 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45658</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0509 | Signing Checks Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0509</link><description>A security issue was found in Sparkle before version 2.64. An attacker can replace an existing signed update with another payload, bypassing Sparkle’s (Ed)DSA signing checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0630 | Western Telematic Inc NPS Series, DSM Series, CPM Series External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0630</link><description>Multiple Western Telematic (WTI) products contain a web interface that is vulnerable to a local file inclusion attack (LFI), where any authenticated user has privileged access to files on the device's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0960 | AutomationDirect C-more EA9 HMI Classic Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0960</link><description>AutomationDirect C-more EA9 HMI contains a function with bounds checks that can be skipped, which could result in an attacker abusing the function to cause a denial-of-service condition or achieving remote code execution on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24963 | Browser mode serves arbitrary files in vitest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24963</link><description>Vitest is a testing framework powered by Vite. The `__screenshot-error` handler on the browser mode HTTP server that responds any file on the file system. Especially if the server is exposed on the network by `browser.api.host: true`, an attacker can send a request to that handler from remote to get the content of arbitrary files.This `__screenshot-error` handler on the browser mode HTTP server responds any file on the file system. This code was added by commit `2d62051`. Users explicitly exposing the browser mode server to the network by `browser.api.host: true` may get any files exposed. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.1.9 and 3.0.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24964 | Remote Code Execution when accessing a malicious website while Vitest API server is listening</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24964</link><description>Vitest is a testing framework powered by Vite. Affected versions are subject to arbitrary remote Code Execution when accessing a malicious website while Vitest API server is listening by Cross-site WebSocket hijacking (CSWSH) attacks. When `api` option is enabled (Vitest UI enables it), Vitest starts a WebSocket server. This WebSocket server did not check Origin header and did not have any authorization mechanism and was vulnerable to CSWSH attacks. This WebSocket server has `saveTestFile` API that can edit a test file and `rerun` API that can rerun the tests. An attacker can execute arbitrary code by injecting a code in a test file by the `saveTestFile` API and then running that file by calling the `rerun` API. This vulnerability can result in remote code execution for users that are using Vitest serve API. This issue has been patched in versions 1.6.1, 2.1.9 and 3.0.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24966 | HTML Injection in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24966</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. HTML Injection occurs when an application improperly validates or sanitizes user inputs, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary HTML code. In this scenario, the vulnerability exists in the "Add Target" functionality of the application, where the Target Organization and Target Description fields accept HTML payloads. The injected HTML is rendered and executed in the target area, potentially leading to malicious actions. Exploitation of HTML Injection can compromise the application's integrity and user trust. Attackers can execute unauthorized actions, steal sensitive information, or trick users into performing harmful actions. The organization's reputation, customer trust, and regulatory compliance could be negatively affected. This issue affects all versions up to and including 2.2.0. Users are advised to monitor the project for future releases which address this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24967 | Stored XSS on Admin Panel When Deleting a User in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24967</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the admin panel's user management functionality. An attacker can exploit this issue by injecting malicious payloads into the username field during user creation. This vulnerability allows unauthorized script execution whenever the admin views or interacts with the affected user entry, posing a significant risk to sensitive admin functionalities. This issue affects all versions up to and including 2.20. Users are advised to monitor the project for future releases which address this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24968 | Business Logic And Unrestricted Project Deletion Lead To Take Over the System in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24968</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. An unrestricted project deletion vulnerability allows attackers with specific roles, such as `penetration_tester` or `auditor` to delete all projects in the system. This can lead to a complete system takeover by redirecting the attacker to the onboarding page, where they can add or modify users, including Sys Admins, and configure critical settings like API keys and user preferences. This issue affects all versions up to and including 2.20. Users are advised to monitor the project for future releases which address this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0444 | Use after free in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0444</link><description>Use after free in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0445 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0445</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0451 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions API in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to eng...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0451</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions API in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24971 | OS Command Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;/upload/init&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;filename&amp;#x27; (RCE) in DumpDrop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24971</link><description>DumpDrop is a stupid simple file upload application that provides an interface for dragging and dropping files. An OS Command Injection vulnerability was discovered in the DumbDrop application, `/upload/init` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code remotely when the **Apprise Notification** enabled. This issue has been addressed in commit `4ff8469d` and all users are advised to patch. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24373 | Unrestricted Access to PDF Documents via URL Manipulation in woocommerce-pdf-invoices-packing-slips</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24373</link><description>woocommerce-pdf-invoices-packing-slips is an extension which allows users to create, print &amp; automatically email PDF invoices &amp; packing slips for WooCommerce orders. This vulnerability allows unauthorized users to access any PDF document from a store if they: 1. Have access to a guest document link and 2. Replace the URL variable `my-account` with `bulk`. The issue occurs when: 1. The store's document access is set to "guest." and 2. The user is logged out. This vulnerability compromises the confidentiality of sensitive documents, affecting all stores using the plugin with the guest access option enabled. This issue has been addressed in version 4.0.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48019 | Apache Doris: allows admin users to read arbitrary files through the REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48019</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal'), Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in Apache Doris.


Application administrators can read arbitrary
files from the server filesystem through path traversal.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.8, 3.0.3 or later, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25039 | Authenticated Remote Command Injection in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25039</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM) allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary commands on the underlying host. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands as a lower privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23058 | Authenticated Broken Access Control Vulnerability in ClearPass Policy Manager Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23058</link><description>A vulnerability in the ClearPass Policy Manager web-based management interface allows a low-privileged (read-only) authenticated remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to data and the ability to execute functions that should be restricted to administrators only with read/write privileges. Successful exploitation could enable a low-privileged user to execute administrative functions leading to an escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23059 | Sensitive Information Disclosure in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23059</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager exposes directories containing sensitive information. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability allows an authenticated remote attacker with high privileges to access and retrieve sensitive data, potentially compromising the integrity and security of the entire system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23060 | Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23060</link><description>A vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager may, under certain circumstances, expose sensitive unencrypted information. Exploiting this vulnerability could allow an attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle attack, potentially granting unauthorized access to network resources as well as enabling data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0364 | BigAntSoft BigAnt Server Account Registration Bypass to File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0364</link><description>BigAntSoft BigAnt Server, up to and including version 5.6.06, is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution via account registration. An unauthenticated remote attacker can create an administrative user through the default exposed SaaS registration mechanism. Once an administrator, the attacker can upload and execute arbitrary PHP code using the "Cloud Storage Addin," leading to unauthenticated code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45659 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45659</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9644 | Four-Faith F3x36 bapply.cgi Auth Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9644</link><description>The Four-Faith F3x36 router using firmware v2.0.0 is vulnerable to an 
authentication bypass vulnerability in the administrative web server. Authentication is not enforced on some administrative functionality when using the "bapply.cgi" endpoint instead of the normal "apply.cgi" endpoint. A remote and unauthenticated can use this vulnerability to modify settings or chain with existing authenticated vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9643 | Four-Faith F3x36 Hidden Debug Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9643</link><description>The Four-Faith F3x36 router using firmware v2.0.0 is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to hard-coded credentials in the administrative web server. An attacker with knowledge of the credentials can gain administrative access via crafted HTTP requests. This issue appears similar to CVE-2023-32645.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23690 | EOL Netgear FVS336v3 Telnet Configuration Backup Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23690</link><description>The end-of-life Netgear FVS336Gv2 and FVS336Gv3 are affected by a command injection vulnerability in the Telnet interface. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands as root over Telnet by sending crafted "util backup_configuration" commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22206 | Extension - joomsky.com - SQL injection in JS jobs component version 1.1.5 - 1.4.2 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22206</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the JS Jobs plugin versions 1.1.5-1.4.2 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the 'fieldfor' parameter in the GDPR Field feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22641 | WordPress FM Notification Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prem Tiwari FM Notification Bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FM Notification Bar: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22642 | WordPress Dynamic Conditions plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RTO GmbH Dynamic Conditions allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dynamic Conditions: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22643 | WordPress OnePress theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22643</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FameThemes OnePress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects OnePress: from n/a through 2.3.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22653 | WordPress Music Press Pro plugin &amp;lt;=1.4.6 -  Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in templaza Music Press Pro allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Music Press Pro: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22662 | WordPress SendPulse Email Marketing Newsletter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SendPulse SendPulse Email Marketing Newsletter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SendPulse Email Marketing Newsletter: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22664 | WordPress Survey Maker Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Survey Maker team Survey Maker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Survey Maker: from n/a through 5.1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22674 | WordPress Product Blocks for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22674</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Get Bowtied Product Blocks for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Product Blocks for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22675 | WordPress Alert Box Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22675</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22696 | WordPress Document Block – Upload &amp;amp; Embed Docs, PDF, PPT, XLS or Any Documents plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22696</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EmbedPress Document Block – Upload &amp; Embed Docs. This issue affects Document Block – Upload &amp; Embed Docs: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22697 | WordPress Responsive Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CyberChimps Responsive Blocks allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Responsive Blocks: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22699 | WordPress Traveler Code plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary SQL Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22699</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Traveler Code. This issue affects Traveler Code: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22700 | WordPress Traveler Code plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary SQL Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Traveler Code. This issue affects Traveler Code: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22730 | WordPress Ksher plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22730</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ksher Ksher allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ksher: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22794 | WordPress World Cup Predictor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22794</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Landoweb Programador World Cup Predictor allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects World Cup Predictor: from n/a through 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23645 | WordPress Find Content IDs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Optimize Worldwide Find Content IDs allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Find Content IDs: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24598 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.17.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.17.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24599 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tribulant Newsletters allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24602 | WordPress WP24 Domain Check plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24602</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP24 WP24 Domain Check allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP24 Domain Check: from n/a through 1.10.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24648 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.2.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24648</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in wpase.com Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE): from n/a through 7.6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24677 | WordPress Post/Page Copying Tool to Export and Import post/page for Cross site Migration Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24677</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WPSpins Post/Page Copying Tool allows Remote Code Inclusion. This issue affects Post/Page Copying Tool: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0825 | CRLF injection in Cpp-httplib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0825</link><description>cpp-httplib version v0.17.3 through v0.18.3 fails to filter CRLF characters ("\r\n") when those are prefixed with a null byte. This enables attackers to exploit CRLF injection that could further lead to HTTP Response Splitting, XSS, and more.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0510 | Thunderbird displayed an incorrect sender address if the From field of an email used the invalid group name syntax that is described in CVE-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0510</link><description>Thunderbird displayed an incorrect sender address if the From field of an email used the invalid group name syntax that is described in CVE-2024-49040. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.7 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1009 | An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via crafted XSLT data, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1009</link><description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via crafted XSLT data, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1010 | An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via the Custom Highlight API, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1010</link><description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via the Custom Highlight API, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1011 | A bug in WebAssembly code generation could have lead to a crash. It may have been possible for an attacker to leverage this to achieve code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1011</link><description>A bug in WebAssembly code generation could have lead to a crash. It may have been possible for an attacker to leverage this to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1012 | A race during concurrent delazification could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1012</link><description>A race during concurrent delazification could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1013 | A race condition could have led to private browsing tabs being opened in normal browsing windows. This could have resulted in a potential pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1013</link><description>A race condition could have led to private browsing tabs being opened in normal browsing windows. This could have resulted in a potential privacy leak. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1014 | Certificate length was not properly checked when added to a certificate store. In practice only trusted data was processed. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1014</link><description>Certificate length was not properly checked when added to a certificate store. In practice only trusted data was processed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1015 | The Thunderbird Address Book URI fields contained unsanitized links. This could be used by an attacker to create and export an address book ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1015</link><description>The Thunderbird Address Book URI fields contained unsanitized links. This could be used by an attacker to create and export an address book containing a malicious payload in a field. For example, in the “Other” field of the Instant Messaging section. If another user imported the address book, clicking on the link could result in opening a web page inside Thunderbird, and that page could execute (unprivileged) JavaScript. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1016 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 115.19, Firefox ESR 128.6, Thunderbird 115.19, and Thunderbird 128.6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1016</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 115.19, Firefox ESR 128.6, Thunderbird 115.19, and Thunderbird 128.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1017 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 128.6, and Thunderbird 128.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1017</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 128.6, and Thunderbird 128.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1018 | The fullscreen notification is prematurely hidden when fullscreen is re-requested quickly by the user. This could have been leveraged to per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1018</link><description>The fullscreen notification is prematurely hidden when fullscreen is re-requested quickly by the user. This could have been leveraged to perform a potential spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1019 | The z-order of the browser windows could be manipulated to hide the fullscreen notification. This could potentially be leveraged to perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1019</link><description>The z-order of the browser windows could be manipulated to hide the fullscreen notification. This could potentially be leveraged to perform a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1020 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134 and Thunderbird 134. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1020</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134 and Thunderbird 134. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11623 | Stored XSS in authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11623</link><description>Authentik project is vulnerable to Stored XSS attacks through uploading crafted SVG files that are used as application icons. 
This action could only be performed by an authenticated admin user.
The issue was fixed in 2024.10.4 release.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13699 | Qi Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13699</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘cursor’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in versions 1.8.5, 1.8.6, and 1.8.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 12:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27137 | Apache Cassandra: unrestricted deserialization of JMX authentication credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27137</link><description>In Apache Cassandra it is possible for a local attacker without access
 to the Apache Cassandra process or configuration files to manipulate 
the RMI registry to perform a man-in-the-middle attack and capture user 
names and passwords used to access the JMX interface. The attacker can 
then use these credentials to access the JMX interface and perform 
unauthorized operations.


This is same vulnerability that CVE-2020-13946 was issued for, but the Java option was changed in JDK10.


This issue affects Apache Cassandra from 4.0.2 through 5.0.2 running Java 11.


Operators are recommended to upgrade to a release equal to or later than 4.0.15, 4.1.8, or 5.0.3 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24860 | Apache Cassandra: CassandraNetworkAuthorizer and CassandraCIDRAuthorizer can be bypassed allowing access to different network regions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24860</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Cassandra allowing users to access a datacenter or IP/CIDR groups they should not be able to when using CassandraNetworkAuthorizer or CassandraCIDRAuthorizer.

Users with restricted data center access can update their own permissions via data control language (DCL) statements on affected versions.




This issue affects Apache Cassandra: from 4.0.0 through 4.0.15 and from 4.1.0 through 4.1.7 for CassandraNetworkAuthorizer, and from 5.0.0 through 5.0.2 for both CassandraNetworkAuthorizer and CassandraCIDRAuthorizer.




Operators using CassandraNetworkAuthorizer or CassandraCIDRAuthorizer on affected versions should review data access rules for potential breaches. Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 4.0.16, 4.1.8, 5.0.3, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0890 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
Insecure default credentials for the Telnet function in the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0890</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
Insecure default credentials for the Telnet function in the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version 1.00(AAFR.4)C0_20170615 could allow an attacker to log in to the management interface if the administrators have the option to change the default credentials but fail to do so.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40891 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the management commands of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40891</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the management commands of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version 1.00(AAFR.4)C0_20170615 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via Telnet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40890 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CGI program of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40890</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CGI program of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version 1.00(AAFR.4)C0_20170615 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23015 | Apache Cassandra: User with MODIFY permission on ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser via unsafe actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23015</link><description>Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions vulnerability in Apache Cassandra. An user with MODIFY permission ON ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser within a targeted Cassandra cluster via unsafe actions to a system resource. Operators granting data MODIFY permission on all keyspaces on affected versions should review data access rules for potential breaches.

This issue affects Apache Cassandra through 3.0.30, 3.11.17, 4.0.15, 4.1.7, 5.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 3.0.31, 3.11.18, 4.0.16, 4.1.8, 5.0.3, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13356 | DSGVO All in one for WP &amp;lt;= 4.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Account Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13356</link><description>The DSGVO All in one for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the user_remove_form.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete admin user accounts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13510 | ShopSite &amp;lt;= 1.5.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13510</link><description>The ShopSite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13529 | SocialV - Social Network and Community BuddyPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13529</link><description>The SocialV - Social Network and Community BuddyPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'socialv_send_download_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download arbitrary files from the target system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13733 | SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13733</link><description>The SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's skt-blocks/post-carousel block in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13403 | WPForms Lite &amp;lt;= 1.9.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via fieldHTML Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13403</link><description>The WPForms – Easy Form Builder for WordPress – Contact Forms, Payment Forms, Surveys, &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘fieldHTML’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10237 | SMC BMC Firmware Image Authentication Design Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10237</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the BMC firmware image authentication design 

 at Supermicro MBD-X12DPG-OA6

. An attacker can modify the firmware to bypass BMC inspection and bypass the signature verification process</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10238 | fld-&amp;gt;used_bytes without sanity check causes stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10238</link><description>A security issue in the firmware image verification implementation 

 at Supermicro MBD-X12DPG-OA6. An attacker can upload a specially crafted image that will cause a stack overflow is caused by not checking fld-&gt;used_bytes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10239 | fld-&amp;gt;used_bytes without sanity check causes stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10239</link><description>A security issue in the firmware image verification implementation at Supermicro MBD-X12DPG-OA6 . An attacker with administrator privileges can upload a specially crafted image, which can cause a stack overflow due to the unchecked fat-&gt;fsd.max_fld.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12046 | Medical Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12046</link><description>The Medical Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 via the 'namedical_elementor_template' shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the content of draft, pending, and private posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13514 | B Slider- Gutenberg Slider Block for WP &amp;lt;= 1.1.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Private Post Disclosure via bsb-slider Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13514</link><description>The B Slider- Gutenberg Slider Block for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.5 via the 'bsb-slider' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20904 | Out-of-bounds write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20904</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20905 | Out-of-bounds read and write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read and write out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20905</link><description>Out-of-bounds read and write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read and write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20906 | Improper Export of Android Application Components in Settings prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable ADB.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20906</link><description>Improper Export of Android Application Components in Settings prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable ADB.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20907 | Improper privilege management in Samsung Find prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to disable Samsung Find.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20907</link><description>Improper privilege management in Samsung Find prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to disable Samsung Find.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22204 | Extension - regularlabs.com - Remote code execution vulnerability in the Sourcerer extensions &amp;lt; 12.0.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22204</link><description>Improper control of generation of code in the sourcerer extension for Joomla in versions before 11.0.0 lead to a remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22205 | Extension - admiror-design-studio.com - Path traversal in the Admiror Gallery 4.x component for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22205</link><description>Improper handling of input variables lead to multiple path traversal vulnerabilities in the Admiror Gallery extension for Joomla in version branch 4.x.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20881 | Out-of-bounds write in accessing buffer storing the decoded video frames in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20881</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in accessing buffer storing the decoded video frames in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20882 | Out-of-bounds write in accessing uninitialized memory for svc1td in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20882</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in accessing uninitialized memory for svc1td in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20883 | Improper access control in SoundPicker prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20883</link><description>Improper access control in SoundPicker prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20884 | Improper access control in Samsung Message prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20884</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Message prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20885 | Out-of-bounds write in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20885</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20886 | Inclusion of sensitive information in test code in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get test ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20886</link><description>Inclusion of sensitive information in test code in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get test key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20887 | Out-of-bounds read in accessing table used for svp8t in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20887</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in accessing table used for svp8t in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary memory. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20888 | Out-of-bounds write in handling the block size for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20888</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in handling the block size for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20889 | Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to rea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20889</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary memory. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20890 | Out-of-bounds write in decoding frame buffer in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20890</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in decoding frame buffer in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20891 | Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream of video thumbnails in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20891</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream of video thumbnails in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary memory. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20892 | Protection Mechanism Failure in bootloader prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to allow to execute fastboot command. U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20892</link><description>Protection Mechanism Failure in bootloader prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to allow to execute fastboot command. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20893 | Improper access control in NotificationManager prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to change the configuration of notific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20893</link><description>Improper access control in NotificationManager prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to change the configuration of notifications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20894 | Improper access control in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.97.1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20894</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.97.1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20895 | Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.87.6 allows physical attackers to install arbitrary appli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20895</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.87.6 allows physical attackers to install arbitrary applications to bypass restrictions of Setupwizard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20896 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in EasySetup prior to version 11.1.18 allows local attackers to access sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20896</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in EasySetup prior to version 11.1.18 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20897 | Improper access control in Secure Folder prior to version 1.9.20.50 in Android 14, 1.8.11.0 in Android 13, and 1.7.04.0 in Android 12 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20897</link><description>Improper access control in Secure Folder prior to version 1.9.20.50 in Android 14, 1.8.11.0 in Android 13, and 1.7.04.0 in Android 12 allows local attacker to access data in Secure Folder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20898 | Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.2.00.12 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20898</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.2.00.12 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20899 | Improper access control in PushNotification prior to version 13.0.00.15 in Android 12, 14.0.00.7 in Android 13, and 15.1.00.5 in Android 14 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20899</link><description>Improper access control in PushNotification prior to version 13.0.00.15 in Android 12, 14.0.00.7 in Android 13, and 15.1.00.5 in Android 14 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20900 | Out-of-bounds write in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20900</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20901 | Out-of-bounds read in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20901</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20902 | Improper access control in Media Controller prior to version 1.0.24.5282 allows local attacker to launch activities in MediaController's pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20902</link><description>Improper access control in Media Controller prior to version 1.0.24.5282 allows local attacker to launch activities in MediaController's privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12597 | HT Mega &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via block_css and inner_css</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12597</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'block_css' and 'inner_css' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13607 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13607</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8 via the 'exportusereraserequest' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level permissions and above, to export ticket data for any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13114 | WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13114</link><description>The WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13115 | WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13115</link><description>The WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13325 | Glossy &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13325</link><description>The Glossy WordPress plugin through 2.3.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13326 | iBuildApp &amp;lt;= 0.2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13326</link><description>The iBuildApp WordPress plugin through 0.2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13327 | Musicbox &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13327</link><description>The Musicbox WordPress plugin through 2.0.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13328 | Giga Messenger Bots &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13328</link><description>The Giga Messenger  WordPress plugin through 2.3.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13329 | Solidres &amp;lt;= 0.9.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13329</link><description>The Solidres  WordPress plugin through 0.9.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13330 | Justrows Free &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13330</link><description>The JustRows free WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13331 | WP Dream Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.0.1b - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13331</link><description>The WP Dream Carousel WordPress plugin through 1.0.1b does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13332 | TransFinanz &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13332</link><description>The TransFinanz WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0368 | Banner Garden Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0368</link><description>The Banner Garden Plugin for WordPress plugin through 0.1.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0466 | Sensei LMS &amp;lt; 4.24.4 - Unauthenticated sensei_email/sensei_message Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0466</link><description>The Sensei LMS  WordPress plugin before 4.24.4 does not properly protect some its REST API routes, allowing unauthenticated attackers to leak sensei_email and sensei_message Information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24982 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Activity Log WinterLock versions prior to 1.2.5. If a user views a malicious page while l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24982</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Activity Log WinterLock versions prior to 1.2.5. If a user views a malicious page while logged in, the log data may be deleted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 04:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22475 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to DDOS 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.10 contains a use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Impl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22475</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to DDOS 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.10 contains a use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 02:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1003 | HP Anyware Agent for Linux – Potential Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1003</link><description>A potential vulnerability has been identified in HP Anyware Agent for Linux which might allow for authentication bypass which may result in escalation of privilege. HP is releasing a software update to mitigate this potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>