<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:19:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-47141 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47141</link><description>IIBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.5 could allow an authenticated user with CONNECT privileges to cause a denial of service using a specially crafted query.  IBM X-Force ID:  270264.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27859 | IBM Db2 code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27859</link><description>IBM Db2 10.1, 10.5, and 11.1 could allow a remote user to execute arbitrary code caused by installing like named jar files across multiple databases.  A user could exploit this by installing a malicious jar file that overwrites the existing like named jar file in another database.  IBM X-Force ID:  249205.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47152 | IBM Db2 information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47152</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.5 is vulnerable to an insecure cryptographic algorithm and to information disclosure in stack trace under exceptional conditions.  IBM X-Force ID:  270730.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47158 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47158</link><description>IBM DB2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.1, 10.5, and 11.1 could allow an authenticated user with CONNECT privileges to cause a denial of service using a specially crafted query.  IBM X-Force ID:  270750.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47747 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47747</link><description>IBM DB2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.1, 10.5, and 11.1 could allow an authenticated user with CONNECT privileges to cause a denial of service using a specially crafted query.  IBM X-Force ID:  272646.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6290 | WP SEO Press &amp;lt; 7.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6290</link><description>The SEOPress WordPress plugin before 7.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6384 | WP User Profile Avatar &amp;lt; 1.0.1 - Author+ Avatar Deletion/Update via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6384</link><description>The WP User Profile Avatar WordPress plugin before 1.0.1 does not properly check for authorisation, allowing authors to delete and update arbitrary avatar</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6447 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.3.6 - Unauthenticated Event Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6447</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.3.6 lacks authentication and authorization, allowing unauthenticated visitors to access private and password protected Events by guessing their numeric id/event name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6456 | WP Review Slider &amp;lt; 13.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6456</link><description>The WP Review Slider WordPress plugin before 13.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6625 | Product Enquiry for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 3.1 - Arbitrary Enquiry Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6625</link><description>The Product Enquiry for WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 3.1 does not have a CSRF check in place when deleting inquiries, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin delete them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6626 | Product Enquiry for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 3.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6626</link><description>The Product Enquiry for WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 3.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7082 | WP All Import &amp;lt; 3.7.3 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7082</link><description>The Import any XML or CSV File to WordPress plugin before 3.7.3 accepts all zip files and automatically extracts the zip file into a publicly accessible directory without sufficiently validating the extracted file type. This may allows high privilege users such as administrator to upload an executable file type leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7170 | EventON-RSVP &amp;lt; 2.9.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7170</link><description>The EventON-RSVP WordPress plugin before 2.9.5 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7194 | Meris &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7194</link><description>The Meris WordPress theme through 1.1.2 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48118 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Quest Analytics LLC IQCRM v.2023.9.5 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48118</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Quest Analytics LLC IQCRM v.2023.9.5 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the Common.svc WSDL page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45193 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45193</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.5 federated server is vulnerable to a denial of service when a specially crafted cursor is used.  IBM X-Force ID:  268759.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:06:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47746 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47746</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 could allow an authenticated user with CONNECT privileges to cause a denial of service using a specially crafted query.  IBM X-Force ID:  272644.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50308 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50308</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5 under certain circumstances could allow an authenticated user to the database to cause a denial of service when a statement is run on columnar tables.  IBM X-Force ID:  273393.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0430 | IObit Malware Fighter v11.0.0.1274 - Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0430</link><description>IObit Malware Fighter v11.0.0.1274 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x8001E00C IOCTL code of the ImfHpRegFilter.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0605 | Using a javascript: URI with a setTimeout race condition, an attacker can execute unauthorized scripts on top origin sites in urlbar. This b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0605</link><description>Using a javascript: URI with a setTimeout race condition, an attacker can execute unauthorized scripts on top origin sites in urlbar. This bypasses security measures, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution or unauthorized actions within the user's loaded webpage. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0606 | An attacker could execute unauthorized script on a legitimate site through UXSS using window.open() by opening a javascript URI leading to u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0606</link><description>An attacker could execute unauthorized script on a legitimate site through UXSS using window.open() by opening a javascript URI leading to unauthorized actions within the user's loaded webpage. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0204 | Authentication Bypass in GoAnywhere MFT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0204</link><description>Authentication bypass in Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.4.1 allows an unauthorized user to create an admin user via the administration portal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45792 | Directory Traversal in Project File Format allows overwrite (Zip Slip)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45792</link><description>Project files may contain malicious contents which the software will use to create files on the filesystem. This allows directory traversal and overwriting files with the privileges of the logged-in user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 17:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0783 | Project Worlds Online Admission System documents.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0783</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Online Admission System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file documents.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251699.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 17:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0784 | biantaibao octopus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0784</link><description>A vulnerability was found in biantaibao octopus 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/role/list. The manipulation of the argument dataScope leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251700.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 17:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45790 | Omron FINS memory protection susceptible to bruteforce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45790</link><description>The Omron FINS protocol has an authenticated feature to prevent access to memory regions. Authentication is susceptible to bruteforce attack, which may allow an adversary to gain access to protected memory. This access can allow overwrite of values including programmed logic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 17:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0782 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System pass-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0782</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file pass-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name/User Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 16:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0778 | Uniview ISC 2500-S VM.php setNatConfig os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0778</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Uniview ISC 2500-S up to 20210930. Affected by this issue is the function setNatConfig of the file /Interface/DevManage/VM.php. The manipulation of the argument natAddress/natPort/natServerPort leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251696. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 16:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0781 | CodeAstro Internet Banking System pages_client_signup.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0781</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CodeAstro Internet Banking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file pages_client_signup.php. The manipulation of the argument Client Full Name with the input &lt;meta http-equiv="refresh" content="0; url=https://vuldb.com" /&gt; leads to open redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251697 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 16:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44395 | Autolab has Path Traversal vulnerability in Assessment functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44395</link><description>Autolab is a course management service that enables instructors to offer autograded programming assignments to their students over the Web. Path traversal vulnerabilities were discovered in Autolab's assessment functionality in versions of Autolab prior to 2.12.0, whereby instructors can perform arbitrary file reads. Version 2.12.0 contains a patch. There are no feasible workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 14:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22895 | DedeCMS 5.7.112 has a File Upload vulnerability via uploads/dede/module_upload.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22895</link><description>DedeCMS 5.7.112 has a File Upload vulnerability via uploads/dede/module_upload.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 14:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36772 | CloudLinux
 CageFS 7.0.8-2 or below insufficiently restricts file paths supplied to
 the sendmail proxy command. This allows local users to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36772</link><description>CloudLinux
 CageFS 7.0.8-2 or below insufficiently restricts file paths supplied to
 the sendmail proxy command. This allows local users to read and write 
arbitrary files outside the CageFS environment in a limited way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 14:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36771 | CloudLinux
 CageFS 7.1.1-1 or below passes the authentication token as command line
 argument. In some configurations this allows local user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36771</link><description>CloudLinux
 CageFS 7.1.1-1 or below passes the authentication token as command line
 argument. In some configurations this allows local users to view it via
 the process list and gain code execution as another user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0775 | Kernel: use-after-free while changing the mount option in __ext4_remount leading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0775</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the __ext4_remount in fs/ext4/super.c in ext4 in the Linux kernel. This flaw allows a local user to cause an information leak problem while freeing the old quota file names before a potential failure, leading to a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 13:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22233 | CVE-2024-22233: Spring Framework server Web DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22233</link><description>In Spring Framework versions 6.0.15 and 6.1.2, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when all of the following are true:

  *  the application uses Spring MVC
  *  Spring Security 6.1.6+ or 6.2.1+ is on the classpath


Typically, Spring Boot applications need the org.springframework.boot:spring-boot-starter-web and org.springframework.boot:spring-boot-starter-security dependencies to meet all conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 12:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20189 | In Clojure before 1.9.0, classes can be used to construct a serialized object that executes arbitrary code upon deserialization. This is rel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20189</link><description>In Clojure before 1.9.0, classes can be used to construct a serialized object that executes arbitrary code upon deserialization. This is relevant if a server deserializes untrusted objects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 05:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52354 | chasquid before 1.13 allows SMTP smuggling because LF-terminated lines are accepted.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52354</link><description>chasquid before 1.13 allows SMTP smuggling because LF-terminated lines are accepted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 05:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47352 | Technicolor TC8715D devices have predictable default WPA2 security passwords. An attacker who scans for SSID and BSSID values may be able to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47352</link><description>Technicolor TC8715D devices have predictable default WPA2 security passwords. An attacker who scans for SSID and BSSID values may be able to predict these passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 05:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21484 | Versions of the package jsrsasign before 11.0.0 are vulnerable to Observable Discrepancy via the RSA PKCS1.5 or RSAOAEP decryption process. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21484</link><description>Versions of the package jsrsasign before 11.0.0 are vulnerable to Observable Discrepancy via the RSA PKCS1.5 or RSAOAEP decryption process. An attacker can decrypt ciphertexts by exploiting this vulnerability. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to have access to a large number of ciphertexts encrypted with the same key.&#13;&#13; Workaround &#13;&#13;This vulnerability can be mitigated by finding and replacing RSA and RSAOAEP decryption with another crypto library.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 05:18:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22113 | Open redirect vulnerability in Access analysis CGI An-Analyzer released in 2023 December 31 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22113</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in Access analysis CGI An-Analyzer released in 2023 December 31 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arbitrary websites and conduct phishing attacks via a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23770 | darkhttpd through 1.15 allows local users to discover credentials (for --auth) by listing processes and their arguments.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23770</link><description>darkhttpd through 1.15 allows local users to discover credentials (for --auth) by listing processes and their arguments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23771 | darkhttpd before 1.15 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier for remote attackers to bypas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23771</link><description>darkhttpd before 1.15 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier for remote attackers to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23768 | Dremio before 24.3.1 allows path traversal. An authenticated user who has no privileges on certain folders (and the files and datasets in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23768</link><description>Dremio before 24.3.1 allows path traversal. An authenticated user who has no privileges on certain folders (and the files and datasets in these folders) can access these folders, files, and datasets. To be successful, the user must have access to the source and at least one folder in the source. Affected versions are: 24.0.0 through 24.3.0, 23.0.0 through 23.2.3, and 22.0.0 through 22.2.2. Fixed versions are: 24.3.1 and later, 23.2.4 and later, and 22.2.3 and later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 03:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23750 | MetaGPT through 0.6.4 allows the QaEngineer role to execute arbitrary code because RunCode.run_script() passes shell metacharacters to subpr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23750</link><description>MetaGPT through 0.6.4 allows the QaEngineer role to execute arbitrary code because RunCode.run_script() passes shell metacharacters to subprocess.Popen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23751 | LlamaIndex (aka llama_index) through 0.9.34 allows SQL injection via the Text-to-SQL feature in NLSQLTableQueryEngine, SQLTableRetrieverQuer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23751</link><description>LlamaIndex (aka llama_index) through 0.9.34 allows SQL injection via the Text-to-SQL feature in NLSQLTableQueryEngine, SQLTableRetrieverQueryEngine, NLSQLRetriever, RetrieverQueryEngine, and PGVectorSQLQueryEngine. For example, an attacker might be able to delete this year's student records via "Drop the Students table" within English language input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23752 | GenerateSDFPipeline in synthetic_dataframe in PandasAI (aka pandas-ai) through 1.5.17 allows attackers to trigger the generation of arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23752</link><description>GenerateSDFPipeline in synthetic_dataframe in PandasAI (aka pandas-ai) through 1.5.17 allows attackers to trigger the generation of arbitrary Python code that is executed by SDFCodeExecutor. An attacker can create a dataframe that provides an English language specification of this Python code. NOTE: the vendor previously attempted to restrict code execution in response to a separate issue, CVE-2023-39660.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 01:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0776 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Comment cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0776</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Comment Handler. The manipulation with the input &lt;div onmouseenter="alert("xss)"&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251678 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0774 | Any-Capture Any Sound Recorder Registration memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0774</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Any-Capture Any Sound Recorder 2.93. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument User Name/Key Code leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0772 | Nsasoft ShareAlarmPro Registration memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0772</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nsasoft ShareAlarmPro 2.1.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name/Key leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251672. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0773 | CodeAstro Internet Banking System pages_client_signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0773</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CodeAstro Internet Banking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file pages_client_signup.php. The manipulation of the argument Client Full Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251677 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0770 | European Chemicals Agency IUCLID Desktop Installer iuclid6.exe default permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0770</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in European Chemicals Agency IUCLID 7.10.3 on Windows. Affected is an unknown function of the file iuclid6.exe of the component Desktop Installer. The manipulation leads to incorrect default permissions. The attack needs to be approached locally. VDB-251670 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0771 | Nsasoft Product Key Explorer Registration memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0771</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Nsasoft Product Key Explorer 4.0.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name/Key leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251671. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52353 | An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS through 3.5.1. In mbedtls_ssl_session_reset, the maximum negotiable TLS version is mishandled. For examp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52353</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS through 3.5.1. In mbedtls_ssl_session_reset, the maximum negotiable TLS version is mishandled. For example, if the last connection negotiated TLS 1.2, then 1.2 becomes the new maximum.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 22:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23744 | An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 3.5.1. There is persistent handshake denial if a client sends a TLS 1.3 ClientHello without extensions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23744</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 3.5.1. There is persistent handshake denial if a client sends a TLS 1.3 ClientHello without extensions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 22:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23730 | The OpenAPI and ChatGPT plugin loaders in LlamaHub (aka llama-hub) before 0.0.67 allow attackers to execute arbitrary code because safe_load...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23730</link><description>The OpenAPI and ChatGPT plugin loaders in LlamaHub (aka llama-hub) before 0.0.67 allow attackers to execute arbitrary code because safe_load is not used for YAML.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23731 | The OpenAPI loader in Embedchain before 0.1.57 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, related to the openapi.py yaml.load function argu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23731</link><description>The OpenAPI loader in Embedchain before 0.1.57 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, related to the openapi.py yaml.load function argument.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23732 | The JSON loader in Embedchain before 0.1.57 allows a ReDoS (regular expression denial of service) via a long string to json.py.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23732</link><description>The JSON loader in Embedchain before 0.1.57 allows a ReDoS (regular expression denial of service) via a long string to json.py.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6531 | Kernel: gc&amp;#x27;s deletion of an skb races with unix_stream_read_generic()  leading to uaf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6531</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux Kernel due to a race problem in the unix garbage collector's deletion of SKB races with unix_stream_read_generic() on the socket that the SKB is queued on.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0769 | D-Link DIR-859 HTTP POST Request hedwig.cgi path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0769</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-859 1.06B01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /hedwig.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service with the input ../../../../htdocs/webinc/getcfg/DHCPS6.BRIDGE-1.xml leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15037 | go4rayyan Scumblr Task cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15037</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in go4rayyan Scumblr up to 2.0.1a. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Task Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.2 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 5c9120f2362ddb7cbe48f2c4620715adddc4ee35. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-251570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23726 | Ubee DDW365 XCNDDW365 and DDW366 XCNDXW3WB devices have predictable default WPA2 PSKs that could lead to unauthorized remote access. A remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23726</link><description>Ubee DDW365 XCNDDW365 and DDW366 XCNDXW3WB devices have predictable default WPA2 PSKs that could lead to unauthorized remote access. A remote attacker (in proximity to a Wi-Fi network) can derive the default WPA2-PSK value by observing a beacon frame. A PSK is generated by using the first six characters of the SSID and the last six of the BSSID, decrementing the last digit.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23725 | Ghost before 5.76.0 allows XSS via a post excerpt in excerpt.js. An XSS payload can be rendered in post summaries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23725</link><description>Ghost before 5.76.0 allows XSS via a post excerpt in excerpt.js. An XSS payload can be rendered in post summaries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0521 | Code Injection in paddlepaddle/paddle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0521</link><description>Code Injection in paddlepaddle/paddle</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7063 | The WPForms Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form submission parameters in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7063</link><description>The WPForms Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form submission parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0623 | The VK Block Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.31.1.1. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0623</link><description>The VK Block Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.31.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the vbp_clear_patterns_cache() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear the patterns cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0679 | The ColorMag theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the plugin_action_callback() func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0679</link><description>The ColorMag theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the plugin_action_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to install and activate arbitrary plugins.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46447 | The POPS! Rebel application 5.0 for Android, in POPS! Rebel Bluetooth Glucose Monitoring System, sends unencrypted glucose measurements over...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46447</link><description>The POPS! Rebel application 5.0 for Android, in POPS! Rebel Bluetooth Glucose Monitoring System, sends unencrypted glucose measurements over BLE.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47024 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47024</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and escalate privileges via a crafted script to the UserSelfService component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51906 | An issue in yonyou YonBIP v3_23.05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the ServiceDispatcherServlet u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51906</link><description>An issue in yonyou YonBIP v3_23.05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the ServiceDispatcherServlet uap.framework.rc.itf.IResourceManager component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51924 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uap.framework.rc.itf.IResourceManager interface of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51924</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uap.framework.rc.itf.IResourceManager interface of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51925 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51925</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-31314 | File upload vulnerability in ejinshan v8+ terminal security system allows attackers to upload arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31314</link><description>File upload vulnerability in ejinshan v8+ terminal security system allows attackers to upload arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51892 | An issue in weaver e-cology v.10.0.2310.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the FrameworkShellCont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51892</link><description>An issue in weaver e-cology v.10.0.2310.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the FrameworkShellController component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51926 | YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the nc.bs.framework.comn.serv.CommonServletDispatcher com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51926</link><description>YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the nc.bs.framework.comn.serv.CommonServletDispatcher component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51927 | YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the com.yonyou.hrcloud.attend.web.AttendScriptController.runScri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51927</link><description>YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the com.yonyou.hrcloud.attend.web.AttendScriptController.runScript() method.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51928 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51928</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>