<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-5073 | Essential Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 5.9.21 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Twitter Feed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5073</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Twitter Feed component in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5327 | PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) &amp;lt;= 2.7.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5327</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘pp_animated_gradient_bg_color’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36267 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in Redmine DMSF Plugin versions prior to 3.1.4. If this vulnerability is exploited, a logged-in user may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36267</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in Redmine DMSF Plugin versions prior to 3.1.4. If this vulnerability is exploited, a logged-in user may obtain or delete arbitrary files on the server (within the privilege of the Redmine process).</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5207 | POST SMTP Mailer – Email log, Delivery Failure Notifications and Best Mail SMTP for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5207</link><description>The POST SMTP – The #1 WordPress SMTP Plugin with Advanced Email Logging and Delivery Failure Notifications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the selected parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator access or higher to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5341 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Heading Title Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5341</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'size' attribute of the Heading Title widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3277 | Yumpu ePaper publishing &amp;lt;= 2.0.24 - Missing Authorization to PDF Upload, Publishing, and API Key Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3277</link><description>The Yumpu ePaper publishing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload PDF files and publish them, as well as modify the API key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3943 | WP To Do &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via wptodo_addcomment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3943</link><description>The WP To Do plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wptodo_addcomment function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add comments to to do items via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3945 | WP To Do &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via wptodo_manage()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3945</link><description>The WP To Do plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wptodo_manage() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add new todo items via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3946 | WP To Do &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3946</link><description>The WP To Do plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3947 | WP To Do &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via wptodo_settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3947</link><description>The WP To Do plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wptodo_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4218 | AffiEasy &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Various Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4218</link><description>The AffiEasy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This is due to plugin improperly releasing the tagged and patched version of the plugin - the vulnerable version is used as the core files, while the patched version was included in a 'trunk' folder. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform a variety of actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4356 | List categories &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4356</link><description>The List categories plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'categories' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 04:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2253 | Testimonial Carousel For Elementor &amp;lt;= 10.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2253</link><description>The Testimonial Carousel For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URL values the plugin's carousel widgets in all versions up to, and including, 10.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 03:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3063 | WPB Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3063</link><description>The WPB Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the output of 'tags' added to widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied tag attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 03:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3190 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.107 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Text Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3190</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's text field widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.107 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Please note that this vulnerability is different in that the issue stems from an external template. It appears that older version may also be patched due to this, however, we are choosing 1.5.108 as the patched version since that is the most recent version containing as known patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 03:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3269 | Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 4.9.13 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3269</link><description>The Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access to functionality due to a missing capability check on the dlm_uninstall_plugin function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to uninstall the plugin and delete its data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 03:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5223 | Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks and WordPress Blog Plugin – PostX &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5223</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks and WordPress Blog Plugin – PostX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file uploading feature in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 03:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3726 | Login Logout Register Menu &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;llrmloginlogout&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3726</link><description>The Login Logout Register Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'llrmloginlogout' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 02:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5514 | MinMax CMS - Hidden Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5514</link><description>MinMax CMS from MinMax Digital Technology contains a hidden administrator account with a fixed password that cannot be removed or disabled from the management interface. Remote attackers who obtain this account can bypass IP access control restrictions and log in to the backend system without being recorded in the system logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 02:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36114 | Decompressors can crash the JVM and leak memory content in Aircompressor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36114</link><description>Aircompressor is a library with ports of the Snappy, LZO, LZ4, and Zstandard compression algorithms to Java. All decompressor implementations of Aircompressor (LZ4, LZO, Snappy, Zstandard) can crash the JVM for certain input, and in some cases also leak the content of other memory of the Java process (which could contain sensitive information). When decompressing certain data, the decompressors try to access memory outside the bounds of the given byte arrays or byte buffers. Because Aircompressor uses the JDK class `sun.misc.Unsafe` to speed up memory access, no additional bounds checks are performed and this has similar security consequences as out-of-bounds access in C or C++, namely it can lead to non-deterministic behavior or crash the JVM. Users should update to Aircompressor 0.27 or newer where these issues have been fixed. When decompressing data from untrusted users, this can be exploited for a denial-of-service attack by crashing the JVM, or to leak other sensitive information from the Java process. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 20:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35221 | Denial of service when publishing a package on rubygems.org</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35221</link><description>Rubygems.org is the Ruby community's gem hosting service. A Gem publisher can cause a Remote DoS when publishing a Gem. This is due to how Ruby reads the Manifest of Gem files when using Gem::Specification.from_yaml. from_yaml makes use of SafeYAML.load which allows YAML aliases inside the YAML-based metadata of a gem. YAML aliases allow for Denial of Service attacks with so-called `YAML-bombs` (comparable to Billion laughs attacks). This was patched. There is is no action required by users. This issue is also tracked as GHSL-2024-001 and was discovered by the GitHub security lab.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 20:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35492 | Cesanta Mongoose commit b316989 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the scpy function at src/fmt.c. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35492</link><description>Cesanta Mongoose commit b316989 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the scpy function at src/fmt.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MQTT packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35434 | Irontec Sngrep v1.8.1 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the function rtp_check_packet at /sngrep/src/rtp.c. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35434</link><description>Irontec Sngrep v1.8.1 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the function rtp_check_packet at /sngrep/src/rtp.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted SIP packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36016 | tty: n_gsm: fix possible out-of-bounds in gsm0_receive()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36016</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tty: n_gsm: fix possible out-of-bounds in gsm0_receive()

Assuming the following:
- side A configures the n_gsm in basic option mode
- side B sends the header of a basic option mode frame with data length 1
- side A switches to advanced option mode
- side B sends 2 data bytes which exceeds gsm-&gt;len
  Reason: gsm-&gt;len is not used in advanced option mode.
- side A switches to basic option mode
- side B keeps sending until gsm0_receive() writes past gsm-&gt;buf
  Reason: Neither gsm-&gt;state nor gsm-&gt;len have been reset after
  reconfiguration.

Fix this by changing gsm-&gt;count to gsm-&gt;len comparison from equal to less
than. Also add upper limit checks against the constant MAX_MRU in
gsm0_receive() and gsm1_receive() to harden against memory corruption of
gsm-&gt;len and gsm-&gt;mru.

All other checks remain as we still need to limit the data according to the
user configuration and actual payload size.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 18:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35512 | An issue in hmq v1.5.5 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted requests.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35512</link><description>An issue in hmq v1.5.5 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34715 | Partial Password Exposure Vulnerability in Fides Webserver Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34715</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. The Fides webserver requires a connection to a hosted PostgreSQL database for persistent storage of application data. If the password used by the webserver for this database connection includes special characters such as `@` and `$`, webserver startup fails and the part of the password following the special character is exposed in webserver error logs. This is caused by improper escaping of the SQLAlchemy password string. As a result users are subject to a partial exposure of hosted database password in webserver logs. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.37.0`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31079 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31079</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause other potential impact. This attack requires that a request be specifically timed during the connection draining process, which the attacker has no visibility and limited influence over.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32760 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32760</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 encoder instructions can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause or other potential impact.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34161 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34161</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module and the network infrastructure supports a Maximum Transmission Unit (MTU) of 4096 or greater without fragmentation, undisclosed QUIC packets can cause NGINX worker processes to leak previously freed memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35200 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35200</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35284 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35284</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack due to insufficient input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35311 | Yubico YubiKey 5 Series before 5.7.0, Security Key Series before 5.7.0, YubiKey Bio Series before 5.6.4, and YubiKey 5 FIPS before 5.7.2 hav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35311</link><description>Yubico YubiKey 5 Series before 5.7.0, Security Key Series before 5.7.0, YubiKey Bio Series before 5.6.4, and YubiKey 5 FIPS before 5.7.2 have Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35283 | A vulnerability in the Ignite component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to condu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35283</link><description>A vulnerability in the Ignite component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack due to insufficient input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46297 | An issue was discovered on Mercusys MW325R EU V3 MW325R(EU)_V3_1.11.0 221019 devices. A WAN attacker can make the admin interface unreachabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46297</link><description>An issue was discovered on Mercusys MW325R EU V3 MW325R(EU)_V3_1.11.0 221019 devices. A WAN attacker can make the admin interface unreachable/invisible via an unauthenticated HTTP request. Verification of the data sent by the user does not occur. The web server does not crash, but the admin interface becomes invisible, because the files necessary to display the content are no longer available. A reboot of the router is typically required to restore the correct behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28974 | Dell Data Protection Advisor, version(s) 19.9, contain(s) an Inadequate Encryption Strength vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28974</link><description>Dell Data Protection Advisor, version(s) 19.9, contain(s) an Inadequate Encryption Strength vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35333 | A stack-buffer-overflow vulnerability exists in the read_charset_decl function of html2xhtml 1.3. This vulnerability occurs due to improper ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35333</link><description>A stack-buffer-overflow vulnerability exists in the read_charset_decl function of html2xhtml 1.3. This vulnerability occurs due to improper bounds checking when copying data into a fixed-size stack buffer. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by providing a specially crafted input to the vulnerable function, causing a buffer overflow and potentially leading to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, or data corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36427 | The file-serving function in TARGIT Decision Suite 23.2.15007 allows authenticated attackers to read or write to server files via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36427</link><description>The file-serving function in TARGIT Decision Suite 23.2.15007 allows authenticated attackers to read or write to server files via a crafted file request. This can allow code execution via a .xview file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4358 | Registration Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4358</link><description>In Progress Telerik Report Server, version 2024 Q1 (10.0.24.305) or earlier, on IIS, an unauthenticated attacker can gain access to Telerik Report Server restricted functionality via an authentication bypass vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36362 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5, 2024.03.2 path traversal allowing to read files from server was pos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36362</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5, 2024.03.2 path traversal allowing to read files from server was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36363 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 several Stored XSS in code inspection reports were possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36363</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 several Stored XSS in code inspection reports were possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36364 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 improper access control in Pull Requests and Commit status publisher...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36364</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 improper access control in Pull Requests and Commit status publisher build features was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36365 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5, 2024.03.2 a third-party agent could impersonate a cloud agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36365</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5, 2024.03.2 a third-party agent could impersonate a cloud agent</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36366 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 an XSS could be executed via certain report grouping and filtering o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36366</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 an XSS could be executed via certain report grouping and filtering operations</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36367 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS via third-party reports was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36367</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS via third-party reports was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36368 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 reflected XSS via OAuth provider configuration was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36368</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 reflected XSS via OAuth provider configuration was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36369 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS via issue tracker integration was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36369</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS via issue tracker integration was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36370 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS via OAuth connection settings was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36370</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS via OAuth connection settings was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36371 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS in Commit status publisher was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36371</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 stored XSS in Commit status publisher was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36372 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.05.5 reflected XSS on the subscriptions page was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36372</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.05.5 reflected XSS on the subscriptions page was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36373 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 several stored XSS in untrusted builds settings were possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36373</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 several stored XSS in untrusted builds settings were possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36374 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 stored XSS via build step settings was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36374</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 stored XSS via build step settings was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36375 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 technical information regarding TeamCity server could be exposed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36375</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 technical information regarding TeamCity server could be exposed</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36376 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 users could perform actions that should not be available to them based on their permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36376</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 users could perform actions that should not be available to them based on their permissions</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36377 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 certain TeamCity API endpoints did not check user permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36377</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 certain TeamCity API endpoints did not check user permissions</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36378 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 server was susceptible to DoS attacks with incorrect auth tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36378</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.03.2 server was susceptible to DoS attacks with incorrect auth tokens</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36470 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 authentication bypass was possible in specific edge cases</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36470</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2022.04.6, 2022.10.5, 2023.05.5, 2023.11.5 authentication bypass was possible in specific edge cases</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25975 | Arbitrary File Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25975</link><description>The application implements an up- and downvote function which alters a value within a JSON file. The POST parameters are not filtered properly and therefore an arbitrary file can be overwritten. The file can be controlled by an authenticated attacker, the content cannot be controlled. It is possible to overwrite all files for which the webserver has write access. It is required to supply a relative path (path traversal).</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5185 | Data Poisoning in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5185</link><description>The EmbedAI application is susceptible to security issues that enable Data Poisoning attacks. This weakness could result in the application becoming compromised, leading to unauthorized entries or data poisoning attacks, which are delivered by a CSRF vulnerability due to the absence of a secure session management implementation and weak CORS policies weakness. An attacker can direct a user to a malicious webpage that exploits a CSRF vulnerability within the EmbedAI application. By leveraging this CSRF vulnerability, the attacker can deceive the user into inadvertently uploading and integrating incorrect data into the application’s language model.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42005 | IBM Db2 on Cloud Pak for Data privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42005</link><description>IBM Db2 on Cloud Pak for Data and Db2 Warehouse on Cloud Pak for Data 3.5, 4.0, 4.5, 4.6, 4.7, and 4.8 could allow a user with access to the Kubernetes pod, to make system calls compromising the security of containers. IBM X-Force ID: 265264.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5039 | HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.5.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5039</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25977 | Session Fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25977</link><description>The application does not change the session token when using the login or logout functionality. An attacker can set a session token in the victim's browser (e.g. via XSS) and prompt the victim to log in (e.g. via a redirect to the login page). This results in the victim's account being taken over.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25976 | Reflected Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25976</link><description>When LDAP authentication is activated in the configuration it is possible to obtain reflected XSS execution by creating a custom URL that the victim only needs to open in order to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser. This is due to a fault in the file login.php where the content of "$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']" is reflected into the HTML of the website. Hence the attacker does not need a valid account in order to exploit this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27313 | XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27313</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine PAM360 is vulnerable to Stored XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability is applicable only in the version 6610.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52881 | tcp: do not accept ACK of bytes we never sent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52881</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: do not accept ACK of bytes we never sent

This patch is based on a detailed report and ideas from Yepeng Pan
and Christian Rossow.

ACK seq validation is currently following RFC 5961 5.2 guidelines:

   The ACK value is considered acceptable only if
   it is in the range of ((SND.UNA - MAX.SND.WND) &lt;= SEG.ACK &lt;=
   SND.NXT).  All incoming segments whose ACK value doesn't satisfy the
   above condition MUST be discarded and an ACK sent back.  It needs to
   be noted that RFC 793 on page 72 (fifth check) says: "If the ACK is a
   duplicate (SEG.ACK &lt; SND.UNA), it can be ignored.  If the ACK
   acknowledges something not yet sent (SEG.ACK &gt; SND.NXT) then send an
   ACK, drop the segment, and return".  The "ignored" above implies that
   the processing of the incoming data segment continues, which means
   the ACK value is treated as acceptable.  This mitigation makes the
   ACK check more stringent since any ACK &lt; SND.UNA wouldn't be
   accepted, instead only ACKs that are in the range ((SND.UNA -
   MAX.SND.WND) &lt;= SEG.ACK &lt;= SND.NXT) get through.

This can be refined for new (and possibly spoofed) flows,
by not accepting ACK for bytes that were never sent.

This greatly improves TCP security at a little cost.

I added a Fixes: tag to make sure this patch will reach stable trees,
even if the 'blamed' patch was adhering to the RFC.

tp-&gt;bytes_acked was added in linux-4.2

Following packetdrill test (courtesy of Yepeng Pan) shows
the issue at hand:

0 socket(..., SOCK_STREAM, IPPROTO_TCP) = 3
+0 setsockopt(3, SOL_SOCKET, SO_REUSEADDR, [1], 4) = 0
+0 bind(3, ..., ...) = 0
+0 listen(3, 1024) = 0

// ---------------- Handshake ------------------- //

// when window scale is set to 14 the window size can be extended to
// 65535 * (2^14) = 1073725440. Linux would accept an ACK packet
// with ack number in (Server_ISN+1-1073725440. Server_ISN+1)
// ,though this ack number acknowledges some data never
// sent by the server.

+0 &lt; S 0:0(0) win 65535 
+0 &gt; S. 0:0(0) ack 1 &lt;...&gt;
+0 &lt; . 1:1(0) ack 1 win 65535
+0 accept(3, ..., ...) = 4

// For the established connection, we send an ACK packet,
// the ack packet uses ack number 1 - 1073725300 + 2^32,
// where 2^32 is used to wrap around.
// Note: we used 1073725300 instead of 1073725440 to avoid possible
// edge cases.
// 1 - 1073725300 + 2^32 = 3221241997

// Oops, old kernels happily accept this packet.
+0 &lt; . 1:1001(1000) ack 3221241997 win 65535

// After the kernel fix the following will be replaced by a challenge ACK,
// and prior malicious frame would be dropped.
+0 &gt; . 1:1(0) ack 1001</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28826 | Unrestricted upload and download paths in check_sftp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28826</link><description>Improper restriction of local upload and download paths in check_sftp in Checkmk before 2.3.0p4, 2.2.0p27, 2.1.0p44, and in Checkmk 2.0.0 (EOL) allows attackers with sufficient permissions to configure the check to read and write local files on the Checkmk site server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3412 | WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin – Migration Backup Restore &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3412</link><description>The WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin – Migration Backup Restore plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the wpstg_processing AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 08:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36015 | ppdev: Add an error check in register_device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36015</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ppdev: Add an error check in register_device

In register_device, the return value of ida_simple_get is unchecked,
in witch ida_simple_get will use an invalid index value.

To address this issue, index should be checked after ida_simple_get. When
the index value is abnormal, a warning message should be printed, the port
should be dropped, and the value should be recorded.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5086 | Essential Addons for Elementor PRO – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 5.8.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Team Member Carousel Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5086</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor PRO – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Team Member Carousel widget in all Pro versions up to, and including, 5.8.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36014 | drm/arm/malidp: fix a possible null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36014</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/arm/malidp: fix a possible null pointer dereference

In malidp_mw_connector_reset, new memory is allocated with kzalloc, but
no check is performed. In order to prevent null pointer dereferencing,
ensure that mw_state is checked before calling
__drm_atomic_helper_connector_reset.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3050 | Site Reviews &amp;lt; 7.0.0 - IP Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3050</link><description>The Site Reviews WordPress plugin before 7.0.0 retrieves client IP addresses from potentially untrusted headers, allowing an attacker to manipulate its value. This may be used to bypass IP-based blocking</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3921 | Gianism &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3921</link><description>The Gianism WordPress plugin through 5.1.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3937 | Playlist for Youtube &amp;lt;= 1.32 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3937</link><description>The Playlist for Youtube WordPress plugin through 1.32 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6743 | Unlimited Elements for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.89 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Remote Code Execution via template import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6743</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.89 via the template import functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 04:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4611 | AppPresser &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Improper Missing Encryption Exception Handling to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4611</link><description>The AppPresser plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to improper missing encryption exception handling on the 'decrypt_value' and on the 'doCookieAuth' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they previously used the login via the plugin API. This can only be exploited if the 'openssl' php extension is not loaded on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0434 | WordPress Tour &amp;amp; Travel Booking Plugin for WooCommerce – WpTravelly &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Missing Authorization via ttbm_new_place_save</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0434</link><description>The WordPress Tour &amp; Travel Booking Plugin for WooCommerce – WpTravelly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ttbm_new_place_save' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create and publish new place posts. This function is also vulnerable to CSRF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 03:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5150 | Login with phone number &amp;lt;= 1.7.26 - Authentication Bypass due to Missing Empty Value Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5150</link><description>The Login with phone number plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.7.26. This is due to the 'activation_code' default value is empty, and the not empty check is missing in the 'lwp_ajax_register' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user email. The vulnerability is patched in version 1.7.26, but there is an issue in the patch that causes the entire function to not work, and this issue is fixed in version 1.7.27.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5204 | Swiss Toolkit For WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5204</link><description>The Swiss Toolkit For WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This is due to the plugin storing custom data in post metadata without an underscore prefix. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5437 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System save_category cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5437</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function save_category of the file /admin/index.php?page=categories. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266442 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 23:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36112 | Nautobot dynamic-group-members doesn&amp;#x27;t enforce permission restrictions on member objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36112</link><description>Nautobot is a Network Source of Truth and Network Automation Platform. A user with permissions to view Dynamic Group records (`extras.view_dynamicgroup` permission) can use the Dynamic Group detail UI view (`/extras/dynamic-groups//`) and/or the members REST API view (`/api/extras/dynamic-groups//members/`) to list the objects that are members of a given Dynamic Group. In versions of Nautobot between 1.3.0 (where the Dynamic Groups feature was added) and 1.6.22 inclusive, and 2.0.0 through 2.2.4 inclusive, Nautobot fails to restrict these listings based on the member object permissions - for example a Dynamic Group of Device objects will list all Devices that it contains, regardless of the user's `dcim.view_device` permissions or lack thereof. This issue has been fixed in Nautobot versions 1.6.23 and 2.2.5. Users are advised to upgrade. This vulnerability can be partially mitigated by removing `extras.view_dynamicgroup` permission from users however a full fix will require upgrading.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30314 | An issue discovered in 360 V6G, 360 T5G, 360 T6M, and 360 P1 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30314</link><description>An issue discovered in 360 V6G, 360 T5G, 360 T6M, and 360 P1 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30312 | An issue discovered in routers running Openwrt 18.06, 19.07, 21.02, 22.03 and beyond allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30312</link><description>An issue discovered in routers running Openwrt 18.06, 19.07, 21.02, 22.03 and beyond allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23580 | HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by insecure encryption of One-Time Passwords (OTPs)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23580</link><description>HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by insecure encryption of One-Time Passwords (OTPs). This could allow an attacker with access to the database to recover some or all encrypted values.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23579 | HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by insecure encryption of security questions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23579</link><description>HCL DRYiCE Optibot Reset Station is impacted by insecure encryption of security questions. This could allow an attacker with access to the database to recover some or all encrypted values.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35511 | phpgurukul Men Salon Management System v2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "username" parameter of /msms/admin/index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35511</link><description>phpgurukul Men Salon Management System v2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "username" parameter of /msms/admin/index.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35548 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Mybatis plus versions below 3.5.6 allows remote attackers to obtain database information via a Boolean blin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35548</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Mybatis plus versions below 3.5.6 allows remote attackers to obtain database information via a Boolean blind injection</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22641 | TCPDF version 6.6.5 and before is vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) if parsing an untrusted SVG file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22641</link><description>TCPDF version 6.6.5 and before is vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) if parsing an untrusted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35239 | Stored Cross-site Scripting on Components of Umbraco Forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35239</link><description>Umbraco Commerce is an open source dotnet web forms solution. In affected versions an authenticated user that has access to edit Forms may inject unsafe code into Forms components. This issue can be mitigated by configuring TitleAndDescription:AllowUnsafeHtmlRendering after upgrading to one of the patched versions (13.0.1, 12.2.2, 10.5.3, 8.13.13).</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35240 | Stored Cross-site Scripting on Print Functionality in Umbraco Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35240</link><description>Umbraco Commerce is an open source dotnet ecommerce solution. In affected versions there exists a stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) issue which would enable attackers to inject malicious code into Print Functionality. This issue has been addressed in versions 12.1.4, and 10.0.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30313 | An issue discovered in Wavlink QUANTUM D2G routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30313</link><description>An issue discovered in Wavlink QUANTUM D2G routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30306 | An issue discovered in Mercury x30g, Mercury YR1800XG routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30306</link><description>An issue discovered in Mercury x30g, Mercury YR1800XG routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30310 | An issue discovered in Comfast Comfast CF-616AC routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30310</link><description>An issue discovered in Comfast Comfast CF-616AC routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28060 | An issue was discovered in Apiris Kafeo 6.4.4. It permits DLL hijacking, allowing a user to trigger the execution of arbitrary code every ti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28060</link><description>An issue was discovered in Apiris Kafeo 6.4.4. It permits DLL hijacking, allowing a user to trigger the execution of arbitrary code every time the product is executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35583 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35583</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Remarks input field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35581 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35581</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Borrower Name input field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30309 | An issue discovered in D-Link DI-7003GV2 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30309</link><description>An issue discovered in D-Link DI-7003GV2 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35582 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35582</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Department input field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30308 | An issue discovered in Ruijie EG210G-P, Ruijie EG105G-V2, Ruijie NBR, and Ruijie EG105G routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30308</link><description>An issue discovered in Ruijie EG210G-P, Ruijie EG105G-V2, Ruijie NBR, and Ruijie EG105G routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28061 | An issue was discovered in Apiris Kafeo 6.4.4. It permits a bypass, of the protection in place, to access to the data stored in the embedded...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28061</link><description>An issue was discovered in Apiris Kafeo 6.4.4. It permits a bypass, of the protection in place, to access to the data stored in the embedded database file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35510 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /dede/file_manage_control.php of DedeCMS v5.7.114 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35510</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /dede/file_manage_control.php of DedeCMS v5.7.114 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30307 | An issue discovered in TP-LINK TL-R473GP-AC, TP-LINK XDR6020, TP-LINK TL-R479GP-AC, TP-LINK TL-R4239G, TP-LINK TL-WAR1200L, and TP-LINK TL-R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30307</link><description>An issue discovered in TP-LINK TL-R473GP-AC, TP-LINK XDR6020, TP-LINK TL-R479GP-AC, TP-LINK TL-R4239G, TP-LINK TL-WAR1200L, and TP-LINK TL-R476G routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45171 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v018. An Unrestricted Upload of a File with a Dangerous Type can occur under ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45171</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v018. An Unrestricted Upload of a File with a Dangerous Type can occur under the vShare web site section. A remote user, authenticated to the product, can arbitrarily upload potentially dangerous files without restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46694 | Vtenext 21.02 allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, potentially enabling them to execute remote commands. This flaw ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46694</link><description>Vtenext 21.02 allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, potentially enabling them to execute remote commands. This flaw exists due to the application's failure to enforce proper authentication controls when accessing the Ckeditor file manager functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30305 | An issue discovered in Linksys E5600 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30305</link><description>An issue discovered in Linksys E5600 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30311 | An issue discovered in H3C Magic R365 and H3C Magic R100 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30311</link><description>An issue discovered in H3C Magic R365 and H3C Magic R100 routers allows attackers to hijack TCP sessions which could lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33450 | SQL Injection in Finereport v.8.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33450</link><description>SQL Injection in Finereport v.8.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36107 | Information disclosure in minio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36107</link><description>MinIO is a High Performance Object Storage released under GNU Affero General Public License v3.0. `If-Modified-Since` and `If-Unmodified-Since` headers when used with anonymous requests by sending a random object name requests can be used to determine if an object exists or not on the server on a specific bucket and also gain access to some amount of
information such as  `Last-Modified (of the latest version)`, `Etag (of the latest version)`, `x-amz-version-id (of the latest version)`, `Expires (metadata value of the latest version)`, `Cache-Control (metadata value of the latest version)`. This conditional check was being honored before validating if the anonymous access is indeed allowed on the metadata of an object. This issue has been addressed in commit `e0fe7cc3917`. Users must upgrade to RELEASE.2024-05-27T19-17-46Z for the fix. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36109 | Cross-site Scripting with Markdown rendering in CoCalc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36109</link><description>CoCalc is web-based software that enables collaboration in research, teaching, and scientific publishing. In affected versions the markdown parser allows `</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5433 | Path Traversal in Campbell Scientific CSI Web Server and RTMC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5433</link><description>The Campbell Scientific CSI Web Server supports a command that will return the most recent file that matches a given expression. A specially crafted expression can lead to a path traversal vulnerability. This command combined with a specially crafted expression allows anonymous, unauthenticated access (allowed by default) by an attacker to files and directories outside of the webserver root directory they should be restricted to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5434 | Weak Encoding for Password vulnerability in Campbell Scientific CSI Web Server and RTMC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5434</link><description>The Campbell Scientific CSI Web Server stores web authentication credentials in a file with a specific file name. Passwords within that file are stored in a weakly encoded format. There is no known way to remotely access the file unless it has been manually renamed. However, if an attacker were to gain access to the file, passwords could be decoded and reused to gain access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36110 | Cross-site scripting in ansibleguy-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36110</link><description>ansibleguy-webui is an open source WebUI for using Ansible. Multiple forms in versions &lt; 0.0.21 allowed injection of HTML elements. These are returned to the user after executing job actions and thus evaluated by the browser. These issues have been addressed in version 0.0.21 (0.0.21.post2 on pypi). Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for these issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24919 | Information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24919</link><description>Potentially allowing an attacker to read certain information on Check Point Security Gateways once connected to the internet and enabled with remote Access VPN or Mobile Access Software Blades. A Security fix that mitigates this vulnerability is available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43842 | Incorrect access control in the account management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43842</link><description>Incorrect access control in the account management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users to alter user and administrator accounts credentials via HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43843 | Incorrect access control in the account management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43843</link><description>Incorrect access control in the account management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users to read user and administrator accounts passwords via HTTP GET request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43844 | Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 have default credentials for the privileged web interface account. The user is not asked to change the crede...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43844</link><description>Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 have default credentials for the privileged web interface account. The user is not asked to change the credentials after first login. If not changed, attackers can log in to the web interface and gain administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43845 | Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 have default credentials for the privileged telnet account. The user is not asked to change the credentials ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43845</link><description>Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 have default credentials for the privileged telnet account. The user is not asked to change the credentials after first login. If not changed, attackers can log in to the telnet console and gain administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43846 | Incorrect access control in logs management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote attackers to get the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43846</link><description>Incorrect access control in logs management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote attackers to get the device logs via HTTP GET request. The logs contain such information as user names and IP addresses used in the infrastructure. This information may help the attackers to conduct further attacks in the infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43847 | Incorrect access control in the outlet control function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43847</link><description>Incorrect access control in the outlet control function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users to control all the outlets as if they were the administrator via HTTP POST requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43848 | Incorrect access control in the firewall management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43848</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firewall management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users to alter local firewall settings of the device as if they were the administrator via HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43849 | Incorrect access control in firmware upgrade function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43849</link><description>Incorrect access control in firmware upgrade function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users to submit a firmware image via HTTP POST requests. This may result in DoS or remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43850 | Improper input validation in the user management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43850</link><description>Improper input validation in the user management function of web interface in Aten PE6208 2.3.228 and 2.4.232 allows remote authenticated users to cause a partial DoS of web interface via HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33402 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/approve_petty_cash.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33402</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/approve_petty_cash.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35341 | Certain Anpviz products allow unauthenticated users to download the running configuration of the device via a HTTP GET request to /ConfigFil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35341</link><description>Certain Anpviz products allow unauthenticated users to download the running configuration of the device via a HTTP GET request to /ConfigFile.ini or /config.xml URIs. This configuration file contains usernames and encrypted passwords (encrypted with a hardcoded key common to all devices). This affects IPC-D250, IPC-D260, IPC-B850, IPC-D850, IPC-D350, IPC-D3150, IPC-D4250, IPC-D380, IPC-D880, IPC-D280, IPC-D3180, MC800N, YM500L, YM800N_N2, YMF50B, YM800SV2, YM500L8, and YM200E10 firmware v3.2.2.2 and lower and possibly more vendors/models of IP camera.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35344 | Certain Anpviz products contain a hardcoded cryptographic key stored in the firmware of the device. This affects IPC-D250, IPC-D260, IPC-B85...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35344</link><description>Certain Anpviz products contain a hardcoded cryptographic key stored in the firmware of the device. This affects IPC-D250, IPC-D260, IPC-B850, IPC-D850, IPC-D350, IPC-D3150, IPC-D4250, IPC-D380, IPC-D880, IPC-D280, IPC-D3180, MC800N, YM500L, YM800N_N2, YMF50B, YM800SV2, YM500L8, and YM200E10 firmware v3.2.2.2 and lower and possibly more vendors/models of IP camera.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35342 | Certain Anpviz products allow unauthenticated users to modify or disable camera related settings such as microphone volume, speaker volume, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35342</link><description>Certain Anpviz products allow unauthenticated users to modify or disable camera related settings such as microphone volume, speaker volume, LED lighting, NTP, motion detection, etc. This affects IPC-D250, IPC-D260, IPC-B850 IPC-D850, IPC-D350, IPC-D3150, IPC-D4250, IPC-D380, IPC-D880, IPC-D280, IPC-D3180, MC800N, YM500L, YM800N_N2, YMF50B, YM800SV2, YM500L8, and YM200E10 firmware v3.2.2.2 and lower and possibly more vendors/models of IP camera.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30164 | Amazon AWS Client VPN has a buffer overflow that could potentially allow a local actor to execute arbitrary commands with elevated permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30164</link><description>Amazon AWS Client VPN has a buffer overflow that could potentially allow a local actor to execute arbitrary commands with elevated permissions. This is resolved in 3.11.1 on Windows, 3.9.1 on macOS, and 3.12.1 on Linux. NOTE: although the macOS resolution is the same as for CVE-2024-30165, this vulnerability on macOS is not the same as CVE-2024-30165.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30165 | Amazon AWS Client VPN before 3.9.1 on macOS has a buffer overflow that could potentially allow a local actor to execute arbitrary commands w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30165</link><description>Amazon AWS Client VPN before 3.9.1 on macOS has a buffer overflow that could potentially allow a local actor to execute arbitrary commands with elevated permissions, a different vulnerability than CVE-2024-30164.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35343 | Certain Anpviz products allow unauthenticated users to download arbitrary files from the device's filesystem via a HTTP GET request to the /...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35343</link><description>Certain Anpviz products allow unauthenticated users to download arbitrary files from the device's filesystem via a HTTP GET request to the /playback/ URI. This affects IPC-D250, IPC-D260, IPC-B850, IPC-D850, IPC-D350, IPC-D3150, IPC-D4250, IPC-D380, IPC-D880, IPC-D280, IPC-D3180, MC800N, YM500L, YM800N_N2, YMF50B, YM800SV2, YM500L8, and YM200E10 (IP Cameras) firmware v3.2.2.2 and lower and possibly more vendors/models of IP camera.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35563 | CDG-Server-V5.6.2.126.139 and earlier was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the permissionId parameter in CDGTempPermi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35563</link><description>CDG-Server-V5.6.2.126.139 and earlier was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the permissionId parameter in CDGTempPermissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26024 | SUBNET Substation Server Reliance on Insufficiently Trustworthy Component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26024</link><description>SUBNET Solutions Inc. has identified vulnerabilities in third-party components used in Substation Server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34852 | F-logic DataCube3 v1.0 is affected by command injection due to improper string filtering at the command execution point in the ./admin/trans...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34852</link><description>F-logic DataCube3 v1.0 is affected by command injection due to improper string filtering at the command execution point in the ./admin/transceiver_schedule.php file. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a file name containing command injection. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow the attacker to execute system commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34854 | F-logic DataCube3 v1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload via `/admin/transceiver_schedule.php.`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34854</link><description>F-logic DataCube3 v1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload via `/admin/transceiver_schedule.php.`</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35401 | TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the FileName parameter in the UploadF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35401</link><description>TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the FileName parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35403 | TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the desc parameter in the function setIpPortFilterRule...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35403</link><description>TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the desc parameter in the function setIpPortFilterRules</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22590 | The TLS engine in Kwik commit 745fd4e2 does not track the current state of the connection. This vulnerability can allow Client Hello message...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22590</link><description>The TLS engine in Kwik commit 745fd4e2 does not track the current state of the connection. This vulnerability can allow Client Hello messages to be overwritten at any time, including after a connection has been established.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30212 | Microchip Harmony 3 Core library allows read and write access to RAM via a SCSI READ or WRITE command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30212</link><description>If a SCSI READ(10) command is initiated via USB using the largest LBA 
(0xFFFFFFFF) with it's default block size of 512 and a count of 1,

the first 512 byte of the 0x80000000 memory area is returned to the 
user. If the block count is increased, the full RAM can be exposed.

The same method works to write to this memory area. If RAM contains 
pointers, those can be - depending on the application - overwritten to

return data from any other offset including Progam and Boot Flash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36472 | In GNOME Shell through 45.7, a portal helper can be launched automatically (without user confirmation) based on network responses provided b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36472</link><description>In GNOME Shell through 45.7, a portal helper can be launched automatically (without user confirmation) based on network responses provided by an adversary (e.g., an adversary who controls the local Wi-Fi network), and subsequently loads untrusted JavaScript code, which may lead to resource consumption or other impacts depending on the JavaScript code's behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33800 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_student1.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33800</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_student1.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the index parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33801 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_subject_routing.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33801</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_subject_routing.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33802 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_student_subject.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33802</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_student_subject.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the index parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33803 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_exam.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33803</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_exam.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33804 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_subject.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33804</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_subject.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33805 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_student.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33805</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_student.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33806 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_grade.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33806</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_grade.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33807 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_teacher_timetable.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33807</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_teacher_timetable.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the grade parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33808 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_timetable.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33808</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_timetable.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33799 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_teacher.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33799</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_teacher.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35621 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit function of Formwork before 1.13.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35621</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit function of Formwork before 1.13.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Content field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21785 | A leftover debug code vulnerability exists in the Telnet Diagnostic Interface functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21785</link><description>A leftover debug code vulnerability exists in the Telnet Diagnostic Interface functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to unauthorized access. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22187 | A write-what-where vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection Remote Memory Diagnostics functionality of AutomationDirect P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22187</link><description>A write-what-where vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection Remote Memory Diagnostics functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to an arbitrary write. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23315 | A read-what-where vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection IMM 01A1 Memory Read functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23315</link><description>A read-what-where vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection IMM 01A1 Memory Read functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23601 | A code injection vulnerability exists in the scan_lib.bin functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted scan_lib.b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23601</link><description>A code injection vulnerability exists in the scan_lib.bin functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted scan_lib.bin can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24851 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection FiBurn functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24851</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection FiBurn functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a buffer overflow. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24946 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection CurrDir functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24946</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection CurrDir functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger these vulnerability.This CVE tracks the heap corruption that occurs at offset `0xb686c` of version 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E firmware, which occurs when a call to `memset` relies on an attacker-controlled length value and corrupts any trailing heap allocations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24947 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection CurrDir functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24947</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection CurrDir functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger these vulnerability.This CVE tracks the heap corruption that occurs at offset `0xb68c4` of version 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E firmware, which occurs when a call to `memset` relies on an attacker-controlled length value and corrupts any trailing heap allocations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24954 | Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24954</link><description>Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. Specially crafted network packets can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can send malicious packets to trigger these vulnerabilities.This CVE tracks the arbitrary null-byte write vulnerability located in firmware 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E at offset `0xb69c8`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24955 | Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24955</link><description>Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. Specially crafted network packets can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can send malicious packets to trigger these vulnerabilities.This CVE tracks the arbitrary null-byte write vulnerability located in firmware 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E at offset `0xb69fc`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24956 | Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24956</link><description>Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. Specially crafted network packets can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can send malicious packets to trigger these vulnerabilities.This CVE tracks the arbitrary null-byte write vulnerability located in firmware 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E at offset `0xb6a38`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24957 | Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24957</link><description>Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. Specially crafted network packets can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can send malicious packets to trigger these vulnerabilities.This CVE tracks the arbitrary null-byte write vulnerability located in firmware 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E at offset `0xb6aa4`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24958 | Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24958</link><description>Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. Specially crafted network packets can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can send malicious packets to trigger these vulnerabilities.This CVE tracks the arbitrary null-byte write vulnerability located in firmware 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E at offset `0xb6bdc`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24959 | Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24959</link><description>Several out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the Programming Software Connection FileSystem API functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. Specially crafted network packets can lead to heap-based memory corruption. An attacker can send malicious packets to trigger these vulnerabilities.This CVE tracks the arbitrary null-byte write vulnerability located in firmware 1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E at offset `0xb6c18`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24962 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection FileSelect functionality of AutomationDirect P3-55...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24962</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection FileSelect functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.This CVE tracks the stack-based buffer overflow that occurs at offset `0xb6e98` of v1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24963 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection FileSelect functionality of AutomationDirect P3-55...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24963</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Programming Software Connection FileSelect functionality of AutomationDirect P3-550E 1.2.10.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.This CVE tracks the stack-based buffer overflow that occurs at offset `0xb6e84` of v1.2.10.9 of the P3-550E firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33849 | ci solution CI-Out-of-Office Manager through 6.0.0.77 uses a Hard-coded Cryptographic Key.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33849</link><description>ci solution CI-Out-of-Office Manager through 6.0.0.77 uses a Hard-coded Cryptographic Key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35324 | Douchat 4.0.5 suffers from an arbitrary file upload vulnerability via Public/Plugins/webuploader/server/preview.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35324</link><description>Douchat 4.0.5 suffers from an arbitrary file upload vulnerability via Public/Plugins/webuploader/server/preview.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35399 | TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35399</link><description>TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35400 | TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the desc parameter in the function SetPortForwardRules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35400</link><description>TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the desc parameter in the function SetPortForwardRules</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5274 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 125.0.6422.112 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5274</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 125.0.6422.112 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35398 | TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the desc parameter in the function setMacFilterRules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35398</link><description>TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the desc parameter in the function setMacFilterRules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3969 |  XML External Entity injection vulnerability in iManager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3969</link><description>XML External Entity injection vulnerability found in OpenText™ iManager 3.2.6.0200. This could lead to remote code execution by parsing untrusted XML payload</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4429 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in iManager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4429</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ iManager 3.2.6.0200. This
could lead to sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35397 | TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 weas discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the NTPSyncWithHost function via the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35397</link><description>TOTOLINK CP900L v4.1.5cu.798_B20221228 weas discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the NTPSyncWithHost function via the hostTime parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2451 | Improper fingerprint validation in the TeamViewer Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2451</link><description>Improper fingerprint validation in the TeamViewer Client (Full &amp; Host) prior Version 15.54 for Windows and macOS allows an attacker with administrative user rights to further elevate privileges via executable sideloading.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35949 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35949</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file can lead to a buffer overflow. An attacker can arbitrary code execution to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability exists within the code responsible for parsing geometric faces of an OFF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35950 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35950</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file can lead to a buffer overflow. An attacker can arbitrary code execution to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability exists within the code responsible for parsing the header of an OFF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35951 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35951</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file can lead to a buffer overflow. An attacker can arbitrary code execution to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability exists within the code responsible for parsing geometric vertices of an OFF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35952 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35952</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file can lead to a buffer overflow. An attacker can arbitrary code execution to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability exists within the code responsible for parsing comments within the geometric faces section within an OFF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35953 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35953</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF.cpp functionality of libigl v2.4.0. A specially-crafted .off file can lead to a buffer overflow. An attacker can arbitrary code execution to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability exists within the code responsible for parsing comments within the geometric vertices section within an OFF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49600 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the PlyFile ply_cast_ascii functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .ply file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49600</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the PlyFile ply_cast_ascii functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .ply file can lead to a heap buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22181 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the readNODE functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .node file can lead to an ou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22181</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the readNODE functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .node file can lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23947 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23947</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the `igl::MshLoader::parse_nodes` function while handling a `binary` `.msh` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23948 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23948</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the `igl::MshLoader::parse_nodes` function while handling an `ascii`.msh` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23949 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23949</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the `igl::MshLoader::parse_node_field` function while handling an `ascii`.msh` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23950 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23950</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the `igl::MshLoader::parse_element_field` function while handling an `binary`.msh` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23951 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23951</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds write. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the `igl::MshLoader::parse_element_field` function while handling an `ascii`.msh` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24583 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24583</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerabilitty concerns the`readMSH` function while processing `MshLoader::ELEMENT_TRI` elements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24584 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24584</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the readMSH functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .msh file can lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerabilitty concerns the`readMSH` function while processing `MshLoader::ELEMENT_TET` elements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24684 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .off file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24684</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .off file can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the header parsing occuring while processing an `.off`  file via the `readOFF` function. 


We can see above that at [0] a stack-based buffer called `comment` is defined with an hardcoded size of `1000 bytes`.  The call to `fscanf` at [1] is unsafe and if the first line of the header of the `.off` files is longer than 1000 bytes it will overflow the `header` buffer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24685 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .off file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24685</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .off file can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the parsing of comments within the vertex section of an `.off`  file processed via the `readOFF` function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24686 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .off file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24686</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the readOFF functionality of libigl v2.5.0. A specially crafted .off file can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns the parsing of comments within the faces section of an `.off`  file processed via the `readOFF` function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29072 | A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit Reader 2024.2.0.25138. The vulnerability occurs due to improper certification valid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29072</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit Reader 2024.2.0.25138. The vulnerability occurs due to improper certification validation of the updater executable before executing it. A low privilege user can trigger the update action which can result in unexpected elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5428 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System HTTP POST Request save_product cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5428</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_product of the file /admin/index.php?page=manage_product of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266383.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3657 | 389-ds-base: potential denial of service via specially crafted kerberos as-req request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3657</link><description>A flaw was found in 389-ds-base. A specially-crafted LDAP query can potentially cause a failure on the directory server, leading to a denial of service</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5413 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on PhpMyBackupPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5413</link><description>A vulnerability have been discovered in PhpMyBackupPro affecting version 2.3 that could allow an attacker to execute XSS through /phpmybackuppro/scheduled.php, all parameters. This vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to retrieve their session details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5414 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on PhpMyBackupPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5414</link><description>A vulnerability have been discovered in PhpMyBackupPro affecting version 2.3 that could allow an attacker to execute XSS through /phpmybackuppro/get_file.php, 'view' parameter. This vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to retrieve their session details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5415 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on PhpMyBackupPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5415</link><description>A vulnerability have been discovered in PhpMyBackupPro affecting version 2.3 that could allow an attacker to execute XSS through /phpmybackuppro/backup.php, 'comments' and 'db' parameters. This vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to retrieve their session details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37411 | IBM Aspera Faspex cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37411</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.6 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  260139.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28793 | IBM Engineering Workflow Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28793</link><description>IBM Engineering Workflow Management 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. Under certain configurations, this vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  286830.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2199 | 389-ds-base: malformed userpassword may cause crash at do_modify in slapd/modify.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2199</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was found in 389-ds-base ldap server. This issue may allow an authenticated user to cause a server crash while modifying `userPassword` using malformed input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5410 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5410</link><description>Missing input validation in the ORing IAP-420 web-interface allows stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects IAP-420 version 2.01e and below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 10:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5411 | Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5411</link><description>Missing input validation and OS command integration of the input in the ORing IAP-420 web-interface allows authenticated command injection.This issue affects IAP-420 version 2.01e and below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 10:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52547 | Huawei Matebook D16(Model: CREM-WXX9, BIOS: v2.26. Memory Corruption in SMI Handler of HddPassword SMM Module. This can be leveraged by a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52547</link><description>Huawei Matebook D16(Model: CREM-WXX9, BIOS: v2.26. Memory Corruption in SMI Handler of HddPassword SMM Module. This can be leveraged by a malicious OS attacker to corrupt data structures stored at the beginning of SMRAM and can potentially lead to code execution in SMM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52548 | Huawei Matebook D16(Model: CREM-WXX9, BIOS: v2.26) Arbitrary Memory Corruption in SMI Handler of ThisiServicesSmm SMM module. This can be le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52548</link><description>Huawei Matebook D16(Model: CREM-WXX9, BIOS: v2.26) Arbitrary Memory Corruption in SMI Handler of ThisiServicesSmm SMM module. This can be leveraged by a malicious OS attacker to corrupt arbitrary SMRAM memory and, in turn, lead to code execution in SMM</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52710 | Huawei Matebook D16(Model: CREM-WXX9, BIOS: v2.26), As the communication buffer size hasn’t been properly validated to be of the expected si...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52710</link><description>Huawei Matebook D16(Model: CREM-WXX9, BIOS: v2.26), As the communication buffer size hasn’t been properly validated to be of the expected size, it can partially overlap with the beginning SMRAM.This can be leveraged by a malicious OS attacker to corrupt data structures stored at the beginning of SMRAM and can potentially lead to code execution in SMM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52711 | Various Issues Due To Exposed SMI Handler in AmdPspP2CmboxV2. The first issue can be leveraged to bypass the protections that have been put ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52711</link><description>Various Issues Due To Exposed SMI Handler in AmdPspP2CmboxV2. The first issue can be leveraged to bypass the protections that have been put in place by previous UEFI phases to prevent direct access to the SPI flash. The second issue can be used to both leak and corrupt SMM memory thus potentially leading code execution in SMM</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52712 | Various Issues Due To Exposed SMI Handler in AmdPspP2CmboxV2. The first issue can be leveraged to bypass the protections that have been put ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52712</link><description>Various Issues Due To Exposed SMI Handler in AmdPspP2CmboxV2. The first issue can be leveraged to bypass the protections that have been put in place by previous UEFI phases to prevent direct access to the SPI flash. The second issue can be used to both leak and corrupt SMM memory, thus potentially leading code execution in SMM</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48681 | Some Huawei smart speakers have a memory overflow vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause certain functions t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48681</link><description>Some Huawei smart speakers have a memory overflow vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause certain functions to fail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 04:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28886 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in UTAU versions prior to v0.4.19. If a user of the product opens a crafted UTAU project file (.us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28886</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in UTAU versions prior to v0.4.19. If a user of the product opens a crafted UTAU project file (.ust file), an arbitrary OS command may be executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32944 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in UTAU versions prior to v0.4.19. If a user of the product installs a crafted UTAU voicebank installer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32944</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in UTAU versions prior to v0.4.19. If a user of the product installs a crafted UTAU voicebank installer (.uar file, .zip file) to UTAU, an arbitrary file may be placed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>